<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 19:24:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Axion Dark Matter Search with Sensitivity near the Kim-Shifman-Vainshtein-Zakharov Benchmark Using the TM_{020} Mode]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Axions, originally proposed to resolve the CP problem in the strong interaction, remain a leading dark matter candidate. While cavity haloscopes offer the most sensitive technique for detecting axions, searches have largely been limited to masses below 10 μeV. We report a sensitive search for axion dark matter with masses around 21 μeV, utilizing the TM_{020} mode of a cylindrical cavity equipped with an innovative tuning mechanism. Our search achieved a sensitivity of 1.7× the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population Pharmacokinetic and Pharmacodynamic Modeling of Enteric-Coated Aspirin Capsule and Tablet Formulations in Healthy Subjects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This model adequately described the PK and PD of enteric-coated aspirin and demonstrated comparable TXB2 inhibition between the capsule and tablet formulations, supporting their potential interchangeability in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to: "Efficacy and safety of herbal medicine Gongjin-Dan and Ssanghwa-Tang in patients with chronic fatigue: A randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled, clinical trial" Integr Med Res 2024;13:101025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1016/j.imr.2024.101025.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vivo antibody library screening identifies PKM2-targeting M1 antibody with antitumor activity in melanoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce an innovative in vivo antibody screening method to identify antibodies that can inhibit melanoma cell growth and induce apoptosis. By using a lentiviral ScFv library, we developed a platform that allows for the direct suppression of melanoma cell proliferation within a living mouse model. Through this approach, we identified the M1 antibody, which targets PKM2, a key protein involved in tumor progression. The M1 antibody was found to significantly inhibit melanoma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Exsolution-Derived E-Ni/m-MgAlO<sub>x</sub> Catalysts with Anti-Sintering Stability for Methane Dry Reforming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sintering and carbon deposition are primary causes of deactivation in Ni-based catalysts during methane dry reforming (MDR). To address these issues, a scalable exsolution-derived catalyst, E-Ni/m-MgAlO(x), is reported, consisting of ≈9 nm Ni nanoparticles exsolved within a Mg-doped mesoporous alumina matrix via a sol-gel method. This synthesis strategy ensures uniform precursor mixing and controlled exsolution, producing firmly anchored Ni nanoparticles with strong metal-support interactions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanobody engineering for enhanced-sensitivity rapid COVID-19 tests]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanobody-based diagnostics enable rapid and highly specific detection of infectious diseases, supporting early intervention and effective outbreak control. With their small size, high stability, and ease of production, nanobodies serve as promising alternatives to conventional antibodies in various diagnostic platforms, including lateral flow immunoassay (LFIA) for point-of-care testing. In this study, we present a nanobody-based LFIA for the rapid and early detection of coronavirus disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in the Biological Profiles of Fluorine-Containing Pyridine and its Derivatives: A Brief Overview]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorine-containing pyridine derivatives have emerged as pivotal structures in modern drug discovery due to their unique physicochemical properties and diverse pharmacological activities. The incorporation of fluorine into pyridine-based scaffolds enhances drug potency, selectivity, metabolic stability, and Pharmacokinetics (PK) of these compounds, making them highly attractive for therapeutic development. These derivatives have been integrated into numerous Food and Drug Administration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Dimensionality of the Eyberg Child Behavior Inventory (ECBI): A Scoping Review of Its Structural Models Across Contexts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ECBI is psychometrically robust in terms of reliability, yet its factor structure demonstrates inconsistency across cultural and methodological contexts. Given its widespread application across culturally diverse settings, assessing factor structure and measurement invariance is essential for culturally appropriate use and accurate clinical interpretation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Algae-based bioremediation of soil, water, and air: a solution to polluted environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing prevalence of environmental pollutants including both organic and inorganic contaminants in ecosystems is largely due to inappropriate waste disposal. Persistent pollutants, such as heavy metals, plactic debris and industrial chemicals are frequently found in effluents, present a significant concern for Living organisms. Among various waste removal practices, bioremediation is one of the economical and environmentally friendly approaches. The bioremediation process biologically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Silicon Plateau: A Convergence of Novel Materials for Transistor Evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As silicon-based transistors face fundamental scaling limits, the search for breakthrough alternatives has led to innovations in 3D architectures, heterogeneous integration, and sub-3 nm semiconductor body thicknesses. However, the true effectiveness of these advancements lies in the seamless integration of alternative semiconductors tailored for next-generation transistors. In this review, we highlight key advances that enhance both scalability and switching performance by leveraging emerging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary Management of Atherogenic Dyslipidemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: This paper reviews the effects of major macronutrients and specific dietary interventions on atherogenic dyslipidemia, a common trait characterized by increased concentrations of triglyceride-rich and small, dense LDL particles, and reduced HDL-cholesterol.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Measurement of the Decay Dynamics in the Semileptonic Transition of D^{+(0)} into the Axial-Vector Meson K[over ¯]_{1}(1270)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Using e^{+}e^{-} data taken at the center-of-mass energy of 3.773 GeV with the BESIII detector, corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 20.3 fb^{-1}, we report the first measurement of the decay dynamics of the semileptonic decays D^{+(0)}→K^{-}π^{+}π^{0(-)}e^{+}ν_{e}. The amplitude analysis gives the hadronic form factors of the semileptonic D transitions into the axial-vector meson K[over ¯]_{1}(1270) to be r_{A}=(-11.2±1.0_{stat}±0.9_{syst})×10^{-2} and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of the Charged-Particle Multiplicity Dependence of σ_{ψ(2S)}/σ_{J/ψ} in p-Pb Collisions at 8.16 TeV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bound states of charm and anticharm quarks, known as charmonia, have a rich spectroscopic structure that can be used to probe the dynamics of hadron production in high-energy hadron collisions. Here, the cross section ratio of excited (ψ(2S)) and ground state (J/ψ) vector mesons is measured as a function of the charged-particle multiplicity in proton-lead (pPb) collisions at a center-of-mass (CM) energy per nucleon pair of 8.16 TeV. The data corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 175...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measurement of WWZ and ZH Production Cross Sections at sqrt[s]=13 and 13.6 TeV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A measurement is presented of the cross section in proton-proton collisions for the production of two W bosons and one Z boson. It is based on data recorded by the CMS experiment at the CERN LHC at center-of-mass energies sqrt[s]=13 and 13.6 TeV, corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 200 fb^{-1}. Events with four charged leptons (electrons or muons) in the final state are selected. Both nonresonant WWZ production and ZH production, with the Higgs boson decaying into two W bosons, are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluctuation-Response Inequalities for Kinetic and Entropic Perturbations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We derive fluctuation-response inequalities for Markov jump processes that link the fluctuations of general observables to the response to perturbations in the transition rates within a unified framework. These inequalities are derived using the Cramér-Rao bound, enabling broader applicability compared to existing fluctuation-response relations formulated for static responses of currentlike observables. The fluctuation-response inequalities are valid for a wider class of observables and are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecularly Engineered Nanoagents with Efficient Free Radicals Generation and Photothermal Conversion Performance for Enhanced Tumor Photoimmunotherapy via Targeting Lactate Metabolism-Immune Circuit Rewiring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photodynamic therapy (PDT) and photothermal therapy (PTT) have emerged as promising modalities against tumor growth and distant metastases via inducing apoptosis and immunogenic cell death (ICD). However, their therapeutic efficacy is profoundly compromised by the acidic tumor microenvironment fueled by lactate extrusion, orchestrating multifaceted immunosuppression. Herein, a lactate metabolism checkpoint blockade strategy targeting monocarboxylate transporter 4 (MCT4) is proposed to augment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailoring Advanced Metal-Based Nanomedicines for Adaptable Nanodynamic Disease Therapies and Theranostics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advanced metal-based nanomaterials (MBNs) represent a dynamic frontier in nanomedicine, offering a versatile platform for next-generation diagnostics and therapeutics. Their tunable structures and catalytic, optical, and magnetic properties enable diverse nanodynamic therapies (NDTs), including photodynamic, chemodynamic, sonodynamic, thermodynamic, piezoelectric, radiodynamic, and magnetodynamic modalities. In addition to the well-established tumor ablation, MBNs also feature potent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence in Plastic Surgery and Anatomical Education: A New Era of Precision, Personalization, and Accessibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of artificial intelligence (AI) into plastic surgery and anatomic education represents a transformative shift in modern medicine. In clinical practice, AI enhances preoperative planning through data-driven 3D simulations, augments intraoperative precision with real-time anatomic overlays, and supports postoperative care through remote monitoring systems. These innovations foster greater surgical accuracy, personalization, and patient safety. In anatomic education, AI-driven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trajectories of Depressive Symptoms Before and After Retirement Based on Educational Level and Retirement Type]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to examine whether the time since retirement is associated with changes in depressive symptoms before and after retirement, using 14 years of panel data from the Korean Longitudinal Study of Ageing (2006-2020). A total of 11,232 person-wave observations from individuals aged 45 and older were analyzed using fixed-effects regression models. The level of depressive symptoms increased from the year before retirement, peaking around the first year after retirement, and gradually...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between shift work and brain age gap: a neuroimaging study using MRI-based brain age prediction algorithms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate that shift work is associated with accelerated apparent brain aging, even after controlling for systematic model bias and demographic covariates. The observed reduction in BAG with extended shift work exposure may reflect adaptive or selective effects, emphasizing the need for longitudinal studies to clarify these mechanisms. This research highlights the importance of incorporating occupational exposures in neuroimaging and brain health investigations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Cohort Study of Metabolomic Markers Associated With Type 2 Diabetes Risk in Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic and Pharmacodynamic Interaction of Metformin and Ojeok-san in Healthy Volunteers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Co-administration with OJS decreased the plasma concentrations of metformin compared to that with metformin alone. However, the degree of decrease was not significant based on the geometric mean of the C(max) and AUC(last). Considering the OGTT results, these changes in metformin concentration did not affect glucose concentration. In addition, there were no significant findings regarding safety profiles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic and Safety Profiles of MIT-001, a Novel Ferroptosis Inhibitor, After Subcutaneous Administration in Healthy Participants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The systemic exposure of MIT-001 after SC administration increased linearly across the dose levels of 10-40 mg. MIT-001 was well tolerated after a single SC dose of 10-40 mg and multiple SC doses of 20-40 mg in healthy participants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Taxonomic corrections, new records, and life history information on the jumping tree bugs (Hemiptera, Miridae, Isometopinae) of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The identities of two species of Korean Isometopinae (Hemiptera: Miridae) are clarified based on examination of their type material. The following new synonyms are proposed: Isometopus amurensis Kerzhner, 1988 = Isometopus jejuensis Kim & Jung, 2016, syn. nov. and Myiomma ussuriense Ostapenko, 2001 = Myiomma koreanum Oh & Lee, 2025, syn. nov. Isometopus citri Ren, 1987 is reported from Korea for the first time. Life histories of I. amurensis Kerzhner, I. japonicus Hasegawa, 1946, and I. rugiceps...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurses' Work Interruptions and Responses: Multitasking During Medication Tasks and Differences by Nursing Delivery System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aim: This study aimed to report not only the frequency and source of work interruptions but also nurses' responses to them, focusing on multitasking during medication-related work. It also examined the differences in work interruption according to the nursing care delivery system. Background: Work interruptions increase nurses' workload complexities and errors, as they compromise nurses' attention. Design: The time and motion cross-sectional observational study method was used. Method: Data were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Probiotic <em>Lactobacillus</em> sp. as a strategy for modulation of non-comorbid obesity: A systematic meta-analysis and GRADE assessment of randomized controlled trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given the high prevalence of obesity worldwide, effective therapeutic strategies are crucial to prevent and manage obesity-related health conditions. Existing studies indicate that Lactobacillus sp. showed beneficial effects on body weight and adiposity by modifying the gut microbiota; however, no meta-analysis has been conducted assessing the efficacy of Lactobacillus sp-based probiotics on anthropometric parameters, leptin and adiponectin levels, and gut microbiota composition. The aim of this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment outcomes and safety of concurrent chemoradiation in older adults with unresectable stage III non-small-cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with unresectable stage III NSCLC undergoing CCRT, older patients aged ≥70 years had similar PFS and AE rates compared with those aged <70 years. However, OS was worse in older patients. Considering age as a crucial factor in CCRT outcomes, efforts should be made to provide a more meticulous and careful approach for older patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of peripheral-blood neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio with <em>Pneumocystis jirovecii</em> pneumonia in patients with solid tumors: a case-control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with solid tumors, a baseline feature of high NLR (≥6.22) was independently associated with an increased risk of PJP development. Furthermore, the NLR demonstrates potential utility in assessing immune status. Therefore, clinicians should consider initiating PJP prophylaxis earlier or performing earlier PJP screening in patients with solid tumors and elevated peripheral blood NLR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SKKU, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimally invasive repair of pectus excavatum in children: insights from a large cohort at a single institution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings showed no significant increase in the risk of recurrence or major complications with the approach of non-delayed PE repair for all patients aged 5 years and older. Our transition from a single-bar to a multiple-bar repair approach has been crucial for achieving a thorough anatomical remodeling of the entire chest wall. This strategic shift has proven to be a safe and effective surgical method, applicable even to pediatric PE patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proper clinical and pathologic T stage among diverse T descriptors in terms of recurrence after curative surgery for stage I lung adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: For stage I lung adenocarcinoma, in terms of the stage, the solid component on the lung window setting is a more suitable and reliable clinical T descriptor, and the nonlepidic size (NLTS1) is considered a more appropriate model for the pathologic T descriptor.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On-pump versus off-pump coronary artery bypass grafting for left main coronary artery disease: long-term outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that in a high-volume center with experienced surgeons, off-pump CABG for LM CAD can achieve long-term outcomes comparable to on-pump CABG. Larger prospective studies are warranted to confirm these findings and establish optimal patient selection criteria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data sharing in acupuncture meta-analyses: Associations with journal policies and practical considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Mandatory journal data sharing policies were associated with more frequent inclusion of DASs and provision of raw data, but neither a policy nor a DAS alone ensured reusable datasets. Mandatory policies paired with adequate training and supports may help improve transparency, promote reusability and reproducibility of results, and reduce research waste.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing <em>RET</em>-targeted therapy in thyroid cancer: insights and implications from the LIBRETTO-001 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rheumatoid arthritis and risk of gallstone disease: a nation-wide population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The risk of gallstone disease is higher in individuals with RA than in matched controls.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Emerging sustainable and green technologies for improving agricultural production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiographic Risk Factors for Excessive Joint Line Obliquity After Knee Osteotomy for Medial Osteoarthritis: A Phenotype-Based Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative type IV (varus and apex neutral) had a higher risk of excessive postoperative JLO. Specifically, when the preoperative mLDFA was ≥90.2° or the preoperative aJLO was ≥-1.5°, there was an increased risk of excessive postoperative JLO after isolated HTO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing Readability and Usability of Electronic Medicine Package Leaflets in South Korea: A Mixed-Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The current e-labeling format may not sufficiently meet patients' needs for medicine information. To support successful implementation, e-labeling should be redesigned with a focus on patient-centered principles, ensuring equitable access, and being tested in real-world settings. Education and awareness campaigns on how to use e-labeling would provide practical guidance and encourage acceptance among patients. These findings provide patient-centered evidence to inform improvements in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermally Stable Al<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub>/PTFE Composite Separator for High-Safety Lithium-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In response to the growing demand for carbon neutrality and safer energy storage, advanced separator technology is essential for ensuring the stability of lithium-ion batteries (LIBs). Conventional separators, typically made from polyolefin-based polymers, suffer from low thermal stability and poor wettability, leading to safety and performance concerns. In this study, we fabricated a nonwoven polytetrafluoroethylene (PTFE) nanofiber (NF) separator using emulsion electrospinning incorporating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selectively Adsorbed CO and O<sub>2</sub> on Transition-Metal-Incorporated Porphyrin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We have investigated the adsorption of CO and O(2) on transition-metal (TM)-incorporated porphyrin. Our calculations show that one or more CO molecules can be adsorbed on the Sc-, Ti-, V-, Cr-, or Mn-incorporated porphyrin, while only one CO molecule is adsorbed on the Fe- or Co-incorporated porphyrin. In the case of O(2), only one O(2) molecule prefers to adsorb on the TM-incorporated porphyrin, regardless of TM. Moreover, O(2) is strongly bound to the Sc-, Ti-, V-, Cr-, or Mn-incorporated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective Adsorption of Methyl Orange from Aqueous Solution Using MOFs Nanocomposites UiO-66-NH<sub>2</sub>/GO@PVA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The persistent contamination of water resources by synthetic dyes poses a critical global environmental challenge, necessitating the development of efficient and sustainable remediation technologies. This study presents a novel UiO-66-NH(2)/GO/PVA composite for the effective removal of methyl orange (MO) from water solutions. The composite was created by combining graphene oxide (GO) and UiO-66-NH(2) in a poly-(vinyl alcohol) (PVA) matrix, creating a stable and very porous structure. Adsorption...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the Gap between Evidence and Practice: Nationwide Retrospective Analysis of Lipid-Modifying Therapy Prescription Patterns in 5 Million Patients with Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings revealed a significant under-prescription of lipid-modifying therapy in T2DM patients. The universal nature of under-prescription suggests barriers to guideline implementation. These results underscore the urgent need for systematic interventions, including automated identification systems, standardized protocols, and optimized provider education to improve cardiovascular risk management in patients with T2DM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spirodelae Herba ethanol extract attenuates neurotoxicity in hippocampal cells and improves scopolamine-induced cognitive impairment in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results of this study demonstrate the neuroprotective and anti-neuroinflammatory effects of SHE and its strong potential as a preventive and therapeutic agent for cognitive impairment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systemic inflammation at the oral-ocular interface: a 3P medicine perspective on the relationship between periodontitis and eye diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND EXPERT RECOMMENDATIONS IN THE FRAMEWORK OF 3PM: Periodontitis may serve as a predictive biomarker for ocular diseases with shared inflammatory and vascular pathways. Early identification and management of periodontal disease offer a targeted preventive strategy to reduce systemic inflammatory burden and ocular comorbidities. Personalized care models incorporating periodontal status into ocular screening protocols may improve diagnostic precision and enable risk-adapted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Yarrowia lipolytica</em> as a promising cell factory for microbial production of value-added nutraceuticals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The oleaginous yeast Yarrowia lipolytica has emerged as a powerful chassis for the sustainable production of high-value nutraceuticals. Its innate metabolism, characterized by a high flux towards the key precursor acetyl-CoA, makes it an ideal host for synthesizing complex molecules like carotenoids, flavonoids, and specialty lipids. This review summarizes recent progress in engineering Y. lipolytica cell factories, focusing on the synergistic application of metabolic engineering and synthetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Synergistic advances in gene technology, nanobiotechnology, and photonic innovations for next-generation diagnostics and therapeutics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualizing research trends and collaboration networks in surgery: a case study of bilateral axillo-breast approach surgery [2007-2024]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: According to 18 years of bibliometric analysis, research on the BABA surgical technique has expanded significantly, accompanied by growing academic interest and widespread global adoption. Studies related to BABA have been actively conducted in South Korea, the United States, and China, with researchers from other countries increasingly showing interest and beginning to implement the technique in clinical practice. These findings suggest the potential for even broader global...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Extra-adrenal retroperitoneal paraganglioma in a young adult cat diagnosed by imaging, pathology, and immunohistochemistry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paragangliomas are rare neuroendocrine tumors arising from paraganglionic tissues associated with the autonomic nervous system. Although they are uncommon in veterinary medicine, particularly in cats, accurate diagnosis is essential due to their potential malignancy. An 18-month-old neutered male domestic shorthair cat presented with a retroperitoneal mass near adrenal glands. Computed tomography revealed an irregular, mildly contrast-enhancing mass abutting both adrenal glands and displacing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A genome-wide association study of stroke risk in Asian statin users: evidence from KoGES and UK Biobank]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identified CDH13 as a significant genetic marker associated with stroke risk among Asian statin users. These findings provide the first genome-wide evidence for genetic determinants of stroke susceptibility during statin therapy, supporting the development of personalized prevention strategies in Asian populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Achieving Low-Power Analog Resistive Switching in Filamentary Memristive Devices for Energy-Efficient Analog In-Memory Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Analog in-memory computing with memristive devices is a promising solution for overcoming energy inefficiencies of traditional Von Neumann architectures, especially in deep learning applications. However, filamentary memristive devices encounter significant challenges, such as high forming and set voltages and limited resistance in analog switching regions, causing excessive power consumption. Here, an engineering strategy is presented that reduces operational voltage by addressing ionic supply...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing global mental health through education]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wetting Transparency-Induced Enhancement of Moisture Stability in Monolayer Transition Metal Dichalcogenides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2D materials are considered promising candidates for next-generation semiconductor devices. However, their high surface-to-volume ratio makes them highly susceptible to environmental degradation, particularly in the presence of moisture. Monolayer n-type transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDCs), synthesized via chemical vapor deposition (CVD), are especially vulnerable to degradation under humid conditions. In this study, H(2)O adsorption is controlled by utilizing the wetting transparency of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and risk factor evaluation for postoperative nausea and vomiting in cesarean section under general anesthesia compared to the gynecologic surgery: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PONV may occur less frequently in patients undergoing cesarean section under general anesthesia than in those undergoing gynecologic surgery. In obstetric patients, substantial intraoperative blood loss with inadequate fluid replacement, prolonged surgical duration, and a history of abdominal surgery may represent additional risk factor for PONV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Comparative Evaluation of the Xpert MTB/RIF and Xpert MTB/RIF Ultra Assays for Detecting <em>Mycobacterium tuberculosis</em> and Rifampin Resistance in High-resource, Intermediate-burden Settings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Xpert Ultra tends to have increased sensitivity; however, it shows potential diagnostic ambiguity associated with trace- or very low-positive results. These findings highlight the importance of clinical correlation, particularly in culture-negative cases. Indeterminate results in certain rpoB mutations require cautious interpretation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coordination tuning of nanoporous metal films by secondary electrodeposition to optimize methanol electrooxidation activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, the crystal structure of nanoporous noble metal films has been controlled by the construction of secondary nanostructures assembled by a pulsed electrodeposition method. By employing secondary deposition techniques, the nanoporous structure was preserved, while the crystal structure was adjusted to optimize electrochemical performance. The crystal structure of the nanoporous metal film was precisely regulated to suppress the growth of the Au (220) plane in NPGF, as this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refining the Classification of Steatotic Liver Disease: Beyond Self-Reported Alcohol Intake]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the Gap in Elimination of Hepatitis C Virus among People Who Use Drugs in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A long journey with minimally invasive surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Minimally invasive surgery (MIS) has transformed surgical oncology practice over the past four decades. This narrative reflects on Korea's pioneering role in MIS, particularly in colorectal surgery, chronicling its evolution from early laparoscopic cholecystectomy to advanced robotic procedures. Through personal experience, institutional milestones, and landmark clinical trials-including the COREAN trial-this Presidential Lecture at KSERS 2025 reviews the challenges, milestones, and future...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preventing postoperative nausea and vomiting after laparoscopic cholecystectomy: toward personalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimally invasive emergency colorectal surgery in nonspecialist surgical centers: a necessity, not a luxury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting WWPI HECT Domain by Small Inhibitors for Restoring PTEN Tumor Suppressive Role in Glioblastoma Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study has discovered novel inhibitors against the WWPI HECT domain, and a treatment option for glioblastoma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Nationwide Trend Analysis of <em>Helicobacter pylori</em> Treatment between 2010 and 2021 According to Revised Guidelines in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This long-term nationwide trend analysis revealed that real-world prescriptions for H. pylori treatment generally corresponded to the updated guidelines. Efforts are needed to disseminate the revised guidelines to achieve higher compliance rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radial artery superficial palmar branch free flap versus toe pulp free flap for finger pulp reconstruction: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Finger pulp reconstruction remains a challenging aspect of hand surgery and requires a careful balance between functional restoration and donor-site morbidity. Among the various microsurgical options, radial artery superficial palmar branch (RASP) and toe pulp free flaps have emerged as the two most widely used techniques, each offering distinct advantages. This narrative review comprehensively compares these two microsurgical approaches for finger pulp reconstruction. The RASP free flap...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moyamoya Disease and the Risk of Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Moyamoya disease (MMD) is a rare cerebrovascular disorder characterized by the progressive narrowing of arteries at the base of the brain, forming abnormal collateral vascular networks. While vascular parkinsonism is noted in MMD, its link to Parkinson's disease (PD) has not been explored. We aimed to determine whether the risk of PD is increased in patients with MMD and to identify the potential role of the RNF213 gene.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systemic immune-inflammation index and pan-immune value as prognostic indicators of clinical outcomes in mycosis fungoides: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Blood inflammatory markers may provide prognostic insights but remain underexplored in mycosis fungoides (MF). To evaluate the prognostic significance of baseline blood inflammatory markers, including the neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio (NLR), eosinophil-to-lymphocyte ratio (ELR), monocyte-to-lymphocyte ratio (MLR), pan-inflammation value (PIV) and systemic immune-inflammation index (SII), in MF. This retrospective cohort study included MF patients diagnosed between 1997 and 2024 at a tertiary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermodynamic-Kinetic Synergistic Separation of Light Olefins/Paraffins in Post-Synthetically Modified Small-Pore Zeolites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The search for selective microporous adsorbents in light olefin/paraffin separations presents many challenges in replacing current energy-intensive cryogenic distillation processes. Here, it is demonstrated that modified acidic intermediate-silica small-pore zeolites, for example, the proton form of zeolite rho with a Si/Al ratio of 3.3 (H-rho), using ammonium fluoride/hydrogen peroxide etching followed by phosphorus loading, can decisively improve ethylene/ethane and propylene/propane...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cleaving a C-F bond of C<sub>6</sub>F<sub>6</sub> at a gallium(I) centre catalyzed by nitrogen-containing Lewis bases and its kinetic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gallylenes, gallium(I) molecules in the oxidation state of +1, supported by a NacNac or Boxm ligand, underwent an efficient C-F bond cleavage of C(6)F(6) upon addition of a stoichiometric/catalytic amount of nitrogen-containing Lewis bases (LBs). Kinetic studies revealed that the C-F bond cleavage was first-order in terms of the concentrations of gallylene and the added nitrogen-containing LBs. The reaction rate also depended on the nitrogen-containing LBs. DFT calculations indicated that the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UV-mediated anomeric activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the UV-mediated activation of various glycosyl α-trichloroacetimidates (TCAs) to form glycosyl α-chlorides or O-glycosides depending on the carbohydrate, protecting groups, and solvent. In THF, Et(2)O, and CH(2)Cl(2), most of the glycosyl TCAs studied underwent conversion to their respective α-chlorides. In the case of per-acetylated glucosyl TCA, a reaction with THF was observed which caused formation of the 4'-chlorobutyl β-glucoside. O-Glycosylation with primary and secondary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IWT score for predicting cardiac amyloidosis in patients with hypertensive heart disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Half of the patients with HHD demonstrated IWT scores consistent with suspected CA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Late-Onset Systemic Lupus Erythematosus: Clinical Manifestations and Diagnostic and Treatment Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE) is widely recognized as a systemic autoimmune disease predominantly affecting young women. However, since the initial report in 1959, cases of late-onset SLE have been increasingly documented. Late-onset SLE, commonly defined as disease onset at or after 50 years of age, sometimes exhibits different clinical characteristics compared with the typical SLE phenotype. There is a higher proportion of male patients and a lower frequency of skin rash, renal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of predictors of paravalvular leakage after transcatheter aortic valve implantation with fifth-generation self-expandable valve]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paravalvular leakage (PVL) is one of the complications of transcatheter aortic valve implantation (TAVI), and its occurrence has been reported to affect long-term prognosis. We investigated whether the aortic valve calcification measured on preoperative CT is useful in predicting PVL after TAVI using the fifth-generation self-expanding valves. We analyzed 88 consecutive patients who underwent TAVI with the fifth-generation self-expanding valve from March 2023 to March 2024. Significant PVL was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of KGAS, a cell line derived from gastric-type adenocarcinoma of the uterine cervix]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric-type adenocarcinoma (GAS) of the uterine cervix is a rare and aggressive subtype of cervical adenocarcinoma characterized by intrinsic resistance to chemotherapy and poor clinical outcomes due to the lack of effective treatment options. To address this critical unmet need, we established a novel GAS-derived cell line, KGAS, from ascitic fluid collected from a patient with recurrent GAS. Short tandem repeat (STR) analysis confirmed the genetic identity between the primary tumor and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality of life after cultured corneal endothelial cell transplant in patients with bullous keratopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cultured CEC transplant significantly improved vision-related quality of life in patients with bullous keratopathy. The comprehensive improvement across multiple NEI VFQ-25 domains suggests that this novel therapeutic approach may be a viable treatment option for corneal endothelial dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting the treatment-requiring retinopathy of prematurity using birth weight, laboratory data and continuous peripheral capillary oxygen saturation monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: BW and Hb were primary predictors of ROP treatment necessity in this cohort, whereas Alb and inflammatory markers did not show independent associations. Incorporating continuous SpO₂ monitoring provided valuable respiratory insights. Further prospective, multicenter studies are warranted to validate these findings and refine ROP risk stratification strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Prediction of the wall‑invasion pattern of advanced gallbladder carcinoma using extracellular volume fraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges in using intraoperative nausea and vomiting as a primary outcome in network meta-analyses of cesarean delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differences and overlaps in TDP-43 pathology of 'pure' LATE-NC compared to LATE-NC coexisting with Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Limbic-predominant age-related TDP-43 encephalopathy (LATE) is a common substrate of dementia in the elderly. LATE and Alzheimer's disease (AD) share similar clinical features, and their underlying neuropathological changes-LATE-NC and ADNC-commonly co-occur. However, the histomorphological and molecular features of TDP-43 pathology in LATE-NC with or without coexisting ADNC are not yet well understood. We performed immunohistochemistry in paraffin-embedded tissue from the hippocampus, amygdala,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A preliminary study of insect, bacterial, and fungal communities associated with Sus scrofa carrion in a tropical rainforest]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carrion decomposition is an important component of the ecosystem and plays a significant ecological role in the food chain. During decomposition, arthropods and microorganisms help to decompose and recycle organic matter and nutrients. Although research has been conducted on microorganisms and arthropods associated with carrion across different biogeoclimatic ecoregions, no study has identified these communities from carrion placed under a tropical rainforest. Therefore, this study aims to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunomodulatory properties of mesenchymal stem cells within three-dimensional collagen matrices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs) hold promise for treating inflammatory and immune-related diseases; however, their clinical application is limited by poor survival and function post-transplantation. Collagen hydrogels may support MSC viability and function by mimicking the extracellular matrix. This study aimed to evaluate how cell density and collagen concentration within three-dimensional (3D) collagen matrices affect the immunomodulatory behavior of MSCs under inflammatory conditions. MSCs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation of residual lung complications with radiological findings after pulmonary segmentectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Extensive postoperative infiltrative shadows in the residual segment are associated with severe complications after segmentectomy. In cases in which the shadow occupies more than half of the remaining segment, special attention to postoperative management is necessary to prevent lethal complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis and Characterization of Electron-Deficient Perfluorinated Tetrathia[8]Circulene via Sequential Coupling Reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tetrathia[8]circulene is a heteroaromatic framework consisting of an eight-membered ring fused with four thiophene and four benzene units, whose electronic properties are highly tunable by peripheral substituents. Herein, we report the synthesis of a perfluorinated tetrathia[8]circulene bearing hexafluorocyclopentene rings via sequential Suzuki-Miyaura and C─H/C─Cl coupling reactions. Single-crystal X-ray diffraction analysis revealed a highly planar π-conjugated core with dense F···F contacts,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Bayes' Rule and Petz Transpose Map from the Minimum Change Principle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bayes' rule, which is routinely used to update beliefs based on new evidence, can be derived from a principle of minimum change. This principle states that updated beliefs must be consistent with new data, while deviating minimally from the prior belief. Here, we introduce a quantum analog of the minimum change principle and use it to derive a quantum Bayes' rule by minimizing the change between two quantum input-output processes, not just their marginals. This is analogous to the classical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, Synthesis, and Biological Evaluation of Lipid-Modified Derivatives of Tunicamycins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Naturally occurring antibiotic tunicamycin targets bacterial peptidoglycan biosynthesis by inhibiting bacterial phospho-N-acetylmuraminic acid (MurNAc)-pentapeptide translocase (MraY), but it also inhibits human UDP-N-acetylglucosamine (GlcNAc): polyprenol phosphate translocase (GPT), leading to cytotoxicity. This study thoroughly investigated the structure-activity relationship of the fatty acyl side chain of tunicamycin to develop MraY-selective inhibitors, based on structural differences...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of the left medial sectional bile duct joining the right hepatic duct]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a case in which the medial sectional bile duct (B4) drained the right hepatic duct. A 42-year-old man was referred to our hospital after an abdominal ultrasound during a medical check-up revealed a gallbladder polyp. Magnetic resonance cholangiopancreatography did not adequately depict the hepatic hilum bile ducts; therefore, drip infusion cholangiography with computed tomography was performed, which revealed that B4 drained the right hepatic duct. The patient subsequently underwent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40951872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of a Reablement Programme in Community Care in the Netherlands; A Qualitative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings offer critical insights that could guide future efforts to implement reablement programmes more effectively.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40950241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal Assessments of Cardiac Sarcoidosis With Right Ventricular Involvement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethical considerations for the use of ecological momentary assessment in non-suicidal self-injury research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Research examining non-suicidal self-injury (NSSI) in daily life has grown substantially; thus, it is essential in conducting ecological momentary assessment (EMA) research with individuals who self-injure to follow important ethical guidelines. Given the challenges faced by researchers in monitoring, assessing, and responding to risk among those who self-injure, further guidance and research is warranted in informing best-practices for conducting EMA research examining NSSI. We suggest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Workflow for Fibula Free Flap Maxillomandibular Reconstruction With Immediate Prosthodontic Rehabilitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Computer-aided surgical planning has improved functional and aesthetic outcomes in maxillofacial reconstructive surgery. Immediate dental implantation is now being increasingly performed in conjunction with the fibula free flap, with high success rates in maxillomandibular reconstructions. The success of this approach relies on careful patient selection, meticulous surgical planning, and prosthetic implementation. Patient-specific surgical templates for resection, repositioning, and implant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The regulation of PSI cyclic electron transport by both plastoquinone and ferredoxin redox states: correlation with the rate of proton motive force utilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The capacity of plants to protect themselves from stress and efficiently assimilate CO(2) depends on dynamic regulation of photosynthetic electron transport pathways. In the cyclic electron transport around photosystem I (PSI-CET), the ferredoxin (Fd) reduced by PSI donates electrons to plastoquinone (PQ), which then enter the pathway of photosynthetic linear electron transport (LET). It has been postulated that PSI-CET generates the additional proton motive force needed to drive sufficient ATP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laceration of the Left Hepatic Vein Following Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Teaching point: Laceration of the left hepatic vein is a rare but potentially fatal complication of cardiopulmonary resuscitation (CPR) and should be considered in patients with unexplained hemodynamic instability following resuscitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reaction of Diethyl 2‑Hydroxyazulene-1,3-dicarboxylate with Metal Acetates and Alkoxides: Metal Complex Formation and Transesterification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Azulene-embedded heterometallacycles can be handled in air and are expected to have a glossy color derived from the azulenyl ligand. However, very few studies have clearly described the synthesis, structure, and effects of metal species. In this study, the reactions of diethyl 2-hydroxyazulene-1,3-dicarboxylate (DEHA, other abbreviation as H-L) with various metals were investigated to synthesize metal complexes (Metals-L). Metals-L were synthesized by the reaction of metal acetates (Pd, Cu, Ni,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipid Extraction from Wet Polymer-Flocculated <em>Chlorella sorokiniana</em> Using Liquefied Dimethyl Ether without Centrifugation and Drying Pretreatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The energy intensive nature of harvesting microalgae by centrifugation and drying results in a low energy profit ratio for biofuel production from wet microalgae. To address this, microalgal cultures can be flocculated by polymers to reduce energy consumption and avoid centrifugation. Additionally, lipids can be directly extracted from wet microalgae harvested by centrifugation using liquefied dimethyl ether (DME) to reduce energy consumption. In this study, we investigated the lipid extraction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Raman Spectroscopy and FRAP Analysis on Density Heterogeneity and Diffusion Behavior of Complex Coacervation by Arginine-Rich Dipeptides and Poly‑A RNA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Membraneless organelles (MLOs), formed through liquid-liquid phase separation (LLPS), are vital for various cellular functions, including gene expression and RNA metabolism. Destructions of LLPS dynamics, often due to aberrant condensate formation, are implicated in neurodegenerative diseases. Polypeptides composed of repeated dipeptides, namely arginine-rich dipeptide repeat proteins, poly-(proline-arginine) (poly-PR) and poly-(glycine-arginine) (poly-GR), translated from mutated C9ORF72...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alkaline-Induced Degradation Pathways of β‑<em>O</em>‑4-Linked Vanillin Moieties Produced during Lignin Oxidation and the Effect of Na<sup>+</sup>‑Cyclic Polyether Complexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The production of vanillin (4-hydroxy-3-methoxybenzaldehyde) from lignin via alkaline aerobic oxidation offers a viable approach for synthesizing aromatic compounds from biomass. A principal route for vanillin formation involves the liberation of a vanillin molecule through nonoxidative, alkali-induced ether cleavage at the β-O-4 type nonphenolic vanillin end group. Our previous studies using veratraldehyde, a model for the vanillin end, showed that complex cations formed between crown ethers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategic Uniaxial Macropore Sizing for Honeycomb-Structured Scaffolds for Enhanced Bone Reconstruction in Segmental Bone Defects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Segmental bone defects often present as new irregularly growing bones that fail to bridge gaps. Optimizing the scaffold design for direct bone growth can enhance bone defect reconstruction. We evaluated three carbonate apatite honeycomb-structured scaffolds with uniaxial macropores of 280, 440, and 640 μm (labeled P280, P440, and P640, respectively) implanted into critical-sized ulnar defects in rabbits. The scaffold performance was assessed at 4 and 12 weeks postimplantation. P280 formed small...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40949199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical relevance of circulating tumor DNA in HER2-positive advanced gastric cancer: a collaborative study of a phase Ib trial of dual HER2 and PD-1 targeted therapy (Ni-High)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ERBB2 genetic status and mMAF changes in ctDNA may, respectively, predict and reflect the efficacy of chemotherapy with dual-targeted therapy in HER2-positive AGC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948910/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and MRI variables associated with close or positive margins during breast-conserving surgery using MRI projection mapping in breast carcinoma with nonmass enhancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The MRI-PMS led to a low rate of positive margins during BCS in patients with breast cancer with NMEs. Large NMCs and NMEs are associated with positive or close margin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iminophosphonamido stannylenes enable quantitative CO<sub>2</sub> conversion to isocyanates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Iminophosphonamido-supported silylaminostannylenes activate CO(2) to afford siloxystannylene and isocyanates via carbamatostannylene intermediates. DFT calculations support a two-step rearrangement involving nucleophilic attack and silyl migration, offering a rare example of a main-group CO(2) valorisation through isocyanate formation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virtual reality glove for home-based hand and arm stroke rehabilitation (vREHAB)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The addition of the Smart Glove to traditional rehabilitation therapy did not improve hand and arm function in the overall study population but may increase the dose of rehabilitation and improve hand and arm function for patients with mild to moderate upper extremity impairment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct roles of tandem acyl carrier protein domains in the assembly of a macrocyclic polylactone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mutagenesis of the tandem acyl carrier protein (ACP(1)-ACP(2)) domains in the non-reducing polyketide synthase Men2 revealed their distinct roles in menisporopsin A biosynthesis. ACP(1) is essential for multiple esterifications and cyclolactonisation, whilst ACP(2) assembles the aromatic subunits of menisporopsin A. These findings provide a foundation for engineering macrocyclic polylactone compounds.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond symptom improvement: transdiagnostic and disorder-specific ways to assess functional and quality of life outcomes across mental disorders in adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Improving meaningful outcomes is the main goal of clinical care for mental disorders. Traditionally, the focus in clinical research and practice has been on outcome domains that refer to symptom severity or service use (e.g., hospitalization), relate to categorical diagnoses, and favour clinician-rated measures. More recently, self-rated and dimensional as well as transdiagnostic outcome domains have gained traction, and functioning, quality of life and well-being/life satisfaction, along with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40948079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation between LC-MS/MS and ELISA methods for quantitative analysis of desmosine-containing solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Thus, the developed ELISA enables highly accurate determination of desmosine concentrations, comparable to LC-MS/MS, suggesting that ELISA is a potentially useful in vitro diagnostic tool.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regioselective Zr<sub>5</sub> Nanocluster Photocatalyst for Precise Protein Editing Under Mild Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the impact of oxidative modifications on protein structure and function is of central importance in protein chemistry, necessitating precise and controlled methods for introducing such modifications. Herein, we report a strategy for regioselective chemical editing of a protein using a novel Zr(5) nanocluster as a visible-light photocatalyst. The [Zr^(IV) (5)(μ─ΟΗ)(2)(μ─Ο)(2)(μ(3)─Ο)Cl(2)(H(2)O)(6)(μ-η¹,η²,η¹-tBu-dihyde-O,O',O″)(5)] (Zr(5)) cluster features a unique [Zr(5)O(5)]...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Theory Describing the Radius of Gyration of Polymers in Solution Based on the Integral Equation Theory of Molecular Liquids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel theoretical framework has been developed to predict the radius of gyration of polymers in solution. The approach is based on the mean-field theory proposed by Flory, which formulates the free energy as a function of the radius of gyration, incorporating both short-range intrachain correlations and long-range intermonomer interactions. The persistence length, representing the local chain flexibility, is evaluated using the three-dimensional reference interaction site model self-consistent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Open-Ended Urinary Catheters in Preventing Catheter-Related Bladder Discomfort: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OEFC placement represents a broadly applicable and effective strategy to reduce CRBD following urological surgery. Catheter tip design appears to play a pivotal role in CRBD prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40947576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of and Attitudes Toward Technology Among Young People Living With HIV in San Francisco: Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital technology is an important tool for engaging and delivering care to and for young people living with HIV. This research letter examines how 120 out-of-care young people living with HIV in San Francisco use digital technology, the attitudes they have toward technology, and the anxiety they feel about being without technology. Our findings emphasize the importance of being aware of the unintended consequences of digital health interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma Phosphorylated Tau 217 to Identify Preclinical Alzheimer Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The findings highlight the potential of plasma p-tau217 as a stand-alone test-or when used in a sequential 2-step approach alongside PET or CSF testing-as a cost-effective, scalable, and minimally burdensome strategy for identifying preclinical AD. Tailored screening workflows that incorporate p-tau217 can improve efficiency in participant selection for preclinical AD trials and, in the future, help guide access to disease-modifying treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences with Rough Sex Among Autistic University Students: Descriptive Findings from a Campus Probability-Based Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is little research on autistic adults' rough sex experiences - even though rough sex has become prevalent among young adults. We aimed to explore lifetime sexual experiences, including consensual and non-consensual rough sex, among autistic university students in the U.S. and their perceptions and subjective experiences of rough sex. The study sample consisted of 46 autistic undergraduate and graduate students from a large public Midwestern U.S. university. Participants had engaged in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Family Caregiver Act-Safeguarding the Human Care Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of GLP-1 RAs in Children and Adolescents With Obesity or Type 2 Diabetes: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this systematic review and meta-analysis of 18 trials, GLP-1 RAs significantly improved glycemic, weight, and cardiometabolic outcomes in children and adolescents with T2D or obesity. Available data over a relatively short follow-up suggested suicidal ideation or behaviors were not significantly different, although GI AEs warrant attention in long-term management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five-Year Outcomes from Deep Brain Stimulation of the Subthalamic Nucleus for Parkinson Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Although STN-DBS outcomes declined slightly, possibly due to the progressive nature of the disease, patients with PD sustained significant improvement in motor and activities of daily living scores, along with a stable reduction in anti-parkinsonian medication over the 5-year follow-up period.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frailty and Postoperative Complications in Older Adults With Nonmetastatic Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Testing for COVID-19, Influenza, and RSV in Hospitalized Youths, 2016-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, SARS-CoV-2 clinical testing decreased between 2020 to 2021 and 2023 to 2024 seasons, whereas influenza and RSV testing increased significantly between 2016 to 2020 and 2023 to 2024 seasons; approximately three-quarters of children and adolescents were tested for the 3 viruses in 2023 to 2024.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Airway Devices and End-Tidal Capnography Trends in Cardiac Arrest: A Secondary Analysis of a Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this secondary analysis of PART, EtCO2 values did not differ between LT and ETI. However, due to significant interaction between advanced airway device and EtCO2 trends, individual interpretation of these parameters may not be accurate.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of BRCA1 and BRCA2 Variants in an Unselected Population of Women With Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This large cohort study of women with breast cancer who underwent germline testing provided information about BRCA1 and BRCA2 in a population enriched for Hispanic women and reported the prevalence of P/LP variants when universal BRCA1 and BRCA2 testing is offered to women with breast cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mobile Integrated Health vs a Transitions of Care Coordinator for Patients Discharged After Heart Failure: The Mighty-Heart Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This randomized clinical trial found that MIH conferred no additional benefit on health status or 30-day readmissions for postacute patients with heart failure compared to TOCC alone. Preliminary subgroup analyses suggest potential variations in MIH effects by age and sex; therefore, further research is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superficial Vein Thrombosis: A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: SuVT typically presents as a tender, painful, palpable cord under the skin. Management may include elastic compression stockings, nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, and systemic anticoagulation with fondaparinux 2.5 mg or rivaroxaban 10 mg. SuVTs within 3 cm of a deep vein should be treated with therapeutic dose anticoagulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Over-the-Counter Retail Naloxone Sales]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Health Interventions in Pediatric Perioperative Care: A Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This network meta-analysis of RCTs found that VR, 2D videos, and 2D games significantly reduced pediatric perioperative anxiety and pain and improved induction compliance. These findings support the use of digital health interventions in pediatric perioperative care and their broader clinical adoption.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capturing meaningful change: Initiation and maintenance of reductions in World Health Organization risk drinking levels among mandated college students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Reductions in WHO risk drinking levels hold promise for quantifying meaningful, individual-level initiation and maintenance of reduced drinking among mandated students. (PsycInfo Database Record (c) 2025 APA, all rights reserved).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating psychophysiological and self-report responses to antioral nicotine pouch social media videos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: This study examines young adult oral nicotine pouch (ONP) users' cognitive and emotional responses to user-generated antioral nicotine pouch (a-ONP) TikTok (a video-based social media platform) videos varying in the presence and absence of disgust-eliciting content.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting the Auditory Language Ability of Young Children With Hearing Loss Using Their Mothers' Brain Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Children with congenital hearing loss (HL) have auditory impairments that may place them at increased risk for delays or variability in language development. However, obtaining reliable brain markers for early classification of young children with HL versus those with normal hearing (NH), as well as for precise assessment of HL children's language ability, remains a challenge due to limitations in traditional neuroimaging techniques and theoretical frameworks. To address this gap, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparation enhances the effectiveness of positive emotion regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present research provides a new perspective on how preparation influences cognitive reappraisal to enhance positive emotions. Across two experiments, we examined whether the impact of preparation on positive emotion regulation (ER) is driven by the specific reappraisal tactic employed (self-focused reappraisal vs. situation-focused reappraisal) or by the overarching regulatory goal of enhancing positive emotions. In Experiment 1, 45 participants engaged in self-focused reappraisal, whereas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Provider and caregiver preferences for trauma-informed intervention: Results from a best-worst scaling exercise]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Knowledge of these preferences can be instrumental in planning and designing trauma interventions for JLS-involved youth. (PsycInfo Database Record (c) 2025 APA, all rights reserved).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the risk of sarcopenia among community-dwelling older adults in Israel: a national cross-sectional survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the high prevalence of sarcopenia risk among older adults in Israel and emphasize the importance of early screening to identify at-risk individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Characteristics of Interaction Between Caregivers and Children with Chronic Diseases in Oral Medication‑Taking Situations: A Validation Study of the Interaction Rating Scale]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Group Prenatal Care for Afghan Refugees: A Pilot Program and Initial Demonstration of Feasibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: In 2018 approximately 2400 Afghan refugees resettled in Washington state, and with approximately 16% arriving pregnant, many were in need of immediate prenatal care and psycho-social support. Because it has been shown to alleviate disparities in pregnancy outcomes, CenteringPregnancy, a group prenatal care model, was chosen as an evidence-based program to meet the needs of this community. This article aims to describe the feasibility and experience of CenteringPregnancy for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breastfeeding Conversations with a Home Visitor and Breastfeeding Continuation in Postnatal Enrollees]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Breastfeeding is associated with many health benefits for both mothers and children, yet U.S. breastfeeding rates are far below the Healthy People 2030 goals. Furthermore, disparities in breastfeeding rates exist, whereby some demographic groups have even lower rates. This study examines the association between dosage of breastfeeding conversations with a home visitor on breastfeeding continuation in participants who enrolled postnatally.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Analysis of Patient-Reported Outcomes in Chronic Pruritus: Patients with Chronic Liver or Kidney Diseases Exhibit Higher Psychological Distress than Those with Atopic Dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results highlight the need for holistic, patient-centred management strategies that address both the physical and psychological aspects of CP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tribal-Led Commercial Tobacco Prevention: Outcomes from the California American Indian Tobacco Initiative Evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Commercial tobacco-related health disparities persist for American Indian and Alaska Natives in the USA despite widespread reductions in commercial tobacco use in the general population. Addressing these disparities requires a culturally relevant approach but the diversity of Tribal communities, including historical, cultural, social, and economic differences, can make uniform public health interventions that are culturally relevant challenging to design. The California Tribal Initiative to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive and vascular (dys)function after COVID-19]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[COVID-19 is a systemic infection that causes endothelial dysfunction, contributing to severe cases. While vascular complications are well-documented, their impact on vascular structure, function, and cognition remains unclear. This cross-sectional study explored vascular and cognitive differences across patients with mild, moderate, and severe COVID-19, examining correlations between global cognitive performance and vascular parameters. This study included 83 working-age patients (30-65 years,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knowledge domains and emerging trends in aldosterone and kidney disease prognosis: a bibliometric analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This targeted bibliometric analysis fills a specific gap by clarifying how aldosterone research shapes our understanding of kidney disease prognosis. The findings highlight the need for more integrated, multidisciplinary approaches and support continued clinical and translational research to refine therapies and improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Labor market entry prospects of people with visual impairments: evidence from administrative register data in the Netherlands]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The UN's Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities includes a right to equal work opportunities. People with visual impairments (VI) are targeted by this convention and experience low employment rates. The initial transition from education to labor is a predictor for later labor market participation. Exploiting administrative register data, we identified a graduated subpopulation with VI and matched them to a control group. This paper evaluates (1) group differences in various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social Communication, Repetitive Behaviors and Interests, and Adaptive Behavior in Girls With Autism Spectrum Disorder Without Intellectual Disability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Social communication, repetitive behaviors and interests, and adaptive behavior in girls with autism spectrum disorder (ASD) without intellectual disability were compared to a group of typically developing (TD) girls. Thirty seven girls 7;5-15;2 were included: 18 ASD and 19 TD. Groups were matched on age and IQ. Social Communication Questionnaire (SCQ), Autism Diagnostic Observation Schedule (ADOS-2), and Vineland Adaptive Behavior Scales (VABS-2) were administered. Item level scores within the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Development and Use of Office of New Drugs Custom Medical Queries for Safety Analyses of Clinical Trial Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of safety data by the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) is a critical step in the review of marketing applications for drugs and biologics. It can be difficult to identify a safety signal, and important signals can be missed if not evaluated comprehensively. Adverse events reported by study participants constitute a major source of safety data, and while previously established standard term groupings have been useful for analysis (e.g., Standardised MedDRA^(®) Queries), the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Newborn screening for congenital adrenal hyperplasia due to 21 hydroxylase deficiency: the Italian experience 2006-2019]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study confirms the efficacy of NBS in early detection of classic 21OH-CAH, emphasizing the need for timely reporting and second-tier testing to improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient Neutral Nitrate-to-Ammonia Electrosynthesis Using Synergistic Ru-Based Nanoalloys on Nitrogen-Doped Carbon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrocatalytic nitrate reduction reaction (NO(3)RR) represents a sustainable and environmentally benign route for ammonia (NH(3)) synthesis. However, NO(3)RR is still limited by the competition from hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) and the high energy barrier in the hydrogenation step of nitrogen-containing intermediates. Here, we report a selective etching strategy to construct RuM nanoalloys (M = Fe, Co, Ni, Cu) uniformly dispersed on porous nitrogen-doped carbon substrates for efficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[People with epilepsy and intellectual disability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The prevalence of epilepsy is high in people with intellectual disability (ID) and increases with growing severity of the ID. People with epilepsy and ID are not only at risk of different types of seizure-related complications (such as injuries and sudden unexpected death) but also of different types of physical impairments and of psychiatric, cognitive and behavioral comorbidities. ID is also associated with drug-resistant epilepsy (OR 3.38). Polytherapy is frequent in this population and leads...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioactive compounds from marine algae in pancreatic cancer therapy: mechanistic insights into fucoidan and phlorotannins: a review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic cancer is one of the most lethal tumors, marked by a dismal prognosis, few treatment alternatives, and resistance to standard pharmacological interventions. Marine algae are becoming a source of bioactive chemicals with significant anticancer properties. This review examines fucoidan, a sulfated polysaccharide, and phlorotannins, polyphenols exclusive to brown algae, emphasizing their therapeutic effects and molecular mechanisms in pancreatic cancer. Fucoidan inhibits tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular mechanisms of synovial pathology in osteoarthritis: insights from CXCL10 and MC4R expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoarthritis (OA) is a common progressive joint disorder marked by synovial inflammation, cartilage degeneration, the formation of osteophytes, though its underlying molecular mechanisms remain unclear. This study integrated bioinformatics and experimental validation to identify key genes in OA synovium and their association with immune infiltration. Analysis of the GSE82107 dataset (10 OA, 7 controls) revealed 909 differentially expressed genes (525 upregulated, 384 downregulated). WGCNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[S1PR5 as a prognostic biomarker in colon cancer: insights into efferocytosis-related mechanisms and immune modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colon cancer remains a major cause of global cancer mortality, characterized by complex interactions between genetic, epigenetic, and immune factors. This study investigates the prognostic value of efferocytosis-related genes and their role in colon cancer progression and immune modulation. A prognostic signature relied on efferocytosis-related genes was developed using univariate Cox and least absolute shrinkage and selection operator (LASSO) regression analyses. Immune infiltration, immune...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergy of advanced machine learning and deep neural networks with consensus molecular docking for virtual screening of anaplastic lymphoma kinase inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study addresses the urgent need for an AI model to predict Anaplastic Lymphoma Kinase (ALK) inhibitors for Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer treatment, targeting the ALK-positive mutation. With only five Food and Drug Administration approved ALK inhibitors currently available, effective drugs remain in demand. Leveraging machine learning (ML) and deep learning (DL), our research accelerates the precise screening of novel ALK inhibitors using both ligand-based and structure-based approaches. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A review on microbial-biofilm mediated mechanisms in marine microplastics degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the buildup of plastic in the marine environment is a long-standing problem, it has only lately been realized how relevant this pollution may be to the ocean. Microplastic fragments are an emerging concern in this field. Due to their small size, they are easily consumed by marine animals and, combined with the poisons and bacteria that colonize the plastic, can accumulate in the food chain. Unlike non-plastic biofilms, plastic biofilms are diverse and driven by a complex web of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Label-free HCR-facilitated nanozyme catalysis and fluorescence simultaneous amplification for ultrasensitive dual-signal sensing of foodborne Salmonella typhimurium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A label-free hybridization chain reaction (HCR)-facilitated nanozyme catalysis and fluorescence simultaneous amplification strategy is proposed for the ultrasensitive fluorescence-colorimetric dual-mode detection of S. typhimurium in complex food matrices. In the approach, aptamer-functionalized magnetic beads specifically captured S. typhimurium, and the cDNA triggered HCR to generate long and rigid double-stranded DNAs (dsDNAs), which could be inserted with SYBR Green I (SGI) and regulate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of machine learning models for predicting patient-perceived benefit following lumbar disc herniation or spinal stenosis surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Using nationwide registry data, we developed and temporally validated machine learning models to predict patient-perceived benefit one year after lumbar spine surgery. The disc herniation model showed possibly useful discrimination and good calibration, supporting its potential to inform clinical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three-dimensional quantitative CT analysis of the C2 spinous process and its implications for spinous process screw fixation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The C2 spinous process provides sufficient anatomical space for screw fixation. Horizontal and oblique screw trajectories offer longer and potentially more stable fixation paths and may serve as effective alternatives in salvage or supplementary scenarios.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Special considerations for assessing Major Adverse Kidney Events (MAKE) in children &lt; 2 years of age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Behavioral variation across multiple phases of intravenous cocaine self-administration among genetically diverse mouse populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetic and other predisposing factors can influence the progression from initiation of drug intake to compulsive substance use through distinct biobehavioral processes. Operant cocaine self-administration studies in laboratory mice offer a powerful method to dissect the biology of this progression from initiation, dose-response, extinction, and cued reinstatement in a controlled, tractable system. However, many such studies encompass limited genetic diversity and rarely examine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catheter ablation of tachyarrhythmias in children: state of the art and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The integration of advanced imaging technologies represents transformative progress in paediatric electrophysiology, enabling safer, more precise interventions with significantly reduced radiation exposure. These innovations establish new paradigms for personalized paediatric cardiac care, promising improved long-term outcomes for vulnerable populations requiring catheter ablation procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Agricultural SDHIs Induce Azole Resistance in Aspergillus fumigatus via Mitochondrial Sdh1 Suppression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Aspergillus fumigatus poses significant clinical challenges due to its increasing azole resistance. This study investigates the sdh1 gene's role in regulating azole susceptibility, mitochondrial function, and virulence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GPCR Heterodimers: Implications for Biased Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[G protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs) are key mediators of cellular signaling, participating in various physiological and pathological processes. Emerging evidence reveals that GPCRs can form functional heterodimers, wherein two distinct receptor subtypes interact mutually to generate unique signaling complexes. GPCR heterodimers play a crucial role in modulating cellular responses and are involved in biased signaling, a phenomenon where receptor activation preferentially triggers specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40952428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250915152423&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>