<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 07:40:50 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between usual source of care characteristics and health outcomes in diabetes mellitus: a focus on medication adherence and healthy behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings underscore that the functional quality of the USC, particularly the fulfillment of comprehensiveness and coordination, is crucial in improving medication adherence. Simply having a USC is insufficient. The lack of association with healthy behaviors suggests that physicians may focus more on pharmacological control, highlighting the need for multifaceted interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of autologous adipose-derived stem cells in subjects with moderate to severe atopic dermatitis: a multicenter, randomized, single-blind, placebo-controlled, phase 2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AtMSC therapy improved moderate to severe AD, offering a promising treatment option with potential applications in chronic inflammatory diseases. Further investigation, including double-blind phase 3 trials, is needed to confirm these findings and explore additional biomarkers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Stakeholders' Perceptions of Acceptability and Feasibility of Targeted Gardening for Particulate Matter Alleviation in National Coastal Industrial Complexes: Towards Conceptualizing Governance-centered Long-term Management Framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Growing concern over long-term particulate matter (PM) exposure in coastal industrial complexes highlights limitations in addressing stakeholders' perceptions of acceptability and feasibility (A&F) for targeted gardening for particulate matter alleviation (TGPMA) as a participatory governance strategy towards long-term management. A perception-based survey conducted in the Yeosu National Industrial Complex, South Korea, used statistical and network analyses to examine these perceptions. Results...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noninvasive subterahertz glucose monitoring using a communication inspired eye diagram]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global prevalence of diabetes mellitus (DM) continues to rise, highlighting the need for noninvasive, painless continuous blood glucose monitoring to support disease management and reduce long-term complications. Here, we report noninvasive subterahertz (sub-THz) glucose monitoring using communication-inspired eye diagram (sub-THz GlucoEye). The method detects distortion in the modulation pattern of sub-THz carrier signals reflected from the fingertip, resulting from relaxation time...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cathelicidin LL37-loaded extracellular vesicles from Edwardsiella piscicida promote antibacterial and wound-healing activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacterial extracellular vesicles (BEVs) have emerged as a promising therapeutic platform, offering the potential to be engineered for targeted molecular delivery. In this study, the human cathelicidin antimicrobial peptide (LL37) was encapsulated into extracellular vesicles derived from the fish pathogen Edwardsiella piscicida (EpEVs) through co-incubation. LL37-encapsulated EpEVs (EpEVs-LL37) were isolated by ultracentrifugation and characterized with a mean particle size of 73.6 ± 1.4 nm and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human cardiac organoids highlight cardiotoxicity of the tire rubber antioxidant 6PPD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[N-(1,3-dimethylbutyl)-N'-phenyl-p-phenylenediamine (6PPD), a tire rubber antioxidant and environmental contaminant, poses potential human cardiovascular health risks. However, these remain poorly understood. In this study, we established human induced pluripotent stem-cell-derived cardiac organoids (hiPSC-COs) to evaluate 6PPD cardiotoxicity. The organoids exhibited mature cardiac characteristics, containing multiple cell types, including cardiomyocytes, smooth muscle cells, and cardiac...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-target mechanisms of Bojungikki-tang in psoriasis-like dermatitis: Integrative network and transcriptomic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that BJT ameliorated psoriasis-like inflammation by concurrently regulating pivotal pro-inflammatory cytokines and two distinct steps of the AA pathway, which may be related to its multi-component composition. These findings indicate the therapeutic potential of the multi-component drug BJT on multiple targets for psoriasis-like inflammation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic profiles of Moutan Cortex after single and repeated administration in a dinitrobenzene sulfonic acid-induced colitis model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Moutan Cortex (MC), the dried root bark of Paeonia suffruticosa, is used in traditional Chinese and Korean medicine to treat enteritis for its anti-inflammatory properties. This study compared the pharmacokinetic (PK) profiles of paeonol and paeoniflorin in normal and dinitrobenzene sulfonic acid (DNBS)-induced colitis rats, and to determine how repeated low-dose MC [MC(L), 0.5 g/kg] or high-dose MC [MC(H), 2.5 g/kg] alters PK and disease severity. Using ultra-performance liquid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triterpenoids and sterols from <em>Pseudocydonia sinensis</em> fruits and their anti-inflammatory activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fruit of Pseudocydonia sinensis is widely valued for both medicinal and dietary applications in East Asia. Ethnomedical records describe its traditional use for relieving various diseases, such as diarrhoea, vomiting, myalgia, and rheumatoid arthritis. Here, we reported the discovery of one new megastigmane ester (1), two new triterpenoid esters (2 and 3), and 12 known compounds (4-15) from the ethanol extract of P. sinensis fruits. These isolates were further evaluated for their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[YouTube Searching and Self-Treatment Behaviors Among Patients With Benign Paroxysmal Positional Vertigo Before and After Clinic Visits: Prospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: YouTube has become a popular platform for patients seeking health-related information, including guidance on managing benign paroxysmal positional vertigo (BPPV). As self-diagnosis and self-treatment through online content grow more common, concerns have arisen regarding their influence on patients' health care decisions and treatment outcomes. However, little is known about how YouTube use and self-treatment behaviors change before and after clinical consultation, or whether these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Negative Impact of p21-Activated Kinase 4-Mediated AMP-Activated Protein Kinase Inhibition on Sarcopenia in Mice and Humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We recently identified that AMP-activated protein kinase (AMPK) α2 phosphorylation at S491 is mediated by p21-activated kinase 4 (PAK4), leading to muscular and systemic insulin resistance. This study examined how muscle PAK4 deletion affects atrophy in male mice and its link to human sarcopenia. Dexamethasone treatment increased the mRNA and protein levels of PAK4, which was partially the result of glucocorticoid response elements activation in the promoter of the Pak4 gene. Muscle-specific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered Body Composition in Dizziness and Vestibular Dysfunction: Insights From the Korean National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sarcopenia was found to be significantly associated with dizziness in the group with VD but not in those without it. While this study does not establish a causal relationship, maintaining muscle mass through proper diet and physical activity may be beneficial for individuals with VD. Such efforts could help manage overall health, potentially reducing risks associated with sarcopenia and improving balance. Further longitudinal studies are necessary to explore the potential causal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ion Exchange-Driven Controlled Transformation and Heterostructure Formation of Sn-Based Wafer-Scale 2D Layers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explores two synthesis strategies for tin (Sn)-based two-dimensional (2D) transition metal dichalcogenide (TMD) van der Waals (vdW) layers: (1) direct chemical vapor deposition (CVD) growths of wafer-scale tin diselenide (SnSe(2)), tin disulfide (SnS(2)), and tin telluride (SnTe), and (2) their post-CVD transformations employing anion exchange reactions. While as-grown 2D SnSe(2) layers are confirmed to be intrinsically semiconducting (i.e., bandgap of ∼1 eV and electron mobility of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of Family Interaction Frequency on Depressive Symptoms in Older Adults Aged ≥80 and Living Alone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Encouraging regular interaction among family members could serve as an effective strategy to protect the mental health of older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Analysis on the Efficacy of Monopolar Radiofrequency With Continuous Water Cooling and Conventional Cryogen Spray Cooling in Facial Rejuvenation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: RF-CWC offers a clinically effective and better-tolerated alternative to traditional cryogen-cooled MRF for facial rejuvenation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Chronic Psoriasis Model Using Long-Term Imiquimod Application in IL-10-Deficient Mice: Recapitulating Skin Inflammation, Comorbidities, and Gut-Skin Axis Alterations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The 6-week IMQ-applied IL-10 KO model may better reflect chronic and severe psoriasis with gut-related comorbidities, offering a valuable platform to investigate the gut-skin axis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proposal of Phenotypic Patterns in Facial Atopic Dermatitis: A Single-Center Retrospective Analysis of 100 Cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study identified distinct facial involvement patterns in AD, with centrofacial and periorificial patterns being the most prevalent. These findings underscore the importance of recognizing facial and neck involvement in AD for accurate diagnosis and personalized treatment. Further large-scale studies are needed to validate these results and explore the underlying mechanisms influencing facial involvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyunsaturated Fatty Acids and Skin Cancer: Two-Sample Mendelian Randomization Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This MR analysis supports a causal role of circulating PUFAs in skin cancer development and highlights the importance of FADS-mediated endogenous PUFA metabolism. These findings provide novel insights into the genetic and metabolic underpinnings of skin cancer susceptibility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions and Experiences of Scalp Micropigmentation Among Dermatology Outpatients With Hair Loss: A Survey-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study reveals a disconnect between legal awareness and actual treatment behavior regarding SMP. While most patients understand that SMP is a medical procedure requiring physician oversight, many still receive treatment in non-medical environments. The findings highlight the need to expand access to physician-led SMP services, enhance public education, and reinforce regulatory enforcement to ensure patient safety and align practices with clinical standards.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Hydrochlorothiazide on Nonmelanoma Skin Cancer: A Distributed Network Analysis of 11 Real-world Databases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HCTZ was not associated with the development of NMSC in a Korean hypertensive population, regardless of the duration of drug exposure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Evaluation of Glabellar Area Muscles Movement and Skin Displacement Using 3D Skin Displacement Vector Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This data will serve as an important guide for Botulinum Toxin treatment of glabella wrinkles in Korean patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Prevalence and Associated Factors of Nipple Eczema in Patients With Atopic Dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although the area affected by NE is small, dermatologists should be aware of its association with severe AD characteristics, and its significant impact on patient HRQoL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updates in Treatment for Androgenetic Alopecia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Androgenetic alopecia (AGA) is a common nonscarring hair loss condition that affects both men and women, often resulting in psychological distress and reduced quality of life. AGA pathogenesis involves genetic predisposition and androgen influence, primarily dihydrotestosterone (DHT), which leads to hair follicle miniaturization and progressive hair thinning. AGA remains challenging to manage due to its chronic progression and the combined influence of genetic and environmental factors. Topical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Performance Evaluation of Federated and Centralized Learning for Velum and OTE Segmentation in Sleep Endoscopy Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate segmentation of upper airway structures such as the velum and OTE (oropharynx, tongue base, epiglottis) in drug-induced sleep endoscopy (DISE) images is crucial for predicting the degree and location of obstruction to determine treatment options for obstructive sleep apnea (OSA). This study systematically compares centralized learning (CL) and federated learning (FL) approaches for the semantic segmentation of these regions using multi-institutional DISE video data. A convolutional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why large language models cannot possess consciousness: an integrated information theory perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Current LLMs do not satisfy the structural and informational requirements of consciousness under IIT. Although capable of simulating intelligent language, LLMs remain unconscious systems with a negligible amount of integrated information, underscoring the distinction between linguistic competence and conscious experience.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SPICEiST: subcellular RNA pattern enhances cell clustering of imaging-based spatial transcriptomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the value of leveraging subcellular transcript patterns to overcome the inherent limitations of imaging-based ST, particularly for small gene panels, and may provide new insights into tumor heterogeneity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disease burden of chronic hepatitis B and C patients in South Korea: a population-based 16-year cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CHB/CHC is burdensome in its disease progression risk and medical costs compared to monoinfection. An effective screening strategy for early management of CHB/CHC is warranted for public health in South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral functional limitation and risk of frailty onset in older adults: a sex-stratified 4-Year cohort study with competing risk analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Self-reported oral functional limitation was significantly associated with frailty onset over 4 years, particularly among women. Incorporating oral function assessment into geriatric screening and community health programs may facilitate early identification of risk and the implementation of preventive strategies for frailty.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331404/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sacral dimple: clinical perspectives of lesions hidden beneath the skin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sacral dimples are the most common cutaneous anomalies in newborns. While usually benign anatomical variants, some dimples are indicative of occult spinal dysraphism, such as a tethered cord, dermal sinus tract, or lipomyelomeningocele, that, if undiagnosed, may cause irreversible neurological, orthopedic, and urological deficits. Distinguishing benign from high-risk dimples is essential for timely intervention. This review summarizes the embryological origins, diagnostic criteria, imaging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discordance between antibiotic therapy and recurrent urinary tract infections in young children with thirdgeneration cephalosporin-resistant infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Completing a third-generation cephalosporin course when isolates are not susceptible to thirdgeneration cephalosporins can increase early UTI recurrence rates in Korean children. Reviewing susceptibility on day 5 and switching to an active oral agent may reduce recurrence and limit unnecessary broad-spectrum antibiotic exposure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting visual acuity using optical coherence tomography in patients with neovascular age-related macular degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to assess the feasibility of an artificial intelligence(AI) model to predict visual acuity(VA) using optical coherence tomography(OCT) in treatment-naïve patients with neovascular age-related macular degeneration (AMD). This retrospective study enrolled 240 patients(240 eyes) with pseudophakic neovascular AMD who received antivascular endothelial growth factor therapy. Each patient underwent 10 visits where they underwent best-corrected visual acuity(BCVA) testing and horizontal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of electron ptychography from algorithms, detectors to its applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunneled Peripherally Inserted Central Catheters and Bloodstream Infection: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Subcutaneous tunneling for PICC placement is associated with a significant reduction in CLABSI rate among hospitalized adult patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Long-term correction of hemophilia A via integration of a functionally enhanced FVIII gene into the AAVS1 locus by nickase in patient-derived iPSCs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[O-GlcNAcylation of DDB1 at Ser-764 by OGT promotes cancer cell stemness in colorectal cancer through increased polyubiquitination of p53]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several ubiquitin E3 ligases, including MDM2, COP1, HUWE1, and CUL4A-DDB1, regulate the stability of the p53 protein, which is crucial for maintaining cell survival, promoting apoptosis, facilitating DNA repair, and preventing the stemness of cancer cells. The CUL4A-DDB1 complex is recognized as one of the non-canonical pathways that control p53 stability. However, the role of DDB1 O-GlcNAcylation has not been studied until now. Here, we present new evidence that DDB1 glycosylation mainly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing battery thermal management system using the emulsion of encapsulated phase change material and water in a mini helical tube]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-cancer gene set discovery via scRNA-seq for optimal deep learning based downstream tasks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The application of machine learning to transcriptomics data has led to significant advances in cancer research. However, the high dimensionality and complexity of RNA sequencing (RNA-seq) data pose significant challenges in pan-cancer studies. This study hypothesizes that gene sets derived from single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) data will outperform those selected using bulk RNA-seq in pan-cancer downstream tasks. We analyzed scRNA-seq data from 181 tumor biopsies across 13 cancer types....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controllable-pore porous microneedles for high-speed extraction and biomarker detection of interstitial fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porous microneedles have attracted considerable attention as minimally invasive tools for interstitial fluid sampling and biomarker analyses. However, existing porous microneedle fabrication methods often suffer from low extraction efficiency, primarily because of the inherent trade-off between increasing porosity and maintaining sufficient mechanical strength. Herein, we present a novel approach for fabricating porous microneedles with controllable pore sizes and enhanced extraction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of Potassium-Competitive Acid Blockers Compared With Proton Pump Inhibitors in Patients With Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease and Peptic Ulcer Disease: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: P-CABs demonstrate a comparable AE risk to PPIs but monitoring for hypergastrinemia and hepatic dysfunction is essential. Further research is required to support safer clinical use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Retrospective Cohort Study on the Efficacy of Pregabalin in Patients With Sensitive Skin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Pregabalin improved symptoms in SSS, supporting its potential role in managing neuropathic features and reinforcing the neurogenic hypothesis underlying its therapeutic mechanism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of the Safety Profile of Trastuzumab Deruxtecan by Dose: A Pooled Analysis Across DESTINY Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Gastrointestinal and hematologic TEAEs were most common, with nausea, neutropenia, and fatigue most commonly reported. ILD/pneumonitis occurred in ∼11%-12% of patients, with severe cases infrequent. Most TEAEs were low grade, though dose modifications highlight the need for proactive TEAE management, particularly in older patients and those with renal impairment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bronchodilator Response of TEV/FEV3 and Its Implications in Pediatric Asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis of asthma in children is challenging due to limitations of conventional spirometry, which primarily assesses large airway function and requires considerable patient effort. Terminal expiration volume (TEV)/forced expiratory volume in 3 seconds (FEV3) has been proposed as a new metric that may help assess small airway dysfunction, where TEV represents the volume difference between FEV3 and forced expiratory volume in 1 seconds (FEV1) and reflects terminal expiratory airflow. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Obstructive Sleep Apnea and Atopic Dermatitis in the Korean Adult Population: Results From the 2019-2022 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OSA risk was significantly associated with AD prevalence, having a dose-response relationship. Given the observed associations, incorporating OSA management into clinical strategies may warrant further investigation as a potential avenue for mitigating AD-related risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Prevalence of Allergic Rhinitis in Korean Children: Nationwide Surveys in the Periods 1995-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The prevalence of AR among Korean children has increased over the past few decades, highlighting the importance of continuous surveillance and preventive measures. Identifying modifiable risk factors, such as early-life exposure and environmental influences, is crucial for developing targeted intervention strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Siglec-8 as a Biomarker for Predicting Anti-IL-5 Response in Severe Asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Baseline serum Siglec-8 levels showed a trend toward better predictive performance than other parameters for predicting 6- and 12-month responses to anti-IL-5 therapies in patients with SA. These findings suggest that Siglec-8 may have the potential as a biomarker for guiding treatment decisions, although further validation in larger, prospective studies is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Biologics on Nasal Symptoms in Severe Asthmatics: Findings From the PRISM Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dupilumab demonstrates a significant improvement not only in total SNOT-22 scores but also in the extranasal rhinological, physiologic, and sleep dysfunction domain scores compared to conventional or anti-IL-5 treatment in patients with severe asthma and nasal symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of a Combination Therapy of Montelukast and Antihistamines in Allergic Rhinitis: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Allergic rhinitis (AR) significantly impairs quality of life and often necessitates combination therapies for optimal symptom control. This study aimed to evaluate the efficacy of montelukast-antihistamine combination therapy in patients with AR by using a network meta-analysis. A comprehensive search was conducted using PubMed, Embase, MEDLINE, Scopus, the Cochrane Library, and Google Scholar up to April 2025. The treatment strategies included montelukast alone, antihistamine monotherapies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Signal-enhanced detection of p-tau181 in human plasma as a biomarker for Alzheimer's disease using a multi-channel impedance analyzer with nanoliposome amplification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD), caused by amyloid-β (Aβ) aggregation-derived senile plaques, is among the most prevalent neurodegenerative disorders. Recently, Roche and Lilly announced the development of an AD diagnosis that utilizes phosphorylated tau (p-tau) and apolipoprotein E epsilon 4 allele as biomarkers, rather than Aβ. Additionally, the National Institute on Aging and Alzheimer's Association Research Framework suggests that p-tau molecules can serve as critical biomarkers for AD diagnosis....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Outcomes of Primary Sclerosing Cholangitis in Inflammatory Bowel Disease: A Multinational Study across Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PSC is less prevalent among Asian IBD patients than in Western populations. The increased use of MRCP may enable earlier detection, contributing to milder disease severity and improved clinical outcomes in recent years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health vulnerabilities and periodontal disease in Korean adults: Implications for public health policy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Mental health vulnerabilities were associated with periodontal disease. Although a causal relationship and temporal sequence could not be determined, the findings highlight the need for integrated public health strategies that link dental care with mental health screening and community support systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severe COVID-19, vaccination, and mortality among individuals with asthma: A Nationwide population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The COVID-19 vaccination was associated with reduced long-term mortality in individuals with asthma, regardless of COVID-19 status.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic growth factor profiling platform for 3D tumor models reveals estradiol-responsive cellular mechanisms of immunotherapy resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current organoid culture systems face critical limitations: standardized growth factor formulations fail to capture patient-specific signaling requirements, while single-cell-type approaches overlook tumor-stromal interactions essential for understanding immunotherapy resistance. To address these challenges, we developed an automated biofabrication platform that systematically integrates patient-derived three-dimensional (3D) cultures with comprehensive growth factor profiling across 128...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biochemical predictors of pregnancy in cattle: Enhancing recipient selection for embryo transfer efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study assessed potential biochemical markers to improve the selection of recipient cows in embryo transfer (ET). Previous efforts have focused primarily on the selection of donor cows, along with oocyte quality; however, the physiological status of recipient cows is also important for ensuring successful pregnancies. Blood samples were collected from 30 recipient cows, followed by estrus synchronization. Using their plasmas, their enzymes, metabolites, electrolytes, and related...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical efficacy of induced epiphora by punctal plugging on refractory dry eye disease with ocular surface Damage: Randomized sham-controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Induced epiphora by punctal plugging showed improvement in both subjective and objective outcomes in patients with refractory DED with ocular surface damage. This approach may serve as a potential adjunctive option for patients unresponsive to standard treatments, warranting careful application and longer-term evaluation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-invasive colorectal cancer screening: emerging tools and clinical evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fecal immunochemical test (FIT) is a widely used non-invasive screening method for colorectal cancer (CRC) in many countries, valued for its simplicity, affordability, and reasonable sensitivity. Typically recommended on an annual or biennial basis, the FIT is effective in reducing CRC incidence and mortality by facilitating early detection. Stool DNA tests, including multitarget DNA tests and DNA methylation assays, demonstrate higher sensitivity than FIT for CRC and advanced adenomas,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Adhesive and Thermal Properties of Waterborne Acrylic Pressure-Sensitive Adhesives via Graphene Oxide/Polymeric Surfactant Synergy: Sequential Adsorption-Grafting-Encapsulation Mechanism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A high solids (about 30 wt %) water-borne acrylic pressure-sensitive adhesive (PSA) was prepared by emulsion polymerization using graphene oxide (GO) as a particulate surfactant and a random poly(n-butyl acrylate-stat-acrylic acid) copolymer, P(n-BA-stat-AA), as an auxiliary polymeric surfactant, thereby avoiding the colloidal instability commonly observed with conventional low-molecular-weight surfactants. FT-IR, Raman, and XPS analyses confirmed a sequential "adsorption-grafting-encapsulation"...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Age-Related Patterns in Smartphone Keystroke Dynamics Considering Temporal Variability: Cross-Sectional Study With AI-Based Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrated that smartphone keystroke dynamics reflect age-sensitive behavioral patterns, particularly when analyzed with fine-grained temporal resolution. While the primary goal was not age estimation per se, the ability to model these patterns highlights the potential of keystroke dynamics as a passive, unobtrusive behavioral marker for age-related functional characteristics. These insights may inform future applications in digital health, such as age-sensitive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Chemotherapy Response in Patients With Advanced or Metastatic Pancreatic Cancer Using Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ML models trained on multicenter data can effectively predict early mortality risk and help personalize chemotherapy selection in advanced or metastatic pancreatic cancer, potentially improving clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective CDK6 Degradation via the KLHDC2 E3 Ubiquitin Ligase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We discovered novel small molecule ligands of KLHDC2 and leveraged them to generate KLHDC2-mediated CDK6-selective degraders. Degrader 48a exhibited potent and selective CDK6 degradation (DC(50) = 0.037 μM) over CDK4 (DC(50) > 10 μM) in MOLM-14 cells, leading to pronounced G(0)/G(1) cell-cycle arrest and apoptosis through inhibition of CDK6 downstream signaling. In addition, 48a demonstrated superior growth-inhibitory activity compared to the warhead, palbociclib, in several leukemia cells and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene expression profiling reveals two overarching types of ALCL with distinct targetable biology: an LLMPP study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anaplastic large cell lymphomas (ALCLs) are CD30+ T-cell lymphomas that share pathologic features but differ in presentation, outcome, and genetics. Current classification incorporates clinical presentation and ALK status, but inadequately addresses molecular heterogeneity and therapeutic vulnerabilities. We studied 689 ALCLs in the Lymphoma/Leukemia Molecular Profiling Project and performed expert consensus review, genetic subtyping (ALK, DUSP22, TP63, and triple-negative), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rhodococcus aromaticivorans sp. nov., an o-xylene degrading bacterium, and evidence supporting reclassification of Rhodococcus jostii RHA1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A Gram-positive, aerobic, non-motile bacterium with a rod-coccus shape, designated DK17T, was isolated from a crude oil-contaminated soil and identified as a member of the genus Rhodococcus based on 16S rRNA gene analysis, showing highest similarity (99.93%) to Rhodococcus jostii DSM 44719T. However, average nucleotide identity (ANI) and digital DNA-DNA hybridization (dDDH) values between strain DK17T and type strains within the genus Rhodococcus were below the species delineation thresholds of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of thyroid autoimmunity independent of thyroid hormone levels in pulmonary function decline: A population-based study in euthyroid adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Thyroid autoimmunity, as reflected by elevated TPOAb levels, was associated with a decline in pulmonary function among euthyroid individuals, independent of thyroid hormone levels. Our results support the clinical utility of TPOAb status as an early marker for detecting subclinical pulmonary vulnerability, particularly in older adults and those with a lower BMI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of early recovery in patients with acute peripheral facial paralysis using serial electroneuronography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides the preferred testing time and measurement sites for ENoG to predict early recovery from facial paralysis. Given the personal and social impact of facial paralysis, predicting early recovery is crucial for reassuring patients, providing better treatment, and encouraging early reintegration into society.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socio-ecological factors influencing dietary behaviours among adolescents and young adults in rural Eastern Uganda: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study contributes novel rural-specific evidence from rural Uganda, where AYAs' diets are uniquely constrained by satiety demands, parental dominance, cultural taboos, and seasonal scarcity; contrasting with urban contexts where convenience, autonomy, and wider food environments prevail. Multi-level interventions integrating nutrition education, family and peer engagement, cultural dialogue, and household food security support are essential for promoting healthier diets in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Topographic analysis of vascular changes in retrograde trans-synaptic degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RTSD demonstrated relatively modest vascular compromise compared to NAION, which is presumed to reflect secondary changes due to reduced metabolic demand following retrograde neuronal degeneration. Quantitative structure-vascular analysis using RTSD as a reference model may aid in distinguishing secondary degeneration from primary ischemic injury in optic neuropathies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ni-Catalyzed Cyclotrimerization of Unactivated Internal Alkynes: Ligand-Dependent Regioselectivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A nickel-catalyzed [2 + 2 + 2] cyclotrimerization of unactivated internal alkynes is presented, enabling regioselective access to fully substituted benzene derivatives through ligand control. The transformation proceeds under additive-free conditions and tolerates a wide range of aryl, heteroaryl, and aliphatic alkynes. Regioselectivity is governed by the ligand framework, in which trialkylphosphine ligands promote the exclusive formation of 1,2,4-substituted benzenes, whereas the N-heterocyclic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Clinical Variables on cfDNA Fragmentomic Signatures and Their Potential as Confounders in Cancer Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Physiological factors such as liver enzyme levels and age can significantly alter cfDNA fragmentomic profiles, generating patterns that resemble lung cancer-associated signals. These results highlight the importance of incorporating strategies to mitigate nonmalignant variability when developing cfDNA-based liquid biopsy assays, to ensure their accuracy, specificity, and clinical applicability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of 5-Aminosalicylic Acid Continuation versus Discontinuation in Patients with Ulcerative Colitis Escalated to Advanced Therapy: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Adjusted Effect Estimates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with UC escalated to advanced therapies, 5-ASA continuation was associated with decreased odds of achieving clinical remission compared to discontinuation, with no significant differences observed for secondary efficacy or safety endpoints.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of chimeric FAM72B transcripts generated by intergenic mRNA trans-splicing in breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Family with sequence similarity 72 (FAM72) is a protein-coding gene family located on chromosome 1 (chr1) in humans, and its functional roles, particularly in cancer, remain incompletely understood. Chimeric messenger RNA (mRNA) generated by intergenic mRNA trans-splicing (CRTS) is a novel phenomenon increasingly recognized for its involvement in cancer biology. It involves the fusion of two separate mRNA transcripts from different genomic loci, resulting in a chimeric mRNA molecule with altered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon-ions, protons or photons for head and neck cancer radiotherapy-an in silico planning study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To compare dose to the organ at risk (OAR) and target coverage of carbon-ion beam, protons, and photons for patients with head and neck cancer. Treatment plans for carbon-ion pencil beam scanning (C-PBS) (64 Gy (RBE) in 16 fractions), proton pencil beam scanning (P-PBS), and volumetric modulated arc therapy (VMAT) (70 Gy in 35 fractions for P-PBS and VMAT) were generated and compared using different dose constraints per treatment modality. Dose metrics (e.g. D95,V20) were analyzed. Statistical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical activity and Alzheimer's disease risk across genetic susceptibility: a prospective UK Biobank study using accelerometer data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Objectively measured PA substantially reduces AD risk regardless of genetic predisposition. Even light-intensity activity provides meaningful protection, supporting PA as a broadly applicable preventive strategy across all genetic risk levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of clinical and angiographic outcomes after woven EndoBridge treatment for intracranial aneurysms: an asian multicenter cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Institutional experience appeared to play a role in reducing procedure-related thromboembolic complications. Aneurysmal diameter, neck width, location and patients' smoking status influenced angiographic outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PEGylated Graphene Oxide Enhances <em>In Vitro</em> Transcription by Suppressing RNA Rebinding to T7 Polymerase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In vitro transcription (IVT) using T7 RNA polymerase is a key step in mRNA synthesis for therapeutic applications. However, the generation of double-stranded RNA (dsRNA) byproducts during IVT─primarily due to RNA rebinding and self-priming─triggers innate immune responses and reduces translation efficiency. Here, we present a simple and effective strategy to minimize dsRNA formation during IVT by incorporating PEGylated graphene oxide (PEG-GO). Graphene oxide (GO) preferentially binds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Myeloid Landscape of Large Artery Atherosclerotic and Cardioembolic Thrombi Retrieved by Mechanical Thrombectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardioembolic (CE) and large artery atherosclerosis (LAA) strokes are two main causes of acute ischemic stroke (AIS), carrying a high risk of recurrence. Studies on the composition of CE and LAA thrombi have produced conflicting results, underscoring the need for further investigation into more effective treatment strategies. While myeloid cells such as neutrophils and monocytes are known to promote thrombosis in cardiovascular diseases, their specific roles in thrombosis across AIS subtypes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triggering the onset of thermoelectric performance in BiCuSeO oxychalcogenides: Activation from a low intrinsic carrier concentration via Cd doping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BiCuSeO oxychalcogenides are promising p-type thermoelectric (TE) materials, yet their TE efficiency is limited by an extremely low intrinsic carrier concentration of ∼ 1018 cm-3. In this study, it is demonstrated that systematic Cd doping triggers the onset of TE performance of BiCuSeO. The substitution of Bi3+ with Cd2+ in a series of Bi1-xCdxCuSeO (x = 0, 0.02, 0.04, 0.06, and 0.08) polycrystalline alloys induces a predictable, near-linear increase in carrier concentration, reaching 3.19 ×...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the Letter of SK Bioscience, the SKYVaricella Manufacturer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remote-Controllable Immune-Priming Spot Formation Via Nanocomplexed Hydrogel-Assisted Histotripsy: Immunoasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunotherapy, which harnesses the immune system to eliminate cancer cells, offers durable, and specific responses. However, many tumors exhibit "immune deserts" - immunosuppressive microenvironments with low T cell infiltration due to the dominance of suppressive myeloid cells and limited inflammatory cues. Cancer vaccines combining tumor antigens and adjuvants can potentially convert these immune deserts into immune-active lesions. Yet, systemic administration often leads to adverse effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Effectiveness and Safety of Recombinant Human Follicle-Stimulating Hormone (rhFSH) in Infertile Women undergoing Assisted Reproductive Technology (ART): A Korean Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite widespread rhFSH use in infertile women undergoing ART, real-world comparative data on its effectiveness and safety across different rhFSH types remain limited. Using the HIRA claims database, we included 10,684 women aged 20-39 with infertility (2016-2021) who used only rhFSH in their first in vitro fertilization-embryo transfer (IVF-ET). Outcome variables comprised effectiveness (≥ 11 oocytes retrieved, pregnancy rates and live birth rate) and safety (ectopic pregnancy, miscarriage,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends and Socioeconomic Disparities in Polypharmacy and PIM Use Among 66-Year-Olds in Korea: A Nationwide Study, 2012-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: While PIM use slightly decreased over the study period, it remained above 50%, and polypharmacy prevalence increased among older adults in Korea. Socioeconomic disparities in medication use persist, highlighting the need for targeted interventions and policies to promote safe medication use among vulnerable groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell instructive hydrogels functionalized with polymerized DNA nanostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Novel hyaluronic acid hydrogels functionalized with polymerized DNA nanostructures using rolling circle amplification were developed. These hydrogels exhibited enhanced cell attachment and proliferation through functional DNA-mediated interactions. The system maintained favorable physicochemical properties and enhanced interactions with biological interfaces, demonstrating potential for advanced 3D cell culture applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[eHealth Literacy and Search Frequency in Relation to Objective Sleep Disorder Knowledge: Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: eHealth literacy and search frequency were both linked to greater knowledge of sleep disorders. However, the strength of the literacy-knowledge association differed across levels of search frequency. The relationship was stronger when search frequency was low and weaker among frequent seekers. These findings suggest that eHealth literacy and information-seeking behaviors jointly shape factual knowledge. Supporting eHealth literacy together with guidance on efficient information use...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive Performance of Radiomics-Based Machine Learning for Colorectal Cancer Recurrence Risk: Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Radiomics-based machine learning models, especially those integrating radiomics and clinical features, showed promising predictive performance for CRC recurrence risk. However, this study has several limitations, such as moderate study quality, limited sample size, and high heterogeneity in modeling approaches. These findings suggest the potential clinical value of integrated models in risk stratification and their potential to enhance personalized treatment, though further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitatively controlled and measured-traumatic brain injury impairs adult neurogenesis and alters neuropathological signatures in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rationale: Traumatic brain injury (TBI) poses a significant global health concern, necessitating a comprehensive understanding of its pathophysiology to devise effective treatments. The correlation between the intensity of head impact during injury and resultant neuropathology and behavioral changes in TBI remains unclear. Methods: The Quantitatively Controlled and Measured-TBI (QCM-TBI) system, a novel closed-head injury model, enables precise control and measurement of impact during collision....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A convective transport-enhanced multi-organoid device for therapeutic modeling of the liver-pancreas axis in obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rationale: Obesity-associated metabolic diseases such as metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) and type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM) are increasing rapidly, necessitating physiologically relevant in vitro models of the liver-pancreas axis. While recent multi-organoid systems have advanced inter-organ modeling, many systems still fall short of replicating the complex and directional metabolic interactions required to accurately reflect disease progression. This is partly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nivolumab plus chemotherapy in metastatic gastric cancer with low combined positive score]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This real-world retrospective study suggests modest efficacy of AGC patients with low CPS treated with nivolumab with chemotherapy. Further studies are needed to determine the optimal treatment strategy and to identify predictive biomarkers for therapy selection in patients with low-CPS AGC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bio-signal induced emotion monitoring and detection of anxiety: A sensor-driven approach with regression based random forest]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study addresses the rising importance of mental health by devel oping a novel healthcare plan. We integrate physiological data from sensors, such as Heart Rate (HR) and Galvanic Skin Response (GSR), to predict and manage anxiety. These sensors provide non-invasive insights into the com plex relationship between physiological reactions and mental well-being. To analyze the collected data, we developed a novel algorithm, Regression Based Random Forest (RBRF). Using a large-scale...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Evaluation Framework for AI-Generated Emergency Department Documentation: A Chain-of-Thought Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MEDIVAL demonstrates that progressive CoT strategies systematically enhance automated evaluation of emergency department documentation while maintaining high reproducibility. This offers a viable pre-screening tool for reducing expert workload while supporting reliable AI integration into emergency medicine workflows.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Twelve tips for developing and implementing AI curriculum for undergraduate medical education]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of artificial intelligence (AI) and its growing role in clinical settings have made AI education a priority in undergraduate medical education. To support this, AI curricula must align with existing medical education frameworks while addressing AI's distinctive characteristics. This article outlines twelve actionable tips to guide the development and implementation of such curricula. These include defining the purpose and scope of AI education within the broader context of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STIM1-Dependent Calcium Signaling in Astrocytes Controls Glutamate Accumulation and Ischemic Brain Injury During Acute Stroke in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astrocytes critically influence ischemic stroke outcomes through calcium signaling-dependent mechanisms, which can be both beneficial and detrimental. Stromal interaction molecule 1 (STIM1), a key regulator of store-operated calcium entry, has emerged as an essential mediator of intracellular calcium dynamics in astrocytes, yet its role in acute stroke remains largely unknown. Here, we demonstrate that conditional knockout of astrocytic STIM1 in mice dramatically reduces infarct volume and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpersonal Needs and Dysfunctional Self-Focus Mediate the Effect of Dysfunctional Pandemic Grief on Suicidality Among Nursing Professionals Who Witnessed Patients' Deaths]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Dysfunctional grief experienced by nurses following the loss of patients during the pandemic exacerbated suicidal ideation by fostering a greater focus on negative outcomes and heightened feelings of being a burden. These findings underscore the need for targeted interventions to address these specific cognitive and emotional vulnerabilities to mitigate the risk of suicidal ideation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Detection and Hearing Intervention in Infants With Bilateral Moderate Hearing Loss: Based on a Nationwide Infantile Hearing Aid Support Program in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings suggest that auditory rehabilitation achieves greater focus following the implementation of NHS. This study also provides valuable insights into the hearing status and rehabilitation outcomes of infants with moderate hearing loss. Furthermore, we anticipate that these results will contribute to informing policies aimed at reducing regional disparities in access to auditory rehabilitation services.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated Pre-Pregnancy Blood Pressure and the Risk of Adverse Pregnancy Outcomes: Evidence From a Nationwide Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Even modest increases in pre-pregnancy BP below the clinical threshold for hypertension were associated with a higher risk of adverse pregnancy outcomes. These findings highlight the need for early BP monitoring and management before pregnancy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based classification of acute scrotum using single ultrasound images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A deep learning model demonstrated promising diagnostic performance in differentiating acute scrotal emergencies using single US images. Its feasibility was preliminarily assessed in a small pilot study. These findings support further investigation, with larger and more balanced multicentre studies required to establish clinical utility and effective workflow integration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Species diversity of <em>Diaporthe</em> on mangroves: Taxonomic novelties, pathogenic associations, and phylogenetic reassessment of endophytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diaporthe species are frequently reported as endophytes on mangroves. These species are also known pathogens affecting several important hosts worldwide, but have yet to be explored as pathogens in mangrove environments. In this study, symptomatic leaves and stems of several mangrove species were collected from mangrove forests and estuaries in Thailand. Forty-five Diaporthe strains were isolated from symptomatic leaves and stems of various mangrove species, associated with leaf spots and stem...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhalational versus total intravenous anesthesia in noncardiac surgery: a comparative review of clinical outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inhalational anesthetics have long been the cornerstone of general anesthesia in noncardiac surgery owing to their reliable pharmacokinetics, ease of administration, and cardiopulmonary benefits such as bronchodilation and myocardial preconditioning. Total intravenous anesthesia (TIVA), achieved using short-acting agents such as propofol and remifentanil, and supported by target-controlled infusion systems and depth-of-anesthesia monitors, has emerged as a widely adopted alternative. TIVA is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spontaneous Transanal Small Bowel Evisceration with Distinct CT Findings: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case highlights the critical role of CT in identifying rectal perforation and intrarectal small bowel evisceration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Motor imagery enhances early rehabilitation in patients with high kinesiophobia after total knee arthroplasty: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Motor imagery is an effective adjunct to early rehabilitation after total knee arthroplasty. Its use enhances psychological resilience, supports adherence, and accelerates functional recovery, indicating its value in comprehensive, multidimensional rehabilitation strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world evidence on the safety and effectiveness of integrative Korean medicine for older patients post-traffic accident: A retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid aging of its population, Korea is becoming a super-aged society, and the proportion of older individuals among traffic accident patients continues to rise. Older adults often exhibit delayed recovery after trauma, multimorbidity, and polypharmacy, necessitating a tailored treatment approach. Integrative Korean medicine (IKM) treatment may serve as a suitable alternative, and its effectiveness and safety in older adults involved in traffic accidents warrant further evaluation. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of reading direction fluency in parafoveal information extraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate how semantic and syntactic parafoveal processing differ between fluent left-to-right and non-fluent right-to-left reading directions in individuals accustomed to left-to-right reading. A self-paced rapid serial visual presentation (RSVP) task was employed to evaluate semantic and syntactic congruency effects. Participants, familiar with left-to-right reading, were tested under conditions simulating both fluent left-to-right and non-fluent right-to-left reading...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of false positive and false negative errors in targeted next generation sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: T-NGS results from certified providers exhibit substantial variability in both sensitivity and FP error rates. Conventional pipelines not only increase FP errors but also accumulate recurrent FP-prone alleles. These findings underscore the urgent need for standardized pipelines and rigorous quality control measures to ensure the reliability of T-NGS in clinical diagnostics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of gait parameters between patients with chronic stroke at different ambulation levels and healthy adults: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Significant differences in biomechanical parameters, particularly those related to eccentric contraction in the proximal joints of the unaffected side, were observed between FAC 3 and FAC 4 groups. These disparities highlight the need for tailored gait rehabilitation strategies based on ambulation level.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide association study of lung function decline using elastic-net regression: a prospective analysis in Korean cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study identified novel SNPs associated with FEV(1) decline and developed a GRS that could help predict individuals at higher risk of rapid FEV(1) decline. The influence of genetic factors on the annual rate of decline in FEV(1) may vary depending on phenotypic characteristics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between gastroesophageal reflux disease and incident bronchiectasis: a nationwide representative population-based study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GERD is associated with an increased risk of bronchiectasis. Older age, underweight, coexisting airway diseases, and peptic ulcer disease were risk factors for developing bronchiectasis in GERD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing the effectiveness of in-person and synchronous virtually online for cambodia's rehabilitation health workforce]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights the strengths and limitations of different educational delivery methods in healthcare workforce training. It suggests that a hybrid approach, incorporating both in-person and synchronous virtually online in trainees' native language, may optimize learning satisfaction and engagement in future programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antiemetic use during pregnancy and child neurodevelopment: population-based birth cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This large-scale study found no association between antiemetic exposure during pregnancy and the risk of neurodevelopmental disorders or delays in children, providing reassurance for the use of antiemetics in pregnancy to treat nausea and vomiting. However, the slightly elevated risks observed in certain subgroups warrant further investigation. Meanwhile, these findings may assist in guiding decisions when considering antiemetic treatment during pregnancy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41327197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can reporting mood swings during oral contraceptive use predict peripartum depression? Results from the Swedish longitudinal cohort study Mom2B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using reporting guidelines to improve the reproducibility of cooking Christmas tree meringues: the "People tasting trees" cluster-randomised controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study failed to demonstrate that an improved recipe using the TIDieR reporting guideline with a video tutorial improved the reproducibility in terms of visual aspect, colour, size, taste and sales for Christmas tree meringues. The best way to succeed in reproducing Christmas tree meringues alike those showcased by the recipe-and thereby to improve reproducibility of experiments-remains a mystery still to be solved by further explorations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a novel in vitro micronucleus test using human induced pluripotent stem cell-derived T lymphocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our results demonstrated promising proof-of-principle data as an in vitro MN test and suggest that hiPSC-derived T lymphocytes have a potential to make a significant contribution to the improvement of in vitro genotoxicity studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Japanese version of the perceived service quality scale for community pharmacies: translation, cultural adaptation, and validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The pSQS-J is a valid and reliable instrument for evaluating patient experience in Japanese community pharmacies and may facilitate the advancement of person-centred care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical significance of lipoprotein(a) as a residual risk factor for atherosclerotic coronary plaque progression in statin-treated patients with coronary artery disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Limited evidence exists on the role of lipoprotein(a) [Lp(a)] in the progression of atherosclerotic coronary plaques as assessed by intravascular imaging modality, particularly under low-density lipoprotein cholesterol (LDL-C) lowering therapy. In this study, we aimed to evaluate the clinical significance of Lp(a) as a residual risk factor for coronary plaque progression, using serial intravascular ultrasound (IVUS) in statin-treated patients with coronary artery disease (CAD). This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated polyglutamylation and tau phosphorylation levels are associated with cognitive impairment at diagnosis in patients with primary central nervous system lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: High polyglutamylation levels in PCNSL were associated with cognitive impairment and increased tau phosphorylation at diagnosis. These findings suggest that polyglutamylation may contribute to neurocognitive symptoms by promoting tau pathology. Elucidating this mechanism may provide novel insights into PCNSL pathophysiology and may inform future studies on disease mechanisms and potential treatment targets.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author's reply to the letter to the editor entitled "Comment on 'Association between the urinary sodium-to-potassium ratio and apparent treatment-resistant hypertension in Japanese patients with non-dialysis dependent chronic kidney disease: the Fukuoka kidney disease registry study' "]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Major waves of H2A.Z incorporation during mouse oogenesis and preimplantation embryo development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epigenomes of mammalian oocytes and embryos undergo major transitions essential for successful development. Here, we provide genome-wide maps of histone variant H2A.Z during twelve stages of mouse oogenesis and preimplantation embryo development and relate it to histone marks and genomic features. This revealed that major waves of H2A.Z incorporation occur early in growing oocytes, forming distinct patterns of maternal, embryonic, and persistent H2A.Z enrichment. Late maternal enrichment is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nuclear magnetic resonance for wireless magnetic tracking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wireless trackers have emerged as a crucial technology in minimally invasive medical procedures with their remote localization capabilities. Existing trackers suffer from miniaturization issues and complex designs, which limit their integration into medical devices. We present nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) magnetic sensing, a quantum sensing approach with nT sensitivity for wireless magnetic tracking. NMR magnetic sensing enables millimeter-scale tracking accuracy and versatile miniaturized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Japan Energy Database with hourly and municipal-scale estimates to support local energy system analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving "carbon neutrality" in Japan is complicated by fragmented institutional responsibilities and the absence of municipal-scale energy data. Decarbonization is led by the Ministry of the Environment, reflecting a segmented administrative framework. Moreover, sectoral energy consumption data are not officially published at the municipal level, hindering evidence-based local policy development. To overcome these challenges, we have developed the Japan Energy Database, a comprehensive dataset...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prolonged disease remission of the chronic immunological skin disorder hidradenitis suppurativa with adjunctive bacteriophage therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hidradenitis suppurativa (HS) is a chronic skin disease in which the acute development of noduli, abscesses and in a later stage fistulas remains difficult to control, despite a wide range of recommended treatment options including immunomodulatory biologicals, surgical intervention and antibiotics. Besides being painful, associated lesions have an extensive impact on the quality of life. While HS is primarily an immune-mediated inflammatory disease, the skin microbiota plays a key role in its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining key interventions for rectal cancer surgery: a literature review and expert panel consensus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We propose this list of 37 key interventions as a contemporary framework for assessing rectal cancer surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide comprehensive genomic profiling defines the genomic landscape of hepatocellular carcinoma across etiologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) arises from various etiologies, including viral hepatitis and non-viral liver diseases. Although comprehensive genomic profiling (CGP) is increasingly applied in oncology, the influence of disease etiology on the genomic landscape of HCC and biomarker applicability remains insufficiently characterized. CGP data from 551 patients with HCC, registered in the National Center for Cancer Genomics and Advanced Therapeutics (C-CAT) database, were analyzed after excluding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determining the effect of femoral anteversion and hip alignment parameters on lower limb and knee alignment post-total hip arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Total hip arthroplasty (THA) aims to restore hip joint alignment in patients with osteoarthritis (OA) or osteonecrosis of the femoral head (ONFH). While THA directly affects hip alignment, it also influences leg and patellar alignment, potentially altering knee biomechanics and accelerating osteoarthritis progression. Postoperative alignment changes commonly include increased varus alignment in the operative leg and valgus alignment in the contralateral leg. However, the factors contributing to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oil-sealed RGD-modified alginate hydrogel microwell array for analysis of single-cell-derived extracellular vesicles and particles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose an oil-sealed, arginine-glycine-aspartic (RGD) -modified alginate hydrogel microwell array for the analysis of single-cell-derived extracellular vesicles and particles (EVPs) secreted by adherent cells cultured in enclosed spaces. Taking advantage of the mesh structure of alginate hydrogel, we developed a microwell array with size-selective permeability that allows nutrients to pass through the hydrogel while preventing EVPs from doing so. Continuous single-cell culture in sealed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41331071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of radio frequency heating inactivation on foodborne pathogens in model foods varying in structural matrix complexity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radio Frequency (RF) heating is a promising alternative for conventional heating to inactivate pathogens during food processing, but a knowledge gap exists concerning RF effects on bacteria in relation to different food microstructural aspects. This study focusses on RF inactivation of Listeria monocytogenes and Salmonella Typhimurium in differently-structured food matrices, tackling (i) indirect effects of RF compared to conventional heating in different matrices, and (ii) food matrix rheology...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural mechanism of the Retron-Eco7 anti-phage defense system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retrons are prokaryotic genetic elements involved in anti-phage defense and consist of a non-coding RNA, a reverse transcriptase (RT), and various effector proteins. Retron-Eco7 (previously known as Retron-Ec78) from Escherichia coli encodes two effector proteins (the PtuA ATPase and the PtuB nuclease) and degrades the host tRNA^(Tyr) upon phage infection, thereby protecting host cells against invading phages. However, its defense mechanism remains elusive. Here, we report the cryo-electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ctDNA detectability and representativeness in seven body liquids from patients with metastatic breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liquid biopsies enable non-invasive monitoring and characterization of metastatic cancer, primarily through circulating tumor DNA (ctDNA) in blood. The representativeness of all metastatic sites in these liquid biopsies and the clinical relevance of other body fluids remain uncertain. We performed low-pass whole genome sequencing on 216 liquid and 745 metastatic tissue samples from 20 autopsied female patients with metastatic breast cancer to assess ctDNA detection, fraction, and site...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Authors' reply: Comments on "Physical therapy for peripheral facial palsy: A systematic review and meta-analysis"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combination of averaged bregma-interaural and electrophysiology-guided technique improves subthalamic nucleus targeting accuracy in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate electrode implantation in the subthalamic nucleus (STN) of rats is essential for high-quality electrophysiological and neuromodulation studies but remains technically challenging due to the small size and deep location of the STN. Traditional stereotactic methods, relying on bregma or averaged bregma-interaural based coordinates, often result in misplacement of electrode. Here, we introduce a combined anatomical and functional approach-bregma-interaural and electrophysiology-guided...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WormTracer: A precise method for worm posture analysis using temporal continuity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: WormTracer is accurate, easy to use and applicable to various imaging conditions, providing a promising tool for high-throughput behavioral analyses of C. elegans and enabling more detailed motion quantification than existing methods.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational Analysis of Expressive Behavior in Clinical Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clinical psychological assessment often relies on self-report, interviews, and behavioral observation, methods that pose challenges for reliability, validity, and scalability. Computational approaches offer new opportunities to analyze expressive behavior (e.g., facial expressions, vocal prosody, language use) with greater precision and efficiency. This review provides an accessible conceptual framework for understanding how methods from computer vision, speech signal processing, and natural...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the distribution of adenosine and guanosine on fermented soybean cryosections by MALDI-MSI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bioactive compounds in fermented soybeans (Natto) may reduce cardiovascular disease risk because of their relatively high concentration of vitamin K but may also increase purine levels, thereby increasing the risk of gout. To investigate purine distribution, we overcame the challenges associated with plant cryosection quality by using a conductive adhesive film technique to produce high-quality cryosections suitable for matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization mass spectrometry imaging....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep spatiotemporal clutter filtering of transthoracic echocardiographic images: Leveraging contextual attention and residual learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a deep autoencoder network for filtering reverberation clutter from transthoracic echocardiographic (TTE) images. Given the spatiotemporal nature of this type of clutter, the filtering network employs 3D convolutional layers to suppress it throughout the cardiac cycle. The design of the network incorporates two key features that contribute to the effectiveness of the filter: (1) an attention mechanism for focusing on cluttered regions and leveraging contextual information,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of a novel natural sunscreen from thermophilic cyanobacteria with a potentially unique biosynthetic pathway and its transcriptional response to environmental stresses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycosporine-like amino acids (MAAs) are natural sunscreens with UV-A/UV-B-absorbing capacity and diverse potential biological activities. In this study, eight thermophilic cyanobacterial strains were isolated from a neutral-alkaline hot spring in Thailand. Of these, we have successfully discovered and identified a structurally novel MAA biosynthesized by the thermophilic cyanobacterium Gloeocapsa sp. strain BRSZ. Using high-performance liquid chromatography, high-resolution positive electrospray...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal patterns of neuronal electrical activity evoked by stimulation with a focused femtosecond laser]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuronal networks exhibit spatiotemporal patterns of electrical activity, such as spike location, spike timing, and burst firing among neuronal populations. These spatiotemporal patterns of neuronal activity play important roles in brain function and are modified by external stimuli. Single-neuron stimulation and measurement of neuronal network responses are effective for elucidating information processing in complex neuronal networks. Single-cell stimulation by transient microperforation based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative evaluation of DNS, PAHBAH, and BCA colourimetric assays for quantifying reducing sugars]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colourimetric assays for quantifying reducing sugars are widely used, including for assessing glycoside hydrolase activities. Consequently, there is a need for reliable high-throughput methodologies. Several protocols have been described in literature, with the most commonly used being the dinitrosalicylic acid (DNS), bicinchoninic acid (BCA) and p-hydroxybenzoic acid hydrazide (PAHBAH) assays. This study presents a comparative evaluation of these assays. Our results show that both the DNS and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An autopsy case of sudden infant death caused by cardiac fibroma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A one-month-old girl in good health being carried by her mother in a baby carrier suddenly went into cardiac arrest. She was rushed to the hospital, but was pronounced dead. A forensic autopsy was performed. On the heart, which weighed 63.6 g, a single large, well-defined, round, white tumor was observed in the left ventricular wall. Tumor cells with spindle-shaped small nuclei proliferated along with collagen fiber proliferation. The diagnosis was cardiac fibroma. The tumor had compressed the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discrimination of independent walking by spatiotemporal gait parameter variability in patients with hemiparesis following stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Gait variability in spatiotemporal parameters, a measure related to gait stability, is associated with fall risk in patients with stroke. Assessing gait variability may also be critical for independent walking in patients with hemiparesis following stroke. However, it remains unclear whether gait variability can discriminate between independent walking. This study aimed to evaluate the efficacy of gait variability indicators in discriminating independent walking in patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41330021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rescue PCI in the Pharmaco-invasive Era of STEMI: Insights from the STREAM-2 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Contemporary PI with half-dose tenecteplase in older patients requiring rescue intervention led to less ST resolution and worse 30-day outcomes compared to those with successful fibrinolysis receiving scheduled angiography. Notably, delays to deploying rescue PCI in CH patients were shortened over those previously achieved thereby resulting in similar outcomes to those randomized in the ambulance. Our results reinforce the benefits of functional hub and spoke models with rapid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refining the Substrate-Cofactor Disposition Model of Hyoscyamine 6β-Hydroxylase Catalysis Using Hyoscyamine Analogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyoscyamine 6β-hydroxylase (H6H) is a mononuclear nonheme iron and 2-oxoglutrate dependent oxidase responsible for the biosynthesis of the tropane alkaloid scopolamine. H6H is an ideal model system to study the nonheme iron enzymes as it has dual functions catalyzing both C6-hydroxylation of hyoscyamine and epoxidation of the resulting alcohol. Previous crystallographic and spectroscopic studies have led to a model where substrate disposition relative to the intermediary iron complexes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AquaCropPlotter: A Shiny app for visualizing and analyzing AquaCrop simulation results]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[AquaCrop, a crop growth model developed by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations (FAO), can be used as a planning tool to assist management decisions in both irrigated and rainfed agriculture. AquaCrop simulates the yield of crops in response to water, particularly in conditions where water is a key limiting factor. AquaCrop balances accuracy, simplicity and robustness. However, visualization and analysis of its outputs can be a bottleneck since data generated from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Pulmonary Neuroendocrine Tumor With a Novel In-Frame FOXO3::IRAG1 Fusion and Metastasis to Breast and Ovary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contextual Analysis and Implementation Strategies for an Age-Friendly Emergency Department Uptake: The FRED Study Protocol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Age-friendly EDs are essential for person-centered emergency care, enhancing safety and quality of care for older adults. This study will provide insights into adaptable, evidence-informed implementation strategies that support behavioral change among emergency clinicians to increase patient reach and sustainability of age-friendly interventions for complex ED settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A biofilm reactor packed with aspen wood and polyurethane sponge for biological manganese(II) oxidation and minor metal recovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biogenic manganese oxides (MnOx) are promising agents for the removal and recovery of minor metals from water. However, cultivating heterotrophic Mn(II)-oxidizing microorganisms in non-sterile bioreactors remains difficult, and few continuous-flow reactor designs have been evaluated for their ability to recover minor metals under such conditions. In this study, we operated a laboratory-scale biofilm reactor packed with aspen wood and a polyurethane sponge for 469 d to evaluate its feasibility...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to "TAPSE/PASP Ratio as a Prognostic Marker in HFmrEF: A Missed Opportunity?"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-related optical changes: stability of coma and increased spherical aberrations in the cornea and whole eye]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Total HOAs and SAs in the anterior cornea, total cornea, and whole eye were significantly positively correlated with age, whereas coma exhibited no age-related changes. These findings underscore the importance of considering age-related optical changes in clinical evaluations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Necessary and sufficient condition for hysteresis in the mathematical model of the cell type regulation of Bacillus subtilis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The key to a robust life system is to ensure that each cell population is maintained in an appropriate state. In this work, a mathematical model is used to investigate the control of the switching between the migrating and non-migrating states of the Bacillus subtilis cell population. In this case, the motile cells and matrix producers are the predominant cell types in the migrating cell population and non-migrating state, respectively, and can be suitably controlled according to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spinal anesthesia in a patient with hereditary dysfibrinogenemia who underwent emergency cesarean delivery: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Thromboelastography can aid the anesthesia team in evaluating the risks versus benefits of neuraxial anesthesia in patients with hereditary dysfibrinogenemia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlating Room-Temperature Phosphorescence with Structural Dynamics by Water Accommodation in a Flexible Hydrogen-Bonded Organic Framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic room-temperature phosphorescence (RTP) materials have garnered significant interest in various crucial applications. While RTP emissions typically exhibit a water-induced quenching propensity, the impact of genuine water accommodation into porous materials on RTP properties remains unclear and confusing due to the lack of structural evidence and ambiguous mechanism of water-regulated RTP properties. Herein, we demonstrate the manipulation of RTP properties through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ZEUS: Numerical methods to detect quasi-particles describing excitable media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many complex systems with societal relevance are excitable, including brain tissue, cardiac tissue, heat waves, and epidemic spread. In cardiac tissue, arrhythmias often arise when electrical conduction is blocked by incomplete recovery after a previous stimulation. We recently presented a topological theory for excitable media that also captures conduction blocks. Therein, points where a wave front or a wave back spatially connects to a conduction block were shown to be topologically preserved,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commentary on Aberrant Plasma Cells in the Absence of M-protein: Ancillary Testing beyond Protein Electrophoresis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41329020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetization reversal in TmCr1-xCoxO3 perovskite solid solutions studied by Monte Carlo simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this work, we studied the magnetization reversal (MR) phenomenon in the perovskite solid solution TmCr1-xCoxO3, where magnetic Cr3+ ions were substituted by non-magnetic low-spin (LS) Co3+ ions. Magnetic measurements and Monte Carlo (MC) simulations were performed following a field-cooling (FC) protocol. Samples of TmCr1-xCoxO3 with 0.1 ≤ x ≤ 0.8 were synthesized and structurally characterized. Samples with 0.1 ≤ x < 0.5 were synthesized at 1200 °C in the air atmosphere, while those with 0.5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extended verification of an automated MALDI-TOF mass spectrometry system for high throughput serum M-protein measurement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EXENT^(®)-GAM enables sensitive and reproducible quantification and isotyping of M-proteins below the detection limit of SPEP and sIFE. Its ability to resolve analytical challenges posed by SPEP and sIFE represents a significant advancement. Further clinical studies are needed to confirm its potential in residual disease detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability of capturing plantar foot geometry using a handheld 3D scanner for dose-response modeling of custom-made foot orthoses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results demonstrated that the digitization of linear anthropometric and geometric measurements of the human foot, obtained using a handheld 3D scanning system in a non-weight-bearing condition, exhibit good to excellent reliability. Additionally, the curvilinear metrics, related to the plantar surface curvature, showed high consistency, supporting its usage to quantify plantar geometry and provide insights into the role of geometric characteristics in dosage-response modeling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41328813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251203024041&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>