<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:20:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic effects of Poncirus fructus on colonic dysfunction and visceral pain in a zymosan-induced irritable bowel syndrome mouse model through interstitial cells of Cajal and ion channel modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PFE exerts multi-target effects by modulating ICC activity, suppressing inflammation, and regulating key ion channels involved in visceral pain. These findings suggest that PFE has therapeutic potential for the management of IBS symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel anodic nanostructured stainless steel-304L oxide as an emerging electrode material for high energy density asymmetric supercapacitors: experimental and DFT insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrode material plays a significant role in the performance of supercapacitors. Therefore, the development of a novel electrode material for high energy density, high power density, and stable supercapacitors is highly desirable. The emergence of the stainless steel 304L (SUS-304L) oxide nanostructure as an electrode material provides an opportunity to explore its supercapacitive behavior. In the present study, a simple and facile technique of anodization was employed to synthesize...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft Ionic Materials: Design and Applications in Functional Electrochemical Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[By integrating the rapid ionic transport of ionic liquids with the structural integrity of polymers, ionogels achieve high conductivity, mechanical flexibility, and environmental stability. These attributes position them as promising solid-state electrolytes for soft electronics. Recent molecular innovations have yielded ionogels with remarkable stretchability, toughness, and multifunctionality, broadening their scope of applications. This Perspective highlights molecular-level strategies, such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Translational value of understanding brain-spinal interactions in persistent pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kinetically-controlled intermediate-direct-pinning for homogeneous energy landscapes in quasi-two-dimensional perovskites for efficient and narrow blue emission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quasi-two-dimensional perovskite structures hold great potential as active layers in blue perovskite light-emitting diodes. However, they face challenges of limited emission efficiency and broadened spectra due to phase inhomogeneity. Here, we report an intermediate-direct-pinning method to develop a uniform-phase quasi-two-dimensional structure with a homogeneous energy landscape. By forming a strong cation-π interaction complex, we stabilize a metastable intermediate phase with retarded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoactivated conductive MOF thin film arrays on micro-LEDs for chemiresistive gas sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrically conductive metal-organic frameworks (cMOFs) are emerging as promising chemiresistors due to their diverse compositions, chemical properties, porosity, and room-temperature conductivity, enabling the design of energy-efficient devices. However, limited activation in this regime hinders sensitivity and reversibility. In this study, cMOF thin films are integrated onto a micro-LED (μLED) platform using a layer-by-layer method, enabling photoactivated gas sensing even at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Versatile Biosensing Tool: CRISPR-Cas12a System-Integrated Electrochemical Biosensor for Severe Fever with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome Virus Detection in Clinical and Environmental Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome virus (SFTSV) is a highly lethal zoonotic virus with a maximum mortality rate of 30%. Despite its risks and potential for human-to-human transmission, the standard diagnostic method has been absent for SFTSV detection. Therefore, this study introduces a versatile SFTSV biosensing technology using the electrochemical-clustered regularly interspaced short palindromic repeat (EC-CRISPR) system. The sensing membrane is functionalized with the 2WJ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of PD-L1 expression in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma among preoperative biopsy, surgical resection and metastatic lymph node]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our analysis highlights the heterogeneity of PD-L1 expression across different specimen types. Significant variability exists between the preoperative biopsy and surgical resection, and between surgical resection and metastatic lymph node in patients with HNSCC. These findings suggest that PD-L1 expression varies in response to tumor microenvironment across various tumor areas and time frames. Therefore, individualized PD-L1 assessment for each specimen type is crucial for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and control of a robotic assistant walking aid for fall risk reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Falls are a major risk factor among the elderly, often resulting in injuries that compromise independence and quality of life. Conventional walking aids lack active stabilization capabilities and are therefore limited in effectively preventing balance-related accidents. This paper presents the design and control of a smart robotic assistant aimed at reducing fall risk in elderly users by providing real-time balance support. The proposed system uses a wearable inertial measurement unit to detect...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epithelial-derived cytokines in the pathogenesis of severe asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Airway epithelial cells function as the first physical barrier against pathogens and are key regulators of immune responses by producing a wide array of cytokines involved in both innate and adaptive immunity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opportunities and challenges in the application of spatiotemporal transcriptomics in plant research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal heterogeneity is recognized as a key driver of functional diversity in tissues. Spatial transcriptomics, which integrates high-throughput transcriptomics with high-resolution tissue imaging, enables the precise mapping of gene expression patterns at the tissue section level. This technology overcomes the limitations of traditional transcriptomics by providing spatial context and applying unbiased bioinformatics approaches. With the rapid advancement of sequencing technologies,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of total urethral thickness using ultrasonography in cats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Urethral wall thickness is a potential indicator of pathological changes in the feline lower urinary tract. However, reference values for total urethral thickness in cats have not been established. This study aimed to develop ultrasonographic reference ranges for total urethral thickness in clinically normal cats and to evaluate the effects of breed, sex, neutering status, body weight, and bladder volume. We further compared urethral thickness between healthy cats and those...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the Prognostic Value of a Pan-Cancer Circulating Tumor DNA Next-Generation Sequencing Panel in Advanced Cancer Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Longitudinal monitoring of ctDNA using a pan-cancer NGS panel provides meaningful prognostic information in patients with advanced cancers. Post-treatment ctDNA dynamics may better reflect disease progression than baseline ctDNA status alone, highlighting the need for further validation in larger cohorts, particularly in gastric, lung, head and neck, and esophageal cancers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparative study of online and face-to-face gatekeeper training using the suicide CARE program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Online gatekeeper training is a feasible and effective alternative to face-to-face instruction, particularly in settings with limited resources or during emergencies. While each format offers distinct advantages, hybrid models may yield the most comprehensive benefits. These findings support the inclusion of scalable online training in national suicide prevention strategies. Suicide prevention, gatekeeper training, Suicide CARE, online education, face-to-face education, and community...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of symptoms of suspected adenomyosis uteri using herbal medicine modified Bojungikgi-tang: a case report with ultrasound monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case suggests that herbal medicine may be a safe and effective option for managing adenomyosis, supporting further research into integrative treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limited versus extended arch replacement during acute type A aortic dissection repair for nonsyndromic patients with dissected arch vessels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In nonsyndromic patients with AVD undergoing ATAAD repair, EA replacement was associated with an increased risk of stroke, whereas hemiarch replacement did not lead to increased aorta reinterventions, suggesting that hemiarch replacement is an acceptable option for repairing ATAAD in these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is salsolinol a friend or foe? Revisiting its roles in neurotoxicity and cellular protection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salsolinol (1-methyl-6,7-dihydroxy-1,2,3,4-tetrahydroisoquinoline, SAL) is a dopamine-derived tetrahydroisoquinoline, first identified in the urine of a Parkinson's disease patient treated with L-DOPA. SAL is generated endogenously via both enzymatic and non-enzymatic Pictet-Spengler condensation of dopamine with acetaldehyde. It is also found in dietary sources such as bananas, mushrooms, and cocoa, as well as in certain microbes. SAL has been detected in cerebrospinal fluid and various brain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amiodarone as a model compound for assessment of mitochondrial toxicity in hepatocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondria are essential for cellular energy production and play a critical role in maintaining overall cellular homeostasis. Mitochondrial dysfunction primarily affects energy-demanding tissues such as heart and skeletal muscle, as well as tissues (e.g., the liver) that are exposed to xenobiotics. In fact, mitochondrial toxicity is recognized as a major contributor to drug-induced liver injury (DILI). However, reliable methods for assessment of mitochondrial toxicity in vitro or in vivo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case study on the evaluation of skin sensitization for 23 selected fragrance ingredients using a defined approach based on OECD Guideline 497]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Twenty-three single-ingredient substances, selected from materials labeled as allergens in cosmetic fragrances, were assessed for skin sensitization potential using a defined approach (DA) based on the OECD Guideline 497 Integrated Testing Strategy version 2 (ITSv2). According to the ITSv2, skin hypersensitivity data for these selected substances were integrated. In chemico data (from the Direct Peptide Reactivity Assay, DPRA) and in vitro data (from the human Cell Line Activation Test, h-CLAT)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chitooligosaccharides as a potential immune modulator for reducing particulate matter 10-induced inflammation in pulmonary damage models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of chitooligosaccharides (COS) on proinflammatory cytokines and nuclear factor-κB (NF-κB) activation in particulate matter 10 (PM10)-induced mice. Results demonstrated that COS treatment significantly reduced proinflammatory cytokines, including interleukin (IL)-6 and IL-1β, particularly in the COS_20 group (20 mg/kg body weight of COS). Lower COS doses correlated with a dose-dependent decrease in proinflammatory cytokine levels and inflammatory cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DOT1L as a Therapeutic Target: Insights into Epigenetic Regulation and Cancer Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Disruptor of Telomeric Silencing 1-Like (DOT1L) has emerged as a critical epigenetic regulator in cancer, primarily because of its role as the sole histone methyltransferase responsible for histone H3 at lysine 79 methylation. This modification affects transcriptional activation, DNA repair, and cell cycle progression. Its dysregulation is associated with both hematological and solid tumors. In Mixed-lineage leukemia (MLL)-rearranged leukemia, DOT1L maintains aberrant gene expression patterns at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Mediating Role of Speak-up Climate in the Relationship Between Nurse Managers' Inclusive Leadership, Patient Safety, and Nurse Job Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Strengthening inclusive leadership and cultivating a supportive speak-up climate may enhance patient safety and contribute to a more satisfied nursing workforce.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Photovoltaic and Ferroelectric Properties of Na<sub>0.5</sub>Bi<sub>0.5</sub>TiO<sub>3</sub>Thin Films via Na/Bi Excess and La Doping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transition metal incorporation into semiconductors not only induces ferroelectric behavior but also supplies localized spins. The resulting spin interactions can give rise to ferromagnetism, offering a versatile route to multiferroic properties. Ferroelectric thin films exhibit intrinsic photovoltaic behavior due to their internal electric fields, which arise from spontaneous polarization and result in conduction and valence band tilting similar to the built-in fields in p-n junctions. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Charge Generation and Collection Enabled by Incorporation of Crystalline Polymer for Ultrafast-Response Dual-Band Perovskite/Organic Photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual-band photodetectors (PDs) capable of selectively responding to both visible and near-infrared (NIR) light are essential for applications in optical communication, medical diagnostics, and artificial vision systems. In this work, we report a high-performance visible/NIR dual-band PD based on a vertically stacked perovskite/organic hybrid structure. To overcome the challenges of high operating voltage and slow response, often stemming from high exciton binding energy and limited charge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioprinted Collagen Cell Constructs with Gradient BMP-2-Loaded Microbeads for Rotator Cuff Tear Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In rotator cuff tears (RCT), surgical intervention is often required to restore damaged tissues because of their limited self-healing capacity. However, surgical treatments often fail to completely restore RCT, particularly in forming their interface regions. Therefore, the development of effective tissue-engineering-based treatments is increasingly necessary to encourage the formation of a bone-to-tendon interface (BTI). This study proposes a cell construct bioprinted using a stem cell-loaded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influencing Factors of Coping Strategies in Mothers of High-Risk Newborns: Perceived Stress and Nursing Support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nurses can support coping by providing clear information about the newborn's condition. Additionally, providing opportunities for mothers to actively participate in newborn care may serve as an effective strategy to enhance adaptive coping strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Imaging Characteristics of Infective Endocarditis-Associated Versus Atrial Fibrillation-Associated Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IE-stroke lesions were more numerous, smaller, and dispersed across multiple vascular territories with higher recurrence rates compared with atrial fibrillation stroke. Despite lesion size difference, parenchymal hematoma rates were similar. These characteristics may aid in distinguishing IE-stroke in patients with embolic stroke and fever.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved efficiency of protein aggregate removal using ubiquitin with a signal peptide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipocalin-2 (LCN2) is a protein secreted by activated astrocytes, and its signal peptide (SP) is essential for secretion and recruitment to the autophagic pathway. SP is a short sequence present at the N-terminus of secreted proteins, such as LCN2, which facilitates transport to the endoplasmic reticulum (ER). Although SP is cleaved during the initial stages of translation in the ER, it influences the subsequent pathways of mature proteins produced in the ER lumen. ER-generated proteins are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pluripotent Stem Cell-Derived Chimeric Antigen Receptor-Natural Killer Cells Targeting Epidermal Growth Factor Receptor 2 for Cancer Immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric antigen receptor-natural killer (CAR-NK) cells are emerging as a promising platform for allogeneic, cell-based immunotherapy. Among available sources, NK cells derived from pluripotent stem cells (PSCs) provide a renewable and scalable option that overcomes the limitations of primary NK cells. Human epidermal growth factor receptor 2 (HER2), a membrane protein frequently overexpressed in many solid tumors, is an attractive target for cancer immunotherapy. In this study, we designed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal changes in mammographic density and reproductive hormones during the menopausal transition in middle-aged Korean women: effect modification by obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In Korean women undergoing MT, transient increases in MD paralleled E2 elevations, particularly in non-obese women. These findings align with the peak breast cancer incidence in Korean women in their 40s, preceding menopause, and the importance of considering hormonal and MD dynamics, as well as BMI, in breast cancer risk assessment and screening strategies for Asian women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the complexity of cutaneous leishmaniasis patient journey in endemic rural Sri Lanka: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found that, despite certain positive aspects, the CL patient journey is complex, with substantial and pervasive delays and barriers along with psychosocial impacts that persist beyond clinical cure. Our study findings can inform evidence-based, context-specific interventions to reduce the public health burden of CL in resource-limited settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning-based Model for Breast Implant Classification in Ultrasonography: A Multi-Institutional Model Development and Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: By automating the identification process, this tool alleviates the reliance on specialized training among plastic surgeons regarding breast ultrasound, streamlining patient care. Despite limitations, the model shows promise for improving clinical workflows and patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overlap Weights for Binary Outcomes: A Performance Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest superior performance of OW in terms of covariate balance and estimation efficiency in settings with extreme PS and a binary outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Risk for Neuropsychiatric Events in Leukotriene Receptor Antagonist vs. Inhaled Corticosteroid in Children With Asthma: A Nationwide Observational Study With a Complementary Analysis Using Natural Language Processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LTRA use was not found to be associated with a significantly increased risk of NPEs in children with asthma. These findings offer valuable insights to support clinical decision-making in pediatric asthma treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How I do it: robotic living donor right hepatectomy with a focus on parenchymal transection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Robotic articulation facilitates secure closure even in anatomically challenging cases. These standardized techniques enable reproducible outcomes and support their safe adoption by centers new to RDRH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjunctive smart ring monitoring during digital cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia (dCBT-I) has emerged as a treatment for chronic insomnia. Smart rings provide objective, wearable-derived sleep data that may complement subjective sleep diaries, but their role in monitoring treatment response remains unclear. This study evaluated the clinical effectiveness of dCBT-I with smart rings and compared subjective and wearable-derived sleep measures. In this single-arm study, individuals with insomnia completed a dCBT-I program,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stage-specific TRIM10 expression regulates erythroid maturation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mammalian erythroid cells undergo extensive organelle and protein remodeling during erythropoiesis. The transcriptome and proteome of ubiquitin E3 ligases change dynamically during erythroid differentiation, yet mechanisms beyond E3 activity remain unclear. Here, we identify that tripartite motif-containing protein 10α (TRIM10α), an erythroid- and stage-specific E3 ligase, as crucial for stepwise erythroid maturation. TRIM10α self-association to localize on erythroblast surfaces, binding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of molecular weight of hyaluronic acid on corneal cell viability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyaluronic acid (HA) is widely utilized in ophthalmology for its viscoelastic and wound-healing properties; however, its effects vary according to molecular weight (MW). This study evaluates the toxicity induced by HA across corneal epithelial cells, keratocytes, and endothelial cells to ensure its safe clinical application. Human corneal epithelial cells, keratocytes, and endothelial cells were cultured under standardized conditions. Viability was assessed using the Cell Counting Kit-8 (CCK-8)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of normalized T1 signal intensity obtained using an automated segmentation model in lower leg MRI as a potential imaging biomarker in Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease type 1 A]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the potential utility of imaging parameters derived by normalizing muscle signal intensity on T1-weighted lower leg MRIs in Charcot-Marie-Tooth disease type 1 A (CMT1A) patients, using a deep learning-based automated muscle segmentation model. We retrospectively analyzed lower leg MRI data of 107 CMT1A patients. An automated deep learning-based muscle segmentation model was employed to extract muscle signal intensities from four compartments (anterior, lateral, deep posterior, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput evaluation of in vitro CRISPR activities enables optimized large-scale multiplex enrichment of rare variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous high-throughput evaluations of CRISPR activities for a large number of target and guide RNA sequences were based on measuring insertion-deletion frequencies rather than cleavage efficiencies. Here we develop two high-throughput in vitro methods, Cut-seq1 and Cut-seq2, to evaluate Cas9 cleavage efficiency for tens of thousands, or even hundreds of thousands, of guide RNA-target pairs. These methods reveal low correlations between in vitro cleavage efficiencies and insertion-deletion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The influence of diabetic retinopathy on the risk of dementia: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the impact of diabetic retinopathy (DMR) on dementia using clinical data from the Korean National Health Insurance Service. A nationwide, population-based retrospective cohort of 784,205 individuals over the age of 45 was analyzed. DMR diagnoses were confirmed using diagnostic and procedure codes. Covariate data, such as age, sex, income level, visual acuity, systemic and ophthalmic comorbidities, and behavioral factors, were collected from health screenings and claims data....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Dataset of Water Stable Isotopes in Iran's Main Aquifers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the number of global water stable isotope databases (δ^(18)O and δ²H) is growing, accessible groundwater stable isotope data on developing countries (e.g., Iran), are conspicuously lacking. To fill this gap, we conducted a sampling campaign during October 2023 to measure δ^(18)O and δ²H in 202 wells, springs, and qanats across 10 main aquifers in Iran. We also calculated the second-order water isotopic variables, namely deuterium-excess (D-excess) and line-conditioned excess...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of factors associated with foreign substance contamination in restaurant food]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study identified factors associated with foreign substance contamination in food prepared at restaurants in a district of Seoul. Data from 4,747 registered general restaurants were analyzed using the Hygiene Administration System and the Integrated Food Safety Information System. The dependent variable was the report of foreign substance contamination, and independent variables included owner characteristics (e.g., age group) and restaurant characteristics (e.g., cuisine type). Logistic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168203/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved survival in multiple myeloma following prior detection of precursor conditions: a nationwide real-world study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Bleeding-Risk Criteria as a Modifier of Treatment Effect During Antithrombotic Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customized Fenestrated Thoracic Endovascular Aneurysm Repair in an Elderly Patient With Complex Visceral Anatomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term Outcomes of Standardized Strategy in Arterial Switch Operation: An 18-Year Review in a Single Center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our surgical outcomes of ASO following the standardized strategy were favorable, despite concerns regarding long-term adverse events. Complex TGA morphological subtypes demonstrated higher neo-ARD and composite of reoperation and re-intervention rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards Green Cardiovascular Care: Carbon Footprint Analysis in the Management of Coronary Artery Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Greenhouse gas emissions drive climate change, which in turn threatens human health through various pathways, including cardiovascular disease, respiratory illness, and infectious disease. Despite the healthcare sector accounting for 4.4% of global carbon emissions, carbon footprint analysis within the field remains limited. This perspective addresses the importance of carbon footprint assessment in healthcare, particularly in cardiovascular medicine, and illustrates the use of randomized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Is Better for Blood-Seeking Ischemic Myocardium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic Dissection of Aortic Stenosis: Distinct VIC Signatures and the Role of Aging in Valve Remodeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collagen Signaling via DDR1 Exacerbates Barriers to Macromolecular Drug Delivery in a 3D Model of Pancreatic Cancer Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fibrosis is a significant barrier to drug delivery in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC) and contributes to its dismal prognosis. Pancreatic stellate cells (PSCs) drive fibrosis by excessively secreting extracellular matrix proteins such as collagen I. Collagen I is thought to physically obstruct the delivery of macromolecules, such as albumin, antibodies, and nanomedicines. Apart from its structural role, collagen signals through dedicated cell surface receptors, such as the discoidin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pectin Extracted by a Recyclable Molecular Mixture: A Promising Material for Porous Membranes in Quasi-Solid-State Na-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explored a solvent-based extraction of pectin from apple pomace and evaluated the extracted pectin as a precursor for porous quasi-solid-state Na-ion battery membranes, alongside testing hard carbon derived from commercial pectin as an electrode material. A screening of 10 distinct ionic liquids (ILs) and 6 different antisolvents revealed that N,N-dimethylbutylammonium acetate ([DMBA]-[OAc]), combined with ethanol, was highly effective in pectin extraction, while the same IL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of HIV-1 viral protein R-derived-peptides as new E3 ligase-binding components of BRD4 degraders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteolysis targeting chimeras (PROTACs) have become a new modality for drug development of particular importance for cancer chemotherapy. PROTACs are composed of a ligand that binds to the protein of interest (POI) tethered by a linker to a ubiquitin E3 ligase-binding motif. These molecules can degrade the POI by ubiquitination and subsequent digestion using the ubiquitin-proteasome system (UPS). Although more than six hundred E3 ligases are encoded in human genome, only a small number are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marked improvement in severe pulmonary arterial hypertension following airway infection in a patient with a heterozygous BMP9 nonsense mutation: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Pulmonary arterial hypertension (PAH) is a severe and life-threatening disease. Genetic factors, inflammation and immune system play important roles in their pathogenesis. However, their precise roles are still not fully understood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Gold Marker Orientation in the Three-Cusp Coplanar View After Evolut FX Transcatheter Aortic Valve Implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Evaluating the orientation of the gold markers in a 3-CV after Evolut FX implantation is useful for assessing CMA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fine structure investigation and laser cooling study of the LaH molecule]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A theoretical feasibility study of the spin-orbit laser cooling of the molecule LaH has been performed based on a complete active space self-consistent field (CASSCF)/MRCI ab initio calculation with Davidson correction in the Λ ^((±)) and Ω ^((±)) representations. The adiabatic potential energy curves and spectroscopic constants have been investigated for the considered electronic states. The small value of the equilibrium positions difference ΔR (e) between the ground and the electronic states...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bio-dye-sensitized TiO<sub>2</sub> nanophotocatalysts for visible-light-driven sustainable wastewater treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The limited visible-light activity of titanium dioxide (TiO(2)) restricts its application in solar-driven photocatalysis for wastewater treatment. In this study, TiO(2) nanoparticles were sensitized with natural plant-derived dyes-chlorophyll from Eichhornia crassipes (water hyacinth) and anthocyanin from Nymphaea rubra (red water lily)-to extend their optical response into the visible spectrum. Dye extraction was followed by TiO(2) sensitization, and the resulting nanocomposites were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitor-related myocarditis during DUO-E regimen for endometrial cancer: The first case report in gynecologic oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first reported case of ICI-M during DUO-E therapy for endometrial cancer. It underscores the importance of early clinical suspicion, rapid multidisciplinary collaboration, and timely intervention in managing ICI-M, particularly in high-risk patients. Continuous vigilance is warranted throughout the course of ICI therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Caring task-involving climate leads to greater improvements in free-throw shooting biomechanics and motivational responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: There is a need for experimental and cross-disciplinary research in sport psychology, particularly studies that incorporate objective performance assessments into motivational climate research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of reliable identification algorithms for acute heart failure or acute exacerbation of chronic heart failure using clinical data from a medical information database network]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Validated algorithms for identifying acute heart failure and acute exacerbation of chronic heart failure were successfully established. Using these algorithms should facilitate more appropriate pharmacoepidemiological studies related to acute heart failure and contribute to better drug safety assessments based on real-world data in Japan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cycloalkane Incorporation Into the 2',4'-Bridge of Locked Nucleic Acid: Enhancing Nuclease Stability, Reducing Phosphorothioate Modifications, and Lowering Hepatotoxicity in Antisense Oligonucleotides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2'-O,4'-C-Methylene-bridged nucleic acid (2',4'-BNA), also known as locked nucleic acid (LNA), is widely used to modify antisense oligonucleotides (ASOs) because it significantly enhances their ability to form duplexes with target RNAs, thereby boosting ASO activity. However, 2',4'-BNA/LNA exhibits only moderate nuclease stability, necessitating additional modifications, such as phosphorothioate (PS) linkages. Our previous studies demonstrated that oligonucleotides modified with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultralong-Range Periodic Alignment and Structural Coloration of Titanate and Titanoniobate Nanosheets in Aqueous Dispersions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural coloration has been reported for many types of two-dimensional (2D) materials, including metal oxide nanosheets. In particular, metal oxide nanosheets feature a wealth of composition and structure, but their impact on structural color has not been explored. In the current study, we report the structural coloration observed for aqueous suspensions of three types of transition metal oxide nanosheets (Ti(1.73)O(4) ^(1.08-), TiNbO(5) ^(-), and Ti(2)NbO(7) ^(-)) obtained via the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mast cells are essential in the development of exposure-associated exercise-induced bronchoconstriction in a mouse model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Mast cells are crucial in the development of bronchial hyperreactivity and macrophage activation. Additionally, they have a complex interplay with neutrophilic inflammation. These findings highlight the potential of mast cell modulation as therapeutic strategy in exposure-associated EIB.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transposition of the great arteries with ventricular septal defect and pulmonary stenosis: Hemodynamic simulation for palliative strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings support a palliative treatment strategy in which percutaneous ASD enlargement is prioritized, guided by echocardiographic ASD flow patterns. If adequate ASD enlargement cannot be achieved, SPS placement should be performed, with concomitant consideration of PAB.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A post-surgical case of rib osteomyelitis and pleural abscess caused by <em>mycobacterium abscessus</em> after 6 years of lung cancer surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 69-year-old man followed post lung cancer surgery for 6 years presented with back pain. His imaging revealed a pleural abscess and rib osteomyelitis along with the surgical site. Therefore, bone biopsy and culture were performed and the organism was diagnosed as Mycobacterium abscessus by PCR method. As such, the combination antibiotics therapy initiated with imipenem, amikacin, and clarithromycin, and then continued with faropenem, minocycline, clarithromycin, and moxifloxacin for 20 months,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wolfram syndrome: A perspective on gene editing as a therapeutic strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining and Managing End-of-Life Respiratory Changes in Adult Home Hospice Patients: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: End-of-life respiratory changes-agonal breathing, Cheyne-Stokes breathing, and death rattle/noisy breathing-are common in home hospice settings, impacting patient comfort, caregiver distress, and quality of care. Purpose: To identify and critically evaluate literature on definitions, characteristics, and management for end-of-life respiratory changes in home hospice patients. Data Sources: English-language articles in Ovid Medline, Scopus, CINAHL, APA PsycINFO, and Web of Science...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antiproliferative Activity and Target Analysis of 18β-Glycyrrhetinic Acid Derivatives Modified With α, β-Unsaturated Carbonyl Groups]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer is one of the most complex diseases. Its multidrug resistance and poor prognosis make the development of antitumor drugs still a difficult task. 18β-glycyrrhetinic acid (18β-GA) has shown great potential for tumor prevention and treatment. However, inherent defects, such as low bioavailability, limit its use. Herein, based on a molecular hybridization strategy, two series of α, β-unsaturated carbonyl modified 18β-GA derivatives were synthesized using 18β-GA as the parent nucleus. Among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lamellar-Cleavage-Induced Triboluminescence in Discrete Chiral Complexes with Lanthanides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triboluminescence (TL), which is the light emission induced by mechanical stimuli, has attracted significant interest owing to its potential for energy conversion applications. Here, the TL mechanisms of chiral lanthanide complexes (LnL^(val), Ln = Eu, Tb, Sm, Dy, and Gd) were elucidated by focusing on the role of lamellar cleavage of the crystal structure. The modified drop tower system (DTS) quantifies mechanical stimuli used to observe the TL spectra. Chiral EuL^(val) and TbL^(val) exhibit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reference intervals for serum creatinine for healthy adults in central Africa: a post-hoc analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of the uptake of the H<sup>+</sup>/OC antiporter substrate oxycodone across and into brain endothelial and parenchymal cells with in vitro-in vivo extrapolation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of normative spleen volume in a Japanese cohort using automated CT segmentation: diagnostic implications for liver fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biological/targeted synthetic disease-modifying antirheumatic drugs improve not only muscle mass but also phase angle in patients with rheumatoid arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Treatment with b/tsDMARD improved muscle mass and phase angle by blocking inflammatory cytokines and JAK-STAT signaling. Key Points • This study is the first to report that b/tsDMARD treatment is effective not only for increasing muscle mass but also for improving phase angle. • These effects appear to be primarily direct, rather than mediated through disease activity improvement or glucocorticoid reduction. • There were no significant differences in muscle mass gain or phase angle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of two orthologs of bacterial intramembrane metalloprotease RseP by native mass spectrometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intramembrane metalloproteases are conserved in all three domains of life and regulate cellular signal transduction by cleaving membrane-anchored precursors or regulators of transcription factors. Bacterial intramembrane metalloproteases are promising targets for antimicrobial drugs as they are implicated in pathogenicity and drug resistance. Understanding the properties of intramembrane metalloproteases, particularly their interactions with zinc and inhibitors, is important for drug...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for male sexual dysfunction after minimally invasive surgery for rectal cancer: a multicenter prospective subanalysis of the LANDMARC study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Advanced age and Lap surgery were associated with an increased risk of postoperative SD after MIS for rectal cancer. Therefore, Ro surgery may offer protective advantages. Although the predictive accuracy of the nomogram was limited, it may aid preoperative counseling and raise awareness of postoperative sexual outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling and stratifying cell cycle-dependent drug efficacy using a single-cell PLOM-CON approach with correlation anomaly and presage protein signals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In drug discovery, assessing and stratifying drug efficacy on cells is vital. To demonstrate the efficacy of drugs on cells in different cell cycle phases, it is essential not only to analyze multidimensional protein data on the single-cell level but also to establish a methodology for extracting key molecules from subtle differences in cellular states in response to the drug. Here we introduce a single cell-PLOM-CON analysis method by combining multiplex immunofluorescence and image-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Dominant Bacterial Species on Sand Filters Used for Treating Manganese-Containing Mine Water Under Alkaline Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Even after mine closure, continuous chemical treatment of mine water and proper sludge management remain necessary. Previously, a pilot-scale rapid sand filter (RSF) system was applied to treat manganese-containing circumneutral mine water (21 mg/L Mn²⁺, pH 7.0) at a mine site, achieving up to 40% Mn removal. In this study, adjusting the inlet water pH to 8.5 and 9.0 increased Mn removal rates to 89.5% and 95.0%, respectively. Although microbial contribution to Mn²⁺ oxidation under alkaline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precipitation legacy effects on soil microbiota facilitate adaptive drought responses in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drought alters the soil microbiota by selecting for functional traits that preserve fitness in dry conditions. Legacy effects or ecological memory refers to how past stress exposure influences microbiota responses to future environmental challenges. How precipitation legacy effects impact soil microorganisms and plants is unclear, especially in the context of subsequent drought. Here we characterized the metagenomes of six prairie soils spanning a precipitation gradient in Kansas, United States....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: In situ FRET measurement of cellular tension using conventional confocal laser microscopy in newly established reporter mice expressing actinin tension sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive lipid analysis of human meibum and tears]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abnormalities in the tear film lipid layer, which plays a critical role in preventing water evaporation and protecting the corneal surface, lead to dry eye disease. The lipids in this layer include both meibum lipids (from the meibomian glands) and phospholipids of other origins. Meibum lipids include cholesteryl esters, wax monoesters, wax diesters (WdiEs), (O-acyl)-ω-hydroxy fatty acids (OAHFAs), and cholesteryl OAHFAs. Nonetheless, the exact composition of these lipid classes remains largely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gorilla knuckle-walking mechanics suggest independent evolution in African great apes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gorillas and chimpanzees both use knuckle-walking (KW). Whether this behavior is a homologous trait inherited from their last common ancestor or the result of convergent evolution remains debated. This study investigated the biomechanics of gorilla KW by measuring ground reaction forces (GRFs) and comparing them with previously reported chimpanzee data. GRFs were recorded using two in-series force plates embedded in a horizontal beam in the outdoor enclosure of Kyoto City Zoo. Three adult...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brilliant structural colors originating from reflection by nanogaps of nacreous layers in fossilized ammonite shells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vivid-colored ammonite fossils that are mined in Alberta, Canada, are known as gemstones called "Ammolite." The specific colors having narrow reflectance spectra are ascribed to an interference phenomenon on the preserved nacre of fossils. However, the essence of the vivid tones that are different from the structural coloration of other kinds of shells has not been revealed. In this work, we clarified that specific reflection by interlaminar nanogaps (~ 4 nm) of aragonite plates with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168256/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a type 2 diabetes mellitus prediction tool using a large Japanese regional insurance claims database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the increasing global prevalence of diabetes, predictive models are crucial for early interventions, including elderly participants who are often underrepresented in existing models. Existing models, however, are often derived from specific subpopulations or from individuals with prevalent diabetes, which limits their generalizability to the broader population. This study aimed to develop and validate a predictive model for type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM) onset using a large Japanese cohort...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multi-label visualisation approach for malware behaviour analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Modern malware evolves continuously, posing persistent challenges to cybersecurity. Conventional classification approaches typically group malware by its primary objective, emphasising dominant behaviours while overlooking the complex and overlapping strategies common in real-world attacks. Here we present DECODE (DEep Classification Of Dynamic Exploits), a proportional multi-label, context-aware framework that combines object detection, explainable artificial intelligence (XAI), and agent-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031152005&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Cavitated-Ridged Reentrant Coating System for Fabrication of Robust, Fluorine-free Superomniphobic Surfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low surface energy finishing agents, particularly perfluoroalkyl compounds containing long or short fully fluorinated carbon chains, have been widely used for liquid-repellent modification of fabrics. However, fluorinated chemicals are harmful to environment and human health. It remains a formidable challenge to develop fluorine-free super-liquid-repellent coatings. Herein, a fluorine-free superomniphobic coating is provided with rational cavitated-ridged reentrant surface design that resembles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Performance Phthalonitrile Resins Partially Derived from a Furan Bio-Based Chemical Platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phthalonitrile resins are renowned for their outstanding heat resistance, withstanding temperatures exceeding 350 °C. This makes them highly sought after in industries such as aerospace, automotive, electronics, and renewable energy. To improve the sustainability of these materials, bio-derived phenols have been employed for the synthesis of the monomer in this research field. Thermosets derived from these partially bio-based monomers have demonstrated performance on par with their fossil-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[State Proposed Strategies to Expand Access to Medications for Opioid Use Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: States proposed a variety of strategies to expand access to and use of MOUD. Future research could investigate how these approaches, implemented individually or in combination, are associated with outcome change and impact.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age Friendly Health Systems: Pivoting from Breadth to Depth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Age-Friendly Health Systems movement has demonstrated remarkable reach, with thousands of health systems now recognized as Age-Friendly. We have served as co-Editors of this Special Issue, which comes at a pivotal time in the Age-Friendly Health System movement. Published in this Special Issue are articles that meaningfully move the field forward by: (1) describing implementation and effects of Age-Friendly adoption across diverse settings of care; (2) contending with the challenge of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Greater Physician Supply Associated with Lower Mortality in Rural Counties: A 23-Year County-Level Longitudinal Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rural U.S. residents face higher mortality rates and reduced access to primary care physicians. Prior studies report mixed findings on physician supply and health outcomes, and few have examined whether increasing supply reduces rural-urban mortality disparities. The objective was to quantify the marginal benefits of additional primary care physician supply in rural and urban areas, independent of other healthcare and socioeconomic factors. We conducted a 23-year county-level longitudinal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Common characteristics and regulatory mechanisms of airway mucus hypersecretion in lung disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In a healthy human, the airway mucus forms a thin, protective liquid layer covering the surface of the respiratory tract. It comprises a complex blend of mucin, multiple antibacterial proteins, metabolic substances, water, and electrolytes. This mucus plays a pivotal role in the lungs' innate immune system by maintaining airway hydration and capturing airborne particles and pathogens. However, heightened mucus secretion in the airway can compromise ciliary clearance, obstruct the respiratory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting WEE1: a rising therapeutic strategy for hematologic malignancies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hematologic malignancies, including leukemia, lymphoma, and multiple myeloma, are hazardous diseases characterized by the uncontrolled proliferation of cancer cells. Dysregulated cell cycle resulting from genetic and epigenetic abnormalities constitutes one of the central events. Importantly, cyclin-dependent kinases (CDKs), complexed with their functional partner cyclins, play dominating roles in cell cycle control. Yet, efforts in translating CDK inhibitors into clinical benefits have...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steroid sulfatase inhibitor DU-14 prevents amyloid β-protein-induced depressive-like behavior and theta rhythm suppression in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The hippocampus, a major component of the limbic system, is the most important region related to emotion regulation and memory processing. Cognitive impairment and depressive symptoms observed in Alzheimer's disease (AD) patients may be attributed to hippocampal damage caused by amyloid β-protein (Aβ). Our previous studies have demonstrated that a steroid sulfatase inhibitor DU-14 can enhance hippocampal synaptic plasticity and spatial memory abilities in a chronic AD murine model by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conserved translational control in cardiac hypertrophy revealed by ribosome profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A primary hallmark of pathological cardiac hypertrophy is excess protein synthesis due to enhanced translational activity. However, regulatory mechanisms at the translational level under cardiac stress remain poorly understood. Here we examined the translational regulations in a mouse cardiac hypertrophy model induced by transaortic constriction (TAC) and explored the conservative networks versus the translatome pattern in human dilated cardiomyopathy (DCM). The results showed that the heart...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Triacetic Acid Lactone Production from Sugarcane by Fermentation and Crystallization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triacetic acid lactone (TAL) has the potential to serve as a bioderived platform chemical for commercial products including sorbic acid and recyclable polydiketoenamine plastics. In this study, we leveraged BioSTEAM to design, simulate, and evaluate (via techno-economic analysis, TEA, and life cycle assessment, LCA) TAL production from sugarcane. We experimentally characterized TAL solubility, calibrated solubility models, and designed a process to separate TAL from fermentation broths by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence, awareness, and treatment of chronic kidney disease among adults in Yunnan Province, China: findings from the 2023 chronic disease and risk factors surveillance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The estimated CKD prevalence among adults in Yunnan Province in 2023 exceeded the national average (8.2%). CKD awareness and treatment rates were critically low. Targeted early screening programs or community-based interventions should be prioritized as urgent public health initiatives to improve disease recognition and treatment adherence for CKD prevention and management in China's less developed regions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Videos on YouTube, Bilibili, TikTok as sources of medical information on Hashimoto's thyroiditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Social media platforms provide partial support for the dissemination of health information about HT, but the overall video quality remains suboptimal. We recommend that professional creators pursue platform certification to enhance the dissemination of high-quality HT-related videos.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global burden of early-onset pancreatic cancer attributable to metabolic risks from 1990 to 2021, and projections to 2030]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study, based on the Global Burden of Disease (GBD) 2021 data, systematically analyzed the changes in the disease burden of early-onset pancreatic cancer (EOPC) attributable to high fasting plasma glucose (HFPG) and high body mass index (HBMI) among the global population aged 15-49 years from 1990 to 2021 and predicted the mortality trends up to 2030. The results show that metabolic risk factors have a significant impact on EOPC: In 2021, the global deaths from EOPC attributable to HFPG...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between periodontal disease and Alzheimer's disease: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PD may be a modifiable risk factor for AD, and periodontal interventions could contribute to AD prevention and management. Further clinical studies are needed to confirm the therapeutic potential of targeting oral microbiota in AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacterial and host interactions in <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em>-induced septic arthritis-understanding pathogenesis and exploring therapeutic strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Septic arthritis is a severe and rapidly destructive joint infection, primarily caused by Staphylococcus aureus. The interplay between bacterial virulence factors and host immune responses determines disease progression and clinical outcomes. This review discusses the key bacterial factors that contribute to septic arthritis, including S. aureus cell wall components, surface proteins, and secreted toxins. In parallel, host-related factors, such as aging, immune responses, and genetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Dietary high protein-induced diarrhea and intestinal inflammation by activation of NF-κB signaling in piglets" [Animal Nutrition 7 (2021) 1070-1077]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1016/j.aninu.2021.05.002.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glutaredoxin2 reduces age-associated B cell differentiation through maintaining redox homeostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Grx2 acts as a redox checkpoint that limits ABC-driven autoimmunity by modulating ROS. The Grx2-ROS axis represents a potential therapeutic target for SLE and related chronic inflammatory diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research progress on phytochemistry and pharmacology of <em>Staphylea arguta</em> (Lindl.) Byng &amp; Christenh. and prediction of quality markers: a review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This comprehensive review not only consolidates the existing knowledge on Staphylea arguta but also proposes a foundation for its quality standardization. The identified Q-markers will facilitate the development of a robust quality control system, ensuring the safety and efficacy of Staphylea arguta-based products for clinical use. This work is significant for promoting the rational utilization and further development of this medicinal resource.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry-guided discovery of novel GCPII inhibitor scaffolds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: There is an unmet need for therapeutics with a novel mechanism to address Q9 symptoms associated with conditions where aberrant glutamatergic neurotransmission is presumed pathogenic. One enzyme of potential relevance is glutamate carboxypeptidase II (GCPII), a brain metallopeptidase with significantly upregulated activity in nervous tissues following neurodegeneration or injury. Current inhibitors are too polar and charged leading to minimal brain penetration necessitating high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutritional status and prevalence of anemia in patients with Crohn's disease after surgery: a multicenter cross-sectional study in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Malnutrition and anemia were highly prevalent and negatively impacted patients with CD following surgery. Screening and early preventive management of malnutrition and anemia were critical components of postoperative care in CD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sulfated hyaluronic acid for wound repair: Mechanisms, materials, and translational challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sulfated hyaluronic acid (sHA) is emerging as a promising biomaterial for advanced wound dressings because it combines the intrinsic biocompatibility and extracellular matrix (ECM)-like hydration of hyaluronic acid (HA) with added chemical functionality that enhances stability and bioactivity. Chronic wounds, particularly diabetic ulcer, -remain a major clinical challenge due to persistent inflammation, protease/reactive oxygen species (ROS)-rich microenvironments, impaired angiogenesis, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electroacupuncture and vagus nerve stimulation are emerging therapies for hyperemesis gravidarum management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyperemesis gravidarum (HG), an extreme form of nausea and vomiting during pregnancy (NVP), significantly impairs the quality of life of affected individuals. This review examines the multifactorial etiology of the HG and evaluates the efficacy of non-traditional therapeutic approaches, namely, vagus nerve stimulation (VNS) and electroacupuncture. By synthesizing a comprehensive body of literature, we highlight the neurophysiological mechanisms underlying these therapies and propose a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unsupervised semi-automated MRI segmentation detects cortical lesion expansion in chronic traumatic brain injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traumatic brain injury (TBI) is a risk factor for neurodegeneration and cognitive decline, yet the underlying pathophysiologic mechanisms are incompletely understood. This gap in knowledge is in part related to a lack of reliable and efficient methods for measuring cortical lesions in neuroimaging studies. The objective of this study was to develop a semi-automated lesion detection tool and apply it to an investigation of longitudinal changes in brain structure among individuals with chronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Cardiac Disease in a Population-Based Cohort of Myotonic Dystrophy Type 1 and Type 2 in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Myotonic dystrophy type 1 and type 2 (DM1/DM2) are multisystemic disorders that may affect heart function in addition to the progressive skeletal muscle weakness and myotonia that occur. There are limited population-based studies on the prevalence and risks associated with cardiac symptoms in DM1 and DM2.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating electrophysiological correlates of nonconscious processing of facial expressions using dichoptic forward masking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Affective stimuli, such as fearful faces, are assumed to receive prioritized processing over neutral stimuli, making them easier to detect when perception is suppressed using techniques such as visual masking or binocular rivalry. Moreover, some studies suggest that fearful expressions can be processed outside of conscious awareness, as evidenced by enhanced early event-related potentials (ERPs) in response to subliminally presented fearful vs. neutral faces. This might be associated with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prehabilitation: preoperative rehabilitation interventions for lung cancer - a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative rehabilitation interventions have the potential to enhance functional reserve, reduce postoperative complications, and accelerate recovery in individuals undergoing lung resection for lung cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of intrinsic foot muscle strengthening interventions for adults over age 65: a randomized controlled trial protocol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unintentional falls are the leading cause of injury in adults ≥65 years. While causes of falls are multifactorial, weakness or disuse of the intrinsic foot muscles (IFM) can contribute. The purpose of this randomized controlled trial, using an effectiveness-implementation hybrid design, is to analyze the effects of two IFM strengthening interventions (minimal footwear use or strengthening exercises) on IFM size, proprioception, foot structure, and fall risk in older adults. Adults ages ≥65...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between early childhood caries and parental educational status among children in Ile-Ife, Nigeria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate that while education promotes some protective behaviors, it may also contribute to increased dietary risks mediated by environmental and socioeconomic factors. Context-specific actions are required to align the SDG 4 with efforts to reduce ECC prevalence in vulnerable populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A disubstituted aniline probe for enhanced peroxidase-based proximal protein labelling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proteins are biomolecules essential for cellular functions, including cell signaling and regulation. Protein misfolding or mislocalisation can result in various diseases. Peroxidase-mediated proximity labelling has emerged as a powerful tool for studying subcellular proteome and protein-protein interactions. However, the traditional probe, biotin-phenol, suffers from limitations including low protein enrichment efficiency, and the formation of oxidised and polymerised products, complicating the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exosomes from miR-149-3p-transfected menstrual blood-derived mesenchymal stem cells ameliorate inflammation and migration of endometriosis cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The potential of exosomes as miRNA carriers could be considered in developing novel endometriosis therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal study of single-pulse TMS in infants with perinatal brain injury: safety and feasibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Perinatal brain injury is a leading cause of cerebral palsy. Single-pulse transcranial magnetic stimulation (spTMS) provides a non-invasive method for investigating motor pathway development; however, data on the safety and feasibility of its repeated use in infants are limited. This study provides the first longitudinal evaluation of the safety, tolerability, and feasibility of spTMS in infants with perinatal brain injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic Characterization of Human Adenovirus Type 21 Strains - 7 PLADs, China, 2023-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Recombinant HAdV-21a/b subtypes have co-circulated in China in recent years with remarkable genetic conservation. Enhanced surveillance is essential to quantify associated disease burden and guide targeted prevention and control strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of Dengue Virus RNA in Breast Milk Following Peripartum Infection - Guangzhou City, Guangdong Province, China, 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[WHAT IS ALREADY KNOWN ABOUT THIS TOPIC?: Dengue fever is primarily transmitted by Aedes mosquitoes. While most cases are asymptomatic or mild, some may progress to severe complications. Laboratory diagnosis relies on detection of nucleic acid, antigen, or antibodies in blood specimens.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological Characteristics and Spatiotemporal Clustering Analysis of Human Rabies - China, 2005-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings demonstrate that China's rabies control efforts have successfully transitioned the epidemic from widespread endemic transmission to sporadic occurrence with localized clustering. The 2024 resurgence occurred predominantly in historically endemic hotspots identified through spatial analysis. Sustaining these control achievements will require implementing precision prevention strategies specifically targeted at these persistent high-risk counties.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Salmonella</em> <em>enterica</em> ST8333 Was Isolated as Early as July 2015]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Tnfrsf1b</em> Protects Zebrafish Against <em>Klebsiella pneumoniae</em> Infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: tnfrsf1b plays a critical role in regulating host immune responses and protecting zebrafish from K. pneumoniae infection. Targeting the tnfrsf1b signaling pathway may represent a promising therapeutic approach for managing infections caused by hypervirulent K. pneumoniae.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision Synthesis and Modulation of Ion Diffusion Interface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of electrochemical energy storage systems with high-density storage sites is the key and core technology to achieve transformative breakthroughs in battery performance. Herein, we immobilize redox-active naphthalene diamides (TBNDI) within 2D graphdiyne (GDY) to construct carbon-based TBNDI-GDY composite electrodes. This approach creates a hierarchical ion diffusion pathway and enables tunable electronic modulation through a strategic molecular design. The multiredox center...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanotube Derived Ordered Carbons Predicted by Neural Network Potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Searching for novel carbon allotropes with excellent mechanical and interesting electronic properties is valuable, but such a large structural search remains a challenge if purely based on the traditional density functional theory (DFT) combined with Monte-Carlo (MC) methods. Herein, the neural network potential is utilized to accelerate the sampling of the stochastic surface walking algorithm for a global structural search of ordered carbons from carbon nanotubes (CNTs) under pressure. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improvement of the therapeutic management of allergic patients in Europe - An expert think tank's position paper on allergen immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Respiratory allergies are a major global health issue due to their high prevalence and burden on patients, societies, and the health care system. In addition to symptom-relieving pharmacotherapy, allergen immunotherapy (AIT) is the only disease-modifying treatment option currently available that has the potential to prevent disease progression and the onset of asthma. The importance of AIT varies greatly from country to country. To discuss the different aspects of AIT, 20 experts from 12...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41170023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SOD mediates mitochondrial epigenetic regulation in NIHL]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Occupational noise-induced hearing loss (NIHL) is linked to the overproduction of mitochondrial reactive oxygen species after noise exposure. This cross-sectional study investigated the relationship between mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) D-loop region methylation and oxidative stress in 150 participants divided into three age and sex matched groups: a control group (n = 50, workers without noise exposure and with normal hearing), an exposed group (n = 50, workers with significant noise exposure but...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-density atrial mapping, P-wave analysis, and computational simulations in Brugada syndrome: Enhancing the understanding of atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Conventional P-wave parameters do not identify patients with BrS prone to AF. Increased TAAT is related to reduced local CVs, explaining the prolonged P-wave duration observed in patients with BrS. Simulation studies showed significantly higher AF susceptibility initiation in patients with BrS than in controls.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simplified left cardiac sympathetic denervation as an acute strategy for recurrent ventricular tachycardia in multimorbid patients with structural heart disease: A case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this case series of 7 patients, SG-sparing LCSD demonstrated promising results in terms of safety and efficacy for reducing VAs. Further studies are warranted to confirm long-term outcomes with this approach.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-driven clustering and visualization of electrocardiogram signals to enhance screening for atrial fibrillation: The supermarket/hypermarket opportunistic screening for atrial fibrillation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates the potential of our proposed methodology to uncover latent patterns in ECG data, providing deeper insights into individual heart rhythm patterns and supporting more nuanced AF risk assessment and the overall effectiveness of AF detection and management. By embedding interpretable artificial intelligence in screening tools, we aimed to improve early detection and reduce the clinical burden of AF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of a care process model on outcomes in emergency department patients with atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: System-wide CPM implementation improved OAC use, documentation, and cardioversion rates, while reducing admissions. Despite a modest increase in ED LOS, the model supported more consistent, guideline-based AF care, reinforcing the value of multidisciplinary, algorithm-driven strategies in emergency settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomechanically Valid Clear Aligner Therapy for Premolar Extraction Case: A Case Report and Literature Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report details the successful orthodontic management of an adult female with skeletal Class II malocclusion, protrusive facial profile with perioral muscle tension, and mild crowding using clear aligners following extraction of four first premolars. To address the inherent challenges of "roller-coaster effects," a biomechanically appropriate protocol was implemented including rational case analysis and selection, as well as attachment design, anchorage control, overcorrection strategy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant chemoimmunotherapy in HPV-associated vulvar and vaginal squamous cell carcinoma with PD-L1 CPS &lt; 1:Dual pCR evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Neoadjuvant chemoimmunotherapy may be an effective treatment for HPV-associated vulvar/vaginal SCC, potentially independent of PD-L1 CPS status, while improving post-treatment quality of life compared to conventional therapies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing Group-Based Lifestyle Medicine: The Role of the Healthcare Practitioner in Feasibility and Effectiveness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Group-based lifestyle medicine programs present a promising path to preventing and managing chronic diseases and supporting patient wellbeing. Establishing effective implementation strategies can enhance the scalability of comprehensive lifestyle medicine programs in practice. This convergent mixed methods study aimed to investigate the role of the program deliverer in the feasibility and effectiveness of a group-based program: PAVING the Path to Wellness. Semi-structured qualitative interviews...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in training intensity distribution theory for cyclic endurance sports: theoretical foundations, model comparisons, and periodization characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Training Intensity Distribution (TID) has emerged as a crucial component of training load regulation, providing a critical foundation for designing endurance training programs and optimizing performance. This paper systematically reviews the theoretical underpinnings of TID and the evolution of training intensity zone classification. The distribution characteristics, underlying physiological mechanisms, and contextual applicability of three representative models-pyramidal (PYR), threshold (THR),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bilateral distal transradial access for subclavian artery stenosis intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with subclavian stenosis bilateral dTRA is a safe and minimally invasive method for patients and ergonomically comfortable for operators.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169879/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increasing arterial compliance by laser modification of fibro-calcific plaques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This proof-of-concept study demonstrated that modulated diode laser irradiation can modify the mechanical and structural characteristics of fibrocalcific arteries and increase vessel compliance. Additional studies are required in arteries with different levels of calcification and plaque distribution to optimize laser dosimetry for targeted vessel modifications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of inflammatory factors on patients with concurrent lung cancer and acute pulmonary embolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Lung cancer is a leading cause of cancer-related mortality globally, with acute pulmonary embolism (APE) significantly worsening the prognosis of affected patients. Inflammatory pathways are increasingly recognized for their dual role in both oncogenesis and thrombotic events. This study aimed to investigate the prognostic significance of specific inflammatory biomarkers, particularly neutrophil-mediated mechanisms, in lung cancer patients complicated by APE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-Operative Considerations in Relation to Parastomal Hernia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Non-operative management remains a cornerstone of PSH care, requiring an individualized, multidisciplinary approach. Non-operative strategies should emphasize structured follow-up, abdominal support, guided core training, appliance adaptation, and psychosocial wellbeing. Dedicated prospective studies are urgently needed to define evidence-based protocols specific to PSH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Carrageenan and Starch-Based Bioplastics for Packaging Applications (Shopping Bags): Mechanical Characterization, Morphology, and Biodegradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[One approach to mitigating plastic pollution is the development of biodegradable plastic materials, such as bioplastics. Bioplastics are packaging materials that can be naturally degraded by microorganisms. In this study, bioplastics were produced using natural polymer compounds, specifically carrageenan and starch. The combination of starch and carrageenan was investigated to develop bioplastic packaging (shopping bags) with improved properties. This study aimed to evaluate the effect of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fibroblasts as key cellular targets in acupuncture therapy: a mechanistic perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acupuncture, a central modality in traditional Chinese medicine, is widely recognized for its clinical efficacy. In recent years, mechanistic studies have shifted from a neurocentric to a broader perspective encompassing the local microenvironment and systemic integration. This review focuses on the pivotal role of fibroblasts in mediating the mechanotransduction processes triggered by acupuncture. We comprehensively summarize current research findings on the contributions of fibroblasts to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Honeysuckle-Derived Exosome-Like Nanovesicles Protect Against Acute Liver Failure by Modulating Gut Microbiota]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In summary, we developed a novel natural nanomedicine with dual-targeting capabilities and demonstrated its efficacy against ALF, offering a promising therapeutic alternative for this severe condition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anodal transcranial direct current stimulation does not alter GABA concentration or functional connectivity in the normal visual cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Anodal direct current stimulation (a-tDCS) of the visual cortex is a potential rehabilitation tool for vision disorders such as amblyopia and macular degeneration. However, the underlying neural mechanisms are currently unknown. When applied to the human motor cortex, a-tDCS reduces the concentration of gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA), an inhibitory neurotransmitter that modulates neuroplasticity. Our primary aim was to assess whether the same a-tDCS paradigm alters local GABA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A pipelined, resource-efficient convolutional neural network architecture for detecting and diagnosing Alzheimer's disease using brain sMRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Alzheimer's disease (AD) is a progressive neurological disorder that impairs memory and cognitive function in elderly individuals. Early detection is vital to slow disease progression and enable timely therapeutic intervention. Traditional diagnostic approaches for AD, however, often involve high time complexity and significant computational resource utilization, highlighting the need for more efficient automated solutions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multidisciplinary perspectives on personalised prevention in youth mental health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pervasive impact of mental illnesses extends beyond individual suffering, affecting families, communities, and societies at large. Prevention efforts are imperative to mitigate this burden, promoting well-being and resilience across diverse populations. A particularly vulnerable period is adolescence, which is associated with numerous mental health issues that are exacerbated by declining healthy behaviours as well as socioeconomic inequalities. But adolescence also presents an opportune...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emotionally adaptive support: a narrative review of affective computing for mental health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital mental health interventions (DMHIs) have become increasingly prominent as scalable solutions to address global mental health needs. However, many existing tools lack the emotional sensitivity required to foster meaningful engagement and therapeutic effectiveness. Affective computing, a field focused on designing systems capable of detecting and responding to human emotions, offers promising advancements to the emotional responsiveness of these digital interventions. This narrative review...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic profiling and pharmacological evaluation of alkaloids in three <em>Murraya</em> species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study comprehensively investigated the metabolic profiling, pharmacological potential, and biosynthetic regulation of alkaloids in three Murraya species (M. exotica, M. kwangsiensis, and M. tetramera). Through integrative multi-omics approaches, including metabolomics, transcriptomics, network pharmacology, and molecular docking, a total of 77 alkaloids were identified, categorized into 18 structural classes. Comparative analysis revealed species-specific accumulation patterns, with 50...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ProtFun: a protein function prediction model using graph attention networks with a protein large language model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MOTIVATION: Understanding protein functions facilitates the identification of the underlying causes of many diseases and guides the research for discovering new therapeutic targets and medications. With the advancement of high throughput technologies, obtaining novel protein sequences has been a routine process. However, determining protein functions experimentally is cost- and labor-prohibitive. Therefore, it is crucial to develop computational methods for automatic protein function prediction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Deep Learning Approach Toward Differentiating Left versus Right for Idiopathic Ventricular Arrhythmia Originated from Outflow Tract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings demonstrate the effectiveness of DL in a higher level of applications, specifically in the treatment process, compared to conventional ECG analysis applications based on computerized methods. This represents a promising prospect for use in treatment processes without relying on complex and multifaceted diagnostic methods in the future.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative experimental and theoretical study on anomalous Nernst effect of Heusler alloy Co<sub>2</sub>FeSi thin film: estimation of on-site Coulomb interaction at Co site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Co(2)FeSi is considered a half-metallic ferromagnet and a Weyl semimetal, however, its predicted properties have been shown to be heavily influenced by how the on-site Coulomb interaction is incorporated, which remains controversial. In this study, we measure the anomalous Nernst conductivity (α (xy) ) and anisotropic magnetoresistance (AMR) effect of a Co(2)FeSi thin film from low temperature to room temperature, and compare the results with those of first-principles calculations using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multimodal knowledge expansion widget powered by plant protein phosphorylation database and ChatGPT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biological databases are essential for providing curated knowledge, but their rigid data structures and restrictive query formats often limit flexible and exploratory user interactions. In the field of plant phosphorylation, manually curated and reviewed data represent only a small portion of the available knowledge, and users often seek information that goes beyond what is provided in structured databases. While large language models (LLMs) like ChatGPT-4o possess extensive contextual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iodine-complex directed synthesis of PbS quantum dots with enhanced electronic coupling for NIR photodetection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lead sulfide (PbS) colloidal quantum dots (CQDs) are promising materials for near-infrared (NIR) photodetection. However, conventional synthetic approaches often rely on long-chain organic ligands that impede charge transfer, necessitating complex post-synthetic ligand exchanges. Here, we introduce an Iodine-Complex Directed Synthesis (ICDS) method that enables the direct synthesis of iodide-passivated PbS-I QDs in polar solvents, thereby bypassing traditional hot-injection routes and ligand...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing the science of genomic learning healthcare systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Increased collaboration, interoperability, and sharing of genomic information and strategies across gLHS can help define, refine, and disseminate best practices. Such cooperation can improve genomic variant curation and interpretation, diagnostic accuracy, evidence generation, and ultimately patient care through seamless integration of research as an integral component of good clinical care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41169653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031152004&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>