<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 19:21:04 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colossal Spin Hall Conductivity in Charge-Massive Topologically Nontrivial Semimetal Phase of Bi<sub>1-<em>x</em></sub>Sb<sub><em>x</em></sub> (012)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topologically nontrivial semimetals (TSMs) possess spin-momentum locked topological surface states (TSS) with high charge conductivity (σ), offering a platform for low-power spintronic applications. However, its spin Hall conductivity (σ(SH)), another important factor for spintronic applications, remains largely unexplored. Here, we demonstrate that Bi(1-x)Sb(x) in the TSM phase (x = 0.6-0.8), when grown along the distinct (012) orientation, exhibits a colossal σ(SH), far exceeding that of Pt....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superhydrophilic Silica-Coated Au Nanoislands for Efficient Capture and Enhanced SERS Detection of Airborne Biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exhaled breath aerosols contain critical biomarkers for noninvasive and cost-effective early detection of respiratory and other infectious diseases. However, current methods still struggle with a low capture efficiency and limited detection sensitivity for trace biomarkers in complex aerosols. Here we report superhydrophilic ultrathin silica-coated gold nanoislands (scAuNIs) for the highly efficient capture and SERS detection of airborne biomarkers. The scAuNIs are wafer-level fabricated by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Multiomics Validation of Key <em>MUC</em> Gene Expression for the Signature Biomarker in the Pakistani Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In conclusion, our findings suggest MUC3A/MUC4/MUC13/MUC16 as robust diagnostic and prognostic biomarkers and liquid biopsy as a noninvasive approach to be integrated into daily clinical practice. This analysis can also be extended to other malignancies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum Computing Based Design of Multivariate Porous Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multivariate (MTV) porous materials exhibit unique structural complexities based on their diverse spatial arrangements of multiple building block combinations. These materials possess potential synergistic functionalities that exceed the sum of their individual components. However, the exponentially increasing design complexity of these materials poses significant challenges for accurate ground-state configuration prediction and design. To address this, we propose a Hamiltonian model for quantum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Far-field wireless power transmission module with MEMS-based laser steering for optogenetic applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a far-field wireless power transmission system utilizing a mobile laser steering module (MOLASM) for optogenetic applications. The system integrates a MEMS-based active micromirror and features a battery-free architecture, enabling a miniaturized, lightweight, and mobile operation. This design allows for precise laser steering while maintaining a compact form factor. Additionally, laser superimposition using multiple MOLASMs enhances wirelessly transmitted power,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Multidimensional Electronegativity of Selected Atom Types in Organic Molecules Using Graph Neural Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electronegativity can be considered a data-driven concept that has been widely used since Pauling proposed this property. However, updating the electronegativity based on the vast amount of high-quality experimental and computational data has been overlooked. Thus, advances in artificial intelligence (AI), with its ability to manage large data sets and identify underlying patterns, necessitate reconsidering data-driven concepts such as electronegativity. In this work, we present a data-driven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Testing of Human Disease Missense Variants in <em>Caenorhabditis elegans</em> by Targeting <em>COQ2</em> Variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings provide insights into human genetic disease-associated missense variants and demonstrate that C. elegans can be used as a simple, cost-effective in vivo model for testing undetermined missense variants in human disease genes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical composition, aroma profile, antioxidant activity, and sensory attributes of beer according to roasting degree and malt type]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the effects of malt roasting degree on the chemical composition, aroma profile, antioxidant activity, and sensory attributes of brewed beer. Roasting increased carbohydrate content, diastatic power, and Maillard products such as melanoidins and Amadori compounds, contributing to deeper color and enhanced antioxidant activity. Aroma profiling with an electronic nose revealed that roasting shifted key volatile classes, including esters, terpenes, pyrazines, and sulfur...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase-Selective Growth of Violet Phosphorus Crystals via Sn-Bi Flux]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Violet phosphorus (VP), an allotrope of phosphorus, is a two-dimensional van der Waals layered semiconducting material with a tunable band gap ranging from 1.4 to 2.0 eV. Despite its potential for optoelectronic applications, the scalable synthesis of phase-pure, high-quality VP crystals remains a major challenge due to competition from other phosphorus allotropes during growth. Here, we report a phase-selective synthesis strategy based on a Sn-Bi binary metal flux, enabling the growth of VP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-SNPS2: A Multi-Layered LC-MS/MS Platform Integrating Molecular Networking and Retention Time Prediction for Identifying Controlled and New Psychoactive Substances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of unknown controlled substances poses a significant challenge in forensic and analytical sciences. While liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS) enables identification of compounds through spectral database matching, it remains limited for synthesized analogues not present in existing libraries. To address this gap, we developed AI-SNPS2 (Artificial Intelligence Screener for Narcotic Drugs and New Psychoactive Substances 2), an enhanced version of our previously...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circadian Rhythm: Biological Functions, Diseases, and Therapeutic Targets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circadian rhythms are intrinsic 24-h biological cycles that govern various physiological processes. In addition to the hypothalamic suprachiasmatic nucleus, the circadian system is organized in multiple peripheral tissues, such as the brain, heart, bone, liver, and lung. Emerging evidence suggests that disruptions in these rhythms, which are regulated by a network of clock genes, play pivotal roles in human health. A deeper understanding of the interplay between circadian rhythms and tissue...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medical guidelines for fibrodysplasia ossificans progressiva]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fibrodysplasia ossificans progressiva (FOP) is an ultra-rare genetic condition characterized by congenital malformations of the great toes and progressive heterotopic ossification (HO) in specific anatomic patterns. Present management summarized here is focused on early diagnosis, assiduous avoidance of injury and iatrogenic harm, symptomatic amelioration of painful flare-ups, and optimization of residual function. Twenty-one members of the International Clinical Council on FOP (ICC) and seven...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measurement of twenty-one serum steroid profiles by UPLC-MS/MS for the diagnosis and monitoring of congenital adrenal hyperplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our UPLC-MS/MS method provides a sensitive and specific tool for the comprehensive profiling of adrenal steroids, offering improved diagnostic accuracy for CAH. Its ability to differentiate between various CAH subtypes highlights its potential clinical utility in both diagnosis and monitoring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of the bright and dark personality inventory in assessing personality pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The BDPI's Dark 5 may offer complementary value to existing trait-based assessments by capturing additional expressions of maladaptive personality traits. Further research should validate these findings in clinical populations and explore the measurement of Anankastia-relevant constructs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prosthetic reconstruction of a fractured canine tooth in a dog using post and core]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 6-year-old spayed female poodle dog weighing 5 kg was presented with a fractured right upper canine tooth (#104). Dental examination using an intraoral camera and radiography confirmed a tooth fracture with an exposed pulp, resulting in the loss of ~2/3 of the crown. Tooth #104 was diagnosed with a complicated crown fracture. Consequently, root canal therapy was undertaken, involving root canal preparation with hand files and subsequent canal filling with appropriate filling materials. After...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of an Electronic Constant-Speed Injector in Reducing Pain of Local Anesthesia in a Scalp Procedure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The electronic constant-speed injector effectively reduced pain associated with local anesthetic infiltration compared with the manual injection method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of COVID-19 dedicated ward nurse managers in South Korea: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nurse managers in COVID-19 dedicated wards need to establish rules and guidelines within the ward to prevent and reduce confusion. They also need to collaborate with hospital administrators to ensure that staff nurses assigned to COVID-19 dedicated wards receive relevant training and are assigned accordingly. Intervention programs for COVID-19 dedicated ward nurse managers need to be developed and implemented. Policymakers need to develop government-level policies and systems to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health literacy and adherence to physical activity guidelines among adults with hypertension: evidence from a Korean National Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Health literacy is a key determinant of physical activity in adults with hypertension. Enhancing health literacy may improve hypertension management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Divided by discipline? A systematic literature review on the quantification of online sexism and misogyny using a semi-automated approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several computational tools have been developed to detect and identify sexism, misogyny, and gender-based hate speech, particularly on online platforms. These tools draw on insights from both social science and computer science. Given the increasing concern over gender-based discrimination in digital spaces, the contested definitions and measurements of sexism, and the rise of interdisciplinary efforts to understand its online manifestations, a systematic literature review is essential for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into research trends on recurrent laryngeal nerve damage in thyroid surgery (1974-2024): a bibliometric review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This bibliometric analysis underscores the increasing global research focus on RLN injury in thyroidectomy, highlighting the need for enhanced surgical techniques, international collaboration, and standardized practices to improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pleomorphic adenoma with extensive oncocytic change in the parotid gland: a case report and review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Recognition of this oncocytic variant of PA requires a multidisciplinary diagnostic approach to avoid misdiagnosis and overtreatment. Total parotidectomy with facial nerve preservation provides favorable functional and oncologic outcomes. Awareness of this rare variant and proper diagnostic evaluation are essential for optimal patient management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone morphogenetic protein-2-derived osteogenic peptide promotes bone regeneration via osteoblastogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OP5, a low-molecular-weight peptide with strong osteogenic potential, may be a viable alternative to BMP-2 for clinical bone regeneration, minimizing BMP2-associated adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-independent and photocrosslinkable hydrolyzed GelMA with tunable mechanics for biofabrication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermoresponsive and photo-crosslinkable hydrogels are highly desirable for biofabrication; however, conventional gelatin methacryloyl (GelMA) exhibited thermal gelation below 30 °C and high viscosity, restricting its compatibility with concentration-dependent tunability and lower critical solution temperature-type systems. To address these issues, hydrolyzed GelMA (hGelMA) was developed by subjecting GelMA to controlled enzymatic degradation, effectively eliminating thermal gelation while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laying the groundwork for an inter-ministerial One Health response to antimicrobial resistance in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The initiative operationalized the core principles of One Health, i.e., integration, multisectoral collaboration, data sharing, sustainability, and policy integration, while addressing structural gaps in AMR preparedness. Although challenges remain in stewardship, surveillance coverage, and long-term governance, the project provides a durable foundation for the national strategy for future AMR in South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying key features for determining the patterns of patients with functional dyspepsia using machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Through supervised learning, we identified the most important features for PI. Additionally, we proposed a novel unsupervised learning approach for identifying patterns from the patient data. This study could facilitate clinical decision making as it pertains to patients with FD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contribution of Structural Changes in Cellulose Fibers Induced by Alkali Treatment to Their Nanofibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study is to explore the effect of strong alkali pretreatment on manufacturing cellulose nanofibrils (CNFs) with mechanical grinding. The structural change (from cellulose I to cellulose II) and a sharp reduction in the yield of the hemicellulose component (xylose) of cellulose fibers (bleached kraft pulp) were observed after strong NaOH (20 wt %) pretreatment. However, the differences depending on treatment time (1 or 2 h) were not significant. The subsequent mechanical grinding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into the membrane repair mechanism by the coiled-coil-mediated oligomerization of TRIM72]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[TRIpartite Motif-containing 72 (TRIM72, also known as MG53), a RING-type E3 ubiquitin ligase, is critical for plasma membrane repair. Like other TRIM family proteins, TRIM72 has a conserved architecture comprising RING, B-box, coiled-coil, and C-terminal PRY-SPRY domains. While the coiled-coil domain mediates homo-oligomerization, its specific contribution to the membrane repair machinery remains unclear. In this study, we characterized the structural and dynamic properties of the TRIM72...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Evaluation of <em>PKD1</em> Intronic Variants by Minigene Assays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critically Important Cancer Outcomes to Report in Kidney Transplant Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reporting Quality of Randomized Controlled Trials in Antineutrophil Cytoplasmic Autoantibody-Associated Vasculitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although the overall adherence of RCTs in AAV to both CONSORT checklists is good, the reporting of some key items, such as randomization, blinding, adherence to trial protocol, and similarity of interventions is lacking.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Utility of a Multiplex PCR Assay in Detecting Common Mutations of the α-Globin Gene in α-Thalassemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alpha-thalassemia is a hereditary hemoglobin disorder characterized by reduced or absent α-globin gene, and its severity is associated with the number of affected alleles. Several methods are available for detecting α-thalassemia, such as multiplex ligation-dependent probe amplification (MLPA) and PCR-based hybridization strip assay. Multiplex PCR offers a faster, more convenient, and cost-effective alternative. In this study, we aimed to optimize a current PCR-based method for α-thalassemia...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commentary: AI psychosis is not a new threat: Lessons from media-induced delusions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The phenomenon is not new in principle, but interactivity potentially changes the risk profile. Clinically aware LLMs that detect and gently redirect early psychotic ideation, while encouraging professional help seeking, could reduce harm. Design should be guided by therapeutic principles and evidence about current model failures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping the research trends and hotspots of exercise and nutrition in diabetes: a bibliometric and visual analysis (2005-2025)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Over the past two decades, attention to this field has steadily increased, with strong collaboration established among countries, institutions, and journals. Emerging research trends in exercise and nutrition in diabetes are shifting toward a life course-oriented paradigm, personalized self-management support, and more innovative, adaptable intervention formats tailored to accommodate modern lifestyles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The cognitive consequences of fear of falling: assessing the mediating role of social engagement and physical activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Cognitive function is crucial for older adults' independence and quality of life. This study investigated the longitudinal relationship between fear of falling and cognitive function using data from the Korean Longitudinal Study of Ageing. Specifically, it examined whether social engagement (regular informal contact and social activities) and physical activity mediate the impact of fear of falling on cognitive function, informing targeted strategies to mitigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of reactive oxygen species in the pathogenesis and treatment of endometrial cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species (ROS) play dual roles in the pathophysiology of endometrial cancer (EC). Oxidative stress induced by ROS can promote the survival and proliferation of cancer cells, whereas excessive accumulation of ROS can lead to various forms of programmed cell death-including ferroptosis and apoptosis-making ROS potential therapeutic targets in cancer treatment. EC is the most common gynecologic malignancy in developed countries, and its global incidence and mortality rates have been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Edible insect larvae as sustainable sources of chitosan: Influence of species and drying method on functional and structural properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chitosan-a biopolymer produced by the deacetylation of chitin-finds numerous applications and is primarily obtained from the byproducts of marine crustacean processing. Given that this production method has numerous limitations, edible insects have drawn considerable attention as an alternative chitosan source. Herein, chitosan was extracted from the larvae of Protaetia brevitarsis, Allomyrina dichotoma, and Tenebrio molitor subjected to hot-air drying and freeze-drying, and its physicochemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Schiff base crosslinking in biopolymeric food packaging films: Dynamic covalent chemistry for advanced food preservation systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biopolymeric films (BFs) offer sustainable packaging alternatives but face limitations in mechanical strength and moisture resistance. This review explores dynamic covalent chemistry via Schiff base reactions (SBRs) as a transformative strategy to enhance BFs. Crosslinking amino-rich biopolymers (e.g., chitosan, gelatin) with aldehyde donors (e.g., dialdehyde polysaccharides, plant aldehydes) improves film stability, barrier properties, and stimuli-responsive behavior. Plant aldehydes serve dual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prompt engineering for single-best-answer multiple-choice questions in licensing examinations: a narrative review with a case study involving the Korean Medical Licensing Examination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of large language models (LLMs) has generated growing interest in their potential applications for medical assessment and item development. This practice-oriented narrative review examines the potential of LLMs, particularly ChatGPT, for generating and validating single-best-answer multiple-choice questions in health professions licensing examinations, using a Korean Medical Licensing Examination (KMLE)-focused case perspective. We frame LLMs as human-in-the-loop tools rather than...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BiV<sub>1-<em>x</em></sub>O<sub><em>y</em></sub>/Noble Metal Nanoparticle Domains with Reverse Charge Transfer Improves Photoelectrochemical Glycerol to Dihydroxyacetone Conversion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoelectrochemical glycerol oxidation (PecGO) using a BiVO(4) photoanode is a promising strategy for producing high-value-added dihydroxyacetone (DHA), but the selectivity and efficiency are limited to inferior adsorption and activation ability of secondary hydroxyl groups via surface-exposed Bi atoms. Herein, we report a strong metal-support interaction (SMSI) strategy to enrich the surface Bi atom exposure ratio in a BiVO(4) photoanode, while modulating the Bi p-band center through a reverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of sleep duration on the incidence of new-onset chronic kidney disease in community-dwelling adults: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This research identified a relationship between the amount of sleep and CKD in Korean adults. Maintaining an appropriate sleep duration of 7-8 h/day is important for preventing new-onset CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Anticancer Treatment Efficacy With Lycopene: A Comprehensive Review of Clinical and Preclinical Evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lycopene (LYP), the red pigment found in tomatoes, is a non-provitamin A carotenoid recognized for its biological significance and anticancer potential. Beyond its direct anticancer effects, LYP has been shown to enhance the efficacy of various anticancer agents when used in combination. Herein, we have conducted a literature survey using PubMed and ClinicalTrials.gov databases, following the Preferred Reporting Items for Systematic Reviews and Meta-Analyses (PRISMA) guidelines, to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liposomal Hyaluronic Acid Enhances Skin Permeation and Hydration: Evidence from In Vitro, Ex Vivo, and In Vivo Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topically applied hyaluronic acid (HA) hydrates the skin without efficient penetration. This study compared the penetration efficiency of liposomal hyaluronic acid (LPS-HA) against that of conventional HA across different models. Dynamic light scattering revealed that particles of LPS-HA (226.1 nm, PDI 0.2898) were smaller than those of HA (798.4 nm, PDI 0.8709). In Strat-M® membrane assays, permeability over 24 h was higher with LPS-HA (629.37 ± 103.26%) than that of HA (508.04 ± 93.80%;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AOSNP-ADAPTR resource level-based recommendations on practical diagnostic strategies for WHO CNS5 adult-type diffuse gliomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fifth edition of the WHO classification of CNS Tumors (WHO CNS5) has revised the diagnostic and grading criteria for Adult-type Diffuse Gliomas (ADGs) by integrating molecular parameters with histologic features. Conducting molecular testing for most ADGs is now crucial in fulfilling the WHO CNS5 diagnostic criteria. However, due to additional costs and technical barriers, implementing molecular diagnostics is often not feasible in Low-Income Countries (LICs) and Lower Middle-Income...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunometabolic Crosstalk in Adipose Tissue Remodeling: Mechanisms and Therapeutic Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adipose tissue is a dynamic immunometabolic organ whose cellular heterogeneity and functional plasticity are central to systemic energy balance and metabolic regulation. Disruption of immune-adipocyte interactions is closely linked to the development of obesity and related metabolic disorders. In this review, we summarize current advances in understanding of the immune landscape in adipose tissue, with an emphasis on the distinct roles of immune cell subsets. Recent approaches including global...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temperature-Driven Abrupt Changes in the Electronic Structure of 2D Si<sub>2</sub>Te<sub>3</sub>: A First-Principles Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Si(2)Te(3) has emerged as a promising two-dimensional material due to its compatibility with existing silicon-based semiconductor processes, its intrinsic p-type conductivity, which is rare among 2D materials, and its potential for diverse applications. Recently, experimental studies have suggested that Si(2)Te(3) exhibits temperature-dependent changes in its optical and electrical properties. Although these observations are potentially linked to changes in Si-Si dimer orientations, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scale-Up Synthesis of Porous Silicon Structures by Rotary Magnesiothermic Reduction of Silica for Advanced Energy Storage Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 1L-scale dynamic magnesiothermic reduction (DMR) of nonporous silica (1.8 μm in diameter) was conducted using a rotary reactor system to produce porous silicon (pSi) particles for lithium-ion battery (LIB) anodes. The effects of the NaCl (heat scavenger)-to-silica weight ratio (0.8, 3.0, 5.0, and 10.0) were systematically investigated in terms of (i) exothermic reduction heats (monitored in situ and estimated by enthalpy balance), (ii) porosity development in the resulting pSi particles, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of eFOV CT distortion on surface-guided radiotherapy registration: Phantom-based analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This phantom study demonstrated that eFOV reconstruction can compromise SGRT alignment accuracy, particularly when beam centers are located near distorted regions. Alignment remained within clinically acceptable limits when reference points were sufficiently distant from distortion. These findings provide important baseline data under controlled conditions, and clinical validation with patient cohorts is warranted to confirm their generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cyclo-glycylproline, a food-derived diketopiperazine, inhibits bacterial indole production: Implications for diabetic nephropathy prevention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic nephropathy is a kidney disease aggravated by the uremic toxin indoxyl sulfate, which is produced from indole by the gut microbiota. Targeting the bacterial enzyme tryptophan indole-lyase (TIL), which produces indole from L-tryptophan, could be a promising therapeutic strategy. This study investigates diketopiperazines, particularly cyclo-glycylproline [cyclo(Gly-Pro)], as potential TIL inhibitors. Cyclo(Gly-Pro) and other diketopiperazines moderately inhibited indole production from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wet-State Densification of Ionically Cross-Linked Nanocellulose Gels for Producing Stiff Porous Structures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellulose nanofiber (CNF) aerogels can offer both transparency and thermal insulation but typically suffer from mechanical weakness. Here, we report a wet-state densification strategy to overcome this limitation. Flowable CNF dispersions were converted to self-supporting hydrogels via inter-CNF cross-linking with zirconium ions (Zr^(4+)), followed by uniaxial compression and supercritical drying to produce aerogels with bulk densities of 25-95 mg cm^(-3). The compression induced a uniform...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AFragmenter: schema-free, tuneable protein domain segmentation for AlphaFold protein structures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SUMMARY: Protein domain segmentation is a crucial aspect of understanding protein functions and interactions, and it is vital for protein modelling exercises and evolutionary studies. Current segmentation methods often rely on predefined classification schemes, leading to inconsistencies and biases. AFragmenter provides a schema-free and tuneable approach to protein domain segmentation based on network analysis of AlphaFold-predicted structures. Utilizing Predicted Aligned Error values,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput synthesis of multi-element alloy nanoparticles using solvothermal continuous-flow reactor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-throughput synthesis of multi-element alloy nanoparticles (MEA NPs) is essential for accelerating the discovery of advanced materials with complex compositions. Herein, we developed an automated continuous-flow reactor system capable of synthesising a wide variety of MEA NPs under controlled solvothermal conditions (up to 400 °C and 35 MPa). The system demonstrates a high screening throughput, capable of preparing up to 20 distinct samples in a single, automated run, with each synthesis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myosin XI-1 Mediates Salt Tolerance through a Na+ Transport Pathway in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salt stress significantly affects plant growth and productivity; therefore, it is important to understand the molecular mechanisms underlying salt tolerance. Myosin XI, a primary driver of intracellular trafficking and organelle movement in plant cells, has recently been implicated in abiotic stress responses. However, their specific roles in salt tolerance remain unclear. In this study, we demonstrate that the expression of Arabidopsis myosin XI isoforms AtXI-K, AtXI-2, and AtXI-1 is induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Gamification on Task Engagement During an Eye-Tracking Test Battery in 5-Year-Old Children Born Preterm: Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight the potential of serious games in eye-tracking-based cognitive assessments for 5-year-old children born preterm. Specifically, gamification might reduce missing values and increase participant engagement, leading to higher retention rates and more effective tests, without significantly lengthening testing procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneity in Histological Evaluation of Microscopic Colitis in Randomized Clinical Trials: An Umbrella Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This umbrella review highlights the heterogeneity in the definitions of histological outcomes in MC RCTs. The summarized evidence will support ongoing efforts to develop consensus definitions for histological outcomes in order to facilitate clinical trials of medical therapies for MC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry-based profiling of phosphoinositide: advances, challenges, and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phosphoinositides (PIPs), the phosphorylated derivatives of phosphatidylinositol (PI), are low-abundance yet critical components of eukaryotic membranes. They play pivotal roles in a wide array of cellular processes, including signal transduction, membrane trafficking, and cell motility. The seven PIP subclasses, generated by phosphorylation at the 3-, 4-, and 5-positions of the inositol ring, are tightly regulated in both spatial and temporal contexts. Dysregulation of PIP metabolism is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flagella of <em>Aeromonas veronii</em> biotype sobria promote biofilm formation by biofilm-derived outer membrane vesicles (bOMVs)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aeromonas veronii biotype sobria is a gram-negative rod-shaped bacterium commonly found in various water sources. A. veronii sobria can form biofilms and has been implicated in sporadic infections associated with medical devices like catheters. Previous studies have noted that biofilm-derived outer membrane vesicles (bOMVs) can enhance biofilm formation, though the impact varies across different strains. It remains uncertain whether these variances are attributable to bacterial characteristics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-Activity Relationships of Azaquinazolinone Derivatives as <sup>18</sup>F-Labeled PET Probes Targeting Ghrelin Receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ghrelin receptor (GHSR) is expressed in various organs including the brain, pancreas, stomach, and intestine, and is involved in many physiological functions. In vivo imaging of GHSR with positron emission tomography (PET) is expected to contribute to elucidation of the functions and pathophysiology of ghrelin-related diseases. In the present study, to develop novel PET probes targeting GHSR, we newly designed and synthesized 14 azaquinazolinone derivatives and evaluated their utility. Among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal engineering enables room-temperature triplet-DNP in cocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the crystal engineering of cocrystalline polarization matrices for triplet-dynamic nuclear polarization at room temperature. Cocrystals were designed using nicotinamide as a hydrogen bonding coformer to enable the triplet-DNP of aliphatic dicarboxylic acids. The rigid molecular frameworks formed through controlled hydrogen-bonding and π-π interactions maintain sufficiently long T(1) values for spin diffusion, leading to room-temperature triplet-DNP. This crystal engineering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient increase in skeletal-related events after discontinuation of high-dose denosumab in cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SREs increased significantly 6-15 months after high-dose denosumab discontinuation. Elevated ALP was associated with post-discontinuation SREs. These findings emphasize that discontinuation contributes to SRE risk, possibly via rebound bone resorption, and underscore the importance of continuation of therapy whenever possible.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined statistical-biophysical modeling links ion channel genes to physiology of cortical neuron types]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurons have classically been characterized by their anatomy, electrophysiology, and molecular markers. More recently, single-cell transcriptomics has enabled an increasingly fine genetically defined taxonomy of cortical cell types, but the link between the gene expression of individual cell types and their physiological and anatomical properties remains poorly understood. Here, we develop a hybrid modeling approach to bridge this gap: our approach combines statistical and mechanistic models to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry-based analysis of rheumatoid factor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Rheumatoid factor (RF) are autoantibodies that are found in approximately two thirds of patients with rheumatoid arthritis, a chronic autoimmune disease characterized by potentially destructive inflammation of the joints. RF consists of polyclonal antibodies targeting the Fc part of immunoglobulin G. Despite its clinical relevance, RF is not specific for RA, and conventional assays for RF detection, predominantly solid-phase tests detecting IgM RF, suffer from poor harmonization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unmet supportive care needs among head and neck cancer survivors beyond 5 years after diagnosis: a multinational cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: This study investigates unmet supportive care needs (SCNs) among head and neck cancer (HNC) survivors beyond 5 years after diagnosis and examines the association with sociodemographic, clinical and lifestyle factors, and differences in European and non-European regions and healthcare systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening and machine learning-based prediction of translation-enhancing peptides that reduce ribosomal stalling in <em>Escherichia coli</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We previously reported that the nascent SKIK peptide enhances translation and alleviates ribosomal stalling caused by arrest peptides (APs) such as SecM and polyproline when positioned immediately upstream of the APs in both Escherichia coli in vivo and in vitro translation systems. In this study, we conducted a comprehensive screening of translation-enhancing peptides (TEPs) using a randomized artificial tetrapeptide library. The screening focused on the ability of the peptides to suppress SecM...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primed human pluripotent stem cell-derived blastocyst-like cell aggregates with partial lineage specification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This work introduces a more accessible platform for generating human blastocyst-like cell aggregates from primed hPSCs, broadening their utility for investigating early development events. Insights gained from blastocyst-like cell aggregates have the potential to advance the modelling of early-onset diseases, drive innovations in regenerative therapies, and contribute to the development of assisted reproductive technologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of permeability in deep tissue capillaries using a new method reflects the nutrient supply status in a healthy heart]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We have developed a method to assess capillary permeability in deep tissue. This research will improve our understanding of how capillaries exchange substances and support tissue function. This new method will not only provide new insights into studies of cardiac disease risk and sex differences, but also assist in developing more advanced in vitro models. It will further aid in refining the best cell transplantation techniques.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muscle-tendon properties assessed by three-dimensional ultrasound in clinically well-performing clubfoot patients treated with the Ponseti method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Clubfoot is a congenital birth defect affecting musculoskeletal tissues of the affected lower legs, resulting in the typical appearance and changes in muscle-tendon properties. These properties change during development due to growth and activity, but how these properties differ across ages in clubfoot remains not fully understood. This study aimed to describe plantarflexor muscle-tendon volumes between affected and unaffected legs in unilateral clubfoot patients and explore the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Technical success and initial clinical outcome of partial frozen elephant trunk in various aortic arch pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The clinical outcomes of total arch replacement using the partial FET technique were satisfactory. However, surgeons must exercise caution when employing this method for chronic aortic dissection due to its weak radial and spring back forces.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of prehospital pupillary diameter with return of spontaneous circulation and neurological outcome after out-of-hospital cardiac arrest: A multicenter retrospective analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prehospital pupillary diameter is independently associated with both ROSC and 30-day neurological outcome. Although extreme dilation (≥7-8 mm) provides a highly specific marker of futility, low sensitivity precludes its use as a stand-alone criterion. Pupillary assessment may nonetheless contribute, in combination with other prehospital indicators, to a multimodal framework for early decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home-Based sensing of the nervous system with clinical neurophysiology technologies: IFCN handbook chapter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Future advancements are expected with new generations of wearable systems capable of providing long-term monitoring with minimal maintenance. Beyond epilepsy and sleep disorders, home-based technologies are also being investigated in other neurological diseases including movement disorders and neurodegenerative diseases showing the expanding scope of home-based technologies in neurology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41142046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between positive preadmission screening and COVID-19 community transmission: A retrospective observational study during an emergent novel infectious disease pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: After COVID-19 emerged, hospitals adopted preadmission screening to detect asymptomatic cases and avert nosocomial outbreaks; whether such clinical screening should be routine policy remains debated and has not been quantified in Japan.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of Thermoplastic Materials Using Cellulose Acetate as a Backbone via Melt Kneading Extrusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To develop a highly biomass-based thermoplastic resin using cellulose acetate (CA) derived from woody biomass as the base material, cellulose acetate-graft-polylactic acid (CA-g-PLA) composites were successfully synthesized by a transesterification reaction through the melt kneading method using 2-ethylhexanoic acid tin-(II) as a catalyst. Various characterization methods, such as Fourier-transform infrared spectroscopy (FTIR), proton nuclear magnetic resonance (¹H NMR), differential scanning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism of Action and Anti-Inflammatory Activity of Pestalotioquinol A, a Fungus-Derived Cytoprotective Compound]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pestalotioquinol A (pesA) is a novel cytoprotective natural compound previously discovered among Pestalotiopsis microspora metabolites. PesA protects PC12 cells against cell death induced by a peroxynitrite donor, a reactive nitrogen species (RNS). In this study, we analyzed the mechanism of action of pesA and aimed to identify its target proteins. We revealed that the cytoprotective activity of pesA was specific to RNS, such as peroxynitrite and nitric oxide. A cellular thermal shift assay...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alteration of Coal Fly Ash Induced by Aging Treatment: Insights from Mineral Quantification Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mineral composition of coal fly ash (FA) subjected to an aging treatment was analyzed using mineral liberation analysis (MLA) to elucidate the alteration behavior of FA, including changes in the leaching behavior of toxic elements such as B, As, and Se. Three types of FA generated from a coal-fired power plant in Japan, with initial pH values of 4, 9, and 12, were subjected to leaching experiments. These FA samples exhibited different alteration behaviors depending on their initial pH. FA1,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced isoprenoid production in <em>Escherichia coli</em> cells harboring the archaeal mevalonate pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial production of isoprenoids has attracted interest as a white biotechnology approach that yields valuable compounds, such as medicinal, biofuel, and sustainable industrial materials. Enhancement of isoprenoid production in microbial cells has been achieved through metabolic engineering, usually by exploiting one of the biosynthetic pathways supplying the precursors for isoprenoids, i.e., isopentenyl diphosphate and dimethylallyl diphosphate. The pathways used include the naturally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Andexanet alfa-induced heparin resistance during percutaneous coronary intervention for ST-elevation myocardial infarction: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Andexanet alfa is a recombinant modified factor Xa decoy protein used to reverse the anticoagulant effects of direct oral factor Xa inhibitors, including apixaban, rivaroxaban, and edoxaban. While effective in controlling life-threatening bleeding, it may induce heparin resistance, which complicates anticoagulation during procedures requiring urgent revascularization. Its potential to cause significant heparin resistance during percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI) has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41141554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling Transmembrane 6 Superfamily Member 2 p.Glu167Lys-associated Steatotic Liver Disease Using Androgen-treated Human Induced Pluripotent Stem Cell-derived Hepatocyte-like Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We report an improved human hepatocyte differentiation model to investigate metabolic dysfunction with functional VLDL secretory profiles influenced by TM6SF2 gene variant. Our combinatorial analysis of in vitro and human data indicates that male testosterone modifies the effect of E167K on hepatic steatosis but not insulin sensitivity. These data support the hypothesis that male-predominant T2D in E167K carriers is not causative but rather a consequence of persistent steatosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proliferative Cell Targeting and Epithelial Cell Turnover Fuels Hepatitis E Virus Replication in Human Intestinal Enteroids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overall, we established a robust HEV-HIE model that yields high titers of infectious nonenveloped virions. Proliferative cells and the fast intestinal epithelial cell turnover are important features that facilitate efficient HEV replication, and likely also its dissemination. This study suggests that the gut is an HEV reservoir, capable of producing some of the nonenveloped HEV shed in the feces.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring anti-cancer activities of epidermal growth factor-immobilized polymeric nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cytotoxic agents targeting the epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR) exhibit significant potential for cancer therapy as EGFR is overexpressed in various cancers. As alternatives to conventional EGFR inhibitors (EGFRi), which exert side effects on non-cancer cells, EGF-immobilized gold nanoparticles exhibit selective cytotoxicity in EGFR-overexpressing cancer cells by locally enhancing EGFR activation and modulating signal transduction through a signal condensation mechanism. However,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research priorities on physical-mental comorbidity in children and adolescents: an international consensus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physical-mental comorbidity in children and adolescents is an emerging global health concern, yet research remains fragmented and lacks a coordinated agenda. We conducted a global priority setting exercise using the Child Health and Nutrition Research Initiative method. A total of 134 research ideas were scored by 45 experts against five criteria: answerability, effectiveness, potential for paradigm shift, potential for translation and implementation, and impact on equity. The highest-ranked...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micro-photoluminescence spectroscopy of detonation nanodiamonds containing germanium-vacancy centres]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A germanium-vacancy (GeV) centre in nanodiamond is a promising candidate for bright single-photon emitters, fluorescence labelling and quantum sensing due to its narrow zero-phonon line (ZPL) and large Debye-Waller factor. Recently, the GeV centre-containing nanodiamond (GeV-ND) was fabricated by a detonation process, which provides a scalable method capable of producing large quantities of ND particles. However, the optical properties of the GeV-ND at the single-particle level have not been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Human Intestinal Fluids after the Administration of a Solid Meal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Most available data on the composition and solubilizing properties of postprandial human intestinal fluid (HIF) are derived from studies involving liquid meals. These data inform the development of simulated intestinal fluids, widely used in in vitro assays for predicting intestinal drug behavior. However, the typical human diet primarily consists of solid meals, and the physical form of food has been shown to influence gastrointestinal transit and digestion, thereby affecting drug disposition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41140153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superior Antithrombogenic Syndiotactic Poly(Substituted Methylene) with Densely Packed Methoxyethyl Ends of Highly Extended Side Chains at the Solid Film Surface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A syndiotactic poly(substituted methylene) (st-PM) featuring (2-methoxyethoxy)carbonyl side chains (st-PMECM) exhibited considerably superior antithrombogenicity compared to a typical conventional antithrombogenic polyacrylate comprising the same side chain (i.e., poly(2-methoxyethyl acrylate); PMEA). The number of adherent platelets on the surface of the st-PMECM films was 0.8 × 10³ mm^(-2), which was one-fourth of that on the PMEA films (3.2 × 10³ mm^(-2)), and 75% of these platelets were in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41139901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diet self-management and education encounter in confucianism-dominated culture: a qualitative study of taiwanese with poor diabetes control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A diet self-management plan aligning with patients' culture, beliefs, and values is essential to the success of diabetes self-management education (DSME), which requires candid communication between patients and providers. However, in a Confucianism-dominated culture, the emphasis on social hierarchy, respect for authority, and harmony may hinder patients from communicating openly with healthcare teams. This qualitative study was conducted in accordance with the guidelines of the Consolidated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breath to death: nitrogen asphyxiation for execution and assisted suicide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrathecal administration of the Nav1.7 inhibitor PF-05089771 produces rapid and side-effect-free analgesia in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nav1.7 has emerged as a promising target for developing novel analgesics that avoid central side effects, yet clinical trials involving systemically administered Nav1.7 inhibitors have thus far yielded disappointing outcomes. In this study, we explored whether delivering PF-05089771-a highly selective Nav1.7 inhibitor previously tested in clinical settings-directly into the intrathecal space could elicit potent analgesic effects. We assessed pain responses using a range of behavioral assays,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ethical Framework for Weight Loss Medication Use in Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[State Mifepristone Regulation Following GenBioPro v Raynes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autism and Parkinsonism-Terminology and Confounding-Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hospice Cost-Sharing in the Affordable Care Act Marketplace Individual Plans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of emotion regulation and distress with altruistic and egoistic prosociality during COVID-19]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic presents a unique context to explore prosociality during times of distress. Indicative of social proficiency and adaptive functioning, prosociality refers to dispositions to allocate one's attention and energy to the needs of others. Emotion regulation strategies, such as cognitive reappraisal and expressive suppression, may have affected how individuals responded to their distress during the pandemic through varying forms of prosociality. In two samples, we examined how...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opioid Use Disorder and Nonfatal Opioid-Involved Overdose Among Medicaid-Enrolled US Youth, 2020-2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining trauma-informed professional development in schools: A systematic narrative review highlighting culturally responsive, antiracist, and equitable content]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trauma-informed professional development (PD) equips educators with the knowledge and skills to support students affected by trauma while fostering safe and inclusive school environments. However, the variability in trauma-informed PD design, delivery, and outcomes, as well as the inconsistent integration of culturally responsive, antiracist, and equitable (CARE) content, raises questions about its capacity to prevent and address trauma effectively. In this systematic narrative review, 24...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reevaluating the Imiquimod Model: A Barrier to Translational Progress in Psoriasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Once hailed as a breakthrough in psoriasis research, the imiquimod (IMQ) mouse model is now overused, inconsistently applied, and increasingly disconnected from human disease. Nearly a decade after our initial critique, the field remains reliant on a tool that models acute, innate inflammation rather than chronic, adaptive immunity. In this paper, we revisit the limitations of the IMQ model, highlighting methodological drift, poor transcriptomic overlap with psoriasis, and the illusion of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting Mutual Dependence of Phosphatidylinositol-3-Kinase α/δ and Small Ubiquitin-Like Modifier Signaling in Pancreatic Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study introduces a novel rational combination therapy in PDAC. Dual targeting of PI3Kα/δ and SUMO signaling bears potential for clinical translation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of a Serum-Based Biomarker Signature for Detection of Early-Stage Pancreatic Ductal Adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings indicate that PancreaSure is a high-performing biomarker test to aid in the detection of early-stage PDAC. Overall, this work represents an important step toward improving early-stage diagnostic success.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reproductive stage and other risk factors associated with intimate partner violence: a multi-site study of women living with HIV in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: IPV is prevalent among WLHIV, especially during pregnancy. Policies should prioritize comprehensive contraceptive access and IPV screening to address the intersecting epidemics of IPV and HIV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and efficacy of immune checkpoint inhibitors in persons living with HIV at a single, tertiary care cancer center in the US]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that HIV status alone should not preclude use of ICI therapy to improve prognosis among PWH and cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enabling Bottom-Up Li Deposition: A Smart Pore-Size/Lithiophilicity Dual-Gradient Three-Dimensional Host]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrochemical performance of Li composite anodes can be enhanced by introducing a three-dimensional host structure with a gradient configuration. However, the undesirable Li dendrites and Li top-growth behavior are difficult to tackle since the conventional lithiophilicity/conductivity gradient is quickly attenuated with the cycling. Herein, a pore-size gradient is hybridized with a lithiophilic gradient by simply infiltrating molten Li-Mg alloy into the bottom of a double-layered carbon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuropsychiatric Challenges of Friedreich Ataxia in a Patient Residing in a Long-Term Care Facility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methyl substitution effect on aggregation-induced delayed fluorescence luminogens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two tailor-made new aggregation-induced delayed fluorescence luminogens are constructed. The effect of methyl substitution sites on the luminescence behaviors is systematically evaluated. Efficient blue non-doped and doped organic light-emitting diodes are fabricated based on these emitters, furnishing high external quantum efficiencies of 14.3% and 30.4%, respectively.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vivo exposure of mixed microplastic particles in mice and its impacts on the murine gut microbiome and metabolome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics (MPs) are emerging environmental contaminants due to increasing global plastic production and waste. Microplastics, defined as plastic particles less than 5 mm in diameter, are formed through degradation of larger plastics via sunlight, weathering, and microbes. These plastic compounds are widely detected in water, soil, food, as well as human stool and blood. The gut microbiome, often referred to as our second genome, is important in human health and is the primary point of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A clinically applicable method for early interstitial lung disease detection in incident rheumatoid arthritis cases: integration of protein biomarkers and clinical factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This systematic study from discovery to validation identified MMP3 and VWF as potential biomarkers for RA-ILD. The integrated predictive model combining these biomarkers with clinical parameters (KL-6, age, sex) provides a potential tool for early ILD screening in RA patients, offering novel strategies for early diagnosis and intervention of RA-ILD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the editor: "Comparative study of bladder augmentation using different biomimetic scaffolds: electrospun nanofiber vs. extracellular matrix scaffold with adipose-derived stem cells"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[α-Hydroxyalkynyl-protected copper(I) acetelyenediide nanoclusters with anion-dependent photoluminescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoluminescent copper(I) acetelyenediide nanoclusters [(C(2))Cu(15)(CCC(OH)R(2)¹)(10)(ClO(4))(2)(CH(3)OH)(3)](ClO(4)) (Cu15, HCCC(OH)R(2)¹ = ethinylestradiol) and [(C(2))Cu(17)(CCC(OH)R(2)²)(10)(CF(3)CO(2))(5)] (Cu17, HCCC(OH)R(2)² = ethisterone) are synthesised via comproportionation reactions of Cu(0) powder and Cu(II) salts in methanol. The employed α-hydroxyalkynes not only form multidentate α-hydroxyalkynyl ligands to stabilise the clusters from outside, but also release...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143585/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioactive Topographies: Shaping Cell Behavior with Thermally Patterned Poly(ε-caprolactone)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The interface between biomaterials and biological systems critically governs the cellular fate and function. This study presents a straightforward methodology for engineering cell-material interfaces on semicrystalline poly(ε-caprolactone) (PCL) films. Our approach leverages thermomechanical treatments to precisely control the surface presentation of cell-adhesive arginine-glycine-aspartic acid (RGD) peptides. By employing a solvent casting technique, followed by controlled thermal annealing, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient Preferences for a Blood-Based Colorectal Cancer Screening Test: Insights from a Conjoint Analysis Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among individuals not up-to-date with CRC screening, our findings suggest that many would generally prefer a blood-based screening test over other options, but preference may depend on test accuracy. Offering a blood test option may improve CRC screening uptake, particularly among individuals who are unscreened or overdue for screening.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concentrations and ecological risk assessment of pesticide residues on soil biota in irrigated soil of ziway, Ethiopia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pesticide residues in soil samples were analyzed using a gas chromatograph-mass spectrometer (GC-MS). To evaluate the ecological risks posed to significant soil organisms, including earthworms (Eisenia fetida), springtails (Folsomia candida), and nitrogen-mineralizing microorganisms, we employed Toxicity Exposure Ratios (TERs) and Risk Quotients (RQs) to assess potential impacts. The rank order of pesticide in soil based on their concentration was pp'-DDE (37.48 ± 16.76 μg kg-1) > Propoxur...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Home Blood Pressure Monitoring in Routine Care - Factors Associated with Enrollment and Blood Pressures Recorded in the Veterans Health Administration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HBPM is underutilized in eligible VHA patients. Older age was associated with lower likelihood of enrollment but greater number of transmitted BPs. Interventions to improve HBPM utilization could focus on provider and facility factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced discrimination of <em>Clostridioides difficile</em> transmission using whole-genome sequencing and <em>in silico</em> multi-locus variable number tandem repeat analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Whole-genome sequencing (WGS) is used to establish genetic relatedness of bacteria and track outbreaks in healthcare settings. While WGS provides sufficient discriminatory power to make inferences about genetic relatedness and transmission for most bacterial species, WGS for Clostridioides difficile often fails to do so, even at low single-nucleotide polymorphism (SNP) differences. Multi-locus variable number tandem repeat analysis (MLVA), which analyzes rapidly mutating tandem repeat loci, has...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transiently produced IgGs enable universal SARS-CoV-2 diagnosis and differentiation recent from past infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis and differentiating infected from vaccinated animals (DIVA) are the milestone in mitigation, control, and eradication of virus. However, the continuous evolution of new virus strains has hindered the success of many classical techniques, and no DIVA-compatible vaccines are available for severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2). We here develop a universal diagnostic protein-peptide hybrid microarray (PPHM) for different SARS-CoV-2 strains infections and extend...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tonotopy is not preserved in a descending stage of auditory cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous studies based on layer specificity suggest that ascending signals from the thalamus to the sensory neocortex preserve spatially organized information, but it remains unknown whether sensory information descending from sensory neocortex to the thalamus also maintains such spatial organization pattern. By focusing on projection specificity, we mapped the tone response properties of two groups of cortical neurons in the primary auditory cortex (A1), based on the relationship between their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a setup for interferometric two-dimensional heterodyne-detected vibrational sum-frequency generation (2D HD-VSFG) measurements to study liquid interfaces with sub-100 fs time resolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We constructed an apparatus for interferometric 2D heterodyne-detected vibrational sum-frequency generation (2D HD-VSFG) spectroscopy, which is applicable to the study of ultrafast dynamics at liquid interfaces. By using a multiple-plate pulse compressor and Michelson interferometer, we generated IR pump pulse pairs having a broad bandwidth (∼400 cm-1 FWHM) and sufficient energy (∼12 μJ/pulse maximum) to observe transient responses of molecules at a liquid interface. The instrumental responses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum proteins associated with LDL-C and non-HDL-C reduction in response to dietary interventions in the DASH and DASH-Sodium trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Dietary Approaches to Stop Hypertension (DASH) diet reduced low-density lipoprotein (LDL)-cholesterol (C) and non-high-density lipoprotein (HDL)-C levels compared to the control diet. However, the mechanisms underlying the relation between the DASH diet and lipoprotein levels are not fully understood. We identified DASH diet-related proteins that were differently associated with LDL-C and non-HDL-C in two randomized controlled feeding studies comparing a DASH to control diet (DASH and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chimeric fungal-firefly luciferins exhibit red shifted fungal bioluminescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A rational design of new luciferins based upon the combination of luciferins from different lineages is exemplified by the synthesis of chimeric luciferins from a combination of fungal and firefly luciferin. Two new chimeric fungal-firefly luciferins exhibited the furthest red shifted bioluminescence of a fungal luciferin analogue.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An <em>operando</em> photoconductivity platform reveals defect-adsorbate-carrier coupling in ultrathin MoS<sub>2</sub> for solar-driven CO<sub>2</sub> reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the interfacial charge dynamics between a catalyst and adsorbate is vital for advancing solar-driven CO(2) reduction. However, the mechanistic coupling between defects, surface adsorbates, and photogenerated carriers remains poorly defined under operando conditions, limiting rational catalyst design. Here, we introduce a high-sensitivity in situ photoconductivity (PC) platform to probe carrier dynamics in a 3 nm-thick MoS(2) film under simulated gas-phase CO(2) photoreduction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered Neuroretinal Tissue in Childhood Cancer Survivors: Data From the German CVSS Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The pRNFL is thinner in CCS with most common tumor entities, except lymphoma and germ cell tumors. Cranial radiation and platin derivates had negative effects on the pRNFL thickness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori Infection's Dual Impact on the Ocular Surface: Tear Secretion Disruption and Ocular Surface Microbiome Alteration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The H. pylori infection disrupts tear secretion and ocular surface microbiota, potentially via inducing T lymphocyte infiltration and lacrimal gland inflammation, contributing to dry eye pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor Re: "Comparison of 20% Autologous Platelet-Rich Plasma Versus Conventional Treatment in Moderate to Severe Dry Eye Patients"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical and Region Equilibria with Heterogeneous Fluids Using Classical Density Functional Theory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Classical density functional theory has played an important role in adsorption calculations. However, until now, this tool has not been used for adsorption calculations in reactive systems. In this work, a formulation is proposed for minimizing the Helmholtz energy of systems formed by regions of homogeneous and heterogeneous fluids, which can participate in multiple reversible chemical reactions. This methodology allows the determination of not only the saturation conditions (adsorption...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Historical Blood Serum Samples from Wilmington, North Carolina: The Importance of Ultrashort-Chain Per- and Polyfluoroalkyl Substances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[From 1980 to 2017, Wilmington, North Carolina (NC), residents unknowingly consumed high levels of PFAS through drinking water. Some of these PFAS are expected to have short biological half-lives, and current biological sampling will miss these exposures. To assess historical PFAS exposures, we (1) determined PFAS levels in serum samples of Wilmington, NC residents obtained during the years 2010-2016, (2) examined temporal trends of serum PFAS over this period, and (3) associated serum PFAS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated crop-livestock farming systems influence the incidence of <em>Salmonella</em>, <em>Listeria monocytogenes</em>, Shiga toxin-producing <em>Escherichia coli</em>, and indicator bacteria on fresh produce]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Concerns remain about foodborne pathogen contamination risks to integrated crop-livestock farm (ICLF) fresh produce due to farm animal proximity to crop fields and use of biological soil amendments of animal origin (BSAAO). This study aimed to evaluate the extent of microbial contamination in Maryland's Eastern Shore ICLFs and compare results with those from corresponding samples from crop-only farms (COFs), farmers' markets, and supermarkets. Altogether, 1,782 soil, animal reservoir, water, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Environmental reservoirs of hypervirulent <em>Clostridioides difficile</em>: RT078 strains in wastewater and first detection of RT027 in shellfish in Taiwan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clostridioides difficile infection is a global health concern, with increasing community-associated cases. Environmental sources may contribute to transmission. This study assessed hypervirulent C. difficile in wastewater and shellfish in southern Taiwan. From April to September 2020, water samples were collected from two domestic wastewater treatment plants (WWTPs), one hospital WWTP, and shellfish from an aquafarm in Tainan City. C. difficile isolates underwent molecular identification, toxin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative genomics of <em>Nocardia tsunamiensis</em> IFM 10818, a new source of the antibacterial macrolide nargenicin A1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rare actinomycetes belonging to the genus Nocardia are opportunistic pathogens responsible for nocardiosis, especially in immunocompromised individuals. Despite their pathogenicity, they possess diverse metabolic pathways and therefore are potential sources of novel bioactive secondary metabolites, with implications for drug discovery. However, the biosynthetic potential of many Nocardia strains has not been determined. In this study, we evaluated the antibiotic production abilities of 119...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A single amino acid substitution in SED-2 β-lactamase leads to increased inhibitor resistance and an extended substrate spectrum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[β-Lactamases are the leading mechanism of resistance to β-lactam antibiotics in Enterobacterales. Here, we report the detection and characteristics of SED-2, a new member of the Citrobacter sedlakii class A chromosomal β-lactamase SED family. A C. sedlakii isolate recovered during routine screening was subjected to whole genome sequencing. A new variant of SED-1 was identified and named SED-2. blaSED-1 and blaSED-2 were cloned into E. coli DH10β. The donor C. sedlakii and the recombinant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A presumed mouse parvovirus with overlooked high toxicity for human primitive CD34<sup>+</sup> hematopoietic precursors <em>in vitro</em> and in bone marrow-humanized mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two strains of the minute virus of mice (MVM) parvovirus (of the species Protoparvovirus rodent1), named i (immunosuppressive) and p (prototype), show disparate tropism and pathogenicity in mice. Unlike the virulent MVMi, the MVMp is attenuated and infection-restricted in primary mouse hematopoietic cells; however, it does infect human transformed, established, and stem cells. We thus seek here a putative MVMp natural tropism to humans compared to MVMi. Infectious purified MVMp virions suppress...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of the respiratory infectome in children with community-acquired pneumonia: insights from large and short time-scale analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Community-acquired pneumonia (CAP) has emerged as a significant health challenge for young children, especially after the relaxation of COVID-19 restrictions, which coincided with a sharp increase in CAP cases. While pathogen profiling is commonly performed, comprehensive studies examining the total infectome and its dynamic changes during disease progression and in relation to the pandemic remain scarce. To address this gap, we conducted a prospective cohort study involving 58 children...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Benchmark Database for Spin-Flip Gap Calculations in Single- and Multireference Systems Using ΔDFT and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate calculation of spin-flip gaps (SFGs) in molecular systems remains challenging due to the lack of benchmark data and the multireference nature of many open-shell singlet states. Here, we constructed a benchmark SFG database comprising 419 vertical gaps, partitioned into two subsets: SFG-SR (379 gaps from single-reference systems) and SFG-MR (40 gaps from multireference diradicals). Reference values were obtained using CCSD(T) for SFG-SR and MS-CASPT2 or experimental data for SFG-MR. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controllable growth of two dimensional stereoscopic PtTe<sub>2</sub> nanosheets for efficient electrocatalytic hydrogen evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Among the transition metal dichalcogenide family, two-dimensional (2D) PtTe(2) has emerged as a promising electrocatalyst for the hydrogen evolution reaction (HER), due to its high edge catalytic activity, excellent conductivity and chemical stability, etc. However, the active sites of 2D PtTe(2) synthesized on conventional planar insulating substrates are limited to the edges, and the traditional synthetic method is not compatible with low-cost batch production. Herein, we report the large-area...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating the Causal Effect of Realistic Treatment Strategies Using Longitudinal Observational Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundReal-world data can inform health care decisions by allowing the evaluation of nuanced treatment strategies. Longitudinal observational data enable the assessment of dynamic treatment regimes (DTRs), strategies that adapt treatment over time based on patient history, but require causal inference methods to address time-varying confounding. Longitudinal targeted minimum loss-based estimation (LTMLE) is a machine learning-based double-robust approach for improved causal effect...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the link between maternal childhood maltreatment and mother-infant bonding: postpartum depressive symptoms as a mediator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Impairments in mother-infant bonding (MIB) during the postpartum period were shown to adversely affect a child's development. Research suggests that such impairments are associated with mothers' own childhood experiences of maltreatment. Hence, understanding factors that mediate this relationship is essential for developing targeted preventive interventions to support mothers who experienced maltreatment in their own childhood during the perinatal period.Objective: As postpartum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smallest and Robust "Soap Bubbles" with Noniridescent Structural Colors for Versatile Chromatic Engineering and Ultrasensitive Chemical Leak Monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural colors, offering high brightness, extraordinary lightfastness, and sensitive responsiveness, are highly valuable for chromatic engineering but are bottlenecked by intricate manufacturing protocols for sophisticated nanostructures and several existing unmet issues from pragmatic uses. Herein, a versatile submicron "soap bubble" with angle-independent color and ultrasensitive responsiveness is subtly designed and fabricated as a smart structural color pigment (SCP) through a facile and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Natural polymer-based soft actuators: from biomass to bioapplications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nature-inspired soft actuators constructed from polymers have been widely used in wearables, implants, and soft robotics. Despite remarkable progress, conventional soft actuators formed by synthetic polymers exhibit poor sustainability and biosafety, which limit their bioapplications. Recently, natural polymer-based soft actuators have been emerging and opening new avenues for some specific bioapplications thanks to intrinsic renewability, cost-efficiency, biocompatibility, and degradability of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Achieving Excellent and Stable Thermoelectric Properties in p-Type (Mg<sub>3.2</sub>Sb<sub>2</sub>)<sub>0.5</sub>(YbZn<sub>2</sub>Sb<sub>2</sub>)<sub>0.5</sub>-Based Materials via Optimizing Fabrication Processes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing high-performance p-type Mg(3)Sb(2)-based thermoelectric materials is vitally important to the construction of efficient all-Mg(3)Sb(2)-based thermoelectric devices. Herein, by utilizing (Mg(3.2)Sb(2))(0.5)(YbZn(2)Sb(2))(0.5) as an example, we demonstrate that optimizing fabrication processes is crucial to the achievement of excellent and stable thermoelectric properties. High-energy ball milling of melting-annealing-fabricated YbZn(2)Sb(2) with Mg and Sb powders, followed by spark...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and cost-effectiveness of extended nursing roles in dementia care: Results of the cluster-randomized trial InDePendent]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Extended nursing roles in dementia can improve treatment, care, and patient and caregiver outcomes. We tested the efficacy and cost-effectiveness in people living with dementia (PlwD) and caregivers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pancreatic Digestive Enzyme Dispersion into Human Organs Outside the Gastrointestinal Tract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Our recent evidence indicates that pancreatic digestive enzymes, known for breaking down biomolecules in food, also play roles in degenerative processes in acute and chronic conditions, including aging. After synthesis in the pancreas, these catalytic enzymes are released into the small intestine, where they become activated and are highly concentrated. Recent findings show their presence in organs beyond the digestive tract, although their concentrations and distribution across different organs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tremor and disability outcomes following deep brain stimulation for multiple sclerosis-associated tremor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DBS is a potential treatment for severe MS tremor and did not provoke relapse. Targeting VIM alone may optimize tremor control and maintain magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) access.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ticking Time Bomb: The Escalating Threat of Tick-Borne Diseases in Rural Farming Communities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Farmers are a high-risk population, given their increased risk of exposures at worksites that are prime tick habitats. High numbers of tick encounters and perception of risk highlight the need for tick-borne disease prevention strategies to be tailored to farmers and farmworkers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AnyBio - An easy off-the-shelf masked stereolithography bioprinter conversion combined with radical-scavenging strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over the last two decades 3D bioprinting has gained momentum to fabricate tissue mimicking constructs serving as tissue models, animal-free drug screening platforms and tissue replacements for regenerative medicine. Recently, the focus has shifted towards the development of light-based bioprinting methods due to its high accuracy and absence of nozzle-induced shear stress on printed cells. However, light-based bioprinting equipment can be costly and photo-sensitive materials difficult to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Assessment of a Comprehensive Diet and Lifestyle Quality Index in an Argentinian Adult Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We developed a comprehensive Diet and Lifestyle Quality Index (DLQI) and examined its associations with health status and sociodemographic characteristics in Argentinian adults. The DLQI scores range from 0 to 100 points and comprises 49 indicators across 7 dimensions: diet and eating habits, physical activity, rest and sleeping habits, exposure to sunlight and nature, religiosity, abstinence from tobacco and alcohol, and emotional well-being and relationships. Cross-sectional data from 4215...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Climaterna: A decade of daily data on births, deaths, pollution and climate variables for all municipalities in Brazil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article describes a comprehensive dataset integrating public data from validated sources, including the Mortality Information System (SIM) and the Live Births Information System (SINASC) of DATASUS, the Brazilian Daily Weather Gridded Data (BR-DWGD), and pollution data from the CMIP6 models platform. Additionally, for the state of São Paulo, we incorporated air pollution data from monitoring stations managed by CETESB (Environmental Company of the State of São Paulo). The dataset comprises...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data on enhancing the water electrolysis performance of silicon carbide nanoparticles in various electrolytes through oxygen doping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The presented data emphasizes the significant effect of oxygen doping on promoting the electrocatalytic activity and durability of silicon carbide (SiC) nanoparticles towards water electrolysis, including oxygen evolution reaction (OER) and hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) in different electrolytes. This data is particularly relevant for researchers in academia, industrial representatives, and other parties who are focused on enhancing the electrocatalytic properties of metal carbides or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tortuous extracranial arteries contribute to white Matter hyperintensities in aging brains]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: White matter hyperintensity (WMH) is a hallmark imaging biomarker of cerebral small vessel disease and are strongly associated with vascular cognitive impairment in the elderly. Morphological changes in large extracranial brain-feeding arteries, such as the internal carotid (ICA) and vertebral arteries (VA), may alter intracranial hemodynamics and contribute to WMH development. This study examined the relationship between arterial tortuosity and WMHs using magnetic resonance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dysregulation of melatonin rhythm in Parkinson's and Huntington's disease: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that melatonin could serve as a biomarker for the early diagnosis of PD and to track the progression of HD, thus complementing existing diagnostic tools.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impairment of human spatial orientation in the horizontal, but not the vertical plane, due to aging, cognitive decline, or chronic peripheral vestibular loss]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Humans and other vertebrates exhibit anisotropic orientation and navigation skills, with better performances in the horizontal compared to the vertical plane. While horizontal navigation accuracy decreases with higher age, less is known about age effects on vertical spatial abilities. The same is true for disorders which cause spatial memory deficits, e.g., cognitive impairment or chronic peripheral vestibular loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is a neurodegenerative disorder primarily characterized by the loss of dopaminergic neurons in the substantia nigra. While most cases are sporadic, there is growing evidence of a link between PD and metabolic dysfunctions such as type 2 diabetes mellitus, obesity, and metabolic syndrome. Proposed pathogenic mechanisms underlying this overlap include insulin resistance and chronic inflammation. Similar patterns of cellular damage are observed in both metabolic disorders...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alcohol consumption and awareness of its link to dementia development among adults in Uganda: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Awareness of alcohol's role in dementia development was limited, and ageing was commonly misperceived as the sole cause of cognitive decline. Misconceptions about alcohol's health benefits perpetuated its use. Interventions should emphasize education on alcohol's cognitive effects and promote dementia risk reduction strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tailored structured peptide design with a key-cutting machine approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Computational protein and peptide design is emerging as a transformative framework for engineering macromolecules with precise structures and functions, offering innovative solutions in medicine, biotechnology and materials science. However, current methods predominantly rely on generative models, which are expensive to train and modify. Here, we introduce the Key-Cutting Machine (KCM), an optimization-based platform that iteratively leverages structure prediction to match desired backbone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving data bias improves generalization in binding affinity prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The field of computational drug design requires accurate scoring functions to predict binding affinities for protein-ligand interactions. However, train-test data leakage between the PDBbind database and the Comparative Assessment of Scoring Function benchmark datasets has severely inflated the performance metrics of currently available deep-learning-based binding affinity prediction models, leading to overestimation of their generalization capabilities. Here we address this issue by proposing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful treatment of iodixanol-induced type II Kounis syndrome with an intra-aortic balloon pump: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first reported use of IABP for iodixanol-induced KS, suggesting its potential role in refractory cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41143195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251027152056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>