<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:24:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of repeated intratracheal instillation of incense smoke condensate in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Incense smoke condensate (ISC) can have harmful mutagenic and genotoxic effects. Epidemiological and experimental studies have reported the negative effects of incense use on humans. We investigated the toxicological effects of the incense smoke condensate ISC in a 2-week repeated intratracheal instillation model in mice. Twenty-five male mice were divided into four treatment groups and one control group (n = 5 per group). The treatment groups received daily intratracheal instillations of ISC at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Safety, Tolerability, and Pharmacokinetics of ALT-BB4 (A Novel Recombinant Hyaluronidase): A Randomized, Double-Blinded, Placebo-Controlled, Phase 1 Study in Healthy Volunteers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both intradermal and subcutaneous injection of ALT-BB4 demonstrated excellent safety and tolerability, supporting its potential as a promising alternative to traditional animal-derived hyaluronidases. Future studies are warranted to confirm these findings in broader clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute-phase response- and inflammation-, but not extracellular matrix-related proteins in the amniotic fluid are associated with spontaneous preterm delivery in asymptomatic women with midtrimester short cervix]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: To determine whether (i) altered levels of acute-phase response (APR)-, inflammation-, and extracellular matrix (ECM)-related proteins in the amniotic fluid (AF) were associated with spontaneous preterm delivery (SPTD) in asymptomatic women with midtrimester short cervix (SCX) and (ii) if SPTD risk severity was related to the expression levels of inflammation-related proteins in the AF. Methods: This retrospective cohort study included 70 singleton pregnant women diagnosed with a SCX...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Representations of Neuropsychiatric Symptoms in Alzheimer's Disease Continuum Using Pathology-Based Functional Connectivity Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We identified the key regions specific to affective and apathy factors based on the areas with coexistence of amyloid-beta and tau pathologies and the accompanying altered functional connectivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gel-Based Ionic Circuits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionic circuits have emerged as a promising candidate to bridge the gap between biological and artificial systems by applying the mechanically compliant and adaptive nature of gels as ionic conductors. Gel-based ionic circuits exploit the intrinsic characteristics of ions, such as their mass, diversity, and local accumulation, to achieve selectivity, hysteresis, and chemical-electric signal transduction. Their dynamic and nonlinear behaviors not only emulate traditional solid-state electronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PARTHENOPE Charts the Course Toward Precision DAPT: Navigating Future Science in Antiplatelet Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Powered High-Performance WS<sub>2</sub> Photodetector via a Monolithic p-i-n Homojunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lateral homojunction photodetectors (PDs) offer high responsivity and fast response, yet challenges in tailoring carrier concentrations in two-dimensional transition-metal dichalcogenides (TMDs) have limited their implementation. Here, we demonstrate a high-performance self-powered monolithic lateral p-i-n homojunction PD using multilayer WS(2). To our knowledge, this study is the first report of achieving tunable, multilevel compensation doping via WO(X) formation using only time-controlled and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of body composition on prognostic stratification and survival in periampullary carcinoma after pancreatoduodenectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative body composition is associated with OS in patients with periampullary carcinoma. Integrating preoperative SMI status and postoperative SMI changes provide a more nuanced prognostic stratification. Gender-specific body composition analysis may improve prognostic accuracy and postoperative management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic and Phenotypic Evaluation of the Gliadin-Degrading Probiotic Bacillus amyloliquefaciens EG025 from Cheonggukjang for Celiac Disease Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacillus amyloliquefaciens EG025 was isolated from cheonggukjang, a traditional Korean fermented soybean paste. Among multiple isolates from diverse fermented foods, B. amyloliquefaciens EG025 uniquely exhibited potent gliadin-degrading activity, a trait with the potential to attenuate the immunogenicity of gluten peptides implicated in celiac disease. B. amyloliquefaciens EG025 maintained robust enzymatic activity across a wide pH spectrum (neutral to alkaline) and, remarkably, retained over...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging renal mitochondrial dysfunction in chronic kidney disease: a repurposed role for [<sup>99m</sup>Tc]Tc-MIBI SPECT/CT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: [^(99m)Tc]Tc-MIBI kidney SPECT/CT effectively detected renal mitochondrial dysfunction in patients with CKD, suggests its potential as a noninvasive imaging biomarker. SUV may serve as a quantitative parameter for assessing renal mitochondrial dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling of kidney allograft rejection using hiPSC-derived kidney organoids and HLA-mismatched PBMCs: an in vitro co-culture system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study is to establish an in vitro co-culture system to model allograft rejection using kidney organoids system derived from human induced pluripotent stem cells (hiPSCs). We co-cultured kidney organoids derived from wild-type hiPSCs with HLA-mismatched peripheral blood mononuclear cells (PBMCs) from healthy controls (HC) for 24 h. To assess allogeneic rejection modeling, we measured the expression of HLA molecules, (HLA-ABC and HLA-DR), and evaluated cellular damage in the kidney...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An evaluation of zanidatamab, a novel, anti-HER2 biparatopic antibody, for the treatment of biliary tract cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Zanidatamab is a humanized biparatopic IgG antibody that selectively inhibits HER2 signaling pathway by targeting two distinct epitopes in the extracellular domains II and IV of HER2. Zanidatamab received accelerated approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration for the treatment of HER2-positive (immunohistochemistry [IHC] 3+) biliary tract cancer (BTC) in November 2024. Additionally, zanidatamab received approval for the treatment of HER2 IHC 3+ BTC from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Exosome-Augmented Microneedling and Laser Therapies in Full-Face Skin Rejuvenation: A Split-Face Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Exosomes enhanced skin rejuvenation with microneedling and CO2 laser. Picosecond laser showed strong results overall, though exosome benefit was less distinct. Larger studies are warranted to optimize delivery and confirm long-term regenerative effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Node Reporting and Data System Evaluation of Axillary Nodes in Invasive Ductal and Lobular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Although the Node Reporting and Data System (Node-RADS) offers a standardized method for assessing lymph node metastasis, its performance may vary according to the histologic type of breast cancer. Purpose To evaluate the applicability of the Node-RADS score in assessing axillary lymph node involvement in patients with invasive ductal carcinoma (IDC) or invasive lobular carcinoma (ILC). Materials and Methods In this retrospective study, data from consecutive women with pathologically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Quantitative and Qualitative Visual Feedback on Motor Learning in Male Novices During a Badminton Underhand-Clear Striking Task]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the biomechanics of striking tasks, different types of visual feedback for the upper extremities influence motor learning and control in distinct ways. Quantitative feedback (QN), which provides precise numerical data, and qualitative feedback (QL), which offers descriptive or interpretive guidance, may facilitate different aspects of motor skill acquisition. Given that ballistic motor skills, such as the badminton underhand-clear stroke, require not only rapid and coordinated movement...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cryogen-free variable-temperature Kelvin probe force microscopy for probing local chemical potential in van der Waals heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the development of a variable-temperature Kelvin probe force microscopy (KPFM) system based on a Gifford-McMahon cryocooler, which enables stable and highly sensitive operation across a broad temperature range. The system integrates a custom-designed phase-locked loop, automatic gain control, and compact passive vibration isolation stages, effectively suppressing mechanical vibrations intrinsic to cryostats. We demonstrate the system's performance using a monolayer graphene (MLG)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acquisition phase-specific contribution of climbing fiber transmission to cerebellum-dependent motor memory in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climbing fiber (CF) transmission from the inferior olive (IO) triggers complex spikes (Cs) in Purkinje cells (PCs) driven by a burst of calcium spikes. In the context of motor learning, especially the compensatory optic response, CF transmission serves as an instructive signal selectively conveyed to PCs. While the significance of CF input in motor memory formation is widely acknowledged, a comprehensive understanding of its distinct contribution across different temporal windows, spanning from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal conductivity of individual single-crystalline F<sub>16</sub>CuPc nanoribbons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic semiconductors are widely used in flexible electronics, optoelectronic devices, and thermoelectric systems. Among them, copper hexadecafluorophthalocyanine (F(16)CuPc), an n-type organic semiconductor, exhibits excellent chemical and thermal stability, making it suitable for a range of device applications. As device architectures scale down to the nanoscale, understanding the intrinsic thermal transport properties of such materials becomes critical for effective thermal management. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nkx3.2 Inhibits Retinal Degeneration by Modulating Inflammation and Cell Death in RPE]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Nkx3.2 can suppress inflammatory responses and necroptic cell death in RPE. By employing these mechanisms, Nkx3.2 may play a significant role in inhibiting retinal degeneration caused by aging and oxidative stress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-volatile resistive switching characteristics in Cu<sub>2-<em>x</em></sub>S-based memristor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memristors have emerged as promising candidates for high-density non-volatile memory and neuromorphic computing due to their simple structure and low power operation. However, conventional memristive switching devices often require a lot of energy for fabrication processes and high operating voltages, which not only hinder integration with flexible substrates but also impose substantial limitations on overall energy efficiency. In this study, we demonstrated a memristive switching device based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vibrational asymmetry across heptad positions in coiled-coil IR spectra: A simulation study of isotope-labeled amide I modes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Isotope-edited infrared (IR) spectroscopy is a powerful tool for probing site-specific structures and dynamics within proteins. However, the interpretation is often complicated by spectral congestion and environmental heterogeneity. In this study, vibrational exciton models combined with molecular dynamics simulations are employed to examine the frequency distributions and IR spectra of isotope-labeled local modes (ILMs) in parallel coiled-coil dimers. Based on the difference spectra obtained by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidation State Manipulation of NiO<sub>x</sub> for High Performance and Light-Soaking Stability of Perovskite Solar Modules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NiO(x) is widely used for hole-transporting layers in p-i-n-type perovskite solar cells (PSCs) due to its stability, wide bandgap (≈3.5 eV), and solution processability. However, during solution processing, oxygen exposure can induce non-stoichiometry, forming Ni^(≥3 +). While Ni^(≥3 +) enhances hole mobility, it also promotes redox reactions at the interface, undermining long-term stability. To utilize the improved mobility without sacrificing stability, bilayer NiO(x) films with controlled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Review of Electrochemical Metallization and Valence Change Mechanisms in Filamentary Resistive Switching of Halide Perovskite-Based Memory Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Halide perovskites (HPs) are gaining significant attention in data storage, particularly for their application in resistive random-access memory (ReRAM) systems. Their exceptional electrical and light absorption properties position them as potentially revolutionary materials for the memory industry. The use of HPs as resistive switching (RS) materials in ReRAMs is driven by their observed current-voltage hysteresis. This hysteresis is linked to the formation of defects within the HP crystals and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative delirium and quality of recovery in older patients undergoing gastrectomy under general anaesthesia: a reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vessel segmentation for <mml:math xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"> <mml:semantics><mml:mrow><mml:mi>χ</mml:mi></mml:mrow> <mml:annotation>$$ \chi $$</mml:annotation></mml:semantics> </mml:math> -separation in quantitative susceptibility mapping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed method has the potential to facilitate various applications, offering reliable analysis through the generation of a high-quality vessel mask.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Exacerbation of Allergic Inflammation by Combined Exposure to Air-pollutants in a Murine Model of Allergic Rhinitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Coexposure to PM2.5, formaldehyde, and zinc aggravated allergic inflammation in an OVA-induced murine model, with PM2.5 + zinc showing the strongest synergistic effects. These findings highlight the importance of pollutant-pollutant interactions in allergic airway diseases and underscore the need for further studies to elucidate longterm health impacts and human relevance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative Full Thickness Macular Hole Formation after Vitrectomy for the Removal of Epiretinal Membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ERM with LH was a significant factor for MH formation, while thin preoperative CMT showed a marginal association. At the time of MH detection, ERM and CME were observed in most cases, suggesting that tangential traction caused by postoperative ERM or, postoperative CME may represent possible etiologies for MH formation. In patients with ERM with LH or thin CMT, the possibility of MH formation after ERM surgery should be taken into account and careful monitoring is needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive Strategies in Expertise: Optimizing Movement Trajectory for Perception Accuracy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the traces of movement trajectories for perception accuracy in expert performance, focusing on table tennis. Twenty participants (10 experts and 10 novices) performed self-generated movements for extended haptic accuracy tasks, and their performance was analyzed for absolute error and movement trajectory. The results reveal that the expert participants exhibited more movement entropy than novices, strategically sacrificing trajectory predictability to enhance haptic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modelling Assumptions in Cost-Effectiveness Analysis of Antiviral Therapy for High Viremic Indeterminate Phase Chronic Hepatitis B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus statement on peri-implant disease from the Korean Academy of Periodontology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This consensus report presents the first official position statement of the Korean Academy of Periodontology on peri-implant diseases, issued in response to South Korea's rapidly aging population and the associated rise in peri-implant disease management. It reviews the prevalence, classification, and definition of peri-implant diseases, emphasizing that these conditions progress more aggressively and unpredictably than periodontal diseases. The report also identifies systemic and local risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the gap: the essential collaboration between orthodontists and periodontists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Analysis of Growth and Neurodevelopmental Outcomes in Very Low Birth Weight Infants With Congenital Anomalies Over Three Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Congenital anomalies pose significant challenges to the growth and neurodevelopment of VLBWIs. Early and individualized interventions, structured neurodevelopmental follow-up, and multidisciplinary care are essential for improving long-term outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Prediction Model for Acute Exacerbation in Idiopathic Pulmonary Fibrosis: A Study of the Korea IPF Cohort Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results suggest that a model using FVC, 6MWD, and home oxygen use may be useful in predicting AE in patients with IPF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Weekday-to-Weekend Sleep Differences and Poor Mental Health in Young Adulthood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that large differences in sleep duration between weekdays and weekends could be a useful indicator for detecting poor mental health status. However, further research is needed to better understand the mechanisms underlying factors contributing to weekday-to-weekend sleep differences among young adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship Between Aortic Valve and Mitral Annular Calcification With Coronary Artery Calcification in Asymptomatic Individuals: Cross-Sectional and Longitudinal Analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We observed a close correlation between AVC, MAC, and CAC, which is in accord with their common atherosclerotic origin. However, the correlation between MAC and CAC progression but not with AVC suggests that other factors such as hemodynamics may have an important role in the further development of calcification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The tryptophan catabolite pathway in major and simple neurocognitive psychosis: a double-edged sword with two sharpened edges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The alterations in serum TRYCAT levels further emphasize that MNP and SNP represent two biologically distinct subtypes of schizophrenia. The reductions in TRYCATs diminish the antioxidant and immunoregulatory functions of the TRYCAT pathway. Elevated QA levels may exacerbate the disruption of the blood-brain barrier and the immune-related and oxidative neurotoxicity in MNP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891156/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bench-Stable Copper Complex for Trifluoromethylation and <sup>18</sup>F-Labeling of Aryl Iodides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we report an efficient and highly active copper complex ([(TMPhen)(2)Cu(I)][O(2)CCF(2)Cl]) for the trifluoromethylation of aryl iodides. This bench-stable copper complex converts aryl iodides into their corresponding CF(3) derivatives in high yields within 1 h. The protocol is also well-suited for aromatic [^(18)F]trifluoromethylation, offering a rapid and efficient approach for the development of new radiopharmaceuticals within 20 min.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Statistical learning methods for improving predictive performance in time-dependent survival models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that refining time intervals improves the understanding of time-dependent effects in infectious diseases. Incorporating stratified intervals and advanced models enhances risk assessment and predictive accuracy for COVID-19 and other evolving diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Study protocol for a prospective, randomized controlled confirmatory clinical investigation to evaluate the safety and efficacy of a multidisciplinary digital therapeutics in patients with patellofemoral pain syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Patellofemoral pain is a prevalent knee condition affecting up to 40% of individuals, especially females aged teens to 50 s. Standard treatments, including exercise therapy, often yield insufficient long-term results, partly due to low compliance and psychological factors like depression and catastrophizing of pain. A digital therapeutics "MORA Cure PFP," which combines structured progressive exercise and cognitive behavioral therapy via an app, offers a solution to overcome the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-expressed GPNMB orchestrates Siglec-9<sup>+</sup> TAM polarization and EMT to promote metastasis in triple-negative breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metastasis remains the leading cause of cancer-related mortality, driven by complex interactions within the tumor microenvironment (TME). Tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) play a pivotal role in metastatic progression, yet their molecular diversity and upstream regulators remain poorly defined. Glycoprotein nonmetastatic melanoma protein B (GPNMB), overexpressed in subsets of tumors including triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC), is implicated in epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HLA-B*15:01-positive severe COVID-19 patients lack CD8<sup>+</sup> T cell pools with highly expanded public clonotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding host factors driving asymptomatic versus severe disease outcomes is of key importance if we are to control emerging and re-emerging viral infections. HLA-B*15:01 has been associated with asymptomatic SARS-CoV-2 infection in nonhospitalized individuals of European ancestry, with protective immunity attributed to preexisting cross-reactive CD8^(+) T-cells directed against HLA-B*15:01-restricted Spike-derived S(919-927) peptide (B15/S(919)^(+)CD8^(+) T-cells). However, fundamental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maintaining or Increasing Physical Activity Is Essential for Managing Cardiovascular and Cerebrovascular Risks After Total Knee Arthroplasty: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients who underwent TKA demonstrated higher incidences of cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases compared with controls over a 5-year follow-up. Our findings underscore the importance of initiating regular physical activity after surgery, particularly among previously inactive patients. Conversely, the increased cerebrovascular events among patients who ceased activity emphasize the critical need to maintain activity levels after surgery. Therefore, maintaining or initiating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the potential of seaweed extracts to improve vegetative, physiological and berry quality parameters in Vitis vinifera cv. Chardonnay under cool climatic conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seaweed extracts are promising plant biostimulants for viticulture, but their effects on white winegrape cultivars grown under cool climates remain fairly undocumented. Furthermore, information is limited on the biostimulant potential of some brown seaweed species like Ecklonia maxima. This study evaluated the impact of two commercial extracts (derived from Ascophyllum nodosum and Ecklonia maxima) on Vitis vinifera cv. Chardonnay in Belgium during the 2021 and 2022 growing seasons. The extracts,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long COVID and chronic fatigue syndrome/myalgic encephalitis share similar pathophysiologic mechanisms of exercise limitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-acute sequelae of SARS-CoV-2 (PASC or "long COVID") and chronic fatigue syndrome/myalgic encephalitis (CFS/ME) share symptoms such as exertional dyspnea. We used exercise oxygen pathway analysis, comprising six parameters of oxygen transport and utilization, to identify limiting mechanisms in both conditions. Invasive cardiopulmonary exercise testing was performed on 15 PASC patients, 11 CFS/ME patients, and 11 controls. We evaluated the contributions of alveolar ventilation (V̇a), lung...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reassessing Clonal Hematopoiesis as a Cardiovascular Risk Factor in Older Women: It's Not Just Age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spherical harmonic-domain acousto-optic tomography for three-dimensional sound-field reconstructiona)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acousto-optic tomography (AOT), a technology that reconstructs two- or three-dimensional sound fields from optically measured sound-field projections, has been widely studied as an efficient and high-spatial-resolution method for sound field observations. Recently, physical-model-based approaches have made significant progress, with higher accuracy and fewer sampling requirements than conventional methods. Nevertheless, it remains a challenge to reconstruct three-dimensional outgoing sound waves...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[T-Cell Receptor Excision Circle/Kappa-Deleting Recombination Excision Circle-Based Newborn Screening Program for Severe Combined Immunodeficiency in Kumamoto, Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio affects the impact of proton pump inhibitors on efficacy of immune checkpoint inhibitors in patients with non‑small-cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NLR may be a significant stratification factor for evaluating the impact of PPI on PFS and OS in patients with NSCLC undergoing ICI monotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward the Rational Selection of Safe and Sustainable Solvents in Semiconductor Photocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Semiconductor photocatalysis has gained recognition for its sustainability and has seen considerable advancements in recent decades. Despite this progress, the critical role of solvents in influencing photocatalytic performance remains underexplored, particularly in the context of safe and sustainable solvent systems. This perspective advocates for a systematic shift toward the use of safe and sustainable solvents and proposes a rational workflow for their selection, moving beyond conventional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gender differences in higher-order aberrations and refractive error in Japanese school children: the Kyoto Childhood Refractive Error Study (KRES)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In Japanese school children, AL was shorter in the girls than in the boys, although, no gender-related differences were observed in myopia prevalence. The steeper cornea in girls might be associated with that discrepancy, and partially with gender differences of HOAs. Gender-specific differences of AL and HOAs should be considered in the analysis of myopia progression in school-aged children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunohistochemical "null" pattern of all four mismatch repair proteins in Lynch syndrome-associated small bowel adenocarcinoma: a case report and comprehensive genomic profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunohistochemistry for mismatch repair (MMR) proteins is important for evaluating the molecular background of MMR-deficient tumors, including those with Lynch syndrome (LS). The four major MMR proteins function as heterodimers (MLH1/PMS2 and MSH2/MSH6), and usually only one of the MMR subsystems is impaired. However, rare cases of concurrent immunohistochemical loss of all four MMR proteins, termed "null" phenotype, have been reported. We present the first reported case of small bowel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthetic data generation with Worley-Perlin diffusion for robust subarachnoid hemorrhage detection in imbalanced CT Datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: WPDM overcomes the limitations of Gaussian and Simplex noise-based models, generating high-quality, realistic SAH images. It significantly enhances classification performance in imbalanced settings, providing a robust solution for SAH CT detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orthostatic hypotension after kidney transplantation in a patient with diabetic kidney disease: an underrecognized and therapeutic challenge]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Orthostatic hypotension (OH) is characterized by an excessive drop in blood pressure upon standing, leading to impaired quality of life, increased fall risk, and potential cardiovascular complications. It is frequently associated with autonomic dysfunction in patients with neurodegenerative diseases, diabetes mellitus, and aging. Despite its potential impact, OH may be underrecognized in kidney transplant (KT) recipients, particularly in the early post-transplant period, when diuresis-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nationwide estimates of patient numbers and prevalence rates of ulcerative colitis and Crohn's disease in Japan in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The patient numbers and prevalence rates of UC and CD have continued to steadily increase in Japan, suggesting the need for continued monitoring and further investigation to track the disease burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of the learning curve on the outcomes of robotic surgery in obese patients with rectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that during the early phase of the learning curve, operation time may be prolonged in obese patients. However, once the learning curve stabilizes, the issue of prolonged operative time can be overcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Indispensable Value of Small-Molecule Antivirals in Epidemic and Pandemic Preparedness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Harbingers of infectious viral pandemics, such as the H1N1 influenza, SARS, Zika, Ebola, MERS, and SARS-CoV-2, caused major outbreaks in the first two decades of the 21st century. Despite warnings, therapeutic tools that could be rapidly and sustainably scaled at a global level when SARS-CoV-2 emerged were lacking. Small-molecule antivirals can play a crucial role in both individual patient care and broader public health strategies for controlling and mitigating the impact of viral diseases....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[InAs Colloidal Quantum Dot Photodiode Stack for CMOS-Integrated Infrared Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heavy-metal-free III-V semiconductor-based colloidal quantum dots (CQDs), such as InAs, are promising candidates for near- and short-wave infrared detection. However, up-to-date research efforts remain mainly limited to wavelengths below 1100 nm due to challenges in synthesis, junction formation, and passivation for large diameter InAs quantum dots. Systematic investigations into device design, reverse dark current mechanisms, and trap distributions in larger InAs quantum dots remain limited....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Lacticaseibacillus rhamnosus</em> GG in a chewable colonizes the nose and facilitates local immune benefits in allergic rhinoconjunctivitis patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current treatments fall short in managing allergic rhinitis (AR), emphasizing the need for additional strategies. Beneficial bacteria application shows promise in AR; however, most studies focus on oral probiotic administration without monitoring the applied strains in the upper respiratory tract (URT) and their local effects. In this randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled trial, the probiotic Lacticaseibacillus rhamnosus GG was administered via chewable tablets in seasonal AR patients,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of Emission Efficiency and Color Tuning by Mixing Platinum(II) and Palladium(II) Complexes in a One-dimensional Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A series of mixed metal crystals comprising square-planar platinum(II) and palladium(II) complexes, K[M(CN)(2)(dFppy)]·H(2)O (M = Pt^(2+), Pd^(2+); dFppy = 2-(4,6-difluorophenyl)pyridinate), were prepared, and their unique luminescence properties-emerging upon mixing-were revealed. Seven mixed crystals with Pt/Pd ratios of 1:0.5, 1:1, 1:1.5, 1:2, 1:4.5, 1:10, and 1:13 adopt the same crystal structure (P2(1)/c) as the pure metal complexes, in which the metal complexes are stacked with short M⋯M...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A phenazine-linked π-conjugated covalent organic framework for conjugation-driven drug loading]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rational design of π-conjugated covalent organic frameworks (COFs) represents a promising frontier in functional porous materials for drug delivery, particularly when conjugation-affinity correlations can be harnessed. Herein, we report the synthesis and characterization of a structurally unique phenazine-linked π-conjugated COF (TU-32) constructed from 2,7-di-tert-butylpyrene-4,5,9,10-tetraone and 9,10-dihydro-9,10-[1,2]benzenoanthracene-2,3,6,7,14,15-hexaamine hexahydrochloride. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Final results of JCOG0601 randomized trial of R-CHOP versus CHOP combined with dose-dense rituximab for diffuse large B-cell lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These final follow-up data confirmed the nonsuperiority of RW-CHOP in terms of PFS and OS. Standard R-CHOP remains the standard of care for untreated DLBCL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Induction of intercellular interaction and cell fusion by cell-penetrating peptide-conjugated lipids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell fusion is widely used in biomedical applications. However, conventional cell fusion methods, including polyethylene glycol (PEG)-based methods, often exhibit low efficiency. In this study, we investigated an alternative strategy to induce cell fusion with higher efficiency using transactivator of transcription peptide-conjugated PEG-lipids (Tat-PEG-lipids) with lauroyl chains (C12). We demonstrated the homogeneous cell fusion of human acute lymphoblastic leukemia T (CCRF-CEM) cells and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optoregulated mRNA Delivery Controls Pleiotropic Immune Signaling for Tumor-Targeted Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal control of protein expression remains a critical challenge in messenger RNA (mRNA) therapeutics, particularly for tumor-targeted therapy. Here, we introduce a Light-Induced Transfection System (LITS) leveraging photosensitizing polymers to deliver mRNA systemically and activate its translation via light-triggered endosomal escape. This system enables localized protein expression in any irradiated tissue, allowing for spatial control of therapeutic effects. Using interleukin-2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanding Chemistry of Expanded Helicenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Expanded helicenes are interesting compounds created by modifying the original helicene structure through the incorporation of linearly fused benzene rings, enlarging the helical diameter. Motivated by Tilley et al.'s report of a key expanded helicene structure in 2017, several research groups have synthesized such nonplanar aromatic compounds, aiming to explore their impressive structures, properties, and chiroptical performance. This review highlights recent advances in the expanded helicene...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-modal impedance and X-ray characterization enables simultaneous detection of bulk and interfacial crystallization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A multi-modal platform enabling simultaneous impedance spectroscopy and X-ray scattering is presented. When applied to zeolite crystallization, four-electrode impedance measurements reliably track bulk crystallization kinetics in agreement with X-ray diffraction, while two-electrode impedance data reveal artefacts from electrode passivation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutual Phase Stability between Kaolinite-Derived Hexacelsian and Zirconia in a Mixed System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study demonstrates the mutual phase stability and chemical inertness of hexacelsian─the metastable phase of BaAl(2)Si(2)O(8) with a layered structure─and yttria-stabilized zirconia (YSZ) across a wide temperature range up to 1600 °C, through solid-state reactions between kaolinite and BaCO(3), with or without YSZ. Hexacelsian remained without transformation to celsian─the stable BaAl(2)Si(2)O(8) phase without a layered structure─under heating when copresent with ZrO(2). Additionally, while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hidden spin state accessed by light irradiation in an iron(III) high-spin complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A high-spin (HS) iron(III) complex, [Fe(qsal)(2)]Cl·MeOH·H(2)O, was synthesised, and its crystal structures and photo-induced magnetic properties were characterised. Upon photo-excitation, the HS state is converted into a low-spin (LS) state, revealing a thermally inaccessible metastable state. This photo-induced spin switching behaviour suggests the presence of a light-accessible hidden phase.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantifying polycrystallinity effects on skyrmion dynamics and device performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skyrmion-based devices promise energy-efficient spintronic functionalities, but polycrystalline magnetic films can degrade performance by inducing skyrmion pinning. Here, we use micromagnetic modeling to quantify the impact of polycrystallinity-induced variability in key material parameters such as saturation magnetization, Dzyaloshinskii-Moriya interaction, and uniaxial anisotropy on skyrmion stability, dynamics, and hysteresis loops in Co/Pt films and device geometries. We demonstrate that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single Leg Drop and Hop: Insight Into Multisegment Foot Kinematics, Kinetics and the Role of Visual Focus in Healthy Young Adult Males]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Visual input does not influence foot biomechanics during a single-leg drop and hop. This task produces similar joint loading patterns similar to heel-strike running but with reduced power generation at the ankle and midfoot. Contrary to global belief, the single leg drop-hop task is not excessively more demanding in terms of foot joint loading, supporting the earlier use of drop-hop exercises in rehabilitation programs. They offer a controlled way to reintroduce loading while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a CD138-negative therapy-resistant subpopulation in multiple myeloma with vulnerability to splicing factor inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The molecular basis of therapy resistance in multiple myeloma (MM) remains poorly understood. Here, we performed single-cell RNA sequencing coupled with VDJ-targeted sequencing of highly purified primary MM cells from patient bone marrow. This approach uncovered cellular heterogeneity and phenotypic plasticity along the CD138 axis, accompanied by drastic epigenetic alterations. Notably, therapy-resistant subpopulations were identified within a minor fraction of CD138- MM cells, and were shown...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dissociable impacts of physical and psychological factors on side effects after COVID-19 vaccination in Japan: A within-subject repeated measures design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Physical characteristics and lifestyle habits linked with intact immune function enhanced side effects, whereas psychological characteristics linked with impaired immune function also enhanced side effects. These seemingly contradictory results could be explained at least partly by nocebo effects and suggest the need for psychological support for people with high levels of depressive symptoms or trait anxiety. Furthermore, interaction results imply that such support might be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular containment of iron source inhibits larval survival of Schistosoma mansoni and egg-laying behavior of the female adult worms via ovarian atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PHN-(OMe)(2), which has an affinity for Fe(II) ion-binding affinity, significantly affected the survival of larvae and egg-laying behavior of female adult worms. Thus, the strategy for containing the iron source required by S. mansoni could offer valuable insight for developing new drugs to diversify the treatment options for schistosomiasis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severe symptomatic cardiac dysfunction in a patient with BRAF V600E-mutated metastatic colorectal cancer treated with encorafenib, binimetinib, and cetuximab: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case highlights two crucial insights into BRAF/MEK inhibitor-associated CD. First, even severe symptomatic CD can be effectively managed and reversed upon immediate discontinuation of binimetinib and initiation of cardiotropic medications. Second, in such a severe case, rapid recovery is observed. Once stabilized, BRAF-targeted treatment could be continued as doublet therapy without binimetinib to ensure safety and disease control. However, regular echocardiographic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of recumbent isometric yoga on the orthostatic cardiovascular response of patients with myalgic encephalomyelitis/chronic fatigue syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study found that the patients who manifested POTS and performed recumbent isometric yoga for 12 weeks had a reduced increase in PR after standing up. This pilot study suggests that recumbent isometric yoga would be useful as an adjunctive nonpharmacological intervention for improving POTS in patients with ME/CFS. This finding should be confirmed in a larger number of cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AhR signaling in skin-resident CD207<sup>+</sup> cells is involved in UV-B-induced amelioration of neuroinflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental stimuli, including the exposure to ultraviolet (UV)-B light, are known to play a role in the modulation of immune-mediated mechanisms in multiple sclerosis (MS). In experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis (EAE), we have shown that UV-B irradiation ameliorates disease outcome by regulatory T cells (Treg) expansion. Moreover, the UV-B-mediated induction of Treg numbers was also observed in MS. The aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AhR) can be activated by environmental factors including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The RNA-binding protein TRIM71 is essential for hearing in humans and mice and times auditory sensory organ development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The RNA-binding protein TRIM71 is essential for brain development, and recent genetic studies in humans have identified TRIM71 as a risk gene for congenital hydrocephal-us (CH). Here, we show that monoallelic missense mutations in TRIM71 are associated with hearing loss (HL) and inner ear aplasia in humans. Utilizing conditional Trim71 knockout mice carrying a CH and HL-associated mutation, we demonstrate that loss of TRIM71 function during early otic development (embryonic day 9 to 10) causes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital SERS bioanalysis of single-enzyme biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital bioanalysis enables highly sensitive detection of biomolecules at the single-molecule level, making it a widely used technique in biomedical research. However, conventional approaches typically rely on fluorescence detection of single-enzyme reactions, which limits molecular selectivity and the ability to analyze multiple targets simultaneously. To address these limitations, we developed a digital bioanalysis platform based on surface-enhanced Raman scattering spectroscopy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic rewiring of isoniazid sensitivity in <em>Mycobacterium tuberculosis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Isoniazid (INH) inhibits mycolic acid synthesis in Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb) and is a cornerstone of treatment regimens against this deadly pathogen. However, over 10% of Mtb infections are INH-resistant. The compound C10 can sensitize clinically relevant INH-resistant mutants to killing by INH. Thus, understanding the mechanism of action for C10 could aid in designing new strategies for circumventing drug resistance. We find that C10 treatment reroutes carbon flux toward valine, drawing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic restoration of mitochondria-endoplasmic reticulum cross talk for osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoarthritis is a prevalent joint disease in the aging population. The hallmark of osteoarthritis is the degeneration of the joint cartilage, characterized by changes in chondrocytes including mitochondrial dysfunction. However, the precise mechanisms of how this affects chondrocyte homeostasis and whether such processes can be explored as therapeutic targets for osteoarthritis remain unclear. Here, we show that impaired mitochondrial function and disrupted cartilage matrix metabolism due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lysosomal reduced thiols are essential for mouse embryonic development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While it has been appreciated for decades that lysosomes can import cysteine, its significance for whole-organism physiology has remained uncertain. Recent work identified MFSD12 as a transmembrane protein required for cysteine import into lysosomes (and melanosomes), enabling genetic interrogation of this pathway. Here, we show that Mfsd12 knockout mice die between embryonic days 10.5 and 12.5, indicating that MFSD12 is essential for organogenesis. Mfsd12 loss results in the expression of genes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into the substrate uptake and inhibition of the human creatine transporter (hCRT)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892912/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Creatine plays a vital role in cellular energy production and adenosine triphosphate (ATP) homeostasis and has also been identified as a neurotransmitter in the mammalian brain. Creatine is transported into cells by the human creatine transporter (hCRT) (SLC6A8), an Na^(+)/Cl^(-)-dependent symporter encoded on the X chromosome. Mutations in hCRT cause cerebral creatine deficiency syndrome 1, a neurological disorder marked by intellectual disability, speech delay, and seizures. Beyond its role in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892912/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning methods to forecasting human embryo development in time-lapse videos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study assists in the embryo evaluation process by providing early insights into the quality of the embryo for both the transfer and avoid categories of videos. The embryologists recognize the ability of the forecast to depict the morphological changes of the embryo. Additionally, enhancement in image quality has the potential to make this approach relevant in clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining the moderating role of adverse childhood experiences on the link between executive functioning and depressive/anger rumination among adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: There is some support for the interactive relationship between EF and ACEs on rumination. However, statistical significance varies based on model specification and assessment of constructs. It is important to utilize multi-informants to assess ACEs, EF measured across valenced stimuli, and broad conceptualizations of rumination.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling a novel S-Box strategy: The dynamic 3D scrambling approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A close study about the varied anatomies of the S-Box algorithms published in the literature indicates that no attempt has been made using the notion of 3D. To cement the more cryptographic security, this research article ventures to present a novel S-Box algorithm exploiting the notion of 3D. First of all, the algorithm initializes a 3D scrambled S-Box with the value of -1. After that, a 1D array is initialized with all the numbers of the potential S-Box. Now, the values placed in the 1D array...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fecal immunochemical test surveillance in colorectal cancer following adenoma resection: A longitudinal, population-based linked cohort study in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Protocol-adherent follow-up FIT surveillance after adenoma removal was associated with reduced long-term CRC risk, comparable to that observed with direct colonoscopy. However, improving adherence to colonoscopy after a positive FIT surveillance is crucial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gα<sub>q</sub> signaling in primary sensory neurons shifts opioid analgesia to NMDA receptor-driven tolerance and hyperalgesia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Opioids relieve pain by activating μ-opioid receptors (MORs), which inhibit communication between pain-sensing neurons (nociceptors) and the spinal cord. However, prolonged opioid use can paradoxically lead to increased pain sensitivity (hyperalgesia) and reduced analgesic efficacy (tolerance), partly because of the activation of NMDA-type glutamate receptors (NMDARs) at the central terminals of primary sensory neurons in the spinal cord. Here, we identified a critical role for the G protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized models of disorders of consciousness reveal complementary roles of connectivity and local parameters in diagnosis and prognosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study of disorders of consciousness (DoC) is very complex because patients suffer from a wide variety of lesions, affected brain mechanisms, different severity of symptoms, and are unable to communicate. Combining neuroimaging data and mathematical modeling can help us quantify and better describe some of these alterations. The goal of this study is to provide a new analysis and modeling pipeline for fMRI data leading to new diagnosis and prognosis biomarkers at the individual patient level....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visual processing oscillates differently through time for adults with ADHD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ADHD is a neurodevelopmental disorder affecting 3-4% of Canadian adults and 2.6% of adults worldwide. Its symptoms include inattention, hyperactivity and impulsivity. Though ADHD is known to affect several brain functions and cognitive processes, little is known regarding its impact on perceptual oscillations. This study compared the temporal features of visual processing between ADHD and neurotypical individuals in a visual word recognition task through the use of a temporal sampling technique,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Future of snakebite risk in India: Consequence of climate change and the shifting habitats of the big four species in next five decades]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION/SIGNIFICANCE: The integrated risk index indicates that the southwestern region urgently needs priority attention to combat fatalities from envenomation by the Big Four species, while also highlighting the future needs of the northern and northeastern region to aid public health efforts. To mitigate these impacts, local governments and international communities must intensify efforts to counter climate change and protect vulnerable regions from Big Four envenomation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-dose calcium supplementation during pregnancy in low and middle-income countries: A cost-effectiveness analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calcium supplementation during pregnancy can reduce the risk of preeclampsia and preterm birth. Few countries have implemented WHO-recommended high-dose calcium supplementation (1500-2000mg/day), due to adherence and cost concerns. However, low-dose calcium supplementation (one 500mg tablet daily) has recently been shown to be similarly efficacious as high-dose supplementation. We assessed the cost-effectiveness of low-dose calcium supplementation during pregnancy, in low- and middle-income...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptional profiling identification of inflammatory signaling pathways in ulcerative colitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ulcerative colitis (UC) is a chronic type of inflammatory bowel disease (IBD). This study identified core genes and pathways involved in UC by performing transcriptional profiling of colon biopsies from UC patients and healthy controls using data from the Gene Expression Omnibus (GEO) database. A total of 202 samples, including 129 UC patients and 73 healthy controls, were analyzed, measuring the expression of 40,991 genes using a 44K formatted microarray. Differential gene expression (DGE)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antimalarial and neuroprotective effects of ethanolic extracts of the five-flower remedy in an experimental cerebral malaria model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cerebral malaria (CM), a life-threatening consequence of Plasmodium falciparum infection, is associated with a high fatality rate and long-term brain impairment in survivors. Despite advances in malaria treatment, effective therapies to mitigate the severe neurological consequences of CM remain limited. Consequently, novel antimalarial drugs with different mechanisms or neuroprotective advantages are urgently required. This study aimed to explore the potential antimalarial and neuroprotective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determinants of modern contraceptive use among married and sexually active unmarried women aged 15-49 years old in Cambodia: How are geographical and socio-demographic factors associated with access?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Using modern contraceptives is essential for promoting economics, limiting the space of pregnancies, and improving maternal and newborn health outcomes. Despite progress in Cambodia, disparities in contraceptive use persist, particularly across socio-demographic and geographic groups. This study examined the prevalence and determinants of modern contraceptive use among married and sexually active women of reproductive age (15-49 years) in Cambodia, focusing on geographic and socio-demographic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of New Spiro Insecticides against White-Backed Planthoppers with Multitarget Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The invasive white-backed planthopper (WBP) poses a severe threat to global rice crop security, and most populations have developed significant resistance to neonicotinoids. Although these species remain sensitive to mesoionic triflumezopyrim (TFM), both neonicotinoids and TFM are hazardous to pollinating insects. Herein, we disclose a series of new spirocompounds designed via isosteric ring replacement of scaffold hopping. Of these, spirocyclic molecule A11 exhibits satisfactory biosafety to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of tuberculosis in Eastern Africa region from 1990-2021: A systematic analysis for the Global Burden of Disease 2021 Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A significant decline was observed in TB burden across eastern African countries between 1990 and 2021. However, TB rates remain significantly higher than global and African averages. Therefore, continued investment in health systems and tailored interventions is essential to alleviate the disease burdens, specifically in high-prevalence areas.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The MCTOT app: A publicly available tool for statistical cycle-to-threshold analysis and inference of informative but uncertainly determined qPCR data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As a common experimental technique, qPCR (Quantitative Real-time Polymerase Chain Reaction) is widely used to measure levels of nucleic acids, e.g., microRNAs and messenger RNA. While providing accurate and complete data, researchers have inevitably encountered uncertainly determined qPCR data because of intrinsically low amounts of biological material. The presence of incomplete or uncertain qPCR data challenges interpretation accuracy. This study presents a web application that integrates two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Citizen science reveals alarming update on the invasion of the Asian mantleslug Meghimatium pictum in Brazil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Asian mantleslug Meghimatium pictum is an exotic species introduced to Brazil in the late 1990s, but only formally reported in 2011. Since then, it has been deemed an agricultural pest and given the status of an invasive species; furthermore, it has been confirmed as an intermediate host for the nematode Angiostrongylus costaricensis in Brazil. Despite its potential for impacts, no additional studies on the status of its invasion have been conducted since the initial report. In this study,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions on vaccines, vaccine communication and information needs of healthcare professionals involved in older adult vaccination: A cross-country interview study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global population of older adults is growing. Older adults are more vulnerable to infectious diseases compared to younger adults. Vaccines are available to protect older adults against several infectious diseases, yet their uptake remains sub-optimal. Healthcare professionals (HCP) play an important role in vaccine decisions of older adults and subsequently they could improve the vaccine uptake. This study aims to identify HCPs' awareness, attitudes and perceptions regarding older adult...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of mentoring on self-reflection and competence in Final year medical students' internal medicine rotation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Active mentoring had little to no effect on self-reflection and insight of final year medical students in Germany in the setting of an 8-week rotation. Interventional learning studies were well accepted, and participation rate was high. However, form completion rates were low. Future studies should focus on increasing form completion rates through additional incentives.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Density Polyethylenes with Dual Degradability Enabled by In-Chain Photolyzable and Mechanoresponsive Units]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyethylenes are the most widely produced plastics but are also major pollutants due to their exceptional chemical stability. Developing environmentally friendly alternatives that can simultaneously respond to multiple degradation triggers to replace conventional polyolefins is desirable. Herein, a novel class of high-density polyethylene materials that degrade upon exposure to light irradiation and mechanical force is reported. This dual degradability is achieved by incorporating in-chain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex differences in the redox response to fine particulate matter (PM<sub>2.5</sub>) air pollution protects female mice against metabolic and cardiac injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fine particulate matter (PM(2.5)) exposure increases the cardiometabolic disease risk. While there is extensive research on how PM(2.5) impairs cardiometabolic health in male mice, its health impact is largely unexplored in females. To examine PM(2.5)-induced cardiometabolic effects in females, female and male mice (n = 10/group) on a regular (12 h:12 h, RLC) or disturbed (18 h:6 h, DLC) light-dark cycle were exposed to concentrated ambient PM(2.5) (CAP) for 30 days. In females, CAP exposure...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rheumatoid arthritis: emerging insights into molecular mechanisms and targeted immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a chronic, systemic, autoimmune inflammatory disease that characterised by persistent synovial joints inflammation, which ultimately results in progressive joint destruction and significant disability. Ineffective drug treatment for severe arthritis can lead to significant physical disability and a marked decline in quality of life. Recent research has significantly advanced our understanding of the underlying molecular mechanisms of RA, which leads to the emergence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world outcomes of rituximab- and cyclophosphamide-based induction therapy regimens alone and in combination over 24 months in ANCA-associated vasculitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RTX alone was similarly effective to RTX/CYC combination and CYC-AZA therapy in AAV patients, including those with severe renal involvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PRIME 2.0: An Update to The Proposed Requirements for Cardiovascular Imaging-Related Machine Learning Evaluation Checklist]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The PRIME 2.0 checklist is an updated, domain-specific framework designed to standardize the development, evaluation, and reporting of artificial intelligence (AI) applications in cardiovascular imaging. This update specifically responds to rapid advances from traditional machine learning to deep learning, large language models, and multimodal generative AI. The updated checklist was developed through a modified Delphi process by an international panel of clinical and technical experts. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colchicine and Longitudinal Dynamics of Clonal Hematopoiesis: An Exploratory Substudy of the LoDoCo2 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this exploratory analysis, treatment with low-dose colchicine was associated with attenuated clonal expansion in TET2 CH. These findings suggest the potential for colchicine to curb the proliferative advantage of key CH driver mutations and mitigate their associated risk of cardiovascular disease. Further validation in prospective studies is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Tad Bit of Extra Clarity About Clots: Why JACC Took Interest in TADCLOT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Effects and Tolerability of GLP-1 Receptor Agonists: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of 99,592 patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GLP-1 RAs reduce mortality and MACE in high-risk populations, highlighting benefits beyond glycemic control. These come at increased GI and gallbladder risks. Variation in efficacy and tolerability supports tailoring GLP-1 RA therapy to individual patient characteristics and treatment goals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anthropometric Measures, Cardiovascular Outcomes, and Treatment Effects of Finerenone in Cardiovascular-Kidney-Metabolic Disease: Pooled Participant-Level Analysis of Three Global Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest assessment of anthropometrics capturing abdominal adiposity, in addition to BMI, may enhance obesity identification and risk stratification among individuals with CKM conditions. Finerenone consistently reduced adverse cardiovascular outcomes across a wide range of adiposity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Narrative simulation of financial scarcity: Effects on delay discounting, cigarette craving, and cigarette demand in adults who smoke cigarettes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Financial scarcity is associated with greater delay discounting and cigarette smoking. In experimental research, narrative simulation of scarcity increases delay discounting, but the effects of simulated scarcity on smoking behaviors have not yet been examined. In an online survey study, we examined the effects of scarcity narratives on delay discounting, cigarette craving, and behavioral economic demand for cigarettes. Adults who smoke cigarettes were randomized to read brief narratives...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICTV Virus Taxonomy Profile: <em>Duplodnaviria</em> 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The realm Duplodnaviria includes viruses of archaea, bacteria and eukaryotes, with linear dsDNA genomes. Duplodnavirians share a distinct morphogenetic module of four hallmark genes encoding the HK97-fold major capsid protein, a genome packaging ATPase-nuclease (large terminase subunit), a portal protein and a capsid maturation protease. This is a summary of the International Committee on Taxonomy of Viruses (ICTV) Report on the realm Duplodnaviria, which is available at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parents' multimodal spatial language structures infants' in-the-moment attention during spatial play]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We asked how caregivers use spatial language and deictic gestures, in addition to object labeling, with their infants during spatial play, and how such spatial multimodal input scaffolds infants' in-the-moment attention. Forty-nine North American middle-class racially and ethnically diverse caregivers (four fathers, 45 mothers; 51% White and not Hispanic) and their 9-month-old infants (15 girls, 34 boys; 43% White and not Hispanic) played with a puzzle while wearing head-mounted eye trackers....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing difficulties in regulating negative and positive emotions: The Difficulties in Emotion Regulation Scale-Expanded (DERS-X)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Negative and positive emotion regulation are important to psychological well-being. However, most individual-difference measures of emotion regulation focus primarily or exclusively on negative emotion regulation. In the present research, we sought to expand the widely used Difficulties in Emotion Regulation Scale (DERS) by including items assessing positive as well as negative emotion regulation. In Studies 1 and 2, we evaluated the new DERS-Expanded (DERS-X) with Chinese student and clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between bisphenol A exposure and dental caries in U.S. population: insights from the NHANES survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human exposure to bisphenol A (BPA) primarily occurs through diet, but its impact on oral health, especially dental caries, remains underexplored. Data from a nationally representative sample of 5,566 participants aged 12-65 years were analyzed. Dental caries were assessed using the Decayed, Missing, and Filled Teeth (DMFT) and Decayed, Missing, and Filled Surfaces (DMFS) indices, while BPA exposure was measured via urine concentrations adjusted for creatinine. Statistical methods including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SLC6A8-mediated creatine uptake suppresses ERK2-FSP1 signaling and induces ferroptosis in colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor metabolic reprogramming is critical for providing energy to support proliferation and resistance to stress-induced cell death. However, the regulatory mechanisms linking these processes remain incompletely understood. Here, using untargeted metabolomics, we demonstrate that creatine potently induces ferroptosis in colorectal cancer (CRC). Mechanistically, creatine binds extracellular signal-regulated kinase 2 (ERK2), impairing its activation by mitogen-activated protein kinase kinase 1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Left ventricular hypertrophy and myocardial fibrosis in heart failure with preserved ejection fraction: mechanisms and treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heart failure with preserved ejection fraction (HFpEF) accounts for nearly half of all heart failure cases and is characterized by phenotypical heterogeneity with a high prevalence of multiple, often overlapping cardiometabolic disorders. Comorbidities such as hypertension, obesity, or diabetes are present in many HFpEF patients and are hypothesized to contribute to adverse cardiac remodelling and myocardial fibrosis through a variety of haemodynamic and metabolic impairments, with nearly half...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebrospinal fluid flow modulates brain health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cerebrospinal fluid dynamics play an important role in maintaining brain health and clearing metabolic waste from the brain. In this issue of the JCI, Gursky et al. investigate how CSF distribution is affected when its primary efflux pathway - the deep cervical lymph nodes - is disrupted by cauterization. This timely study reveals compensatory fluid drainage routes from the skull, age-dependent adaptations in CSF homeostasis, and the emergence of neuroinflammation when an efflux pathway is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maladaptive trained immunity in viral infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trained immunity (TRIM) is a form of long-lasting functional reprogramming of innate immune cells and their progenitors that enhances responsiveness to subsequent stimuli. Although first characterized in myeloid cells, TRIM was recently extended to nonmyeloid cell types, including endothelial and glial cells, which also exhibit stimulus-driven, memory-like behavior. While initially recognized as a protective mechanism, particularly in the context of vaccines and acute infections, TRIM can also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Letter:</em> The Use of the Terms Biorepository and Biobank as Working Definition for the Virtual Biorepository System: Reply from the Authors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing HIV Genotyping and Drug-Resistance Detection in Low Viral Load Samples Through Exosome Enrichment Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genotypic drug-resistance testing for HIV-1 with low viral loads (VLs) (<1,000 copies/mL) is clinically important but technically challenging. Due to the overlapping physical size characteristics of HIV-1 viral particles (100-120 nm) and exosomes (40-150 nm), simultaneous enrichment of both using size separation technology may offer a new strategy to improve the success rate of genotypic resistance testing in low VL samples. To evaluate the application of exosome enrichment technology in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-free DNA methylomics identify tissue injury patterns in pediatric ARDS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidermal Growth Factor Receptor Activation Stimulates SOX9 Expression in Injured Renal Proximal Tubule Epithelial Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EGFR activation is crucial for SOX9 expression in RPTCs following AKI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intermittent ischemia-reperfusion as a potent insulin-sensitizing intervention via blood flow enhancement and muscle Decanoyl-L-carnitine suppression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A single bout of exercise improves muscle insulin sensitivity for up to 48 hours via the AMP-activated protein kinase (AMPK). Limb ischemia activates AMPK in muscle, and subsequent reperfusion enhances insulin-stimulated vasodilation, potentially eliciting a more pronounced exercise effect with reduced workload. Here, we investigated the combined effect of upper leg intermittent ischemia-reperfusion (IIR) and continuous knee-extension exercise on muscle insulin sensitivity regulation. We found...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of a Specialized Large Language Model with GPT-4o for CT and MRI Radiology Report Summarization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Although the general-purpose large language model (LLM) GPT-4o (OpenAI) has shown promise in radiology language processing, it remains unclear whether the performance of GPT-4o in report summarization is better than that of an LLM specifically designed for this task. Purpose To compare the performance of a specialized LLM with that of GPT-4o in the comprehensive summarization of radiology reports. Materials and Methods A specialized LLM for report summarization (LLM-RadSum) was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional characterization of the plastidial enzyme GPAT in microalgae and its potential role in lipid biosynthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microalgae are a rich source of high-value natural products. The green microalga Chlamydomonas reinhardtii has long been used as a model organism for studying lipid metabolism in photosynthetic organisms. Here, we comprehensively characterized the enzymatic activity and substrate preferences of the plastidial glycerol-3-phosphate:acyl-CoA acyltransferase (GPAT1) from C. reinhardtii. Our results revealed that, in addition to GPAT activity, recombinant GPAT1 is associated with lysophosphatidic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global Uptake of GLP-1 Receptor Agonists in Obese, Non-Diabetic Patients with Cardiovascular Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recommended practices for vision screening in pre-school-age children: A 2025 update]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The NCCVEH recommends that children aged 3 to <6 years have their vision screened annually to identify potential eye health and vision disorders. These updated vision screening recommendations provide lay screeners with a standardized approach for detecting vision problems and ensuring timely intervention and treatment. The NCCVEH will continue to provide vision screening updates at http://nationalcenter.preventblindness.org.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolite Fusion between Breath and Blood Enables More In-Depth Understanding of the Endogenous Metabolome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Blood is a widely used sample type in metabolomics but often loses volatile compounds during analysis. In contrast, exhaled breath offers a noninvasive and complementary matrix that retains these volatiles. However, the accuracy of metabolite identification in breath remains a key challenge. To address this, we developed and integrated three novel strategies to enhance the characterization of the human metabolome: (1) a controlled exercise protocol was applied to capture biologically relevant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Two Novel HIV-1B/CRF01_AE/CRF07_BC Recombinant Forms Among Men Who Have Sex with Men in Hebei Province, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The frequent recombination between subtypes has driven significant HIV-1 genetic diversity in recent years, especially in some areas with co-circulation of multiple subtypes. In this study, we obtained nearly full-length genome sequences of two novel HIV-1 B/CRF01_AE/CRF07_BC recombinants from BD076A and BDL161, with lengths of 8718 bp (HXB2:772-9490) and 8851 bp (HBB2:759-9610), respectively. Both recombination breakpoint and Bootscanning analysis revealed that the recombinant structure of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opioid Timeliness in the Emergency Department and Hospitalizations for Acute Sickle Cell Pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This cross-sectional study found that timely receipt of opioids was associated with a reduction in hospitalizations for SCD pain. The largest decrease in hospitalization was achieved with the first dose within 60 minutes and the second dose within 30 minutes; however, longer second-dose durations were associated with reduced hospitalizations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Approach for Preventing Respiratory Virus Infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peer Coaching to Support Weight Management in Primary Care: A Cluster Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this randomized clinical trial, a low- to moderate-intensity peer-coaching intervention did not result in greater weight loss at 12 months, but it improved attendance at weight management programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Behavioral Economic Framing for Enrollment and Retention of Patients in Remote Blood Pressure Monitoring: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this randomized clinical trial, the behavioral economic approach of opt-out framing vs opt-in framing did not improve enrollment and retention of patients in a remote BP monitoring program. The findings suggest additional approaches are needed to boost participation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chiles v Salazar-Conversion Effort Bans and Free Speech]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel CHRM3-Driven Preclinical Model of Irritable Bowel Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Irritable bowel syndrome (IBS) is a prevalent functional gastrointestinal disorder that significantly reduces patients' quality of life. However, current animal models have limitations in replicating the complex pathophysiology of IBS. In this study, we successfully developed a mouse model by mating intestinal epithelium-specific Cre tool mice with chemically modified human muscarinic acetylcholine receptor 3 (hCHRM3) mice, resulting in specific expression of the hCHRM3 in the intestinal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Preclinical evaluation of glycan-targeting monoclonal antibodies for bimodal near-infrared fluorescence and photoacoustic imaging of gastrointestinal cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micrometastasis and Isolated Tumor Cells in Oral Squamous Cell Carcinoma: Refining Nodal Staging with Emerging Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Accurate identification and interpretation of micrometastasis and ITCs in OSCC represent an evolving frontier in head and neck oncology. Future staging systems should incorporate these elements supported by standardized protocols and high-level evidence. The integration of AI, molecular diagnostics, and radiomics holds the potential to enhance risk stratification and personalize surgical decision-making, reducing overtreatment while ensuring oncologic safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[iThermonitor: A wearable non-invasive high-precision alternative to traditional temperature monitoring in thoracoscopic surgery of lateral decubitus position]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delivery of monoclonal antibodies to the brain: the impact of nanocarrier structure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) are promising therapeutic agents for neurological disorders due to their high specificity. However, their clinical application is significantly hindered by their poor transport across the blood-brain barrier (BBB) and their limited diffusion within the brain parenchyma. While significant efforts have been oriented to tackle the first barrier, the challenge of efficient brain diffusion remains largely underexplored. To address this, we have developed and evaluated two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing Heavy Metals using ICP-MS in Fruits from the Developing World and their Associated Health Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates heavy metal contamination across ten fruit varieties cultivated in Rampal and assesses the potential health risks associated with their consumption. Eight metals-Fe, Cu, Cd, Zn, Cr, Mn, Pb, and As were analyzed using an inductively coupled plasma mass spectrometer. Health risk indicators, including estimated daily intake (EDI), target hazard quotient (THQ), hazard index (HI), and cumulative carcinogenic risk (CR), were employed. All EDI values were below the maximum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic Dissection of Rice Plant-Specific Non-ε Group 14-3-3 Proteins in Response to Phosphate Starvation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The 14-3-3 proteins are highly conserved and widely distributed across eukaryotes. Some 14-3-3 proteins have been identified as regulators of phosphorus (Pi) deficiency tolerance in rice, but their diverse functions remain largely unexplored. In this study, we characterized the role of rice plant-specific non-ε group 14-3-3 proteins (OsGF14a-f) in response to Pi starvation by mutating these genes. We found that the expression of OsGF14a decreased in response to Pi starvation, while the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Author Reflections: Predictors of Unrecovered Early Post-Discharge Pain after Thoracoscopic Sublobar Resection for Stage IA Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psoriatic arthritis incidence and prevalence trajectory in Poland-public-payer, national-level, long-term data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To estimate the actual incidence and prevalence of psoriatic arthritis (PsA) within a 9-year timeframe in Poland. Patients were defined as having PsA if they had at least two visits more than 90 days apart with ICD-10 codes M07.0, M07.1, M07.2, M07.3, or L40.5 and filled at least one reimbursed prescription for peripheral or axial PsA-specific treatments during this period (including methotrexate, sulfasalazine, ciclosporin, leflunomide, biologics, targeted synthetic drugs, or non-steroidal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular risk in axial spondyloarthritis: the interplay of inflammation, traditional risk factors, and management strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiovascular (CV) morbidity and mortality pose major challenges in patients with axial spondyloarthritis (AxSpA), a chronic inflammatory disorder that includes both radiographic and non-radiographic forms. Patients with AxSpA have heightened CV morbidity and mortality, mainly attributable to systemic inflammation and typical CV risk factors like hypertension, hyperlipidemia, diabetes, and obesity. Subclinical atherosclerosis frequently manifests independently of conventional risk factors and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The transcriptional regulation of NUPR1 expression by MYC is implicated in the regulation of ferroptosis in human spermatogonial stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-obstructive azoospermia (NOA) is a leading cause of male infertility, characterized by impaired spermatogenesis. Recent studies suggest that ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of cell death, may contribute to testicular dysfunction, however, its role in NOA remains underexplored. In this study, we investigated the roles of NUPR1 and MYC in regulating ferroptosis in human spermatogonial stem cells (SSCs) and evaluated their potential as therapeutic targets for NOA. Single-cell RNA sequencing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of changes in the trabecular bone of patients with bruxism: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The present review revealed a relationship between bruxism and mandibular bone remodeling, with variations related to sex and age. However, the meta-analysis found no structural differences in the condyle or gonion between individuals with and without bruxism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the role of VAV2 rare variants in primary open-angle glaucoma: genetic insights and pathophysiological mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary open-angle glaucoma (POAG) is the leading cause of irreversible blindness worldwide, primarily due to the degeneration of retinal ganglion cells (RGCs). In this study, we reported vav guanine nucleotide exchange factor 2 (VAV2) as a POAG-associated gene. Through whole exome sequencing (WES) of 398 Han Chinese POAG patients and 2,010 controls, we discovered nine rare VAV2 variants linked to POAG (P_burden=1.40×l0^(-6)). Functional analyses revealed that these variants disrupted normal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of One of the Most Commonly Used Probiotic Strains: Systematic Review and Meta-analysis of Reported Adverse Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Probiotics are defined as live microorganisms that, when administered in adequate amounts, confer a health benefit on the host. Probiotics are widely used in everyday foods and supplements but very few studies have thoroughly evaluated safety. We evaluated adverse events (AEs) for one of the most widely used strains, Bifidobacterium animalis subsp. lactis (BB-12). A systematic review (SR) and meta-analysis (MA) were conducted to evaluate adverse events in human trials using BB-12. Two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DICER1-Related Pediatric Thyroid Neoplasm with Follicular and Morular Growth: A Tumor that Did Not Read the Textbook]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thyroid lesions associated with DICER1 syndrome include multifocal hyperplastic and benign neoplastic proliferations (follicular nodular disease) with characteristic macrofollicular and/or intrafollicular centripetal papillary growth patterns, frequently associated with atrophic and involutional changes. There are also well-differentiated thyroid carcinomas showing intermediate-type nuclei, sometimes combining high-grade areas (tumor-in-tumor pattern) and poorly differentiated carcinomas. Here,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coltsfoot (<em>Tussilago farfara</em> L.; Asteraceae): modern methods of extraction, phytochemistry, nanoparticles synthesis, ethnopharmacology, and biological activities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tussilago farfara L. (Asteraceae), commonly known as coltsfoot, is a widely recognised medicinal plant, traditionally used for treating respiratory, digestive, and circulatory ailments. Its therapeutic potential is attributed to a diverse phytochemical profile comprising alkaloids, flavonoids, and terpenoids, which contribute to its reported neuroprotective, anti-inflammatory, antioxidant, and anticancer activities. Recent studies have also exhibited the plant's utility in the green synthesis of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250902152356&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>