<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 07:40:13 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Family structure, adolescent mental health, and the role of advisors in the cultural and social context of South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prior research consistently reports differences in mental health outcomes among adolescents between intact and non-intact families, highlighting the need to address these disparities. This study aims to investigate the moderating effect of advisers (counselors, teachers, or friends) on the mental health of adolescents from non-intact families. We conducted a cross-sectional study using data from the 2017 Korea Youth Risk Behavior Web-Based Survey, a large, representative nationwide sample of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical frequency comb integration in radio telescopes: advancing signal generation and phase calibration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Very long baseline interferometry (VLBI) enables high-angular-resolution observations in astronomy and geodesy by synthesizing a virtual telescope with baselines spanning hundreds to thousands of kilometres. Achieving high instrumental phase stability in VLBI relies on the generation of high-quality, atomic-referenced RF local oscillator (LO) and RF-comb signals for the effective downconversion of celestial RF signals and precise phase calibration, respectively. As observing frequencies move...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid tungsten oxyselenide/graphene electrodes for near-lossless 2D semiconductor phase modulators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optical phase modulators are critical components in integrated photonics, but conventional designs suffer from a trade-off between modulation efficiency and optical loss. Two-dimensional materials like graphene offer strong electro-optic effects, yet their high optical absorption at telecom wavelengths leads to significant insertion losses. Although monolayer transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDs) provide exceptional telecom-band transparency for low-loss electro-refractive response, their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment nonresponders in lupus nephritis characteristically exhibit persistent type I interferon signalling in monocytes: a longitudinal single-cell transcriptomic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that persistent IFN-I-driven gene expression in monocytes characterises treatment resistance in LN. Our findings suggest that early transcriptional profiling may enable timely identification of nonresponders and warrant further investigation in larger, independent cohorts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic effects of ultrasonic and pH adjustment on sustainable gold bioleaching from waste printed circuit boards]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gold (Au) recovery from waste printed circuit boards (WPCBs) is a growing focus in sustainable resource management, with bioleaching emerging as an environmentally friendly alternative to conventional methods. However, its efficiency remains limited. This study investigates the enhancement of Au bioleaching from WPCBs using Chromobacterium violaceum through the combined application of ultrasonic treatment and alkaline conditions. Initial findings confirm that ultrasonic irradiation significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[1-oxa-3,7-diazaspiro[4.5]decan-2-one derivatives as potent KRAS-G12D inhibitors: A multidisciplinary approach integrating machine learning, synthesis, and biological evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oncogenic RAS mutations, which are common in human tumors and occur in about 30 % of cancer cases, present significant challenges to effective cancer treatment. Among the KRAS family, the KRAS-G12D mutation is a promising target for treating different types of cancer. Current approaches to inhibit the KRAS-G12D mutation have shown limited success, highlighting the urgent need for innovative therapies. In this study, we employed machine learning, followed by scaffold and core hopping...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>225</sup>Ac-NOTA-trastuzumab human dosimetry using inter-radionuclide and biological half-life based allometric extrapolation method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Healthcare Expenditures Among Individuals With and Without Long COVID in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long COVID increases healthcare utilization, yet differences in healthcare spending patterns between individuals with and without long COVID remain poorly characterized, especially at the national level. To evaluate differences in healthcare expenditures among U.S. adults with and without long COVID using nationally representative data. This cross-sectional study analyzed data from the 2022 Medical Expenditure Panel Survey (MEPS), including 16 762 unweighted adults (weighted population: 239 915...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Activity Recognition Dataset for Pedestrians with Mobility Disabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human activity recognition (HAR) provided several benefits to people without disabilities. Researchers have provided public HAR datasets and developed technologies based on these datasets. However, the activities of pedestrians with mobility disabilities have not been actively investigated because related datasets do not exist. In this study, we compile an HAR dataset comprising basic activities for people with and without mobility disabilities (including activity categories of still, walking,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Label-free mid-infrared dichroism-sensitive photoacoustic microscopy for histostructural analysis of engineered heart tissues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many biological tissues, such as cardiac muscle, tendons, and the cornea, exhibit highly organized microstructural alignment that is critical for mechanical and physiological functions. Disruptions in this structural organization are commonly associated with pathological conditions such as fibrosis, infarction, and cancer. However, conventional histological imaging techniques rely on immunofluorescence or histochemical staining, and they evaluate tissue alignment via non-physical 2D...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered resting-state sensorimotor network in patients with obsessive-compulsive disorder: An EEG study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that rsEEG-derived SMN alterations may reflect neurophysiological mechanisms of OCD and serve as candidate biomarkers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483883/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vivo high-throughput toxicity screening of brominated flame retardants using a Caenorhabditis elegans transcription factor RNAi platform]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brominated flame retardants (BFRs) such as tetrabromobisphenol A (TBBPA), hexabromocyclododecane (HBCDD), and decabromodiphenyl ethane (DBDPE) are extensively used in a variety of consumer products, including electronics, textiles, and furniture. However, their environmental persistence and potential for neurodevelopmental toxicity have raised increasing concern. Legacy compounds such as TBBPA and HBCDD are undergoing regulation or being phased out, while alternatives like DBDPE remain poorly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between cumulative low-income status and cardiovascular event incidence and mediating effect of engagement in health behaviour: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that interventions targeting engagement in health behaviour among population with cumulative low-income status may help prevent cardiovascular events and promote cardiovascular health equity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative performance evaluation of DRI and KIMS immunoassays for forensic drug screening in urine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid and reliable detection of illicit drugs such as methamphetamine and Δ9-tetrahydrocannabinol (THC) is critical in forensic toxicology. Immunoassay-based screening methods offer time-efficient alternatives to instrumental techniques, especially for high-throughput forensic applications. This study aims to comparatively evaluate the analytical performance of two widely used DRI and KIMS immunoassay platforms in detecting these drugs in human urine samples, with a focus on forensic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Residual Cardiovascular Biomarkers After Medical Therapy and Their Prognostic Implications Following Percutaneous Coronary Intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among medically treated patients following PCI, elevated fibrinogen levels were associated with adverse outcomes. Further studies are warranted to clarify these associations and to determine whether adjunctive therapies can improve outcomes in this high-risk group. (Gyeongsang National University Hospital [GNUH] Registry; NCT04650529).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantification of residual DNAPL within aquifer system using atmospheric noble gases and radon: Partitioning behavior and field application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dense non-aqueous phase liquids (DNAPLs) are characterized by low solubility and high density, leading to extensive groundwater contamination over both spatial and temporal scales. Identification of sources and quantification of residual DNAPL is therefore critical for designing effective remediation strategies. Radon has been widely used as a tracer for DNAPL quantification due to its preferential phase partitioning behavior towards DNAPL. Building on this concept, noble gases have been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical utility of longitudinal circulating tumor DNA analysis in metastatic colorectal cancer patients receiving palliative chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ctDNA analysis offers a non-invasive approach for comprehensive genomic profiling in mCRC. Its ability to monitor genetic alterations and predict clinical outcomes underscores its potential utility in guiding personalized treatment strategies and monitoring resistance in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacological transglutaminase 2 inhibition enhances temozolomide response in patient-derived glioblastoma tumorspheres]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fertility treatment and risk of non-gynecological cancer: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fertility medications may increase the risk of thyroid cancer while potentially reducing the risk of colorectal cancer in women with infertility. Given the small number of studies and their heterogeneity, these findings should be interpreted cautiously. Further research is needed to clarify these associations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Caregiver priorities and healthcare outcomes in a pediatric home care service for children with medical complexity: a quasi-experimental study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PHCS are associated with decreased healthcare utilization among CMC. Although caregivers reported high satisfaction with the PHCS, the identified unmet needs provide evidence for enhancing service quality and inform future intervention research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Bariatric Surgery on Gout Medication: a Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Over 3 years after BS, overall gout medication use in the BS group declined to a level comparable to that in controls, with a significantly higher ULT discontinuation rate. Discontinuation of acute gout medications did not differ significantly.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical validation of a voice-based AI tool for screening cognitive impairment: a prospective multicenter study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SPICK demonstrated clinically meaningful accuracy with acceptable usability, supporting its potential as an automated, voice-based screening tool for diverse clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orally Administered Nanoparticle Coacervate for Therapeutic Coating of Full Gastrointestinal Tract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral delivery of therapeutic nanoparticles offers a non-invasive approach for treating gastrointestinal diseases, but achieving localized and sustained mucosal exposure while avoiding systemic toxicity remains a major challenge. Here, a Sucralfate-based oral formulation is developed that incorporates therapeutic nanoparticles and transforms into a paste-like coacervate upon contact with intestinal fluid, uniformly coating the entire gastrointestinal tract within 6 h, and clearing through fecal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of the COVID-19 Pandemic on the Mortality of Traumatic Brain Injury Patients Transported by Emergency Medical Services]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this study was to investigate the effects of the COVID-19 pandemic on the mortality of traumatic brain injury (TBI) patients transported by emergency medical services (EMS). Adult TBI patients who were assessed and transported by EMS between January 2018 and December 2021 were analyzed. The main exposure was during the COVID-19 pandemic period at the time of the event. The primary outcome was in-hospital mortality. A total of 18 988 patients were analyzed. The in-hospital...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic tuning of Bloch modes in anisotropic phonon polaritonic crystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phonon polaritons, arising from the coupling of photons with lattice vibrations, enable light confinement on deeply subwavelength scales. Phonon polaritonic crystals (PoCs), leveraging these inherently low-dissipation excitations, have further shown exceptional potential for nanoscale light manipulation through engineered Bloch modes. Yet, their static nature has so far hindered dynamic modulation, thus limiting their adaptability for real-time applications. Here, we demonstrate in situ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large scale analysis of dataset and simulation biases in SLAM research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The performance of visual SLAM and localization methods is generally reported on famous datasets. These datasets are generally captured under human supervision and hence, are prone to human biases. In this work we expose two such biases (capture bias and negative world bias) in well-known SLAM datasets. Photo-realistic simulators provide a platform for gathering data without human supervision and hence human bias. However, not every simulator is suited for benchmarking visual localization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Afatinib exerts an inhibitory effect on T cell-mediated cytotoxicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adoptive T cell therapy has shown significant efficacy in cancer treatment, especially in hematologic malignancies, and is increasingly being explored for solid cancers. Combining T cell therapy with conventional treatments holds promise for enhancing therapeutic effects. In this study, we conducted an in vitro inhibitor screening to evaluate the effects of various inhibitors on T cell-mediated cytotoxic activity against cancer cells. Among the candidates, we identified afatinib as an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural barriers control the spatial extent of slow earthquake slip]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent seismological and geodetic observations have revealed shallow slow earthquakes on subduction megathrusts, offering an opportunity to explore the factors controlling megathrust slip. Identifying these controlling factors helps constrain the potential updip extent of future megathrust ruptures. Here, we investigate the factors controlling the spatial extent of shallow slow earthquakes by integrating tremor locations with uncertainty estimates, detailed bathymetry data, and multichannel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biofilms at work: what limits efficient consortia for industrial production?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biofilms, complex and structured microbial communities encased within extracellular polymeric substances, represent an emerging area of interest in bioprocesses for the production of value-added chemicals. The properties of biofilms offer potential benefits for productivity and cost efficiency, yet the implementation of pilot- and large-scale productive biofilm processes remains a challenge due to their structural, ecological, metabolic, and physicochemical complexities. This review analyzes the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolution of collicular cell types, circuits, and modulatory pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A recent comparative transcriptomics study by Liu et al. highlights that conserved neuronal identity and synaptic gene expression in the superior colliculus of mice, tree shrews, and humans coexist with species-specific differences in primary cilia. These findings indicate that conserved circuit architecture is accompanied with specializations in signaling compartments that modulate circuit function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Childhood oral health is associated with the incidence of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease in adulthood]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Within the limitations of this study, poor childhood oral health, particularly persistent or worsening dental caries and gingivitis, is associated with an increased risk of ASCVD in adulthood. These findings highlight the potential of early oral health interventions in reducing long-term cardiovascular risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between weekly amount of home-visit rehabilitation and changes in activities of daily living: A retrospective cohort study using home-visit nursing station records]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Increased average minutes per week of HR at 6 months is associated with an improvement in BI. This result suggests that an HR of 40 min/week may be insufficient to improve ADL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aβ plaques induce local pre-synaptic toxicity in human iPSC-derived neuron xenografts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Xenotransplantation enables the interrogation of human neuron-specific vulnerabilities to Alzheimer's pathology within a physiologically relevant in vivo context. While amyloid-beta (Aβ) is known to disrupt synaptic integrity, it remains uncertain whether the synaptotoxicity observed in vitro accurately models the disease. Here, we establish a xenotransplantation paradigm in which human neurons integrate into the brains of amyloid precursor protein (APP) transgenic mice that develop amyloid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of micronutrients on fertility and aneuploidy rates in human conceptions: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In order to make clinical recommendations based on uncertain evidence, a systematic review and meta-analysis on the influence of micronutrient supplementation on preclinical and clinical reproductive outcomes was undertaken. PubMed and Scopus were searched until 12 November 2024. Parallel-grouped intervention studies with women undergoing fertility treatment with micronutrient supplementation or addition of micronutrient to in-vitro maturation media were included. The primary outcomes were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knives Out-Rethinking the Learning Curve of Esophageal ESD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scurvy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zonisamide-induced pleural effusion and agranulocytosis: a case report of a rare adverse reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 69-year-old woman with Parkinson's disease (Hoehn and Yahr stage 1.0) developed dyspnea and fever five weeks after initiation of low-dose zonisamide. Laboratory tests revealed marked neutropenia and thrombocytopenia, and chest CT showed bilateral pleural effusion. All abnormalities resolved completely within ten days after discontinuation of zonisamide. To our knowledge, such a combination of agranulocytosis and pleural effusion associated with zonisamide has not been previously reported, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic use of 1,5-AG and HbA1c for early prediction of gestational diabetes: capturing BMI-dependent glycemic phenotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Combining 1,5-AG and HbA1c enhances early prediction of GDM by capturing complementary glycemic abnormalities linked to BMI-specific metabolic phenotypes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone fragility and atypical femoral fractures in SLE: role of disease activity, infection, and treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Despite a gradual reduction in GC dosage, many patients with longstanding SLE remain at elevated risk for fractures. The comparable frequencies of fragility fractures and AFF-related events highlight the clinical relevance of both complications. The prevention of SLE flares and infections may contribute to lowering the risk of fragility fractures. In addition, careful monitoring for AFF/LPT is warranted in patients receiving long-term BP and GC therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative study of the short-term outcomes of gastric cancer surgery between Japanese Gastric cancer association-certified and non-certified institutions: a retrospective cohort analysis using a national database in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Certified institutions demonstrated lower surgical mortality risks, highlighting the benefits of the certification system and the importance of institutional quality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes and recurrence patterns in pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma diagnosed at an early stage: insights from a multicenter cohort study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with early-stage PDAC exhibit a higher risk of remnant pancreatic recurrence than those with stage II disease. These findings underscore the importance of long-term pancreas-focused surveillance in early-stage PDAC to enable timely detection of late recurrence and potentially improve patients outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world outcomes of ustekinumab, vedolizumab, and tumor necrosis factor inhibitors in very-early-onset inflammatory bowel disease: a multi-center cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: UST and VDZ were effective and well tolerated even when used as second-line or subsequent therapies for VEO-IBD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serramyuines A-C, new skeletal C<sub>27</sub>N<sub>3</sub>-type Lycopodium alkaloids from Lycopodium serratum Thunb. var. serratum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whole-genome sequencing identified a deep intronic COL4A5 variant causing aberrant splicing in a female patient with X-linked Alport syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alport syndrome is an inherited kidney disease caused by pathogenic variants in COL4A3, COL4A4, or COL4A5, encoding type IV collagen chains of the glomerular basement membrane. Genetic confirmation is essential for its diagnosis, prognosis, and donor selection; however, conventional sequencing may fail to detect pathogenic variants, leaving a subset of clinically suspected patients without a genetic diagnosis. We report a 16-year-old girl with persistent hematuria and proteinuria, initially...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase-specific impact of patient anatomy on rectal cancer surgery: robotic assistance neutralizes dissection difficulty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the T1w/FLAIR ratio as a proxy for myelin: Associations with myelin water Imaging, diffusion metrics, and cognition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results support the interpretation of T1w/FLAIR ratio as a general marker of tissue health rather than a specific measure for myelin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of Electroconvulsive Therapy in Invasive Motor Cortex Stimulation: A Case Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs versus acetaminophen and risk of venous thromboembolism: An active comparator new user cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although new NSAID users had a lower incidence of VTE than new acetaminophen users, they had a higher incidence compared with non-users. Assuming that acetaminophen does not increase VTE risk, these findings suggest that NSAIDs themselves may not increase VTE risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunomodulatory effects of primed amniotic fluid-derived mesenchymal stem/stromal cells with IFN-γ from unexplained recurrent miscarriage sources]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The immunomodulatory properties of mesenchymal stem/stromal cells (MSCs) are strongly influenced by IFN-γ priming and may vary depending on their tissue of origin. This study investigates whether the immunoregulatory responses of human amniotic fluid-derived MSCs (hAF-MSCs) to IFN-γ are altered when derived from individuals with unexplained recurrent pregnancy loss (RPL). We analyzed 10 well-characterized hAF-MSC clones, equally divided into non-RPL and RPL groups, to assess IFN-γ-induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inverse correlation between plasma pyrophosphate hydrolysis and early growth of abdominal aortic aneurysm: a pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) is often associated with vascular calcification, the calcium-phosphate crystal deposition in the aortic wall, which could impact aneurysm progression and/or stability. Tissue-nonspecific alkaline phosphatase (TNAP) hydrolyzes pyrophosphate-a natural inhibitor of calcification-thereby promoting calcium deposition. This study analyzes phosphatase activity and pyrophosphate dynamics in the plasma of AAA patients, randomly selected from the whole VIVA cohort,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal analysis of neutralizing antibodies against SARS-CoV-1 and different SARS-CoV-2 strains in breakthrough and unvaccinated COVID-19 patients in Thailand (2021-2022)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of SARS-CoV-2 variants that evade immune responses poses challenges to effective prevention. We prospectively enrolled 111 COVID-19 patients in Thailand (2021-2022), who received homologous or heterologous vaccines or were unvaccinated. Plasma neutralizing antibody (nAb) levels against SARS-CoV-1 and 13 SARS-CoV-2 strains were measured using a multiplex surrogate virus neutralization test (sVNT) assay within a year. nAb levels increased in two weeks, showing strong inhibition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional assessment of protein variants in structured domains by fluorescence cross-correlation spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the expanding catalogue of novel disease-genes, there is an increasing need to establish the significance of potential disease-causing variants. Based on the idea that pathogenic variants in structured protein domains disturb folding and association with macromolecular assemblies, we employed Fluorescence Correlation and Cross-Correlation Spectroscopy (FCS and FCCS) to assess in vivo protein complex formation. Since the molecular underpinning of BRCA-associated breast and ovarian cancers is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: The cold-induced lipokine 12,13-diHOME promotes fatty acid transport into brown adipose tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A new form of diabetes caused by INS mutations defined by zygosity, stem cell and population data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The INS c.16 C > T (insulin p.Arg6Cys, R6C) variant was reported to cause autosomal dominant monogenic diabetes, yet its pathogenicity has been questioned. R6C preproinsulin exhibits impaired translocation into the endoplasmic reticulum (ER). We explored R6C pathogenicity using integrative clinical, genetic, and functional approaches.Homozygous INS R6C individuals presented early-onset insulin-treated diabetes, whereas heterozygous carriers showed variable or absent glycemic phenotypes....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Out of distribution detection with attention head masking for multimodal document classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Detecting out-of-distribution (OOD) data is critical for ensuring the reliability and safety of deployed machine learning systems by mitigating model overconfidence and misclassification. While existing OOD detection methods primarily focus on uni-modal inputs, such as images or text, their effectiveness in multi-modal settings, particularly documents, remains underexplored. Moreover, most approaches prioritize decision mechanisms over optimizing the underlying dense embedding representations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating single-cell and bulk transcriptomes identifies B cell features associated with neoadjuvant chemoradiotherapy sensitivity in rectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant chemoradiotherapy (nCRT) is the main treatment for Locally Advanced Rectal Cancer (LARC). The response to nCRT varies from a complete response to no response. The impact of the B cells in this process is poorly understood. This study aimed to characterize the B cells types associated with response or resistance to nCRT. We applied the "Scissor" algorithm to integrate single-cell RNA-seq data with bulk transcriptome data from colorectal cancer samples, thereby identifying B cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning models predict long COVID outcomes based on baseline clinical and immunologic factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Machine learning models identify patients at risk for developing long COVID based on baseline clinical characteristics. These models guide early interventions, improve patient outcomes, and mitigate the long-term public health impacts of SARS-CoV-2.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10,000 years of centennially-resolved climate and sea-level change archived in Svalbard beach-ridge system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus expert recommendations for referral of Parkinson's disease patients for deep brain stimulation surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deep brain Stimulation (DBS) surgery effectively alleviates troublesome motor symptoms of Parkinson's disease (PD) such as tremor, rigidity, bradykinesia, motor fluctuations and dyskinesia. It also improves some non-motor symptoms and quality of life. DBS should thus be considered when these symptoms interfere with quality of life despite optimal medical treatment. While DBS benefits are clear, access by eligible patients remains low. Patients and their caregivers should be educated regarding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multi-objective optimization-driven screening approach for maximizing hydrogen storage capacities in MOFs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The inherent tradeoff between gravimetric and volumetric hydrogen storage capacities in metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) limits their commercial viability. While benchmarked MOFs like MOF-5, IRMOF-20, and PCN-610 perform well at 77 K, maintaining their performance at elevated temperatures (298 K) remains challenging. To address this, a multi-objective particle swarm optimization framework was developed to identify promising MOFs for hydrogen storage. The optimization was guided by predictions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peripheral inflammation mediates cognitive deficits in drug-naive schizophrenia through hippocampal-thalamo-visual circuitry dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Converging evidence indicates that dysregulated cortico-subcortical connectivity underpins core cognitive impairment in schizophrenia (SCZ). However, the mechanistic basis linking this disrupted brain function to cognitive deficits remains elusive. We hypothesized that dysfunction within the hippocampal-thalamocortical circuitry mediates the impact of peripheral inflammation on cognitive deficits in SCZ. We recruited 62 drug-native patients with SCZ and 44 age and sex-matched healthy controls...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between second-generation antipsychotics and metabolic outcomes in patients with schizophrenia and metabolic abnormalities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Second-generation antipsychotics (SGAs) were found to have varying metabolic side-effects for patients with schizophrenia, while no studies have examined the associations between adding or switching low-risk SGAs and metabolic outcomes. This real-world observational study aimed to examine the association of adding or switching to low-risk SGAs with metabolic syndrome and metabolic abnormalities for patients with schizophrenia from 25 healthcare organizations across Zhejiang Province, China....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutralizing human monoclonal antibodies to poliovirus map to the receptor binding site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poliovirus remains a serious threat to human health. Complete eradication of wild-type poliovirus has not yet succeeded, making the development of successful antivirals critical. Microneutralization assays against all three poliovirus serotypes identified a panel of human monoclonal IgGs, which are either serotype-specific or cross-neutralizing. Here, through cryoEM single particle analysis, we solved high resolution structures of four distinct poliovirus-FAb complexes. These antibodies bind to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cycloreversion-enhanced toughness and degradability in mechanophore-embedded end-linked polymer networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enhancing the toughness while achieving triggerable degradation in single-network polymer systems without modifying their inherent chemical composition or network architecture remains a significant challenge. Here we demonstrate a smart end-linked polymer network that "self-strengthen" during use yet "self-destruct" upon certain stimuli. Embedding nonscissile cyclobutane-fused tetrahydrofuran mechanophores within the middle of end-linked polymer networks significantly enhances both toughness and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing general measurements in quantum Monte Carlo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum Monte Carlo is one of the most promising approaches for dealing with large-scale quantum many-body systems. It has played an extremely important role in understanding strongly correlated physics. However, two fundamental problems, namely the sign problem and general measurement issues, have seriously hampered its scope of application. We propose a universal scheme to tackle the problems of general measurement. The target observables are expressed as the ratio of two types of partition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A chromosome region linked to neurodevelopmental disorders influences locomotor behavior through sex-specific neural circuits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biological sex shapes the manifestation and progression of neurodevelopmental disorders (NDDs), however, the underlying mechanisms remains unclear. Hemideletion of the 16p11.2 region (16p11.2 del/+) is associated with NDDs, and 16p11.2 del/+ mice exhibit sex-specific, striatum-related phenotypes relevant to NDDs. In this study, using snRNA-seq, we identify cell type- and sex-specific transcriptomic changes in D1- and D2-spiny projection neurons (SPNs), with greater impact in males. Fiber...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel LC-MS/MS multi-group method for simultaneous determination of antimicrobial residues in legume-based alternative proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry (LC-MS/MS) method was developed and validated for the simultaneous analysis of three different classes of veterinary drugs-antibiotics, antifungals, and antiparasitics-in legume-based alternative protein samples, e.g. beans, peas, and nuts. The sample preparation process utilized a modified dilute-and-shoot (DnS) technique, achieving recoveries ranging from 72.08 to 108.11% for 18 of the 26 target analytes. The method demonstrated excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TheMeCat: Dataset of Thermocatalytic Conversion of CO<sub>2</sub> to Methanol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Data-driven materials discovery to accelerate the development of new catalysts for the green transition shows great promise, but requires machine-interpretable experimental data. For this purpose, we compiled the TheMeCat dataset for the thermocatalytic conversion of CO(2) to methanol. TheMeCat is curated from experimental literature sources, and designed for hybrid computational and experimental catalyst workflows. The dataset captures key catalyst features, process parameters, and methanol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunable enantioselective electrocatalytic functionalization of unactivated alkenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The tunable enantioselective functionalization of alkene feedstocks represents a highly desirable yet predominantly unresolved tactic for generating high-value scaffolds. Herein, we report a tunable enantioselective electrolytic system for dehydrogenative allylation, dehydrogenative alkenylation, and hydroalkylation reactions with identical substrates to afford structurally diverse products. This success hinges on the rational design of the stereoselective coupling of an electrogenerated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute exercise rewires the proteomic landscape of human immune cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The positive effect of exercise on the immune system is widely acknowledged, but the molecular response of immune cells to exercise remains largely unknown. Here, we perform mass-spectrometry-based proteomic analysis on peripheral blood mononuclear cells (PBMC) at a depth of >6000 proteins. Comparing high-intensity interval exercise (HIIE) and moderate-intensity continuous exercise (MICE), matched for time and workload, we identify versatile changes in the proteomic makeup of PBMCs and reveal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Possible liquid-nitrogen-temperature superconductivity driven by perpendicular electric field in the single-bilayer film of La<sub>3</sub>Ni<sub>2</sub>O<sub>7</sub> at ambient pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, high-temperature superconductivity (HTSC) is found in the La(3)Ni(2)O(7)/SrLaAlO(4) ultrathin film with critical temperature T(c) above the McMillan limit at ambient pressure (AP). It is eager to enhance T(c) of La(3)Ni(2)O(7) at AP. We propose that a perpendicular electric field strongly enhances T(c) in the single-bilayer film of La(3)Ni(2)O(7) at AP. Under electric field, the layer with lower potential energy will accept electrons flowing from the other layer to fill in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From the lens of early-career researchers: bridging science, technology, arts, and humanities to tackle antimicrobial resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial resistance (AMR) is a silent pandemic that presents a global challenge, urging researchers to develop innovative and transdisciplinary solutions. Our initiative aims to promote collaboration across science, engineering, economics, social sciences, and the arts to address the complex dimensions of AMR. We highlight the unique role of early-career researchers (ECRs) in advancing such cross-cutting approaches and conclude that empowering ECRs through equitable support and recognition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revitalizing T cells: breakthroughs and challenges in overcoming T cell exhaustion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[T cell exhaustion is a prevalent phenomenon in chronic infections and tumor microenvironments, severely compromising the effectiveness of antitumor and antiviral immunity. In recent years, there has been significant progress in understanding the underlying mechanisms of T cell exhaustion, including external factors and intrinsic cellular changes that drive this dysfunctional state. Key external factors such as persistent antigen exposure, immune checkpoint signaling, and the cytokine milieu, as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[tRNA m<sup>1</sup>A modification is essential for gut homeostasis and function of group 3 innate lymphoid cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Group 3 innate lymphoid cells (ILC3s) play crucial roles in maintaining intestinal homeostasis and defending against bacterial infections. However, the epigenetic mechanisms that regulate ILC3 responses are not well understood. In this study, we show that Trmt61a, the methyltransferase responsible for the m¹A58 tRNA modification, is predominantly expressed in ILC3s. We found that specific depletion of TRMT61A in ILC3s leads to dysregulated cell cycle and a reduction in cell numbers. Notably,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484094/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure insight into FtsZ function maintaining under acid stress of Streptococcus mutans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the acid resistance mechanism of S. mutans is crucial for preventing dental caries. FtsZ is the core protein for cell division in bacteria that can polymerize into Z-rings and drive cytokinesis. Our previous study revealed that the FtsZ in S. mutans (SmFtsZ) has higher self-assembly and GTPase activity under acidic stress, which may be responsible for acid resistance and cariogenesis of S. mutans. However, the functional structure mechanism of SmFtsZ under low pH conditions is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remodeling the tumor dormancy ecosystem to prevent recurrence and metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dormant tumor cells, major contributors to tumor recurrence and metastasis, are characterized by cell cycle arrest and reactivation potential. Tumor dormancy arises from the dynamic interplay between intrinsic tumor properties and extrinsic factors within the tumor ecosystem. This ecosystem operates at two distinct levels: the tumor microenvironment (TME) and the systemic macroenvironment (SME). Within the dormant TME, tumor cells engage in complex interactions with surrounding stromal cells,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamically reconfigurable topological routing in nonlinear photonic systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The propagation path of topologically protected states is bound to the interface between regions with different topology, and as such, the functionality of linear photonic devices leveraging these states is fixed during fabrication. Here, we propose a mechanism for dynamic control over a driven dissipative system's local topology, yielding reconfigurable topological interfaces and thus tunable paths for protected routing. We illustrate our approach in non-resonantly pumped polariton lattices,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A CD8αβ co-receptor modified to contain an intracellular CD28 signaling tail enhances TCR-engineered T cell function independent of solid-tumor-associated co-stimulatory ligands]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adoptive transfer of T cells engineered with tumor-specific T cell receptors (TCRs) has shown limited efficacy in solid tumors, hindered by insufficient persistence, tumor trafficking, and dependence on tumor-associated co-stimulatory ligands. In a phase I trial (NCT04639245) for patients with metastatic MAGE-A1-expressing tumors and adequate organ function; one participant received treatment, which was well-tolerated. In this case and NSG murine models, infusion of CD4/CD8 T cells co-expressing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stable Cu<sup>δ+</sup> sites derived from analogous rectifying interface in AgCu biphasic aerogels for efficient urea electrosynthesis at low potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Urea electrosynthesis through CO(2) and NO(3)^(-) coupling presents a promising alternative to energy-intensive industrial processes. However, intricate catalytic mechanisms and competitive reactions impede achieving high-efficiency C-N coupling. Herein, we constructed analogous rectifying interfaces in AgCu biphasic aerogels, by leveraging electronegativity difference to derive stable Cu^(δ+) active sites, which simultaneously promoted *NOH adsorption and *CO coverage, thereby improving C-N...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction Note: BICC1 drives pancreatic cancer progression by inducing VEGF-independent angiogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MCJ modulates mitochondrial ETC flux to promote lipid metabolism-driven enhancement of cell proliferation and migration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial metabolism plays a crucial role in cancer progression and is associated with effective channeling of electrons through Complex I. The ability to adapt this electron flow as per cellular demands is critical for energy homeostasis. Our observations suggest that proliferating cells regulate the electron entry point through alterations in the levels of Methylation-Controlled J-protein (MCJ). Elevated MCJ levels were found to promote aggressive proliferative and migratory phenotypes,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light management in monolithic all-perovskite tandem solar cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-perovskite tandem solar cells represent a promising strategy for breaking the Shockley-Queisser limits inherent in single-junction solar cells. Reasonable light management and optical design are necessary for all-perovskite tandem solar cells to improve power conversion efficiency. In this review, the recent progresses in light management for monolithic all-perovskite tandem solar cells are summarized comprehensively. The current-matching conditions, optical challenges, and potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peptide-functionalized membrane camouflage for endogenous H<sub>2</sub>S-induced photothermal immunotherapy of orthotopic colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The significant challenges pose by the high recurrence and metastasis rates of colorectal cancer (CRC) persist in its diagnosis and treatment. Activating innate immunity in CRC treatment has the potential to reduce drug resistance and side effects. Here, we develop a biomimetic platform by utilizing antimicrobial peptide-functionalized CRC cell membranes to encapsulate a cobalt-based metal-organic framework (C), hereby called peptide-functionalized camouflage C (PfCC). When injected into...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Untargeted breathomics identifies metabolic signatures of immune activity, intestinal integrity, and fatigue in systemic lupus erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first study to characterise the breath metabolome in SLE. VOC signatures reflected immunometabolic perturbations, oxidative stress, and gut barrier integrity. Breathomics may provide a noninvasive means to monitor disease activity and symptom burden in SLE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implications of fibrosis marker dynamics after hepatitis C cure: Insights from paired biopsies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Noninvasive fibrosis markers can be used at a low threshold to determine the stage of liver fibrosis, although their predictive performance decreases after HCV eradication.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strengthening Translational Pathways: The Need for Readiness and Fairness Assessment in Transfusion AI Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anomaly detection of screw loosening of different implant-abutment connection designs using resonance frequency analysis: An in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RFA combined with machine learning reliably detected screw loosening across various types of implant-abutment connections. This method offers a noninvasive, quantitative tool for the early detection of mechanical complications in implant dentistry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of predicted post-PCI FFR derived from coronary computed tomography angiography versus observed angiographic FFR: emerging concept of wireless end-to-end physiology-guided PCI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Predicted post-PCI FFR(CT) values derived from CCTA-based virtual PCI have an excellent correlation with observed post-PCI FFRangio values derived from invasive coronary angiography after stenting. These findings highlight the novel concept of wireless end-to-end physiology guided PCI, integrating pre-PCI FFR(CT) and post-PCI angiographic FFR as complementary tools.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modified splenic arteriovenous fistula creation at tail of transplanted pancreas prevents thrombosis in simultaneous pancreas-kidney transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liver diseases and low serum albumin as potential confounders in the association between low total cholesterol and elevated all-cause and cancer mortality: The Japan Multi-Institutional Collaborative Cohort (J-MICC) study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated all-cause and cancer mortality in low TC individuals was likely confounded by baseline liver diseases and serum albumin. Further research is needed to identify additional confounders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning Image Reconstruction Improves Image Quality in Dual-Low Dose Dual-Energy CT Portal Venography Compared to Adaptive Iterative Image Reconstruction Algorithm-Veo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DLIR substantially improves image quality in DE-CTPV compared with ASIR-V 50%, even when utilizing dual-low dose protocol. By providing consistent, high-quality imaging across multiple portal venous segments, DLIR may offers a safer and more reliable approach for preoperative evaluation and postoperative monitoring in liver transplantation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pupillary Reaction to Opioids on Awake Subjects: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pupillometry shows promise as an objective indicator of opioid effect and pain response, particularly in settings where subjective pain reporting may be limited or unreliable. However, its interpretation must account for patient-specific and clinical confounding factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Ultrasound-enhanced extraction unlocks superior functional properties and bioactive profles in Fucus vesiculosus proteins: A comprehensive characterization study" [International Journal of Biological Macromolecules, 311 (2025) 143913]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive validity of the Obsessive-Compulsive Inventory-4 and Florida Obsessive-Compulsive Inventory-II severity scale]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient and accurate screening tools are crucial for improving early identification and treatment outcomes among individuals with obsessive-compulsive disorder (OCD). This study evaluated the sensitivity and specificity of two OCD screening measures: the Obsessive-Compulsive Inventory-4 (OCI-4) and the Florida Obsessive-Compulsive Inventory-II (FOCI-II) severity scale. The measures were administered in a large transnational sample of Spanish speaking Latin American adults (N = 1696) with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lung injury associated with electronic cigarette use or vaping: A narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[EVALI is a rapidly developing toxic inhalation syndrome that has been linked to electronic cigarettes. It is characterized by a wide variety of radiological and histological patterns, with diffuse alveolar damage and acute respiratory distress syndrome being the most severe forms. This condition mainly affects young people and typically has a nonspecific clinical presentation. The diagnosis is one of exclusion, making it essential to thoroughly investigate into the medical history in order to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Major depressive disorder: susceptibility, underlying mechanisms, and emerging therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483978/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional insights into the nitrogenase-like enzyme superfamily]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogenases are the only enzymes capable of converting atmospheric nitrogen into bioavailable ammonia, an essential process for all life on Earth. Early ancestors of bona fide nitrogenases and their maturases gave rise to several structural homologues with diverse functions. The nitrogen fixation-like enzyme superfamily comprises ancient metalloproteins involved in elemental processes that range from the biosynthesis of bacteriochlorophyll in bacterial photosynthesis to the biosynthesis of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research progress on early biomarkers for occupational noise-induced hearing loss]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The group of works exposed to occupational noise worldwide is constanthy expanding, with hearing loss becoming a pressing issue that poses serious challenges to public health, economic and society. While current clinical diagnosis primarily relies on elevated hearing thresholds, detectable pre-decibel hearing loss damage has already occurred in the inner ear. Therefore, early biomarkers of noise-induced hearing loss are crucial for the early detection of noise-induced hearing loss and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpretation of GBZ 89-2024 "Diagnostic Standard for Occupational Mercury Poisoning"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The new version of GBZ 89-2024 "Diagnostic Standard for Occupational Mercury Poisoning" was issued on May 9, 2024 and implemented on May 1, 2025. This professional standard is a supporting of the "Law of the People's Republic of China on Prevention and Control of Occupational Diseases" and a mandatory national occupational health standard. This article interprets and expounds the background, revision process, main contents, difficulties and significance of the diagnostic criteria, to help...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The decline of lung function and risk factors analysis in patients with coal workers'pneumoconiosis complicated with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To investigate the decline of lung function and related risk factors in patients with coal workers' pneumoconiosis complicated with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) . Methods: In December 2022, a retrospective analysis was performed for coal workers' pneumoconiosis complicated with COPD who were admitted to Hunan Prevention and Treatment Institute for Occupational Disease from 2017 to 2018, and the demographic data, lung function, blood eosinophil value (EOS), smoking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of noise exposure levels at workplace positions in the national mining industry in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To understand the noise hazard levels at mining industry workplaces to provide a scientific basis for occupational disease prevention policies. Methods: The monitoring result data on occupational hazard factors in the workplace for 2023 were obtained from the National Surveillance System for Occupational Hazards during September to October 2024. Descriptive analysis was then conducted on the noise exposure results at workplace positions in mining industry enterprises, categorized by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483941/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of occupational stress risk factors and risk prediction research for female coal miners]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To analyze the risk factors of occupational stress among female coal miners and construct a risk prediction model. Methods: In July 2023, a cluster sampling method was conducted to select all female workers on duty at a large coal mine in Gansu Province during a specific period (totaling 1437 individuals) as research subjects. Occupational stress levels were assessed through questionnaire surveys. A total of 1435 valid questionnaires were collected, with an effective recovery rate of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483940/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of dust monitoring results of enterprises in the national mining industry in 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To grasp the concentration levels of coal dust, silica dust and other dusts in the workplaces of employers in the national mining industry in 2023, and to identify the key points for occupational disease prevention and control. Methods: In December 2024, the concentrations of coal dust, silica dust and other dusts in the workplaces of 7903 mining enterprises across the country in 2023 were analyzed. Methods such as Kruskal-Wallis H rank sum test and Chi-square test were used to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meta-analysis of influencing factors on the progression of pneumoconiosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: Meta-analysis was performed to determine the influencing factors on the progression of pneumoconiosis, providing a basis for optimizing prevention and treatment strategies for pneumoconiosis. Methods: The research date was from April 10(th), 2025 to May 5(th), 2025, PubMed, Embase, Web of Science, CNKI, VIP Chinese Science and Technology Journal Database, Wanfang and other Chinese and English databases were searched, and the search time was from the establishment of the database to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meta-analysis of influencing factors of pulmonary tuberculosis in occupational pneumoconiosis patients in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To explore the influencing factors of pulmonary tuberculosis in occupational pneumoconiosis patients in China. Methods: In February 2025, through the CNKI, Wanfang, VIP databases, and PubMed, MedLine, Web of Science, and Embase databases (established up to February 25, 2025), we screened literature on the influencing factors of occupational pneumoconiosis patients with pulmonary tuberculosis in China. Fixed effect or random effect models were selected to analyze the impact of 10...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of influencing factors and intervention on work-related musculoskeletal disorders among fire rescue personnel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To investigate the factors influencing work-related musculoskeletal disorders (WMSDs) among fire rescue personnel and evaluate the effectiveness of a multidimensional intervention approach, in order to provide scientific evidence for the prevention of WMSDs among fire rescue personnel. Methods: A random sampling method was adopted. From March to November 2022, 5119 fire rescue personnel from 10 administrative districts of a certain city were investigated as the baseline research...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Annual progress in chronic obstructive pulmonary disease 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), as the third leading cause of death globally, continues to impose a growing disease burden and has become a major public health challenge. Over the past year, breakthrough progress has been made in the field of precision diagnosis and treatment. In screening and diagnosis, a multi-tiered screening system based on healthcare resource stratification has established a comprehensive pathway from questionnaire-based initial screening to simplified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical characteristics and genetic spectrum of adults with primary ciliary dyskinesia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To characterize the clinical features and genetic variant spectrum of adult patients with primary ciliary dyskinesia (PCD) in China and to explore phenotypic differences across distinct genotypes, with a focus on comparisons among commonly detected genetic variants. Methods: This study was a single-center, retrospective cohort investigation that enrolled 73 adult patients diagnosed with PCD at the Second Xiangya Hospital of Central South University between January 2015 and March 2025....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and genetic features of Chinese patients with Birt-Hogg-Dubé syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: To summarize the clinical and genetic characteristics of Chinese patients with Birt-Hogg-Dubé syndrome (BHD). Methods: We retrospectively analyzed the clinical data of patients diagnosed with BHD between January 1, 2015, and April 30, 2025, at Peking Union Medical College Hospital, Chinese Academy of Medical Science (Beijing center); the First Affiliated Hospital of USTC, University of Science and Technology of China (Hefei center); and the First Affiliated Hospital of Guangzhou...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current status and prospects of exploring the etiology of diffuse cystic lung disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The true prevalence of diffuse cystic lung diseases (DCLDs) in the Chinese population is not well understood. Current real-world estimates suggest that both the incidence and prevalence of these conditions are likely substantially underestimated. As healthcare professionals, it is imperative to enhance recognition of the etiological complexity of DCLDs and avoid attributing imaging findings solely to common entities such as bullae or emphysema. Multidisciplinary collaboration, integrating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current status and challenges of registry-based research on rare respiratory diseases in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Respiratory rare diseases are a category of conditions related to the respiratory system that have a low incidence rate. Patients with these diseases are at high risk of misdiagnosis or missed or delayed diagnosis during diagnosis and treatment, and the lack of effective treatment options can lead to a significant deterioration in their quality of life and increased risk of mortality. Conducting registry research on respiratory rare diseases can help outline the natural history of these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning detecting aggression among mood disorder patients visited in psychiatric emergency departments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Aggression, which is highly prevalent in patients with mood disorders, has been proven valuable in detecting the progression from hypomania to manic episode, enabling a timely diagnosis and treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What retrospective and dynamic assessments tell us about youth depression: A network analysis perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Traditional assessments of depressive symptoms often rely on retrospective self-reports, which may be affected by cognitive and memory biases. Few studies have compared retrospective and dynamic (real-time) assessments to examine the consistency and structure of depressive symptom reporting. This study aimed to compare retrospective and dynamic assessments of depressive symptoms in youth using network analysis to explore symptom-level associations and clustering.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacillus subtilis-derived extracellular vesicles displaying superoxide dismutase exhibit superior antioxidant ability in ameliorating skin damage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Skin, as the most crucial natural shields that envelopes human body, the integrity and function of which is destroyed by various harmful stimuli. Skin damage often involves excessive oxidative stress, which impairs the healing process. Thus, it is urgent to explore novel and effective strategy to tackle this problem. While superoxide dismutase (SOD) has strong antioxidant capacity, its clinical use is limited by poor stability and low penetration. Bacterial extracellular vesicles (BEVs),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolomic Insights into the Neuroprotective Actions of Ziziphi Spinosae Semen and Jujuboside B against Aβ-Induced Toxicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ZSS and JuB exert multi-target anti-AD effects by rebalancing neurotransmitters, modulating metabolic networks, and activating protective genetic pathways, supporting their potential as functional food-derived candidates for mitigating Aβ(1-42)-induced neurotoxicity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting acute developmental toxicity of chemicals in embryos of the African clawed frog (Xenopus laevis): calibration and validation of regression-based quantitative structure activity relationship models for hazard assessment of chemicals in anuran amphibians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Global decline of amphibian populations has been correlated with a range of endogenous and exogenous variables including their unique physiology and ecology, exposure to chemicals, habitat reduction, climate change, as well as biological hazards such as emerging infectious diseases. The African clawed frog (Xenopus laevis) is an OECD test species used in toxicity testing as a specific proxy for humans and environmentally relevant species, for which acute toxicity data for a range of chemicals...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incorporating co-design in cardiovascular research: tips, tricks, and tools]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Co-design is increasingly used in cardiovascular health research. Conducting co-design is an iterative process that involves collaboration with end-users, such as clinicians and people with lived experience. However, co-design is logistically, practically, and methodologically challenging. This methods paper aims to clarify what co-design is, why and when to use co-design, and how co-design research can be conducted. This paper, therefore, provides practical tools and examples to deal with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternative splicing dynamics during human cardiac development in vivo and in vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiomyocytes differentiated in vitro from human induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSC-CMs) are increasingly used in studies of disease mechanisms, drug development, toxicity testing, and regenerative medicine. Alternative splicing (AS) plays a pivotal role in cardiac development. However, the extent to which iPSC-CMs recapitulate native cardiac splicing patterns remains poorly understood. Here, we provide a comprehensive temporal map of AS regulation during human cardiac development....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oligodendrocyte mechanotransduction channel TMEM63A regulates myelin sheath geometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oligodendrocytes, the myelinating cells of the central nervous system, precisely sculpt their insulating membranes to match axon size, ensuring fine-tuned action potential propagation. How oligodendrocytes estimate axon caliber to adapt myelin sheath geometry is unknown. The biochemical measure of axonal size provided by neuregulin 1 for Schwann cells is dispensable in oligodendrocytes, and we reasoned that biophysical cues might instead be required. By combining transcriptomics, in vivo optical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cathepsin-D-mediated MHC class I degradation contributes to immune evasion in colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microsatellite stable (MSS) colorectal cancer (CRC) is often considered a "cold" tumor with limited response to programmed death-1 (PD-1) antibody monotherapy. The mechanisms underlying its intrinsic resistance to immunotherapy remain unclear. Here, we show that cathepsin D (CTSD) is highly expressed in MSS CRC and contributes significantly to immunotherapy resistance. Mechanistically, CTSD, acting as a protease, interacts with the α2 domain of the major histocompatibility complex (MHC) class I...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbiota utilization of intestinal amino acids modulates cancer progression and anticancer immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The human microbiota modulates cancer progression through largely unexplored mechanisms. Defining causal pathways is essential for monitoring and fine-tuning the microbiota to improve cancer treatment. Given that amino acid (aa) metabolism is often dysregulated in cancer, we assessed the role of microbiota pathways that modulate intestinal aa levels on colorectal tumor progression in mice. We found that the Bacteroides gene bo-ansB affects tumor responses to dietary asparagine (Asn) by reducing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biocompatible semiconducting molybdenum diselenide nanosheets with glycyrrhizic acid for enhanced photothermal cancer therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanosheets of molybdenum diselenide (MoSe(2)), a representative two-dimensional (2D) transition metal dichalcogenide, have attracted considerable attention for biological and medical applications due to their excellent biocompatibility and near-infrared (NIR) absorption capabilities. In this work, we present a simple method for preparing 2D therapeutic nanosheets that incorporate glycyrrhizic acid (GA), a naturally derived amphiphilic surfactant with anticancer properties, for the liquid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights on the translocation, distribution, metabolism, and potential exposure risk of chlorfenapyr and the toxic metabolite tralopyril in soil-cultivated lettuce and the effect of chromium(VI)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pesticides and heavy metals frequently coexist in vegetables. Consequently, it is crucial to concurrently investigate the behavior of pesticides and heavy metals in vegetables to ensure environment and food safety. This study examines the absorption and distribution of chlorfenapyr in lettuce, finding that it is primarily localized at the application site with limited upward and downward translocation. The presence of Cr(VI) enhances the accumulation and translocation of chlorfenapyr, as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From untargeted discovery to targeted quantification: Discovery of characteristic peptides for quantitative monitoring of allergen degradation in fermented soybean meal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soybean meal is an important protein source in animal feed, but its nutritional value is limited by allergenic proteins such as glycinin and β-conglycinin. Microbial fermentation can reduce these allergens by proteolytic degradation, yet a lack of methods to directly monitor the resulting peptide profiles hinders precise evaluation of fermentation efficacy. This study developed a workflow combining untargeted peptidomics with targeted quantification to investigate the relationship between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endogenous denitrification: A sustainable strategy for residual sludge reduction and nitrogen removal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Residual sludge-rich in organic matter, microorganisms, heavy metals, and other contaminants-remains a major operational and environmental challenge for wastewater treatment plants, with direct implications for ecological safety, resource recovery, and long-term sustainability. This review provides a comprehensive assessment of existing physical, chemical, and biological sludge reduction technologies, with a particular focus on the emerging and innovative role of endogenous denitrification as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upcycling sediment wastes into S-scheme heterojunctions for efficient photocatalytic tetracycline degradation: Performance, DFT calculations and toxicity assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a green and economical ZnO/sediments (ZNS) S-scheme heterojunction photocatalyst was constructed using SM-550 (calcination temperature was 550 °C) as the raw material, which effectively removes tetracycline (TC) from water under the 300 W xenon lamp irradiation. The experimental results showed that the optimal ZNS7:3 composite photocatalytic system exhibited significantly better TC degradation activity than ZnO (11.36 %) and SM-550 (16.00 %), with the TC degradation rate of 73.58...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for fatigue symptoms in the general population over 7 years: Findings from the Cooperative Health Research in the Region of Augsburg F4 and FF4 studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Baseline fatigue was linked to behavioural, medical, and psychosocial risk profiles, while longitudinal analyses revealed distress and prior fatigue as the key predictors of elevated fatigue symptoms over time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local environmental changes boost predation risk in forage fish: application to the sand lance in the eastern Seto Inland Sea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Changes in environmental conditions can modify the strength of prey-predator interactions in marine ecosystems by altering top-down and bottom-up drivers. This study examined potential top-down effects on the biomass of a forage fish, the sand lance Ammodytes japonicus, in oligotrophic waters of the eastern Seto Inland Sea, Japan. The biomass of sand lance has decreased over the last several decades, possibly due to reduced prey availability associated with declining nutrient levels. We analyzed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges in managing driving licence legislation when using B-Phosphatidylethanol to identify high levels of alcohol use in primary care patients: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results reveal that difficulties in complying with the legal obligation to report unfit drivers prevent the systematic use of PEth, obstructing the identification of harmful alcohol use and dependence. Clearer guidance on the implementation of the driving licence regulations and the clinical use of PEth are necessary to support physicians in handling this complex issue.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifunctional POSS-based nanoparticles functionalized with silver, SPIONs, and rhamnolipid for antibacterial applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nano-engineered materials, particularly those featuring bio-based surface modifications, are emerging as effective tools in combating bacterial infections. In this study, polyhedral oligomeric silsesquioxane (POSS) nanoparticles were functionalized with silver nanoparticles (Ag), superparamagnetic iron oxide nanoparticles (SPIONs), and the biosurfactant rhamnolipid (RL)-either individually or in combination-to evaluate their antibacterial and antibiofilm activities against Staphylococcus aureus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Music therapy and Benson relaxation in postoperative care: A randomized controlled trial on pain and kinesiophobia after lumbar discectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MT and BRM are effective, non-pharmacological adjuncts for improving postoperative outcomes. MT appears superior for faster pain relief, whereas BRM may offer an earlier benefit for kinesiophobia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving Oral Health Care for Frail, Community-Dwelling Older People: Exploring Barriers and Facilitators for Interprofessional Collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In conclusion, this study, identified critical barriers and facilitators for effective interprofessional collaboration and better oral health care for community-dwelling frail older people at the micro, meso, and macro levels. Improvement requires increasing awareness and education among professionals, better integration of oral health care in multidisciplinary care networks, shared electronic medical record systems, and adequate reimbursement. These findings should inform guidelines...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Broadening the Goods and Services Tax to healthy foods could exacerbate chronic disease in Australia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flavan derivatives from the fruits of Daemonorops draco Bl. and their protective effects on oxygen-glucose deprivation-induced endothelial cell injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fifteen previously undescribed flavan derivatives (1-15), along with 13 known analogues (5a, 16-24) were isolated from the fruits of Daemonorops draco Bl. Six pairs of isomers (1a/1b, 2a/2b, 3a/3b, 4a/4b, 6a/6b, and 18a/18b) were resolved by using chiral-phase HPLC separation. Their structures were elucidated by spectroscopic data analysis, single-crystal X-ray diffraction, and electronic circular dichroism (ECD) calculations. Compounds 1a/1b possess an unusual spiro[benzofuran-2,4'-chromen]...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coronary artery segmentation in non-contrast calcium scoring CT images using deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Precise localization of coronary arteries in Computed Tomography (CT) scans is critical from the perspective of medical assessment of various heart pathologies. Although manifold methods exist that offer high-quality segmentation of coronary arteries in cardiac contrast-enhanced CT scans, the potential of less invasive, non-contrast CT is still not fully exploited. Since such fine anatomical structures are hardly visible in this type of medical image, the existing methods are characterized by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The essential role of nurse clinician-scientists in an artificial intelligence-driven era of healthcare delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computation-Guided Placement of Nonfullerene Acceptor Core Halogenation for High-Performance Organic Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The strategic molecular design of nonfullerene acceptors (NFAs) plays a crucial role in enhancing the efficiency of organic solar cells (OSCs). Here, working from first-principles theoretical computation, we report a new series of quinoxaline-based NFAs (Qx-PhHal, where Hal = F, Cl, or Br) with varying halogen substitution on the central acceptor core of the molecules to investigate their impact on OSC performance. Notably, OSCs incorporating the brominated NFA demonstrate a significantly higher...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Salmonella typhimurium co-expressing cytolysin A and hyaluronidase suppresses tumor growth and metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, various attenuated bacteria have been studied as cancer therapies due to their unique characteristics, which include tumor-targeting bioactivity and immunogenicity. Previously, we reported a Salmonella typhimurium strain, CNC018, which is attenuated by 10⁵-10⁶-fold compared with the wild-type strain but retains tumor-targeting specificity. However, although these bacteria suppress tumors at the early stage in mice, the tumors often regrow at later stages. Therefore, to increase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trait psychoticism is associated with greater intersubject neural dissimilarity during naturalistic social movie viewing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psychoticism refers to maladaptive traits associated with eccentricity, perceptual dysregulation, and unusual beliefs. This study explored how individual differences in psychoticism map into neural responses during naturalistic movie-watching. By utilizing social movies with differing demands of inference, we examined how relevant correspondence of individual differences emerges as a function of movie features. A total of 157 individuals were assessed with traits of psychoticism, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41484190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Calcium carbonate hybrid microcomposite for oral delivery of luteolin, a poorly water-soluble phytocompound]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop a β-cyclodextrin (β-CD)-stabilized calcium carbonate (CaCO(3)) microcomposites to improve the oral bioavailability of luteolin, a poorly water-soluble phytocompound. Luteolin-loaded CaCO(3) microcomposites without and with β-CD (F1 and F2) were fabricated using a precipitation-based biomineralization technique and achieved an excellent loading capacity of 40.5-43.0 %. The physicochemical properties of the formulations were comprehensively characterized, and the in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41483986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CTCF-Binding Sites Demarcate Chromatin Domains Enriched With Histone H3K9me2 or H3K9me3 and Restrict the Spreading of These Modifications in Human Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CTCF-binding sites are frequently found at the boundaries of chromatin domains enriched with specific histone modifications in vertebrate genomes, where they function as barriers that limit the spreading of these modifications. However, their role in domains marked by H3K9me2 or H3K9me3 remains poorly understood. In this study, we analyzed CTCF-binding sites and the distribution of H3K9me2 and H3K9me3 around them in human K562 cells, and investigated the spreading of these modifications...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Riemannian denoising model for molecular structure optimization with chemical accuracy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce a framework for molecular structure optimization using a denoising model on a physics-informed Riemannian manifold (R-DM). Unlike conventional approaches operating in Euclidean space, our method leverages a Riemannian metric that better aligns with molecular energy change, enabling more robust modeling of potential energy surfaces. By incorporating internal coordinates reflective of energetic properties, R-DM achieves chemical accuracy with an energy error below 1 kcal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interplay of Silver-Mean Quasiperiodicity and Weyl Semimetal Phase in WTe_{2}]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the intercalation of epoxy resin into a Weyl semimetal, WTe_{2}, by using a scanning tunneling microscopy. We show that intercalant molecules have self-similar height variations with the silver-mean quasiperiodicity and also that they create phason and soliton defects to yield a mean coherence length of 15 sequential order. In addition, we unravel that weak quasiperiodic potentials imposed by the intercalation layer drive a WTe_{2} surface to have an enhanced conductance near the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal Exposure to Polypropylene Nanoplastics Disrupts Sex- and Region-Specific Lipid Metabolism in the Brains of C57BL/6N Mouse Offspring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polypropylene nanoplastics (PPNPs), produced through the degradation of widely used plastic products, are increasingly recognized as emerging environmental contaminants with potential neurodevelopmental toxicity. However, the long-term biochemical consequences of prenatal PPNP exposure on brain development remain poorly understood. In this study, we performed a region- and sex-specific targeted lipidomic analysis to examine how maternal oral exposure to PPNPs during pregnancy and lactation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The health effects of diaphragmatic breathing: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DB is a promising complementary therapy for specific conditions, including GERD, but the evidence base is constrained by methodologically weak and heterogeneous primary studies. Future research requires rigorous, standardized trial designs to establish its clinical value. Despite these limitations, DB is a low-cost, accessible, and apparently safe intervention for select conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Localized vitamin D delivery via 3D-printed nanofiber sheets combined with systemic supplementation enhances tendon-to-bone healing in a rabbit rotator cuff tear model: A preclinical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this preclinical rabbit model, dual delivery of vitamin D using localized nanofiber sheets and systemic supplementation enhanced tendon-to-bone healing and muscle regeneration compared to single interventions. These findings provide a foundation for future studies aimed at optimizing delivery methods and evaluating safety and efficacy in clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morning sleep inertia and its associated factors: Findings from a nationwide study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sleep inertia was associated with sleep duration, chronotype, sleep-related symptoms, and anxiety. These findings underscore the need for targeted interventions to alleviate the adverse impact of sleep inertia on daily functioning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The traffic controller: GARLH4 dictates neuroligin synapse-type preference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroligin isoforms are commonly thought to intrinsically specify synapse identity. In this issue, Yamasaki et al. (https://doi.org/10.1083/jcb.202507190) show that the auxiliary protein GARLH4 (LHFPL4) instead dictates neuroligin preference via competitive hierarchy, enabling dynamic reassignment between excitatory and inhibitory postsynaptic domains.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological Justification Criteria of Pediatric Computed Tomography in Kenya]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Computed tomography is acknowledged as the most widely used imaging technique in both adults and children. Although computed tomography offers valuable diagnostic information, it contributes to a high radiation dose and poses relatively high risks of stochastic effects to patients. Stochastic risks are of special concern in pediatric imaging since children are more vulnerable to effects of ionizing radiation than adults. Therefore, the justification of pediatric computed tomography examinations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidic Solid-State pH Sensor for Dynamic Monitoring of Extracellular pH in Live Cell Cultures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate, real-time monitoring of the extracellular acidification is crucial for understanding the dynamics of cellular metabolism. Here, we present a microfluidic device with a solid-state potentiometric pH sensor for monitoring the extracellular acidification rate (ECAR) in live cell culture. The sensor employs a two-electrode configuration made up of Ag/AgCl and RuO(2) electrodes. The sensor showed excellent analytical capabilities, a consistent Nernst response with high sensitivity (-93...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260104024007&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>