<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:21:29 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into the antiviral efficacy of AG7404 against human rhinovirus 3C proteases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human rhinoviruses (hRVs) are major causative agents of the common cold and contribute to lower respiratory tract infections. Although extensive research efforts continue to explore potential therapeutic interventions, no clinically approved antiviral treatment currently exists for hRV infections. This study provides the structural basis of hRV 3C protease inhibition in several serotypes by AG7404, a modified rupintrivir derivative. AG7404 showed potent antiviral activity against hRV-B14,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapy for Atrial Fibrillation in Patients with Drug-Eluting Stents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with atrial fibrillation who had undergone implantation of a drug-eluting stent at least 1 year earlier, NOAC monotherapy was noninferior to combination therapy for net adverse clinical events. (Funded by Cardiovascular Research Center and Samjin Pharmaceutical; ADAPT AF-DES ClinicalTrials.gov number, NCT04250116.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Scalable Strategy for PCM-Based Thermal Buffering Sheets: Combining 2D BNNS with 0D Silica Microcapsules for Energy-Efficient Thermal Management Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of electronic devices has made thermal management a critical issue. In this study, we present phase change material (PCM)-based thermal buffering sheets that provide both heat transfer and heat delay functions. Boron nitride nanosheets (BNNS) with high aspect ratios were obtained by exfoliating bulk h-BN. The conventional exfoliation process had a low yield. In this study, the process was designed to be suitable for large-scale production. To prevent PCM leakage during...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Water Makes the Surface Slippery; Friction on Water/Au(111) Investigated with Variable-Pressure Friction Force Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the influence of water on tribological properties is crucial for advancing lubrication science, yet precise control of water vapor pressure and nanotribological measurements remain challenging. In this study, we investigated the effect of water on the friction and surface morphology of Au(111) using variable-pressure atomic force microscopy. Our results show a decrease in friction with increasing water vapor pressure, attributed to water molecule adsorption. By monitoring the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbial exopolysaccharides as a sustainable food ingredient and their health benefits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many studies focus on regulating gut microbiota dysbiosis using beneficial bacteria, and postbiotics, particularly microbial exopolysaccharides (EPSs), are notable for their stability and potential in functional foods. EPSs are valued for their diverse structural properties and significant health benefits, especially for gut health. They are utilized as applications across various industries, including food, pharmaceuticals, biomedicine, and environmental management. However, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence, structural, and immunoinformatics-driven multi-epitope vaccine design targeting non-structural proteins of West Nile Virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[West Nile Virus (WNV), a globally distributed mosquito-borne flavivirus, poses a significant public health threat due to its potential to cause severe neurological complications and the absence of licensed vaccines or specific antiviral treatments. In this study, we applied an integrated artificial intelligence, structural, and immunoinformatics-driven approach to design a multi-epitope subunit vaccine (MESV) targeting the non-structural proteins NS1 and NS4B, which play key roles in viral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A minimal ion-chemistry model for predicting benign paroxysmal positional vertigo risk based on endolymphatic calcium and pH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Benign paroxysmal positional vertigo (BPPV) arises from detachment of otoconia-calcium carbonate (CaCO(3)) crystals embedded in a protein matrix-whose stability depends on endolymph ionic composition and pH. Age-related calcium metabolism, acid-base imbalance, and hormonal factors can impair otoconia integrity, yet, to our knowledge, no prior quantitative model integrates these biochemical parameters to predict BPPV risk. Beyond the established mechanical mechanisms of canalithiasis and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Chemical Recycling of Waste Polystyrene via Catalytic Pyrolysis over Waste Shell-Derived Calcium Oxide Catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a series of seashell-based catalysts was synthesized via simple heat treatment and applied to the catalytic pyrolysis of buoy polystyrene (BPS) for the recovery of styrene monomer. This thermal process facilitates the phase transformation of CaCO(3) into CaO, thereby enhancing its catalytic activity with a 56.5 wt % styrene monomer yield from BPS at 350 °C, highlighting its potential as an efficient and environmentally friendly solution for marine waste valorization. A comparative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adding Yttrium to SO<sub>4</sub> <sup>2-</sup>/ZrO<sub>2</sub> Catalysts To Improve the Synthesis Performance of Esters for Electrical Insulating Oils]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Synthetic ester insulating oils exhibit excellent electrical insulating properties, biodegradability, and oxidative stability, rendering them attractive alternatives to conventional mineral- and vegetable-based insulating oils. Typically, synthetic ester insulating oils are prepared via esterification reactions between fatty acids and alcohols using various catalysts. In particular, the solid acid catalyst SO(4) ^(2-)/ZrO(2) is commonly used in this process. In this study, a small amount of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Challenges and recommendations for embracing digital tools for one health surveillance in LMICs: Viewpoints from a special session of 17th ISVEE]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The adoption of digital tools presents a critical opportunity to enhance One Health initiatives in low- and middle-income countries (LMICs). At the 17th International Symposium of Veterinary Epidemiology and Economics (ISVEE17), a special session explored the role of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) applications in addressing zoonoses, animal diseases, food safety, and antimicrobial resistance (AMR) in Asia and Africa countries. This paper highlights key insights from that session,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of university teachers' transformational leadership on students' social-emotional competence: the mediating role of teacher-student relationship and learning engagement with moderated by self-efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the context of increasing emphasis on holistic student development in higher education, transformational leadership (TL) demonstrated by university faculty has been linked to positive student outcomes, including social-emotional competence (SEC). This study explored the associations between TL and students' SEC by examining two potential mediating processes-the quality of teacher-student relationships (TSR) and students' learning engagement (LE)-as well as the moderating role of self-efficacy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional and genomic insights into BHET-degrading <em>Stenotrophomonas</em> sp. isolated from the marine plastisphere]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enzymatic degradation of polyethylene terephthalate (PET) has dramatically advanced through protein engineering of PETase, accelerating the biocatalytic depolymerization process. However, the subsequent microbial valorization of PET-derived intermediates, such as bis (2-hydroxyethyl) terephthalate (BHET) and terephthalic acid (TPA), remains limited because of restricted availability and suboptimal activity of specific biocatalytic enzymes. In this study, eight microbial species were isolated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Microphysiological Interface of Skeletal Myobundles and Inflamed Adipose Tissue for Recapitulating Muscle Dysfunction in an Obese Microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Systemic inflammation associated with obesity impairs skeletal muscle function through paracrine signaling from intermuscular adipose tissue-adipose depots situated between adjacent skeletal muscle groups-as well as from visceral adipose tissue, which consist of infiltrating macrophages surrounding inflamed adipocytes. These signals disrupt metabolic homeostasis and reduce muscle contractility, yet existing models are limited in their ability to recapitulate the crosstalk between skeletal muscle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synaptic and Non-Synaptic Functions of PTPRD: A Receptor Tyrosine Phosphatase at the Crossroads of Neural Circuitry and Metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein-tyrosine phosphatase receptor-type D (PTPRD) is an adhesion-coupled phosphatase that translates extracellular binding codes into intracellular phosphotyrosine signaling from embryogenesis through adulthood. Alternative inclusion of the Ig-domain mini-exons meA and meB tailors the ectodomain surface, thereby dictating high-affinity engagement with IL1RAPL1, IL1RAP, Slitrks, LRFN4/5 (SALM3/5), neuroligin-3, and other postsynaptic partners. Intracellularly, the catalytically active D1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting Progesterone Receptor Membrane Component 1 to Improve Muscle Development and Glucose Homeostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings identify skeletal muscle PGRMC1 as a pivotal regulator of glucose metabolism and highlight its inhibition as a promising muscle-targeted therapeutic approach for T2D management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Step Synthesis of Mesoporous Vinyl Polymers via Hierarchical Assembly of Stereocontrolled Chains and Their Unique Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mesoporous materials, vital in energy, environmental, and medical applications, require resource-intensive production. Mesoporous vinyl polymers, p-alkyl-N-phenyl-acrylamide (APAA) polymers is introduced, which offer unprecedented advantages in mass production. APAA monomers swiftly form syndiotactic chains through Monomer Aggregation-mediated Rapid, Radical Stereocontrolled (MARRS) polymerization, spontaneously creating mesoporous structures. Structural analyses (X-ray, NMR, DSC, FTIR, TEM, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Repeated gadolinium-based contrast agent exposure increases depression-like behavior in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In rats repeatedly administered GBCA, no locomotor activity or anxiety was observed, but depression-like behavior increased.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Layered coordination polymer nanoflakes of copper tetracyanonickelate: Efficient electrocatalyst for high-performance non-enzymatic glucose sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Layered coordination polymer nanoflakes of copper tetracyanonickelate CuNi(CN)(4) were synthesized as a bimetal nanocomposite by a facile co-precipitation technique at room temperature and applied to electrochemical glucose sensing, demonstrating strong potential as a non-enzymatic electrode material. The integration of Cu and Ni centers within a cyanide-bridged Prussian blue-type framework afforded abundant redox-active sites and a high surface area, facilitating efficient electron transfer and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a LASSO-Based FDG PET/CT model for predicting colorectal adenoma in asymptomatic individuals undergoing colonoscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A multivariable model integrating FDG PET/CT-derived metabolic features with clinical parameters enables noninvasive prediction of colorectal adenomas. This imaging-based approach may help identify individuals most likely to benefit from colonoscopy, potentially improving the efficiency of CRC screening strategies in opportunistic or high-risk settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-based identification and experimental evaluation of Oroxin A as a FYN kinase inhibitor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[FYN, a member of the Src family kinases (SFKs) and a non-receptor tyrosine kinase, plays a critical role in signal transduction within the nervous system and is instrumental in the activation and development of T lymphocytes. While the biological significance of FYN kinase in various cellular processes is well recognized, its potential as a therapeutic target remains largely unexplored. In this study, we investigated the potential of natural products (NPs) as preferential inhibitors of FYN...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Duration of aggravated symptoms affects satisfaction after degenerative lumbar surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In our study, 70.4% of patients who underwent short level lumbar fusion surgery for degenerative LSS were satisfied with the treatment. Additionally, we identified that longer duration of aggravated symptoms (particularly beyond 12 months), advanced age, and severity of neuropathic pain were risk factors for lower satisfaction rates. It can be suggested that timely surgical intervention, before the progression of neuropathic pain and development of age-related comorbidities, can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physics-based compact model for 2D TMD FETs with full-range validation from single device to circuit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional (2D) semiconductors, particularly transition-metal dichalcogenides (TMDs), offer transformative potential for next-generation electronics because of their ultrathin atomic structures and superior electrostatic gate control. However, the practical realization of complex integrated circuits based on 2D TMD-based field-effect transistors (2D FETs) is critically constrained by the absence of robust, accurate, compact, and computationally efficient models suitable for SPICE...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cu/Pd-Catalyzed Ligand-Controlled Regiodivergent Hydroarylation of Allenes Using Diisobutylaluminum Hydride]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a ligand-controlled, regiodivergent Cu/Pd-catalyzed hydroarylation of unactivated allenes. The reaction proceeds via Cu-catalyzed hydroalumination with DIBAL-H and subsequent additive-free Pd-catalyzed cross-coupling with aryl bromides. The key feature of this work is the discovery that modulation of the palladium ligand decisively enables complete regiodivergence. Bulky monodentate Xphos ligands promote exclusive γ-selective arylation, while bidentate Josiphos-type ligands switch the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Assessment of Facial Scars After Acellular Dermal Matrix Grafting Post-Skin Cancer Resection: Focus on Color and Contraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Scars following ADM grafting initially exhibit suboptimal results; however, marked improvements are evident by 12 months post-healing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison between the new Xpert <em>Mycobacterium tuberculosis/</em>Rifampicin (MTB/RIF) Ultra assay and Xpert MTB/RIF for diagnosis of extra-pulmonary tuberculosis in a tertiary care center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis remains a significant global health challenge, with the re-emergence of Mycobacterium tuberculosis (MTB) posing serious concerns, especially in its extra-pulmonary forms. Rapid and accurate diagnosis is crucial for effective management. This study evaluates the performance of the Xpert MTB/RIF Ultra assay compared with the Xpert MTB/RIF and traditional microscopy (Ziehl-Neelsen stain) in diagnosing extra-pulmonary tuberculosis (EPTB) in a tertiary care center in northern India. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sibeprenlimab in IgA Nephropathy - Interim Analysis of a Phase 3 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sibeprenlimab resulted in a significant reduction in proteinuria as compared with placebo in patients with IgA nephropathy. (Funded by Otsuka Pharmaceutical Development and Commercialization. VISIONARY ClinicalTrials.gov number, NCT05248646.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Full Spin-Orbit Torque Switching of the Magnetic Cluster Octupole in Mn<sub>3</sub>Sn/W Bilayer via Interface Engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current-induced switching of magnetic octupoles in noncollinear antiferromagnetic (AFM) Mn(3)Sn has gained much interest in the development of fast and energy-efficient magnetic memory devices. Though full switching of Mn(3)Sn AFM order has been achieved in the epitaxial film prepared by molecular beam epitaxy, the switching rate (ξ) of sputtered Mn(3)Sn films has been mostly limited to 40% due to crystalline imperfections. Herein, our study reports how the Mn-deficiency affects SOT switching...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Responsive Nanodelivery System Synergizes Elevation in Hypoxia with PD-L1 Blocking to Activate Systemic Immunity and Inhibit Distant Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The hypoxia of the tumor microenvironment is insufficient to fully activate the efficacy of hypoxia-activated prodrugs (HAPs), while severe hypoxia elevates the expression of the hypoxia-inducible factor (HIF-1α), leading to tumor metastasis and immune evasion. This study has constructed a nanomicelle (HACA/GOx@AF/TPZ) that is composed of a coassembly of hyaluronic acid-cinnamaldehyde Schiff base (HACA), glucose oxidase (GOx), tirapazamine (TPZ), and acriflavine (AF). HACA/GOx@AF/TPZ releases...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning predicts EGFR mutation status from histology images in non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[EGFR mutation screening in non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) remains variable globally and represents a significant care gap, despite international recommendations and molecular testing guidelines. Recently, the use of deep learning (DL) methods to extract clinically actionable features from routine histology images has gained regulatory approval for multiple clinical applications. Therefore, the integration of predictive DL to complement molecular EGFR mutation screening may improve biomarker...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated diagnostic approaches for superficial radial neuropathy: The role of ultrasonography in enhancing morphological assessments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ultrasonography is useful for evaluating lesion location and structural abnormalities in superficial radial neuropathy and can be complementary to electrodiagnostic tests for diagnosing superficial radial neuropathy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implications of bronchoalveolar lavage fluid cellular analysis in fibrotic interstitial lung disease combined with CT quantification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although BAL fluid cellular analysis alone does not differentiate radiologic patterns or offer prognostic values, elevated BAL neutrophil levels combined with a high fibrosis score on CT may help to identify patients at higher risk of early fibrosis progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inflammation-suppressing effects of tofu whey-derived Aquaforte on human keratinocytes stimulated with 2,2'-azobis(2-amidinopropane) dihydrochloride]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tofu, a traditional food made from soybeans, has been widely consumed in the world but tofu production generates significant by-products such as tofu whey, and other residues. In the present study, Aquaforte, derived from tofu whey, was investigated for its antioxidative and anti-inflammatory properties in combating oxidative stress-induced damage in human keratinocytes (HaCaT). Antioxidant capacities were assessed through antioxidant properties were evaluated through DPPH and ABTS assays in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The combined effects of acidulant and VERDAD N6 on the microbiological and physicochemical properties of <em>Tteokbokki</em> rice cake]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the impact of packaging methods on the reduction of Listeria monocytogenes, Salmonella Typhimurium, and enterohemorrhagic Escherichia coli in Tteokbokki rice cakes. The 5-log reduction time and death rates of these pathogens were assessed in rice cakes treated with acidulants (0%, 0.5%, and 1%) and VERDAD N6 (0%, 0.2%, 0.4%, 0.6%, and 0.8%) at refrigerated(4 °C and 10 °C) and ambient temperatures(25 °C). Pathogen inactivation was more rapid at 25 °C across all treatments....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced glutathione production by a non-GMO <em>Saccharomyces cerevisiae</em> mutant isolated via acrolein resistance-mediated screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop a non-genetically modified organism (non-GMO) Saccharomyces cerevisiae strain with enhanced glutathione production using UV-induced random mutagenesis. Among 30 wild-type strains, S. cerevisiae KACC 48331 was selected for its high glutathione production. A #14 mutant with significantly higher glutathione content was isolated via acrolein resistance screening. Optimal batch fermentation was established at 20 °C and pH 4.5 using a cost-effective medium of molasses and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemoenzymatic synthesis and identification of medium- and long-chain triacylglycerol congeners]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Medium- and long-chain triacylglycerols (MLCTs) offer rapid energy release and essential nutritional benefits, making them valuable in functional foods. In this study, MLCTs containing caprylic acid (C8:0; C) and linoleic acid (C18:2; L) were synthesized via a chemoenzymatic strategy combining lipase-catalyzed reactions and Steglich esterification. Four distinct MLCT congeners-CCL, CLC, LLC, and LCL-were obtained with yields of 52-67% (asymmetrical) and 71-84% (symmetrical), and purified using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of a standardized extract (HemoHIM G) from <em>Angelica sinensis, Ligusticum chuanxiong,</em> and <em>Paeonia lactiflora</em> on cyclophosphamide-induced immunosuppression in BALB/c mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Angelica sinensis, Ligusticum chuanxiong, and Paeonia lactiflora have traditionally been used as medicinal herbs in East Asia; HemoHIM G is a standardized extract of the three herbs. However, its immune improvement abilities are unexplored. Hence, this study aimed to investigate the immune-enhancing effects of HemoHIM G on cyclophosphamide (CTX)-induced immunosuppression in a murine model. As a result, HemoHIM G improved weight recovery lowered by CTX and helped improve white blood cell counts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low molecular weight porcine placenta peptide (Placenderm®) as a functional ingredient for hair health: evidence from in vitro and in vivo studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hair loss, marked by thinning hair, reduced density, and increased scalp visibility, is a growing concern. The hair growth cycle is regulated by a dynamic balance between stimulatory growth and inhibitory cytokines. While placenta extracts have demonstrated regenerative, anti-aging, and immunomodulatory effects, their potential role in promoting hair follicle regeneration remains largely unexplored. This study investigated the effects of low molecular weight porcine placenta peptides...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitigation of heterocyclic amines, polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, and acrylamide in air-fried chicken and beef: effects of cooking methods and marinades]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated how air frying conditions, temperature, time, searing, marination, and spices, affect the formation of heterocyclic amines (HCAs), polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (PAHs), and acrylamide in whole chicken and beef steak. 10 HCAs, 4 PAHs, and acrylamide were quantified using UHPLC-(ESI)-QqQ and GC-MS. Higher temperatures and searing increased HCAs and acrylamide levels, especially in beef. In chicken, marination with milk or beer has reduced HCAs by up to 60.6%, with no...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton boron capture therapy: microdosimetry and treatment planning study with boron]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Proton-boron capture therapy (PBCT) has been proposed as a method to enhance the biological effectiveness of proton therapy through the p + ^(11)B → 3α nuclear reaction. The resulting alpha particles may increase local radiation quality, but the dosimetric and microdosimetric consequences remain uncertain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preserved ictal responsiveness in right mesial temporal lobe epilepsy: metabolic correlates in posterior temporal networks with FDG-PET]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Consciousness impairment in right MTLE is specifically associated with posterior lateral temporal dysfunction, with broader posterior temporal vulnerability suggested by subthreshold trends. These findings identify posterior lateral temporal hypometabolism as a potential biomarker of impaired responsiveness in right MTLE and highlight the value of FDG-PET for characterizing consciousness-related network dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blooming as a New Nurse Amid Trials and Uncertainty: A Qualitative Content Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: New nurses experience significant uncertainty, self-doubt, and a gap between academic learning and the realities of clinical practice during their transition to practice. The findings provide a deeper understanding of their transition experiences and offer a foundation for strategies that support adaptation and workforce retention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Evaluation of the gastric microbiota based on body mass index using 16S rRNA gene sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fcimb.2025.1651316.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210949/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid and Accurate Diagnosis of Joint Infections: Potential Clinical Effect of the BioFire Joint Infection Panel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The JI panel showed high concordance with culture-positive cases and identified additional pathogens in culture-negative samples. Its rapid turnaround time and improved detection support antimicrobial stewardship by enabling earlier, targeted therapy. However, its utility is limited by fixed coverage and exclusion of off-panel pathogens.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Warm Autoimmune Haemolytic Anaemia Management in Asia-Pacific: A Delphi Panel Expert Consensus and Systematic Literature Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This research emphasises the need for evidence-based, regionally adaptable treatment algorithms for wAIHA in the APAC region. Ongoing data gaps related to epidemiology, outcomes and quality of life must be addressed to enhance patient care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision gene editing: The power of CRISPR-Cas in modern genetics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gene editing has transformed molecular biology by enabling precise modifications to genomic DNA across a wide variety of organisms. Gene editing technologies make it possible to add, remove, or modify specific DNA sequences, with a range of applications including gene knockouts, therapeutic gene correction, and the design of targeted genetic traits. These techniques depend on two main DNA repair mechanisms: homology-directed repair (HDR), which facilitates precise changes to the genome, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Malignancy risk in AUS thyroid lesions: comparison between FNA and CNB with implications for NIFTP diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CNB may serve as a more reliable diagnostic tool for cases initially classified as AUS, particularly when repeat insufficient results are obtained or when diagnosing FNs and NIFTP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing text-level reading fluency and engagement in immigrant children through a structured singing-based intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Reading fluency is a key component of academic success, yet immigrant children often face difficulties in developing this skill in a new language due to limited phonological awareness, reduced exposure, and differences between home and school language environments. This pilot study examined the effects of a singing-based intervention designed to improve reading fluency and attitudes toward reading among immigrant children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-centered design of lipid-based nanocarriers to overcome biological barriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As technology has evolved in response to pressing human challenges, drug delivery systems (DDSs) have also evolved to overcome complex biological barriers. Particularly, the continuous development of therapeutic strategies has enabled the integration of nanotechnology, leading to the emergence of diverse nanoscale DDSs. Concerns about the potential toxicity of nanomedicines diverted attention to lipid-based nanocarriers (LBNs), regarded as safer and more biocompatible platforms. In this review,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic pre-subtemporal keyhole approach: Anatomical feasibility and clinical applications [SevEN-016]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Endoscopic endonasal approaches (EEAs) are routinely used to resect skull base lesion. However, they are laterally restricted when addressing lesions that extend into the petroclival region or lateral brainstem.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Symptoms of Borderline Personality Disorder in People With Affective Disorders: A Network Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that, although the symptom networks of BPD were largely comparable across affective disorder subgroups, structural differences emerged between the clinical and control groups. Notably, "Feel empty" consistently appeared as the most central symptom across all groups. These findings highlight the relevance of targeting "Feel empty" as a key focus for clinical intervention in affective disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chitosan based smart injectable hydrogels for biomedical applications: A comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chitosan-based smart injectable hydrogels (CS-SIHs) have emerged as multifunctional platforms for drug delivery, regenerative medicine, and tissue engineering (TE), owing to their inherent biocompatibility, biodegradability, and responsiveness to external stimuli such as pH, temperature, and ionic strength. These smart hydrogels offer controlled, localized therapeutic release and mimic the extracellular matrix (ECM), thereby fostering cell adhesion, proliferation, and differentiation. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights into <em>Campula oblonga</em> (Digenea: Brachycladiidae): Morphological, phylogenetic, and pathological studies in narrow-ridged finless porpoise (<em>Neophocaena asiaeorientalis</em>) from Korean waters]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Various marine parasites exploit marine mammals as definitive hosts; however, comprehensive parasitological studies remain lacking because of the inherent challenges in host sampling. This study aimed to investigate the pathological effects of Campula oblonga on the hepatobiliary system of the narrow-ridged finless porpoise (Neophocaena asiaeorientalis). We detected a digenean species, C. oblonga, in the hepatobiliary systems of 143 out of 196 (72.96 %) narrow-ridged finless porpoises stranded,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Streptomyces rimosus</em>-inoculated soil exposure modulates metabolomic profiles under chronic stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exposure to natural environments, including soil and microorganisms, is known to enhance emotional well-being and mitigate psychiatric disorders such as anxiety and depression. This study investigated the effects of short-term exposure to Streptomyces rimosus-inoculated soil, on mice with chronic restraint stress (CRS)-induced anxiety and the associated metabolic changes. Behavioral tests, including the light/dark box, open field, and novelty-suppressed feeding tests, revealed that exposure...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Core principles of responsible generative AI usage in research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In a rapidly evolving Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) landscape, researchers, policymakers, and publishers have to continuously redefine responsible research practices. To ensure guidance of GenAI use in research, core principles that remain stable despite technological advancement are needed. This article defines a list of principles guiding the responsible use of GenAI in research, regardless of use case and GenAI technology employed. To define this framework, we conducted an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic engineering of <em>Yarrowia lipolytica</em> for enhanced microbial production of medium-chain α, ω-diols from alkanes via CRISPR-Cas9 mediated pathway optimization and P450 alkane monooxygenase overexpression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Medium- to long-chain α, ω-diols are valuable building blocks for polyesters and polyurethanes, yet their microbial synthesis from inexpensive alkane feedstocks remains largely undeveloped. The oleaginous yeast Yarrowia lipolytica offers advantages over bacterial systems such as Escherichia coli for alkane conversion due to its inherent capacity to metabolize hydrophobic substrates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global, regional, and national burden of hypertensive heart disease in 1990-2021, with forecasts to 2050: a Global Burden of Disease Study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The rising burden of HHD calls for a shift away from traditional, fragmented approaches focused solely on blood pressure control. Integrated clinical and policy responses are urgently needed to address the complex and multifactorial nature of the disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of home and clinical blood pressure variability on arteriosclerosis and metabolic indicators: a prospective multicenter registry study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Home systolic BPV showed consistent associations with vascular inflammation and arterial stiffness, but not with metabolic parameters. These findings support home BPV as a distinct cardiovascular risk marker with potential relevance for risk stratification and preventive management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of aerobic and inspiratory strength muscle training on exaggerated blood pressure response during exercise in hypertensive patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both AE and IMST attenuated SBP responses during submaximal exercise in hypertensive individuals. These findings highlight a potential for exercise training to mitigate EBPR in hypertension.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and initial clinical application of a digital health-enabled 3D VR education model to improve health literacy in thyroid surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ray-traced 3D VR educational models are feasible for improving patient health literacy during preoperative counseling. This digital technology-based approach offers a practical and scalable tool to support more informed, meaningful discussions and enhance patient understanding.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STK32C as a Therapeutic Target in Colorectal Cancer via HSP90-PI3K/AKT/mTOR Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emerging evidence implicates serine/threonine kinase 32C (STK32C) overexpressed in bladder cancer and brain tissues acts as a molecular target for doxorubicin resistance, yet its role in colorectal cancer (CRC) remains unclear. Thus. this study investigates the oncogenic mechanism of STK32C in CRC and its interplay with HSP90 and the PI3K/AKT/mTOR signaling axis. STK32C was markedly upregulated in CRC cell lines (HCT116, HT29, SW480, SW620) compared to normal fibroblasts (CCD-18Co) with poor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Effects of Radiotherapy and PD‑1 Blockade in a Human‑Mimetic BRCAness Model of Triple-Negative Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BRCA1‑deficient triple‑negative breast cancer (TNBC) presents significant treatment challenges owing to the absence of estrogen receptor (ER), progesterone receptor (PR), and human epidermal growth factor receptor 2 (HER2) targets, exhibits marked molecular heterogeneity that precludes the application of effective targeted therapies, and harbors a highly immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment. Here, we used the Brca1^(co/co) MMTV‑Cre mouse model that recapitulates human BRCA1‑mutant TNBC,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-convulsant efficacy of long-acting injectable cannabidiol formulation (IVL5005) in the pentylenetetrazol-induced convulsions, with pharmacokinetic characterization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Cannabidiol (CBD) has demonstrated therapeutic potential in neurological disorders, particularly epilepsy. Epidiolex®, an FDA-approved oral CBD solution, is indicated for rare epileptic disorders such as Lennox-Gastaut syndrome and Dravet syndrome. However, its clinical utility is limited by rapid metabolism, short duration of action, and low oral bioavailability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystallinity-Preserving Atomic Layer Etching of Ultrathin In<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub> for Stable Oxide Nanoelectronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Indium oxide (In(2)O(3)) is a promising channel material for advanced electronics, offering high electron mobility, a wide bandgap, and excellent compatibility with atomic layer deposition (ALD). However, conventional bottom-up ALD processes cannot achieve and sustain ultrathin crystalline layers owing to poor nucleation behavior and insufficient grain connectivity. Herein, we present an atomic layer etching (ALE) approach for In(2)O(3) that combines hydrogen-plasma-assisted surface modification...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Thyroid Cancer-specific Mortality Metrics: a Response to Recent Commentary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Phase 3, Randomized Trial Investigating the Safety, Tolerability, and Immunogenicity of V116, an Adult-Specific Pneumococcal Conjugate Vaccine, in Pneumococcal Vaccine-Naïve Adults 18-64 Years of Age at Increased Risk of Pneumococcal Disease, STRIDE-8]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: V116 elicits robust immune responses and is well tolerated in adults 18-64 years of age with conditions associated with an increased risk of PD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of Spirocyclic Molecules from Cyclic β-Diketones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this review, recently developed straightforward and efficient strategies for the construction of spirocyclic molecules are summarized. Cyclic 1,3-diketones serve as versatile synthons and can be employed in one-pot, single-step reactions as well as in multistep sequences and multicomponent processes with a variety of reacting partners, including aldehydes, ketones, amines, isatins, and acenaphthoquinone. These transformations can be facilitated either by using stoichiometric amounts of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Design Strategy in Polymer Electrolyte Membrane Fuel Cells: Micro-channeling Architectures in Carbon Nanotube Sheets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maintaining high performance under varying relative humidity (RH) conditions remains a significant challenge for polymer electrolyte membrane fuel cells (PEMFCs). This difficulty arises from the delicate balance required between mass transport and water management. This study presents an alternative PEMFC design that replaces conventional bipolar plates by incorporating a carbon nanotube sheet (≈30 µm) as a functional interlayer. The engraved channel-rib CNT sheet, fabricated via laser...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemoresistive and Catalytic Dual-Signal Pd-WO<sub>3</sub> MEMS Sensor for Reliable H<sub>2</sub> Monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The demand for H(2) monitoring in its production and utilization grows rapidly to ensure operational efficiency and safety. Given the high flammability of H(2), it is crucial to detect levels below the lower flammability limit (4%) in a sensitive, rapid, and reliable manner. Although integrating multiple sensor types can improve selectivity and accuracy, such systems often involve bulky architecture and time-consuming operation. This study presents a dual-signal H(2) sensor based on a single...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cold Atmospheric Plasma-Activated In Situ Hydrogel Induces Hair Regeneration Via Immune Microenvironment Remodeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hair loss is a prevalent condition with limited effective treatments. Here, a cold atmospheric plasma (CAP)-activated in situ hydrogel is reported, which modulates the hair follicle immune microenvironment and promotes hair regeneration. CAP irradiation induces the gelation of a tyramine-grafted hyaluronic acid solution containing interleukin-2 (HTsol/IL2), forming a hydrogel (CAPgel/IL2) that retains CAP-induced reactive oxygen species and IL2 within its matrix. In vivo, subcutaneous injection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating patency rates and complications of arterioarterial grafts in patients undergoing hemodialysis: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AAGs demonstrate high patency and low complication rates in high-risk hemodialysis patients with exhausted access sites, central venous stenosis, or cardiac comorbidities. By avoiding venous shunting and excessive preload, AAG represents a safe salvage access. Larger multicenter studies are needed to validate long-term outcomes and optimize surgical selection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Sex-Specific Mechanisms in Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus by Single-Cell Analysis in Pancreatic Islets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unstimulated Highly Sensitive Thyroglobulin &lt;0.2 ng/mL: Insufficient to Predict Stimulated Thyroglobulin &lt;1 ng/mL?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Lipid-Lowering Strategies: RNA-Based, Small Molecule, and Protein-Based Therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dyslipidemia remains a central modifiable risk factor for atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD). While 3-hydroxy-3-methylglutaryl coenzyme A (HMG-CoA) reductase inhibitors, commonly known as statins, as well as ezetimibe, fibrates, and omega-3 fatty acids have established roles in lipid lowering, significant residual risk persists in many patients due to insufficient low-density lipoprotein cholesterol (LDL-C) reduction, elevated triglyceride-rich lipoproteins, and genetically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Polydeoxyribonucleotide-Releasing Contact Lenses on Corneal Wound Healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Polydeoxyribonucleotide-CL was effective in promoting corneal wound healing and epithelial cell proliferation and in reducing inflammation. Therefore, it may be useful for treating contact lens complications or corneal injuries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Design of Superhydrophilic In@Zn@Cu NW@Cu Foam Anode for High-Performance Zinc-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of Zn-based anodes for aqueous Zn-ion batteries has attracted significant attention due to the high capacity of Zn, its low cost, environmental friendliness, and safety. However, dendrite formation and hydrogen evolution reactions (HERs) during Zn plating and stripping pose major challenges to their practical application, limiting the stability and efficiency of Zn-ion batteries. This study presents a super-hydrophilic In@Zn@Cu nanowire (NW)@Cu foam anode designed to enhance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of fixed-duration venetoclax plus obinutuzumab in untreated Japanese CLL and SLL: a phase 2 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This phase 2 study (NCT05105841) evaluated the safety and efficacy of a fixed-duration 12-cycle regimen of venetoclax plus obinutuzumab in Japanese patients with previously untreated chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) or small lymphocytic lymphoma (SLL). The primary efficacy endpoint was the complete remission (CR)/complete remission with incomplete marrow recovery (CRi) rate, assessed by an independent review committee (IRC) according to the 2008 International Workshop on CLL criteria. Ten...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcome of chemotherapy dose reduction in overweight Japanese children with acute lymphoblastic leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sternalis or rectus? An analysis of terminological usage based on case reports of the sternalis muscle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The sternalis muscle is a relatively rare anatomical variant that lies superficial to the pectoralis major muscle. In English-language literature, it is commonly referred as "sternalis muscle" or "rectus sternalis." Although the second edition of the Terminologia Anatomica (TA) officially designates "sternalis muscle" as the standard term, terminological inconsistencies persist. This study investigated the actual usage of these terms based on a literature review of previously published case...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correlation between intrahepatic iodine quantity after portal vein embolization and future liver remnant hypertrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher iodine content in the FLR was associated with greater FLR hypertrophy after portal vein embolization. However, because the correlation observed in this study was modest, the predictive ability of this parameter could not be established. Nevertheless, DECT-based iodine quantification may provide complementary information on FLR function and warrants further investigation as a potential biomarker in future studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of meningeal lymphatic vessels with delayed contrast enhanced vessel-wall MRI in cerebral infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Delayed meningeal enhancement observed in patients with large cerebral infarctions likely reflects alterations in brain clearance pathways. The absence of such enhancement in MMD supports that these enhancements are not attributable to collateral circulation. Phantom validation confirmed that the imaging parameters used in the DANTE T1-SPACE sequence were sufficient to detect subtle contrast enhancement in the clinically relevant T1 range.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Educational gradient in physiological risk factors in a workplace: a decomposition analysis of biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explores the educational inequality in a workplace in Japan in relation to the physiological risk factors. It investigates the difference in the prevalence rates of being overweight, hypertensive, dyslipidemic or diabetic between male employees who have undergone university education and those who have not. Combining the mandatory annual health check-up data, annual stress check survey data and personnel data (total sample size=7,428), this study conducts a decomposition analysis to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to the letter to the editor from Memuna Jehan zeb and colleagues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic factors for 5 year relapse-free survivors following curative resection for stage II/III colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Five clinical factors-age ≥ 80 years, elevated CEA level, anemia, macrocytosis, and a high RDW-were identified as independent prognostic indicators among 5 year relapse-free survivors after stage II/III CRC resection. These findings highlight the importance of individualized long-term follow-up strategies, even beyond 5 years after surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost of reusable vs. single-use ureteroscopes in complex renal surgeries: a randomized cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Single-use flexible ureteroscopes offer economic advantages in ECIRS, particularly in complex case settings, as the aggressive use of flexible URS increases the scope damage risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Genetic Characterization of Antimicrobial-resistant Escherichia coli from Wild Boar Meat in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial-resistant bacteria must be controlled from a "One Health" perspective, including in wild animals and associated products. We examined the prevalence and genetic characteristics of antimicrobial-resistant Escherichia coli in wild boar meat from a local market in Japan. A total of 152 E. coli isolates were recovered from 51 of 62 wild boar meat samples (82.3%). Among these isolates, 11 (7.2%) were resistant to one or more antimicrobial agents, including ampicillin, streptomycin,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: Performance of creatinine and cystatin C-based equations to estimate glomerular filtration rate in African children with sickle cell anemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term kidney function stabilization with fludrocortisone in autosomal recessive renal tubular dysgenesis: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Renal tubular dysgenesis (RTD) is a rare disorder characterized by impaired development of the proximal tubules and kidney dysfunction due to decreased fetal renal plasma flow and renin-angiotensin system (RAS) inhibition. Fetal anuria causes severe oligohydramnios and Potter sequence, and most patients die within days after birth due to refractory hypotension, anuria, and respiratory distress. While vasopressin and fludrocortisone therapy have been reported, the long-term efficacy remains...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Key mechanisms of affective disorders : CRC/TRR 393 project on mechanisms of emotion regulation, expectation, social cognition, and cognitive-behavioral rhythms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Gaining a deeper understanding of the cognitive-emotional mechanisms in the progression of affective disorders will help to predict symptom changes and course of illness as well as to identify key targets of intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational analysis of water coverage formation on Pt(111) surface under humid conditions with the effect of applied voltage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DFT calculations with implicit treatment of solvation effects are applied to the study of water coverage buildup and formation of dehydrogenated species (*OH and *O) on the surface of Pt electrode in response to the applied voltage. Using our previous work on initial step of water adsorption on Pt(111) at low voltage (0.5 V vs. standard hydrogen electrode (SHE)) as a starting point, we analyze subsequent stages of water coverage formation when higher potential is applied. Our study reveals that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pseudomonas aeruginosa-driven Humoral Immune Activation in Lung Transplantation: A Treatable Trait to Avert Chronic Lung Allograft Dysfunction?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liquid-Crystalline Biomineral Nanofibers: 1D Inorganic Materials with a High Aspect Ratio and Anisotropic Self-Assembled Nanocomposites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In nature, shark tooth enameloid exhibits an intricate anisotropic structure composed of high-aspect-ratio fluorapatite (FAp) fibrous nanocrystals, which impart exceptional mechanical properties. Mineral-based liquid-crystalline (LC) colloids provide a promising strategy for constructing such anisotropic structural materials. However, fibrous nanoparticles with high aspect ratios are prone to irreversible aggregation and gelation due to their large surface area. Consequently, the development of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-driven rheological modulation of solventless polymer networks enabled by precisely architected flexible star polysiloxanes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the synthesis and photoresponsivity of precisely designed liquid star-shaped poly(dimethyl siloxane) (PDMS) with anthracene end groups. Owing to the efficient end-linking of the flexible PDMS arms upon the first UV irradiation (λ = 365 nm, UV(365)), the storage modulus (G') increased from 4.7 Pa to 119 kPa (>25 000-fold), and the physical state became a rubbery solid. Subsequent irradiation with UV light at a shorter wavelength (λ = 254 nm, UV(254)) decreased G' toward the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association between total precipitation and diarrhea morbidity: A multicountry study across diverse climate zones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Associations between precipitation and diarrhea morbidity differed by country/region and climate zone. This study provides valuable evidence showing that location-specific prevention measures should be considered to mitigate the diarrhea burden associated with precipitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Study of Batch and Semibatch Reactive Crystallization of l‑Glutamic Acid with aid of PATs, focusing on Polymorphism and Crystal Habit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This work investigates the reactive crystallization of l-glutamic acid under different supersaturation generation strategies. Using PATs such as ATR-FTIR and in situ microscopes enables real-time monitoring of the supersaturation trajectory as well as the nucleation and growth behavior. In the batch process, crystallization starts instantaneously after the acid is added, leading to fines and clusters in the final products. Conversely, in the semibatch process, acid is dosed continuously, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Objective evaluation of platelet-rich plasma mesotherapy on facial skin quality: An interim split-face analysis using an advanced imaging system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides novel objective evidence that PRP mesotherapy significantly improves facial gloss, a key feature of healthy young skin. An exploratory trend toward pore reduction was also observed, although mechanistic interpretations remain hypothesized owing to the absence of biophysical and structural measurements. Moving beyond subjective assessments, these findings support the potential of PRP for enhancing facial brightness, smoothness, and overall skin quality. Further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41211201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Added value of serum proteins to clinical and ultrasound information in predicting the risk of malignancy in ovarian tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Assessment of Different Neoplasias in the Adnexa (ADNEX) is the best-performing model to estimate the risk of malignancy in ovarian tumors. We assessed the incremental value of serum proteins over ADNEX predictors in an exploratory multicenter study. In a cohort of 932 patients with an adnexal mass scheduled for surgery, 33 serum proteins were preoperatively quantified using multiplex high-throughput and electrochemiluminescence immunoassays. Using multivariable logistic regression, ADNEX...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flavivirus-based bivalent nanoparticle vaccines induce neutralizing antibodies and Th1 responses against flavivirus and coupling antigens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective vaccines against flaviviruses, including Japanese encephalitis virus (JEV), are widely used. We developed antigen-loaded nanoparticle vaccines, using JEV virus-like particles (JEV-VLPs) as carriers. The severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) spike receptor-binding domain (S-RBD) was covalently coupled to specific peptide insertion sites on the JEV envelope protein. Mice immunized with these coupled particles (JEprME-S-RBD) produced high levels of neutralizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coloration of Ethyleneamine-Diacrylate-Based Porous Polymer-Toluene Systems Induced by the Christiansen Effect: Color Control by the Molecular Design of the Polymer Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aza-Michael addition reaction of ethyleneamine, diethylenetriamine (DETA), triethylenetetramine (TETA), tetraethylenepentamine (TEPA), or pentaethylenehexamine (PEHA) with poly-(ethylene glycol) diacrylate (PEGDA) in ethanol at 20 °C yielded the corresponding porous polymers. The surface morphology of the porous polymers was composed of connected particles or cocontinuous monolithic structure, which were induced by phase separation. The TETA- and TEPA-PEGDA porous polymers turned half...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Changes in Pellets of Calcium Phosphate Ester Salts after Exposure to Simulated Body Fluid with the Addition of Alkaline Phosphatase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salts composed of calcium and phosphate esters (SCPEs) have been proposed as potential components for developing next-generation artificial bones, known as bioresponsive materials, due to their ability to transform into hydroxyapatite (HAp) in the physiological environment via enzymatic mediation by alkaline phosphatase (ALP). Previous studies have investigated the reaction behavior of the SCPE powders in simulated body fluid (SBF) modified with ALP. The reaction rates were influenced by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microneedle-Integrated Screen-Printed Electrode Modified with Gold Nanoparticle-Boron-Doped Diamond Nanoparticle Nanocomposites for Electrochemical Theophylline Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Theophylline is a drug with a narrow therapeutic index, with normal plasma levels ranging from 10 to 20 mg/L. Theophylline overdose can lead to several symptoms, including nausea, vomiting, headaches, pancreatitis, and death. Thus, it is important to monitor theophylline after its consumption. Microneedles (MNs) can be integrated with screen-printed electrodes (SPE) to enable the minimally invasive monitoring of theophylline. In this study, we developed a highly sensitive and accurate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inclusion Complexes of Stearyl Glycyrrhetinate with γ‑Cyclodextrin and Cyclodextrin-Based Metal-Organic Frameworks: Solid-State Characterization and Improved Solubility in Fasted-State Simulated Intestinal Fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, stearyl glycyrrhetinate (SG), a poorly water-soluble derivative of glycyrrhetinic acid, was formulated into inclusion complexes with γ-cyclodextrin (γCD) and cyclodextrin-based metal-organic frameworks (CD-MOF-1) using the evaporation method (EVP) in the solid state. Powder X-ray diffraction and differential scanning calorimetry analyses confirmed the disappearance of SG's crystalline and melting peaks, suggesting complexation and amorphization. Meanwhile, solid-state ^(13)C...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noncompetitive Fluorescence Polarization Aptamer Assay for Detecting SARS-CoV‑2 Variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the SARS-CoV-2 pandemic has subsided with the widespread rollout of vaccines, emerging variants continue to pose significant public health challenges. While current diagnostic technologies can sensitively detect specific variants, there is an increasing need for broad-spectrum detection methods that are less affected by viral mutations. In particular, the development of diagnostic techniques that are not only broadly applicable but also rapid and cost-effective is highly desirable for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prolonged psychiatric symptoms revealed as nonconvulsive status epilepticus in ring chromosome 20 syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ring chromosome 20 (r[20]) syndrome is a rare epilepsy-associated chromosomal disorder often accompanied by intellectual disability and psychiatric symptoms. It lacks distinctive physical features and typically exhibits normal brain imaging; therefore, its diagnosis is frequently delayed, especially when clinicians are unfamiliar with it. Nonconvulsive status epilepticus (NCSE), a hallmark of this syndrome, can be overlooked even by epilepsy specialists, who interpret it as a psychiatric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in baseline HbA1c and body-mass index in randomised trials of people with type 1 diabetes from 1993 to 2025: an IMI2 SOPHIA systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The prevalence of obesity has increased globally over the past few decades for the general population and people with type 2 diabetes. Existing research suggests that the body-mass index (BMI) of individuals living with type 1 diabetes has also increased substantially. This double burden of type 1 diabetes and obesity is concerning and may further increase the risk for microvascular and macrovascular complications associated with type 1 diabetes. We aimed to evaluate trends in BMI...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An international consensus on the design of clinical trials for advanced combination treatment (ACT) in inflammatory bowel disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Advanced Combination Treatment (ACT) refers to the dual use of two advanced therapies-either two biologics, two small molecules, or one biologic and one small molecule. There is a lack of guidance regarding clinical trial design for ACT in patients with inflammatory bowel disease (IBD). Key uncertainties remain regarding aspects such as eligibility criteria, pharmacotherapy regimens, safety considerations, and standardised trial design configurations for both induction and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RiSID: River Surface Image Dataset for Instance Segmentation of Floating Macroplastic Debris]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rivers constitute a major pathway of macroplastic debris, which has the potential to have adverse impacts on marine ecosystems and oceans. It is essential to develop image-based technology for quantifying macroplastic debris floating on river surfaces and then grasping plastic transport from land. The river surface image dataset (RiSID) comprises 7,356 original images recorded at 11 sites on seven rivers during high-flow conditions in Japan, along with pixelwise segmentation annotations for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrocardiographic P-wave indices and onset of atrial fibrillation and histological fibrosis in a general Japanese population: a prospective cohort analysis of the Hisayama Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: P-wave duration and PTFV1 are useful indicators for assessing AF risk. Furthermore, prolonged P-wave duration reflects the extent of left atrial fibrosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biological significance of sperm-independent calcium oscillations in immature oocytes of mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sperm-independent Ca ^(2+) oscillations are induced in immature oocytes, and presumably contribute to oocyte quality; however, its physiological role remains unclear. We studied the significance of Ca ^(2+) oscillations in ovarian functions using extramitochondrial citrate synthase ( eCs )-deficient (KO) female mice. In wild-type mice, the percentage of Ca ^(2+) oscillation-induced oocytes gradually decreased during their juvenile period, and dropped at the beginning of their adult period,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Ce</em> -NeRV3D - a <em>C. elegans</em> Neuron RNA-seq Visualization tool in 3D]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Caenorhabditis elegans provides a tractable model for neural circuit studies, with complete connectomes and single-cell transcriptomic atlases available. Here, we present Ce -NeRV3D ( C. elegans Neuron RNA-seq Visualization tool in 3D), a Blender plug-in that allows visualizing the expression patterns of an unlimited number of genes within the worm's 3D nervous system. The tool enables users to explore the spatial distribution of gene co-expression with customizable color mapping, overlay...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41210177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A prospective evaluation of the inoculation of homogenised tissue and bone biopsies in blood culture bottles for the diagnosis of orthopaedic-device-related infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fracture-related infections (FRIs) and periprosthetic joint infections (PJIs) occur in nearly 2 % of patients with orthopaedic devices, contributing to significant morbidity and mortality. Effective microbiological diagnosis of these infections remains challenging, with the homogenisation of bone/tissue biopsies recognised as the most reliable pre-analytical procedure. This prospective study compared the inoculation of homogenised samples into a BacT/ALERT ^(^(®)) VIRTUO ^(^(®)) system using FA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RapTB: a lung-derived hemoglobin fragment with activity against <em>Mycobacterium tuberculosis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis (TB) remains difficult to treat due to the need for prolonged multidrug therapy and the global rise of drug-resistant Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb) strains. Endogenous antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) have emerged as promising candidates for host-directed therapies. Given the pulmonary nature of TB, we hypothesized that human lung tissue contains peptides with intrinsic antimycobacterial activity. We screened a peptide library derived from human lung tissue and identified a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A new triclinic polymorph of 6,6'-{(1<em>E</em>,1<em>E</em>')-[(1,2-di-phenyl-ethane-1,2-di-yl)bis-(aza-neylyl-idene)]bis-(methane-ylyl-idene)}bis-(2-chloro-phenol)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The redetermined structure of a new polymorph of 6,6'-{(1E,1E')-[(1,2-di-phenyl-ethane-1,2-di-yl)bis-(aza-neylyl-idene)]bis-(methane-ylyl-idene)}bis-(2-chloro-phenol), C(28)H(22)Cl(2)N(2)O(2) was reported. The title compound was synthesized under microwave irradiation at 90 K, within 10 min. The asymmetric unit comprises a potentially tetra-dentate Schiff base ligand that crystallizes in the triclinic system with space group P1. The structure displays intra-molecular O-H⋯N hydrogen bonding,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal structures of the silver iodide sulfates Ag<sub>3</sub>ISO<sub>4</sub> and Ag<sub>4</sub>I<sub>2</sub>SO<sub>4</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The crystal structures of two phases in the AgI-Ag(2)SO(4) system, Ag(3)ISO(4)(AgI:Ag(2)SO(4) = 1:1; systematic name: tris-ilver iodide sulfate), and Ag(4)I(2)SO(4) (AgI:Ag(2)SO(4) = 2:1; systematic name: tetra-silver diiodide sulfate), were determined by single-crystal X-ray diffraction. The crystal structure model of Ag(3)ISO(4) contains triangularly arranged Ag atoms in zigzag ladder chains extending parallel to the a axis. The Ag zigzag ladder chains alternate with rows of SO(4) groups,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of knee flexion angle on infrapatellar fat pad hemoglobin during isometric quadriceps exercise]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[Purpose] This study aimed to elucidate the optimal knee flexion angles and contraction intensities for isometric quadriceps exercises to enhance the hemoglobin concentration in the infrapatellar fat pad. [Participants and Methods] This observational, cross-sectional study included 13 healthy young adults. Oxygenated hemoglobin in the infrapatellar fat pad was measured using near-infrared spectroscopy, and the change was calculated by subtracting the value after isometric quadriceps exercise...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The treatment efficacy of complete decongestive therapy for breast cancer-related lymphedema from the perspective of skin mechanical properties: a case study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[Purpose] To quantitatively assess skin mechanical properties in a case of breast cancer-related lymphedema (BCRL) and examine their clinical utility. [Participant and Methods] A 69-year-old female was diagnosed with BCRL of the left upper extremity. In this case, the patient was admitted to our institute for two weeks of intensive lymphedema drainage. Complex decongestive therapy (CDT), the standard treatment for lymphedema, was administered during hospitalization. Pre-intervention and at one-...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Effects of the Concurrent Ingestion of Rosuvastatin and Magnesium Oxide: A Multicenter, Randomized, Parallel-Group Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The concurrent use of RSV and MgO did not significantly impact the reduction in LDL-C levels compared with the staggered administration. Simplifying administration without altering efficacy can improve medication adherence, particularly in elderly patients and those with polypharmacy, by reducing treatment complexity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiparametric cardiac magnetic resonance evaluation of myocardial involvement in Duchenne muscular dystrophy: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Duchenne muscular dystrophy (DMD) is a progressive X-linked disorder characterized by degeneration of both skeletal and cardiac muscles. Myocardial involvement is a leading cause of mortality and often progresses subclinically due to patients' limited physical activity. We report the case of a 15-year-old boy with DMD who exhibited asymptomatic left ventricular dysfunction. Cardiac magnetic resonance imaging (CMR) revealed diffuse systolic impairment with reduced circumferential strain....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209090/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Fiber-Tape Flexible Fixation for Chronic Lisfranc Injuries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The fiber tape fixation device under early full weightbearing protocols led to short-term improvements in pain, function, and radiographic stability for chronic Lisfranc injuries, with no observed complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41209071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyphenol-Mediated Antibody Functionalization of Titanium Peroxide Nanoparticles for Cancer Cell Targeting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell targeting would benefit various biotechnological applications such as disease diagnosis and cancer therapy. However, efficiently functionalizing nanoparticles with targeting ligands such as antibodies remains challenging. For example, poly(acrylic acid)-modified titanium peroxide NPs (PAATiOx) have shown promising radiosensitizing effects but suffer from poor tumor accumulation due to a lack of targeting. Herein, we developed a simple, one-pot process to noncovalently graft anti-CD44...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Porous Organic Frameworks Utilizing Halogen···Halogen Interactions of X4-tetra[2,3]Thienylene (X = Br, I): Guest Dynamics and Dielectric Response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[X4-tetrabromo[2,3]thienylene (1, Br4-tetra[2,3]thienylene) and X4-tetraiodotetra[2,3]thienylene (2, I4-tetra[2,3]thienylene) were used to investigate the formation of various guest inclusion crystals through intermolecular halogen···halogen (X···X) interactions and the dynamics of guest molecules. 1 and 2 formed host-guest crystals with aromatic molecules such as benzene (Bz), toluene (Tol), anisole (An), and chlorobenzene (ClBz). X-ray crystal structure analysis revealed the formation of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-Simple and Cost-Effective Synthesis of Highly Stable, Biocompatible, Carboxylic-Functionalized Gold Nanoparticles by Pamoic Acid for Advanced Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This personal account offers a detailed and creative comparison of methods for synthesizing gold nanoparticles (AuNPs) using pamoic acid (PA) and, crucially, states what this route delivers in practice. Specifically, we show that the PA-capped approach enables (i) one-pot, room-temperature synthesis with intrinsic carboxylate functionalization and no thiolated linkers; (ii) decade-scale colloidal stability; (iii) reproducible size control from ~10 to 15 nm spheres to ~75 nm via pH/seed tuning,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Rapid Review of International Evaluations of interRAI Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The implementation of interRAI systems is often influenced by factors including healthcare priorities, policy and service requirements, fragmentation of care systems, and existing data standards. Utilizing a rapid review methodology, PubMed was searched for publications, and senior fellows in countries that implemented or piloted interRAI systems shared reports with a total of 40 papers retained and reviewed. Strengths, barriers, and recommendations were extracted. Comprehensive standardized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infrared Photothermal Heterodyne Imaging in Thermally Thick Medium for Thermo-optic Property Characterizations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Measuring temperature fields in semitransparent media requires the knowledge of material thermo-optic properties. While the current techniques are well established for isothermal thin films, they remain unexplored for thick media where temperature gradients need to be considered. This study proposes to generalize the current methods of infrared heterodyne photothermal imaging to thick media by combining transmittance measurements and thermo-optic modeling to measure simultaneously the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Isogenic Human Myoblast Cell Model for Cystinosis Myopathy Reveals Alteration of Key Myogenic Regulatory Proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Muscle-specific complications are often overlooked in systemic cystinosis treatment. We show that defective CTNS function impairs effective cystine mobilization from lysosomes, thereby affecting the protein levels of myogenic regulators. A deeper understanding of the molecular mechanisms underlying cystinosis myopathy holds promise for the development of targeted, personalized therapies to improve the quality of life for patients living with cystinosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualizing Thiol Stress Responses in Cells with a Water-Soluble Raman Sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate quantification of intracellular thiols in live cells remains challenging owing to the inherent properties of fluorescent probes, such as signal saturation, photobleaching, and dye aggregation, despite the development of numerous thiol-detecting probes. Here, we present (E)-2-cyano-3-isopropylacrylamide (iPrCAA) as a ratiometric Raman probe for quantifying and visualizing intracellular thiol concentrations. iPrCAA is the smallest thiol-detecting probe currently available for live-cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoinduced decarboxylation in fluorescent proteins: charge-transfer states and structure-function relationship]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoinduced decarboxylation of acidic amino acids near the chromophore is observed in various fluorescent protein variants, including avGFP, PA-GFP, DsRed, LSSmOrange, and PSLSSmKate. While a mechanism has been proposed and theoretically supported for GFPs, its generalization to other variants remains unclear. This study investigates the decarboxylation mechanism across different fluorescent proteins, with a particular focus on the red fluorescent proteins DsRed and PSLSSmKate, to establish a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["The 'yay' feeling never faded, especially because I felt the improvement": understanding adherence to a foot strengthening training in older adults through thematic analysis of interviews]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adherence to a foot strengthening program is influenced by factors that change over the course of the intervention. These factors are linked to typical phases encountered consecutively by the participants. The last phase involves the exercises becoming habitual practice, which is, like the second-to-last phase, not reached by every participant. This timeline and the influencing factors offer professionals a tool to approach individuals appropriately to maximize adherence to a foot...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mentalizing under maternal stress: Using a baby simulator to investigate the impact of child-focused distress on maternal mentalizing and arousal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parental mentalizing, or the parent's capacity to think about the child as having an inner psychological world, has been shown to play an important role in sensitive parenting and child socioemotional development. Studies suggest that high levels of stress impair (parental) mentalizing, yet surprisingly few studies have experimentally investigated this. The present study aimed to address this gap by investigating the impact of child-focused stress on parental mentalizing measured using a newly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silyl Lewis Acid-Catalyzed 5-<em>endo-trig</em> Remote Aryl Rearrangement Enabling Dual Migration of Anisole and Amide Groups of <em>N</em>-Cinnamyl-<em>N</em>-alkoxybenzyl Sulfonamides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A silyl Lewis acid-catalyzed 5-endo-trig remote aryl rearrangement of N-cinnamyl-N-alkoxybenzyl sulfonamides in the presence of an oxidant has been developed, affording 5-substituted oxazolidines in high yields. This reaction proceeds through the dearomatization of the arene moiety on the alkoxybenzyl group. Furthermore, derivatization of the oxazolidine product via terminal carbon-selective ring opening of the corresponding aziridine intermediate with various nucleophiles triggers a dual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous <em>In Situ</em> Detection of Ferroptosis-Related Multiple Molecules in Tissue Slices Using Thin-Layer Chromatography Tracing and Raman Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In situ detection of glutathione (GSH) and Fe^(2+) in tissue samples is extremely difficult using conventional mass spectrometry imaging owing to their instability as chemical species. To address this issue, we developed a method for the simultaneous in situ detection of ferroptosis-related molecules in frozen tissue sections using Raman spectroscopy, which is advantageous for multicomponent analysis. This methodology employs thin-layer chromatography (TLC) functionalized with a probe cocktail...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visible-Light-Driven Silylation of C(sp<sup>2</sup>)-O Bonds with Silylboranes via Nickel Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing a general and efficient method for C(sp²)-O bond silylation that tolerates broad silyl groups under mild conditions remains a key challenge. Here, we report that naphthol and phenol derivatives bearing -OPO(3)^(t)Bu(2) and -OC(O)N^(i)Pr(2) leaving groups undergo silylation with silylboranes using a Ni(0) catalyst with no added ligand via C-O bond cleavage. Blue LED irradiation markedly accelerates the reaction, broadening the applicable silyl groups under ambient conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autonomic responses to proprioceptive and visual errors during single-trial reach adaptation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The autonomic nervous system (ANS) plays a crucial role in coordinating brain and bodily responses to cope with unexpected events. Extensive research in cognitive control has demonstrated that error-induced responses in peripheral autonomic measures, such as pupil diameter and heart rate, correlate with the quality of the subsequent behavioral adjustment. Here, we perform ANS measurements during a motor learning task to investigate error-induced phasic ANS responses in implicit motor learning....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indigenous perspectives of a culturally tailored dietary intervention: Qualitative findings from the CHEERS study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A nutritious diet is an important protective factor against hypertension and cardiovascular disease. However, there are substantial barriers to healthy eating within American Indian (AI) communities resulting from colonization, the effects of which are still present today in systemic inequities. To address these inequities, many AI communities work toward restoration of access to and knowledge of traditional (i.e. pre-colonial) foods. The Chickasaw Healthy Eating Environments Research Study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The prevalence of Schizophrenia in Brazil: Social Vulnerability as a Key Consideration for Care and Policy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Schizophrenia is observed across all regions of Brazil, affecting approximately 547,202 individuals. Findings on social determinants replicate previous results. The overrepresentation of socially vulnerable groups underscores the need to address social determinants of health and implement supportive policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of <em>Streptococcus pneumoniae</em><em>-</em>Specific Proteins by Surface-Shaving Proteomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Streptococcus pneumoniae (pneumococcus) is a prominent cause of bacterial pneumonia, meningitis, and septicemia, causing high morbidity and high mortality, particularly in children and the elderly. In this study, proteomics- and genomics-based approaches were used for the identification of pneumococcal protein and peptide biomarkers of S. pneumoniae for diagnostics and prospective targets for treatment. Through a pan-genome analysis, 11 S. pneumoniae strains, demonstrating genetic variation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BBATProt: a framework predicting biological function with enhanced feature extraction via interpretable deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate prediction of protein and peptide functions from amino acid sequences is essential for understanding biological processes and advancing biomolecular engineering. Due to the limitations of experimental methods, computational approaches, particularly machine learning, have gained significant attention. However, many existing tools are task-specific and lack adaptability. Here, we propose a BERT-BiLSTM-Attention-TCN Protein Function Prediction Framework (BBATProt), a versatile framework...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncertainty-aware genomic classification of Alzheimer's disease: a transformer-based ensemble approach with Monte Carlo dropout]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) has complex genetic factors that make accurate prediction from genomic data challenging. Current methods lack confidence estimates for their predictions. Our objective is to develop and evaluate an uncertainty-aware deep learning framework for AD prediction that can identify which predictions are reliable. We developed Transformer-based, Uncertainty-aware, Ensemble Network (TrUE-Net), a deep learning framework that combines transformer and random forest models to predict...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A machine learning framework using urinary biomarkers for pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma prediction with post hoc validation via single-cell transcriptomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC) is a highly lethal cancer with a poor prognosis, thus emphasizing the need for early and accurate diagnostic tools. In this study, we propose a comparative study approach to understand how machine learning (ML) modeling using urinary biomarkers combined with demographic data can predict PDAC. The study also utilized a single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq) analysis to assess and understand gene expressions of included biomarkers. With inclusion of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rehabilitation needs and healthcare utilization of adults with cerebral palsy: A mixed methods study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PurposeThis study aimed to understand and describe the rehabilitation and care complexity needs of adults with cerebral palsy (CP) receiving care in a pediatric healthcare setting.MethodsThis was an exploratory sequential mixed-methods study. Qualitative data included 20 semi-structured interviews with adults with CP and caregivers. Quantitative data included electronic health record data from adults with CP who were active pediatric rehabilitation medicine (PRM) patients over a two-year period...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pediatric Hepatitis-Associated Aplastic Anemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatitis-associated aplastic anemia (HAAA) is a rare but life-threatening disorder that requires early recognition and intervention. Pediatricians play a critical role in identifying cases where acute hepatitis transitions to severe bone marrow failure. This review presents the diagnostic and therapeutic complexities associated with HAAA, emphasizing the importance of a multidisciplinary approach. Key topics include the pathophysiology of immune-mediated marrow suppression, diagnostic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Whole-Population Study of National Trends in Child Abuse and Neglect by Sex, Race, and Ethnicity in the US]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, child maltreatment declined for confirmed cases and remain unchanged for referrals. Disparities persisted, particularly for Black children. This group with the most room for improvement experienced none, whereas that with least room for decline-Asian, Native Hawaiian, and Other Pacific Islander individuals-experienced improvements. Progress is needed in combating drivers of maltreatment, particularly poverty, and in targeting differential barriers to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2024 Diagnostic Criteria for Multiple Sclerosis-A Unified Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More Firearms, More Firearm Deaths of Pregnant Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Detection of Dementia in Primary Care: A Randomized Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This randomized clinical trial found that the combined approach was effective at scale for the early detection of ADRD in primary care settings. This is an important feature in busy primary care settings that can benefit both the health care system and patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and Risk Factors of Epilepsy Among Older Adults in the US Medicare Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Our findings highlight the spatial heterogeneity of epilepsy burden in the US Medicare population and underscore the importance of contextual SEDH factors, such as sleep, mobility, and infrastructure, in shaping disease patterns. These insights may help guide targeted public health interventions and resource allocation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Views of Aging and Symptoms of Posttraumatic Stress Disorder among Older Adult War Veterans in the Context of Renewed War]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: For aging combat veterans, experiencing renewed war in old age can exacerbate coping with age-related challenges. The present study sought to examine how past and current war-related stressors affect long-term trajectories of PTSD symptoms and views of aging (VoA) among a sample of older adult war veterans during wartime.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baseline neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio predicts drug retention of IL-6 inhibitors and JAK inhibitors in rheumatoid arthritis: the ANSWER cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with elevated baseline NLR values, aIL-6R and JAKi may offer superior drug retention compared with TNFi when initiating b/tsDMARD therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capturing trophectoderm-like stem cells enables step-wisely remodeling of placental development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The trophectoderm produced from totipotent blastomeres initiates trophoblast development, while placental deficiencies can cause pregnancy disorders. Yet, a culture system that fully recapitulates the entire placenta development is still lacking, greatly limiting related studies. Here, we captured mouse trophectoderm-like stem cells (TELSCs), which can give rise to all trophoblast lineages and be applied to generate trophoblast organoids. We achieved the induction and maintenance of TELSCs from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of circadian genes in predicting immunotherapy response and survival outcomes in cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Core circadian genes represent promising candidate biomarkers for both cancer survival risk stratification and immunotherapy response prediction. They further enable the development of high-accuracy machine learning models to predict immunotherapy responses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Psychology in Academic Health Centers (APAHC) 2025 Biennial Conference Abstracts, Impact of Psychology in Complex Healthcare Systems: Opportunities, Innovation, and Intentional Growth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41212460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110142121&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>