<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:34:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Cryotherapy and Thermotherapy Using an E-TEET on Pain, Stress, and Satisfaction Among Patients and Healthcare Providers During Intravenous Catheterization: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Intravenous catheterization is a common nursing procedure, although it is invasive and may cause pain and stress. Non-pharmacological interventions such as cryotherapy and thermotherapy have been explored, but practical and effective options remain limited. Purpose: This study aimed to evaluate the effects of cryotherapy and thermotherapy using the Enhanced Thermoelectric Element Tourniquet (E-TEET) a device equipped with a temperature-controlled plate and wireless charging on pain,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Light Scattering for Assessing Aggregation in [<sup>177</sup>Lu]Lu-DOTA-Trastuzumab: A Quality Control Approach for Radioimmunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radioimmunotherapy (RIT) delivers radionuclides to tumors through antibody-based targeting. However, radiolabeling with high-linear energy transfer (LET) isotopes like Lu-177 can induce aggregation, reducing antibody stability and bioactivity. In this study, we evaluated [^(177)Lu]Lu-DOTA-Trastuzumab, a HER2-targeting radioimmunoconjugate, to assess how conjugation chemistry, radiolabeling conditions, and purification methods affect aggregation and therapeutic performance. Dynamic light...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liquid Metal Particles-Graphene Core-Shell Structure Enabled Hydrogel-Based Triboelectric Nanogenerators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of flexible and self-powered electronic systems requires triboelectric materials that combine high charge retention, mechanical compliance, and stable dielectric properties. Here, we report a redox reaction approach to prepare liquid metal particle-reduced graphene oxide (LMP@rGO) core-shell structures and introduce into a poly(acrylic acid) (PAA) hydrogel to create a high-performance triboelectric layer. The spontaneous interfacial reaction between gallium oxide of LMP and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vanillin Beyond Flavor: Therapeutic Potentials and Emerging Applications in Hydrogel-Based Biomaterials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vanillin (4-hydroxy-3-methoxybenzaldehyde) is widely recognized for its aromatic flavor and established pharmacological properties, including antioxidant, antimicrobial, anti-inflammatory, and anticancer effects. While these biological activities underpin its therapeutic potential, recent advances have expanded the application of vanillin into the field of biomaterials. In particular, vanillin's unique chemical structure enables its use as a multifunctional building block for the development of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomimetic Strategies for Bone Regeneration: Smart Scaffolds and Multiscale Cues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bone regeneration remains difficult due to the complex bone microenvironment and the limited healing capacity of large defects. Biomimetic strategies offer promising solutions by using advanced 3D scaffolds guided by natural tissue cues. Recent advances in additive manufacturing, nanotechnology, and tissue engineering now allow the fabrication of hierarchical scaffolds that closely mimic native bone. Smart scaffold systems combine materials with biochemical and mechanical signals. These features...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SHIELD: A Spin-Coated Hydrophobic Interface for Extended Low-Fouling Durability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-specific protein adsorption compromises the accuracy of biosensor measurements. Although hydrophilic and zwitterionic surface modifications have been proposed as solutions, their practical implementation is hindered by their chemical instability and complex synthesis routes. To address these limitations, we developed a simpler yet effective alternative: a fluorinated copolymer-based hydrophobic coating termed SHIELD. The copolymer was synthesized from 2,2,2-trifluoroethyl methacrylate, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for DESCIDE-RD: Determining Effectiveness of Shared Decision Making in Drug Therapy Selection for Rheumatic Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The availability of biologic agents and Janus kinase (JAK) inhibitors has expanded therapeutic options for rheumatic diseases, and international guidelines now recommend shared decision-making (SDM) to guide treatment selection. This study will evaluate whether a structured SDM model enhances patients' perceptions of SDM when selecting biologic agents or JAK inhibitors for rheumatoid arthritis (RA) and ankylosing spondylitis (AS), compared to standard care. This open-label, multicentre,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Redox-Active NiO<sub>x</sub>-Catalyzed Li<sup>+</sup> Capture-Extraction Strategy for tBP-Free Spiro-OMeTAD Enables Exceptional Damp-Heat Stability in Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For the spiro-OMeTAD-based hole-transporting layer (HTL), despite its widespread implementation, the pragmatic deployment of perovskite solar cells remains profoundly constrained by multifaceted intrinsic challenges-most notably the inclusion of tBP and the deleterious migration behaviors of Li^(+) ions-which collectively undermine long-term thermal stability, as even advanced encapsulation schemes fail to arrest irreversible performance degradation. Here, we introduce a redox-catalytic strategy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FAM168B identified as a novel candidate target for chimeric antigen receptor T cell-based cancer therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging-related diseases, particularly cancer, remain major health challenges that demand new therapeutic strategies. Chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cell therapy has emerged as a powerful modality in immuno-oncology, enabling patient-derived T cells to be engineered ex vivo to recognize and eliminate tumor antigens. Here, we identify FAM168B (family with sequence similarity 168 member B, also known as myelin-associated neurite-outgrowth inhibitor, MANI) and its homolog FAM168A (tongue cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anticancer agent FTY720 upregulates cell cycle regulator BTG2 via the SET/TAF-Iβ -PP2A-SMAD3 signaling pathway and induces G2/M arrest in leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinically relevant effective dose k-factors for brain CT derived from Korean body size phantoms and National CT Dose Index Registry Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global increase in computed tomography (CT) use, highlighted by a 40% growth in South Korea over the past decade, has made CT a significant source of medical radiation exposure, emphasizing the need for accurate effective dose (ED) estimation. This study aimed to develop population-specific effective dose conversion factors (k-factors) for brain CT examinations across the range of tube voltages used in Korean hospitals. Clinical dose parameters were obtained from the Korean National CT Dose...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjuvant cytokine-induced killer cell immunotherapy in hepatocellular carcinoma: real-world data and 9-year extended follow-up of a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Adjuvant CIK cell therapy significantly improved RFS in both a RWD study and a 9-year extended RCT follow-up, supporting its reproducible benefit in reducing recurrence after curative treatment of HCC. These consistent findings provide strong evidence for the clinical utility of CIK therapy as a durable adjuvant immunotherapeutic strategy for HCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laparoscopic versus open liver resection for huge hepatocellular carcinoma (≥ than 10 cm): a multicenter propensity score-matched analysis from Eastern and Western referral centers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MILS for huge HCC can be safe and effective in selected cases in referral centers, being able to reduce intraoperative blood loss, and to shorten median hospital stay.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bisphosphonate treatment for secondary osteoporosis in children, youth, and young adults: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic illnesses and their treatments in childhood pose significant risks of bone fragility due to osteoporosis. Bisphosphonates (BP) are commonly used for treatment, yet evidence remains limited and heterogeneous. This systematic review aims to consolidate current empirical evidence on BP efficacy and safety in children, youth and young adults aged ≤ 21 years with secondary osteoporosis. Ovid MEDLINE and EMBASE, PubMed, Web of Science, Cumulative Index to Nursing and Allied Health, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Menopausal Hormone Therapy and Cancer: A Nationwide Retrospective Cohort Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MHT increased overall cancer risk, with EPT and ET elevating risks, unlike tibolone. MHT users faced higher breast, brain, renal, and colorectal cancer risks, but lower uterine cancer risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic Structure Modulations in Ion-Exchanged Hydroxyapatite Investigated by HRTEM and Single Image Denoising]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydroxyapatite (HAP) is widely utilized in various applications, where its properties are strongly regulated by ionic substitution. However, the atomic-scale structural origins of such modulation remain poorly understood. Although high-resolution transmission electron microscopy (HRTEM) enables direct structural characterization, achieving atomic-scale resolution in HAP is challenging due to its beam sensitivity. Low-dose imaging mitigates beam-induced damage but often suffers insufficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CT Screening Challenges Amid Rising Threat of Lung Cancer in Individuals Who Have Never Smoked]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung cancer in individuals who have never smoked (LCINS) constitutes a growing global health challenge, accounting for 10%-25% of lung cancer cases and ranking as the fifth leading cause of cancer-related death worldwide. LCINS is especially common in East Asian women. LCINS arises from multiple nonsmoking-related risk factors, including secondhand smoke, air pollution, radon exposure, genetic susceptibility, and aging. LCINS exhibits unique biologic characteristics, with a predominance of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing CT-derived Normative Liver and Spleen Volumes for Children: Validation in Regional and International Datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Volumetric evaluation of liver and spleen size is useful, yet pediatric reference values remain limited and lack external validation. Purpose To establish normative liver and spleen volumes from contrast-enhanced CT in children and validate them in external regional and international datasets. Materials and Methods In this retrospective study, contrast-enhanced abdominal CT scans (patient age, 2-18 years) from Asan Medical Center and Pusan National University Yangsan Hospital (January...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) in Saxitoxin Research: The Next Frontier for Understanding Marine Dinoflagellate Toxin Biosynthesis and Evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Saxitoxin (STX) is one of the most potent marine neurotoxins, produced by several species of freshwater cyanobacteria and marine dinoflagellates. Although omics-based approaches have advanced our understanding of STX biosynthesis in recent decades, the origin, regulation, and ecological drivers of STX in dinoflagellates remain poorly resolved. Specifically, dinoflagellate STX biosynthetic genes (sxt) are extremely fragmented, inconsistently expressed, and unevenly distributed between toxic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Major Environmental Parameters on Patulin Production by <em>Penicillium expansum</em> OM1 and Its Growth on Apple Puree Agar Media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patulin is a mycotoxin produced mainly by Penicillium expansum on apples. P. expansum is a fruit pathogen that can cause apple soft rot. However, much is unknown about the characteristics of P. expansum and influence of major environmental parameters on its patulin production and growth on apple puree agar media (APAM). In this study, we evaluated the influence of pH, temperature, and relative humidity (RH) on patulin production by P. expansum OM1 and its growth (colony diameter and mycelial dry...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Evolution of Nanoparticle Regulation: A Meta-Analysis of Research Trends and Historical Parallels (2015-2025)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: We analyzed nanoparticle regulation research to examine the evolution of regulatory frameworks, identify major thematic structures, and evaluate current challenges in the governance of rapidly advancing nanotechnologies. By drawing parallels with the historical development of radiation regulation, the study aimed to contextualize emerging regulatory strategies and derive lessons for future governance. Methods: A total of 9095 PubMed-indexed articles published between January 2015 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Paeonia lactiflora</em> Callus-Derived Polynucleotides Enhance Collagen Accumulation in Human Dermal Fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant-derived polynucleotides (PNs) have emerged as promising regenerative biomolecules; however, their mechanisms remain less defined than those of salmon-derived polydeoxyribonucleotides (S-PDRNs). Here, we extracted polynucleotides from Paeonia lactiflora callus (PL-PN) and evaluated their biological effects on human dermal fibroblasts. PL-PN treatment increased cell viability and pro-collagen I α1 secretion. PL-PN enhanced adenosine A2A receptor expression and activated the cyclic adenosine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phlorotannins from <em>Ecklonia cava</em> Regulate Dual Signaling Pathways, IL-17RA/Act1 and ERK1/2, to Suppress Ovarian Cancer Progression and Tumor-Associated Macrophage Activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Collectively, these findings demonstrate that E. cava-derived phlorotannins exert anti-metastatic effects through dual regulation of IL-17RA/Act1 and ERK1/2 signaling pathways, offering mechanistic insight into their therapeutic potential against inflammation-driven malignancies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plant-Derived Secondary Metabolites Tetrahydropalmatine and Rutaecarpine Alleviate Paclitaxel-Induced Neuropathic Pain via TRPV1 and TRPM8 Modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Chemotherapy-induced peripheral neuropathy (CIPN) is a major dose-limiting adverse effect of paclitaxel and is characterized by cold and mechanical allodynia. Effective therapeutic strategies for CIPN remain limited. This study evaluated the analgesic potential of Corydalis yanhusuo (CY) and Evodia rutaecarpa (ER), as well as their major alkaloids tetrahydropalmatine (THP) and rutaecarpine, in a mouse model of paclitaxel-induced neuropathic pain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Review on Medium- and Long-Chain Fatty Acid-Derived Metabolites: From Energy Sources to Metabolic Signals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Medium- and long-chain fatty acids (MLFAs) are increasingly recognized not only as metabolic substrates but also as precursors of diverse bioactive metabolites generated through host and microbial transformations. Recent advances in analytical chemistry and microbiome research have revealed that gut microorganisms catalyze extensive modifications of dietary MLFAs-producing hydroxylated, conjugated, and keto-fatty acids with enhanced potency toward host receptors. These metabolites exhibit dual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extracellular Water and Phase Angle, Markers of Heightened Inflammatory State, and Their Extrapolative Potential for Body Composition Outcomes in Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Aim: Extracellular-to-total body water ratio (ECW/TBW) and phase angle (PhA, PA) reflect hydration and cellular health, but their relationship with bone, muscle, and fat, as primary components of body composition, is not fully elucidated. This study aimed to evaluate sex-specific differences in body composition and assess the diagnostic potential of ECW/TBW and PhA for identifying low bone/muscle mass, as well as increased fat mass, in generally healthy adults. Methods: This post hoc...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TRP Channels from Sensory Coding to Physiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sensory systems allow the detection of external and internal cues essential for adaptive responses. Chemosensation exemplifies this integration, guiding feeding, mating, and toxin avoidance while also influencing physiological regulation. Across taxa, chemical detection relies on diverse receptor families, and emerging evidence reveals that transient receptor potential (TRP) channels-traditionally associated with phototransduction, thermosensation, and mechanotransduction-also mediate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinction Between <em>Aspergillus oryzae</em> and Aflatoxigenic <em>Aspergillus flavus</em> by Rapid PCR Method Based on the Comparative Sequence Analysis of the Aflatoxin Biosynthesis Gene Cluster]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aspergillus oryzae and Aspergillus flavus are closely related species within the Aspergillus section Flavi, sharing approximately 99.5% genomic similarity. Despite this similarity, they differ markedly in their ability to produce aflatoxin, a carcinogenic mycotoxin synthesized by the aflatoxin biosynthesis gene cluster (ABGC). Species and strains included within section Flavi display diverse deletion patterns in the ABGC at the sequence level. In this study, we performed an in-depth comparative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Palmitic Acid Induces Inflammatory Environment and Is Involved in Pyroptosis in a Human Dental Pulp Cell Line]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: We investigated whether palmitic acid (PA) induced the expression of inflammatory cytokines and was involved in pyroptosis in a human dental pulp cell line. Methods: Human dental pulp cells cultured in Minimum Essential Medium Alpha (αMEM) were treated with 1 µg/mL LPS and/or PA (100, 300 and 500 µM). As a control, αMEM was added in the culture medium. The WST-1 assay was performed to assess cell proliferation, and morphological changes in cells were examined. RNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Yu, C.; Song, Y.S. Characterization of Phase Change Materials Fabricated with Cross-Linked Graphene Aerogels. <em>Gels</em> 2022, <em>8</em>, 572]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the original publication [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydroxyapatite-Mediated Mechanical Modulation of GelMA Hydrogels Influences Osteogenic Differentiation of 3D Spheroids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Substrate stiffness critically regulates osteogenic differentiation, yet systematic identification of optimal mechanical conditions in three-dimensional culture remains limited. This study investigated how hydroxyapatite (HAp)-mediated mechanical modulation of gelatin methacryloyl (GelMA) hydrogels influences osteogenic differentiation of encapsulated SAOS-2 spheroids. GelMA hydrogels with HAp at 5, 10, and 15 μg/mL were characterized for mechanical properties and used to encapsulate pre-formed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogels and Organogels for Local Anesthetic Delivery: Advances, Challenges, and Translational Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gel-based depots are increasingly recognized as platforms to extend the intratissue residence of local anesthetics (LAs) while reducing systemic exposure. Hydrogels, organogels, and emerging bigels represent three distinct architectures defined by their continuous phases and drug-matrix interactions. Hydrogels provide hydrated polymer networks with predictable injectability, tunable degradation, and diffusion- or stimulus-responsive release, enabling sustained analgesia in perineural,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioinspired Heat Exchangers: A Multi-Scale Review of Thermo-Hydraulic Performance Enhancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heat exchangers are central to energy and process industries, yet performance is bounded by the trade-off between higher heat transfer and greater pressure drop. This review targets indirect-type heat exchangers and organizes bioinspired strategies through a multi-scale lens of surface, texture, and network scales. It provides a structured comparison of their thermo-hydraulic behaviors and evaluation methods. At the surface scale, control of wettability and liquid-infused interfaces suppresses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compressive Strength Optimization of 3D-Printed Voronoi Trabecular Bone Using the Taguchi Method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The surge in demand for patient-specific orthopedic implants necessitates the precise optimization of design and processing parameters for artificial trabecular bone. This research utilizes Voronoi-based porous structures to replicate the irregular geometry characteristic of natural trabecular bone. All specimens were fabricated through fused deposition modeling (FDM) with polylactic acid (PLA). The study systematically investigated the influence of four primary parameters, namely build...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of RAMPA Therapy on Nasal Cavity Expansion and Paranasal Drainage: Fluid Mechanics Analysis, CAE Simulation, and a Case Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Impaired mucus drainage from the paranasal sinuses is often associated with nasal obstruction and reduced airway function in growing patients. Orthopedic maxillary protraction and expansion techniques can enhance airway dynamics, but their underlying fluid-structure mechanisms remain insufficiently understood. Objective: To validate that the Right Angle Maxillary Protraction Appliance (RAMPA), combined with a semi-rapid maxillary expansion (sRME) intraoral device gHu-1, improves...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase 2, open-label, noncomparative clinical trial evaluating safety and efficacy of posaconazole in pediatric patients with proven/probable invasive aspergillosis or possible invasive fungal disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children with invasive aspergillosis (IA) experience significant morbidity and mortality. Posaconazole is a broad-spectrum triazole antifungal agent indicated for IA treatment in adolescents and adults. A phase 2, open-label, noncomparative, multinational clinical trial in pediatric participants (2-to-<18 years old, body weight ≥10 kg) with possible, probable, or proven IA was conducted. Participants received intravenous posaconazole for ≥1 week, after which they could switch to oral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced Numbers of Blood Dendritic Cell Antigen 3 Positive Dendritic Cells in the Nasal Mucosa Contribute to Severe Inflammation in Patients with Allergic Rhinitis and Chronic Rhinosinusitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundDendritic cells (DCs) are antigen-presenting cells that play a critical role in airway diseases by initiating and regulating immune responses. DCs are classified into plasmacytoid DCs (pDCs) and conventional DCs (cDCs), with the cDC lineage further divided into cDC1 and cDC2 subsets. Each subset exhibits distinct functions in immune regulation and disease pathogenesis. Thus, analyzing DC subsets is crucial for understanding the pathogenesis of airway diseases with diverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationships between Psychological Symptoms and Sociality among Toxic Humidifier Disinfectant Child Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study compares the psychological symptoms of children and sociality in the toxic humidifier disinfectant and norm groups. We examine how psychological symptoms are differentially related to sociality by the two groups. The participants included 130 toxic humidifier disinfectant survivors and 129 children in the norm group. We used the bivariate correlation and a multi-group Structural Equation Model (SEM) to explore group differences in the relationship between psychological symptoms and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shared Decision-Making for Determining Treatment Strategies in Low-Risk Thyroid Cancer: Protocol of a Multicenter Cluster-Randomized Trial (MAeSTro-SDM)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Active surveillance (AS) is recommended for low-risk papillary thyroid microcarcinoma (PTMC) in many guidelines. However, while its clinical application requires incorporation of patient values, implementing shared decision-making (SDM) in practice remains challenging. To generate reliable evidence, facilitate the integration of SDM into routine PTMC managements and improve patient satisfaction, this study developed a PTMC-specific SDM model (SM group) and aims to evaluate whether it improves...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Study Protocol of a Korean Patient-Centered Shared Decision-Making Model for Management of Severe Knee Osteoarthritis: A Multicenter Pragmatic Clinical Trial (K-SDM-KOA)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe knee osteoarthritis (KOA) involves complex, preference-sensitive treatment decisions, ranging from non-operative to surgical options. However, despite the preference-sensitive nature of KOA, existing shared decision-making (SDM) processes often lack clarity in effectively incorporating patients' values and preferences into treatment decisions. Moreover, most SDM models have been developed in western contexts, which may limit their applicability in other cultural settings. To address these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shared Decision-Making for Periodontally Compromised Teeth: Study Protocol for an Ongoing Prospective Multicenter Before-and-After Clinical Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Treatment decisions for teeth with poor periodontal prognosis are often complicated, requiring careful balancing of clinical evidence and patient values. Shared decision-making (SDM) is increasingly recognized as a beneficial approach to align clinical judgment with patient preferences. However, structured SDM implementation in dental settings remains limited. This study was designed to evaluate the effectiveness of a structured SDM protocol compared to usual care decision-making for patients...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward the Implementation of Shared Decision-Making in Korean Clinical Practice: Study Protocol for a Foundational Research Project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shared decision-making (SDM) is an essential component of patient-centered care, yet its implementation in South Korea remains limited due to a persistent physician-centered clinical culture. This project, supported by the Ministry of Health and Welfare, aims to establish a foundation for nationwide SDM implementation by developing a culturally adapted Korean SDM model and creating a framework to support its institutionalization and widespread clinical adoption. This four-year project consists...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-Modifiable Cardiovascular Risk Factors and Coronary Plaque Characteristics in Patients with Acute Coronary Syndromes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with ACS, the burden of NMRFs was not correlated with OCT-defined plaque vulnerability or the prevalence of plaque rupture, both at culprit and non-culprit lesions. Conversely, a higher number of NMRF was linked to a greater probability of calcified plaque and a lower probability of plaque erosion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of patients with idiopathic bronchiectasis in comparison to post-infectious bronchiectasis in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The characteristics of patients with idiopathic bronchiectasis might be a higher body mass index (BMI) and the history of rhinosinusitis in comparison with post-infectious bronchiectasis, potentially serving as exploratory clues to underlying systemic or non-pulmonary factors. Further research is needed to clarify their clinical significance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Length-stable fixation reduces femoral neck shortening in unstable femoral neck fractures: A retrospective comparative study of length-stable dynamic hip screw versus femoral neck system fixation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundFemoral neck shortening following internal fixation of unstable femoral neck fractures can compromise functional recovery, particularly in young, active patients. This study aimed to evaluate the efficacy of a length-stable dynamic hip screw (LSD) construct in minimizing postoperative shortening compared to the femoral neck system (FNS).MethodsA retrospective review was conducted on 65 patients with high-grade unstable femoral neck fractures treated between February 2016 and February...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Long-Term Oncologic and Perioperative Outcomes of Minimally Invasive and Open Pancreatoduodenectomy for Resectable and Borderline Resectable Pancreatic Ductal Adenocarcinoma: Exploring Type 0 Resection as a Potential Indication for MIPD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MIPD is a safe and feasible option for RPC and BRPC PDAC, with oncologic outcomes comparable to OPD. Type 0 tumors, not requiring vascular resection, may represent an optimal indication for MIPD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacially Coupled and Synergistic Effect of Ag/Co<sub>3</sub>O<sub>4</sub>-C Nanocomposites for Enhanced Oxygen Reduction (ORR) and Evolution (OER) Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overpotentials associated with the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) and oxygen evolution reaction (OER) remain key challenges hindering the practical deployment of advanced electrochemical energy conversion technologies such as alkaline fuel cells. While Pt/C demonstrates excellent ORR activity, its sluggish OER kinetics and poor durability in alkaline environments significantly limit its applicability. Herein, we report the design of an Ag/ Co(3)O(4)-C nanocomposite, synthesized via a two-step...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Patency of Hemashield Vascular Grafts Used for Middle Hepatic Vein Reconstruction During Living-Donor Liver Transplantation: A Single-Center Korean Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND The availability of homologous vein allografts is limited. Therefore, prosthetic vascular grafts can be used as alternatives for middle hepatic vein (MHV) reconstruction during living-donor liver transplantation (LDLT). This study evaluated the short- and long-term patency of MHV reconstructions using Hemashield vascular grafts and assessed their effect on post-transplant survival. MATERIAL AND METHODS This retrospective observational study included 149 adult LDLT recipients who...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of adjacent restorative material and distance on the accuracy of inlay cavity impressions with intraoral scanner: an in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Digital impression accuracy of inlay cavities was influenced by adjacent restorative material and interproximal distance, suggesting clinical consideration is needed in CAD/CAM workflows to optimize restoration fit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased vulnerability of alert responses to combined call sequences under anthropogenic noise in bird communication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Noise pollution disrupts animal communication, often via acoustic masking. Beyond masking alone, complex vocal sequences that combine distinct call types may impose additional processing challenges in noisy environments, for both conspecific and heterospecific receivers. We assessed how traffic noise differentially affects behavioral responses to Japanese tits' simple (recruitment) versus complex (combined alert-recruitment) calls in conspecifics and sympatric heterospecific tits using playback...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Overall survival of palbociclib plus endocrine therapy in Japanese patients with HR+/HER2- advanced breast cancer in the first-or second-line setting: a multicenter observational study (P-BRIDGE study)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel PSMA targeting alpha-emitting radioligand [<sup>211</sup>At]PSAt-3-Ga inhibits tumor growth and increases survival in a preclinical model of human xenograft prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the Japanese National clinical database risk calculator as a surrogate frailty assessment tool for older adults with colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The NCD Risk Calculator may serve as a practical surrogate for frailty assessment in older patients undergoing colorectal cancer surgery, particularly in resource-limited settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological study of colovesical fistula as a complication of colonic diverticulitis in Japan: an analysis of claims data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Reaction, diffusion and non-local interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mediating role of caregiver burden in the relationship between patient activities of daily living and positive aspects of caregiving among family caregivers of breast cancer-related lymphedema patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oligoclonal B cell expansion and passenger fusion genes predict response to Nivolumab in recurrent ovarian cancer: phase II Kyoto trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Transient oligoclonal expansion of B cells and passenger fusion genes might serve as predictive biomarkers of response to PD-1 blockade in ovarian cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a clinical prediction model for postpartum hemorrhage after elective cesarean section]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The model we developed can stratify the risk of postpartum hemorrhage and assist in clinical decision-making. Future studies are required to validate the performance of our model.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Significant decrease in the ionization energy of dinaphtho[2,3-<em>b</em>:2',3'-<em>f</em>]thieno[3,2-<em>b</em>]thiophene (DNTT) solid induced by a pinacolborane group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The low carrier density in organic semiconductors leads to high resistivity and contact resistance in electronic devices. Doping has been implemented to solve these issues. We describe herein a molecular modification approach to increase the carrier density. A representative p-type organic semiconductor, dinaphtho[2,3-b:2',3'-f]thieno[3,2-b]thiophene (DNTT), was modified with a pinacolborane (Bpin) group, a reactive functional group in the Suzuki-Miyaura cross-coupling reaction. The resulting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-clear-cell renal cell carcinoma has an immune cold phenotype that impacts response to immune checkpoint inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Data regarding the clinical outcomes of immune checkpoint inhibitor (ICI) therapy and tumor immune microenvironment (TIME) profiles in non-clear-cell renal cell carcinoma (nccRCC) remain limited. Herein, we retrospectively compared the effectiveness profile of first-line ICI combination therapy between clear-cell RCC (ccRCC) and nccRCC. Additionally, genome-wide gene expression and tumor-infiltrating immune cell (TIIC) profiling were performed using RNA-seq and flow cytometry, respectively. Of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rectointercostal plane block for postoperative analgesia in preperitoneal enhanced-view totally extraperitoneal umbilical hernia repair: a new indication area]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infant Immunity after Maternal Nipocalimab in Severe Hemolytic Disease of the Fetus and Newborn]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this cohort of 12 live-born infants, antenatal treatment with nipocalimab resulted in low levels of detectable drug in fetal, neonatal, and infant samples. Treatment was associated with low IgG levels at birth; however, unusual or unexpected childhood illnesses or impaired vaccine responses were not observed. (Funded by Johnson & Johnson; ClinicalTrials.gov number, NCT03842189.).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rate constants for a reactive system of astrophysical interest: a statistical study of CH<sub>2</sub><sup></sup>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A systematic investigation on the different processes involving formation, destruction and (de)excitation of specific rovibrational states of CH^(+) has been carried out based on statistical approaches. Thus, reactive collisions between C^(+)(²P) and H(2)(v, j) and between CH^(+)(v, j) and H for a large number of state-to-state transitions have been studied using a statistical quantum method and a statistical adiabatic channel model. The capabilities of such techniques for the study of the title...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Helix Ring Peptide U11 from the Venom of the Ant, <em>Tetramorium bicarinatum</em>, Acts as a Putative Pore-Forming Toxin, Not a New Kv1.3 Channel Blocker. Comment on Boy et al. A New Kv1.3 Channel Blocker from the Venom of the Ant <em>Tetramorium bicarinatum</em>. <em>Toxins</em> 2025, <em>17</em>, 379]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Boy et al [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Ecological Panel Analysis of Trends in the Geographic Disparities of the Certified Nurse and Certified Nurse Specialist in Japan from 1996 to 2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Japan introduced a certification system for Advanced Practice Nursing Workforce (APNW) in 1996. The Japanese Nursing Association formally certified two types of the APNW: Certified Nurses (CNs) and Certified Nurse Specialists (CNSs). Little is known about the geographic distribution of CNs and CNSs. Methods: We conducted an ecological panel analysis using prefecture-level data from 1996 to 2022. To assess the degree of inequality of CN and CNS among prefectures, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Tanaka et al. Relationship Between Socioeconomic Status and Organized Sports Among Primary School Children: A Gender-Based Analysis of Sports Participation. <em>Sports</em> 2025, <em>13</em>, 165]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the original publication [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive Processing Efficiency (Throughput) Improves with Aerobic Exercise and Is Independent of the Environmental Oxygenation Level: A Randomized Crossover Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aerobic exercise with eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA) may enhance cognition via cerebrovascular pathways. We tested whether mild hyperbaric oxygen (HBO; 1.41 atmospheres absolute [ATA], approximately 30% O(2)) adds to gains in cognitive processing capacity (throughput) versus normobaric normoxia (1.0 ATA, approximately 21% [20.9%] O(2)). Healthy young adults (n = 16) performed cycling exercise at 60-70% VO(2peak) for 60 min, twice weekly, for 4 weeks per environment with a 1-week washout; EPA (2170...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physicochemical and Antioxidant Alterations of Modified and Free Epigallocatechin Gallate Under Thermal Treatment in Air and Vacuum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epigallocatechin gallate (EGCG)-the most abundant catechin in green tea-is a promising component of advanced composite biomaterials. The pharmacological activity of EGCG is typically attenuated upon thermal processing, although the exact effects of heating free and modified EGCG in air and vacuum are unknown. To bridge this gap, we herein examined the effects of heating free and modified (in gelatin containing beta-tricalcium phosphate granules) EGCG in vacuum and air (100-220 °C, 1-16 h) on its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute Intravenous Astaxanthin Administration Modulates Hyperexcitability in Rat Nociceptive Secondary Sensory Neurons Induced by Inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous in vivo studies have clearly demonstrated that the intravenous administration of the carotenoid astaxanthin (AST) suppresses the excitability of rat trigeminal spinal nucleus caudalis (SpVc) neurons. This action is hypothesized to be mediated through the inhibition of both voltage-gated Ca^(2+) (Cav) channels and excitatory glutamate receptor transmission. The objective of this study was to determine whether acute intravenous administration of AST alleviates the hyperexcitability of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Onnamides A and B Suppress Hepatitis B Virus Transcription by Inhibiting Viral Promoter Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We recently reported that onnamide A, a marine-derived natural compound isolated from the sponge Theonella sp., inhibits the entry process of SARS-CoV-2 infection. However, its antiviral activity against other viruses remains largely unexplored. Here, we investigated the effects of onnamide A and its structurally related analog, onnamide B, on hepatitis B virus (HBV) infection. Using iNTCP cells, a hepatoblastoma-derived cell line permissive to HBV infection, we found that onnamides A and B...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antioxidant Clove Extract Inhibits Lipid Droplet Accumulation and Lipid Oxidation in Hepatocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Recent studies have shown that plant-based dietary extracts can prevent the formation of lipid droplets (LDs) and oxidized lipid droplets (oxLDs) in liver cells. These results indicate that these extracts might be useful in addressing metabolic dysfunction-associated fatty liver disease (MAFLD) and its more severe form, metabolic dysfunction-associated steatohepatitis (MASH). In our ongoing study, we evaluated the potential of various food extracts to inhibit the accumulation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualizing the Effect of Process Pause on Virus Entrapment During Constant Flux Virus Filtration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Virus filtration is an essential unit operation used to validate clearance of adventitious virus during the manufacture of biopharmaceutical products such as monoclonal antibodies. Obtaining at least a 10,000-fold reduction in virus particles in the permeate is challenging as monoclonal antibodies are about half the size of the virus particles. Minute virus of mice, FDA-recommended model adventitious virus, was labeled with a fluorescent dye. Laser scanning confocal microscopy was used to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward Rational Design of Ion-Exchange Nanofiber Membranes: Meso-Scale Computational Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review highlights the growing relevance of ion-exchange nanofibrous membranes (IEX-NFMs) in membrane chromatography (MC) for protein purification, emphasising their structural advantages such as high porosity, tunable surface functionality, and low-pressure drops. While the adsorption of IEX-NFMs in MC is expanding due to their potential for high throughput and rapid mass transfer, a critical limitation remains: the precise binding capacity of these membranes is not well understood....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reawakening Differentiation Therapy in Acute Myeloid Leukemia: A Comprehensive Review of ATRA-Based Combination Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[(1) Background: All-trans retinoic acid (ATRA) has transformed the treatment of acute promyelocytic leukemia (APL) by inducing terminal myeloid differentiation. However, its efficacy in non-APL acute myeloid leukemia (AML) is limited. Exploring combination strategies that enhance ATRA-induced differentiation may broaden its therapeutic potential. (2) Methods: A literature search of PubMed using the keywords "ATRA," "myeloid," and "differentiation inducer or enhancer" identified more than 500...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface-Imprinted Polymer Coupled with Diffraction Gratings for Low-Cost, Label-Free and Differential <em>E. coli</em> Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface-imprinted polymer (SIP)-based biomimetic sensors are promising for direct whole-bacteria detection; however, the commonly used fabrication approach (micro-contact imprinting) often suffers from limited imprint density, heterogeneous template distribution, and poor reproducibility. Here, we introduce a photolithography-defined master stamp featuring E. coli mimics, enabling high-density, well-oriented cavity arrays (3 × 10⁷ imprints/cm²). Crucially, the cavity arrangement is engineered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Convolutional Neural Network-Based Detection of Gait Abnormalities in Parkinson's Disease Using Fewer Plantar Sensors in a Smart Insole]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis of Parkinson's disease (PD) is crucial for slowing its progression. Gait analysis is increasingly used to detect early symptoms, with smart insoles emerging as a cost-effective and convenient tool for daily monitoring. However, smart insoles have practical limitations, including durability concerns, limited battery life, and difficulties in minimizing the number of sensors. In this study, we designed a novel deep convolutional neural network model for accurately detecting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of Structural Changes in G-Quadruplex-Forming DNA Oligonucleotides via DNA Methylation Based on Luminol Chemiluminescence Catalyzed by Myoglobin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel, label-free chemiluminescence sensing platform for CpG methylation was developed, leveraging the G-quadruplex (G4) structural sensitivity of G4-protein interactions to eliminate bisulfite conversion. This sensing system is based on the enhancement of luminol chemiluminescence generated from myoglobin upon binding to the G4-forming DNA. At the core of this biosensor is the G4-structure-dependent modulation of the peroxidase-like activity generating luminol chemiluminescence of myoglobin....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidental Cardiac Uptake on <sup>99m</sup>Tc-HMDP Bone Scintigraphy in Oncology Patients: Two Cases of Transthyretin Amyloid Cardiomyopathy with Literature Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In oncology patients, bone scintigraphy performed during routine metastatic screening may facilitate early detection of ATTRwt-CM, enabling timely diagnosis and treatment initiation, potentially improving clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41590238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From BioSkills to LifeSkills-a framework for developing life skills for non-science majors in introductory life science courses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over a decade ago, the national "Vision and Change" report articulated the critical need to reform undergraduate biology education. Since its introduction, reform efforts guided by V&C have focused primarily on the biology major, with less attention to the distinct needs of non-major students in General Education (GenEd) life science courses. For most college students, a life science course represents the only opportunity to develop scientific literacy, a critical skill for making informed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iridium-Catalyzed <em>meta</em>-Selective C-H Silylation of Arenes Enabled by Remote Regiocontrol with a Spirobipyridine Ligand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organosilicon derivatives are important compounds in industry and valuable synthetic intermediates in organic synthesis. Direct introduction of the silicon functionality is an attractive, straightforward synthetic approach to these compounds; however, previously reported catalytic silylation of arenes has suffered from poor site-selectivity. We report that an iridium catalyst in combination with a spirobipyridine ligand selectively silylates mono- and disubstituted arenes at the meta position...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sparsity based inhomogeneous sound field estimation using multiple source-regions kernel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose a method for estimating an inhomogeneous sound field from microphone array signals based on the sparsity of the source distribution. Our approach begins by defining a kernel function as a weighted combination of sub-kernels, each representing spatial correlations within a specific spherical source region. A gradient-based algorithm is developed to update the kernel weights by exploiting the sparsity. Furthermore, we propose a scheme to update the kernel parameters, specifically the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pericardial effusion requiring pericardiocentesis: A delayed manifestation of cardiac TA-TMA in neuroblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shimojilide, a Potent Potent and Selective Antiproliferative Cyclic Lipopeptide from a Marine Cyanobacterium <em>Okeania</em> sp]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shimojilide (1), a new cyclic lipopeptide, was isolated from a marine cyanobacterium Okeania sp. Its structure was elucidated by NMR and chemical derivatization, revealing a peptide-polyketide hybrid with a skipped diene and β-branched methyl group. Shimojilide (1) exhibited potent and selective antiproliferative activity with a unique JFCR39 fingerprint that poorly correlates with those of known anticancer agents, suggesting a distinct mechanism of action. Shimojilide (1) represents a promising...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attitudes of patients, relatives and professionals regarding deactivation of implantable cardioverter-defibrillators: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This review emphasises the need for individualised ICD deactivation discussions. Enhancing communication, education, and training for healthcare professionals is essential. Timely, ongoing conversations about ICD deactivation should be integrated into routine care, ensuring decisions align with patient values, especially in the final stages of life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Porphyrin-Functionalized Graphene Nanoribbons in Solution Phase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structurally defined graphene nanoribbons (sd-GNRs) have gained attention due to their alluring physical properties and potential applications in optoelectronic devices. Edge functionalization of GNRs has proven to be an effective strategy to tailor their optoelectronic properties. However, progress in this area has been hindered by challenges associated with the controlled synthesis of sd-GNRs, resulting in limited exploration of edge-functionalized variants. Here, we report the synthesis of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening and Engineering of Ancestral Sortase Es That Enable High-Fidelity Enzyme Design with Activity Trade-Off]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein grafting techniques that enable conjugation of diverse compounds to target proteins endow them with new functions. Sortase-mediated ligation (SML) is one such method in which sortases catalyze transpeptidation between a substrate protein or peptide bearing a cell wall sorting signal (CWSS) and a nucleophile containing an N-terminal triglycine motif. In this study, we identified novel sortase Es suitable for SML by combining in silico enzyme screening with ancestral sequence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ratiometric hydrostatic pressure sensing in water <em>via</em> dual emissions of a water-soluble donor-acceptor-donor triad]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A water-soluble donor-acceptor-donor triad, Dend-MCM, was developed as a ratiometric chemosensor for hydrostatic pressure. In water, the emission intensity from the locally excited state increased, whereas that from the charge-transfer state decreased owing to stronger solvation effects under high-pressure conditions. These findings enable pressure sensing in polar environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Density-velocity relation is scale-dependent in epithelial monolayers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The relationship between cell density and velocity is often assumed to be negative, reflecting crowding-induced suppression of movement. However, observations across systems reveal a more nuanced picture: while some emphasize contact inhibition of locomotion, others suggest that dense regions exhibit enhanced activity due to force generation. Here, using experimental measurements we show that density-velocity relation in epithelial monolayers is inherently scale dependent. By coarse-graining...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathological diagnosis and therapeutic management of hereditary leiomyomatosis and renal cell carcinoma syndrome-associated renal cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hereditary leiomyomatosis and renal cell carcinoma syndrome (HLRCC) is an autosomal dominant disorder caused by germline loss-of-function mutations in the fumarate hydratase (FH) gene. It is characterized by cutaneous and uterine leiomyomas and an increased risk of highly aggressive renal cell carcinoma (RCC), often associated with poor prognosis. We report the case of a 31-year-old Japanese woman diagnosed with unresectable RCC with nodal and adrenal metastases. Histopathological analysis of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ulcerated nodular fasciitis of the finger mimicking soft tissue sarcoma: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nodular fasciitis (NF) is a benign, self-limiting myofibroblastic proliferation that often mimics soft tissue sarcoma because of its rapid growth, hypercellularity, mitotic activity, and local infiltration. NF typically arises in the forearm, trunk, or upper arm, whereas finger involvement is extremely rare, accounting for 0-2% of cases. Ulceration or protrusion is even more unusual and may further resemble aggressive malignancy. We report a rare case of ulcerated NF of the finger, clinically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concurrent tumor lysis syndrome and 5-fluorouracil encephalopathy during the first cycle of zolbetuximab plus mFOLFOX6 for CLDN18.2-positive gastric cancer: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The safety data on zolbetuximab, a new CLDN18.2-targeting antibody for advanced gastric cancer (AGC), are still exiguous. We report herein a 75-year-old, male patient with CLDN18.2-positive, HER2-negative AGC with weight loss, massive nodal disease, and peritoneal carcinomatosis-related obstructive uropathy. First-line zolbetuximab plus mFOLFOX6 triggered grade 2 nausea, which was followed on day 3 by tumor lysis syndrome (TLS) and 5-fluorouracil (5-FU)-induced hyperammonemic encephalopathy....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute esophageal mucosal injury during pembrolizumab treatment after a hypopharyngeal cancer patient's free jejunal autograft reconstruction, as an immune-related adverse event]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The upper gastrointestinal tract is a relatively rare site for immune-related adverse events (AEs) associated with immune checkpoint inhibitor treatment. A 79-year-old Japanese male with relapsed hypopharyngeal carcinoma after curative surgery with free-jejunum reconstruction and postoperative irradiation developed multiple lung metastases invading the mediastinum. Four months after the anti-PD-1 inhibitor pembrolizumab was initiated, repeated bleeding episodes occurred in the tracheostoma and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prostatic artery pseudoaneurysm presenting with hematuria following robot-assisted radical prostatectomy: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pseudoaneurysm following robot-assisted radical prostatectomy is an infrequent complication. We present a rare case of gross hematuria caused by a pseudoaneurysm. A 76-year-old man was diagnosed with prostatic adenocarcinoma and underwent robot-assisted radical prostatectomy. On postoperative day 9, he presented with gross hematuria and clot retention, accompanied by anemia. Bladder irrigation was performed, resulting in improvement of the hematuria. Contrast-enhanced computed tomography...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitomycin, 5-fluorouracil, and radiotherapy for anal canal cancer in a patient undergoing hemodialysis: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anal cancer is a rare malignancy that accounts for only 0.3% of all cancer cases. Clinical data on treatment strategies for patients with special conditions, such as impaired renal function or those undergoing dialysis, are limited. Herein, we report a case highlighting the efficacy and safety of a combination regimen of mitomycin C (MMC), 5-fluorouracil (5-FU), and radiotherapy (RT) in a patient undergoing dialysis. A 65 year-old woman undergoing hemodialysis three times per week for chronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Mitomycin, 5-fluorouracil, and radiotherapy for anal canal cancer in a patient undergoing hemodialysis: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1007/s13691-025-00821-7.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case report on critical well-leg compartment syndrome: early diagnosis and treatment after cervical cancer surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Well-leg compartment syndrome is a rare yet serious postoperative complication that may develop in limbs not directly involved in surgery. Prompt diagnosis and intervention are essential for limb preservation and optimal recovery. Several risk factors have been identified; however, preoperative prediction remains challenging. This report highlights the importance of early diagnosis through compartment pressure measurement in managing well-leg compartment syndrome following pelvic surgery. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conversion surgery following nivolumab plus SOX therapy for unresectable advanced esophagogastric junction cancer: two case reports with perioperative genomic profiling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nivolumab plus SOX chemotherapy has emerged as an effective first-line treatment for HER2-negative unresectable advanced gastric cancer, and conversion surgery following favorable treatment response is increasingly considered as a potential curative strategy. Here, we report two cases of HER2-negative esophagogastric junction cancer initially diagnosed as unresectable. Case 1 presented with splenic metastasis and tumor thrombus in the splenic vein, and Case 2 with multiple liver metastases and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mixed lesions in premalignant colorectal polyps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colonoscopists occasionally encounter mixed lesions with overlapping histological features. The frequency and combinations of such mixed colorectal polyps remain poorly understood. We comprehensively analyzed the frequencies and combinations of histologically mixed premalignant colorectal polyps. This study had a retrospective, single-center, cross-sectional design. Patients who underwent colonoscopy at the Toyoshima Endoscopy Clinic between March 2022 and July 2023 were eligible. We excised...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shear stress stimuli-induced erythrocytes' mechanical damage, and its relation to erythrocytes' membrane oxidation and cellular aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several similarities between shear-stress-induced mechanically damaged erythrocytes and physiologically aged erythrocytes have been reported, including mechanical fragility, increased aggregability, altered membrane charge, and loss of membrane lipid. Additionally, we found that mechanically circulated blood using a centrifugal blood pump showed an increase in erythrocyte membrane oxidation. This raised the question of how much oxidation can be induced under shear stress and how it relates to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heme-porphyrin metabolism in photodynamic therapy associated with reactive oxygen species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photodynamic therapy is a cancer treatment that is minimally invasive and combines photosensitizers with laser irradiation. Among the photosensitizers used in photodynamic therapy, porphyrin compounds have been widely applied because they specifically accumulate in cancer cells, and this approach has already been introduced into clinical practice. However, the detailed mechanism of porphyrin accumulation in cancer cells has not yet been clarified. The authors focused on the structural similarity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reactive oxygen species generation by photothermal effects of adhesive near-infrared agents on the plasma membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Near-infrared photothermal cancer therapy has attracted increasing attention due to its non-invasiveness, high selectivity, and spatiotemporally controllable local treatment. A novel near-infrared photothermal agent was developed, consisting of a plasma membrane-adhesive indocyanine green conjugated with a polycation bearing quaternary ammonium salt groups, called adhesive indocyanine green, for locally administered near-infrared photothermal cancer therapy. In this study, the photothermal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in redox imaging for cancer diagnosis and therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer remains a leading cause of global morbidity and mortality, necessitating continuous innovations in diagnosis and therapy. Redox biology, the balance between reactive oxygen species production and antioxidant defenses, plays a central role in tumor initiation, progression, and therapeutic response. Elevated reactive oxygen species levels drive DNA damage, genomic instability, and tumor-promoting signaling, whereas adaptive antioxidant responses promote survival, therapeutic resistance, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41589127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of an A/B-<em>cis</em>-Fused Cyclopenta[<em>b</em>]fluorene (6/5/6/5) Ring System for Embellicine A via the Eight-Membered Silylene-Tethered IMDA Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The first synthesis of an A/B-cis-fused cyclopenta[b]fluorene (6/5/6/5) ring system was successfully achieved via an intramolecular Diels-Alder (IMDA) reaction of an eight-membered silylene-tethered precursor. In this key step, a significant conformational change in the diene moiety was achieved by introducing an eight-membered silylene tether, and the desired A/B-cis-fused tetracyclic compound was obtained with complete stereoselectivity. After several functional group manipulations on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41588791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260127143402&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between temporomandibular disorder subtypes and oral health-related quality of life: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with PT and CT symptoms exhibit significantly greater impairments in overall and domain-specific OHRQoL compared with those with IT symptoms, despite the limited number of studies included, highlighting the need for tailored treatment strategies based on TMD subtype.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Metschnikowia sanitii</em> f.a., sp. nov., a new ascomycetous yeast species isolated from mangrove forests in Thailand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seven strains representing a novel ascomycetous yeast species were isolated from the leaf phylloplane (DMKU-SG60) and the floral surface (DMKU-FF11, DMKU-FF12, DMKU-FD2, DMKU-FD6, DMKU-FS1 and ST-387) of mangrove trees in Thailand. Pairwise sequence analysis indicated that the strains were identical or differed by one to two nucleotide substitution(s) in the D1/D2 domains of the large subunit (LSU) rRNA gene. They also were identical or differed by one to four nucleotide substitution(s) in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Benchmarking Density Functional Theory for Accurate Calculation of Nitride Band Gaps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We benchmark exchange-correlation functionals for the calculation of fundamental band gaps of inorganic nitrides. These include conventional functionals such as the local density approximation (LDA), the generalized-gradient (Perdew-Burke-Ernzerhof) approximation (PBE), simple Slater exchange functionals (SLOC), specialized LDA/GGA-derived high local exchange (HLE16) and Armiento-Kümmel semilocal (AK13) functionals, meta-GGA functionals including TASK, the modified Becke-Johnson functional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medicaid Expansion and Breast Cancer Care and Outcomes-What Lies Ahead?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Follow-Up Assessment of Adherence to Methodological Standards in National Inpatient Sample Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Effectiveness of Acceptable-Quality Deceased Donor Kidneys for Transplant in Older Candidates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This economic analysis of increasing the kidney transplantation rate in older adults suggests that using acceptable-quality deceased donor kidneys would be cost-effective or cost saving. Decision-makers should consider policies that make better use of recovered kidneys to increase transplantation rates among older patients and any other patients with similar preferences.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Financial Assistance Policy, Hospital Charity Care, and Medical Debt in Collections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study, Oregon's FAP was associated with a larger decrease in the percentage of the population with medical debt in collections and larger hospital charity care expenditures. State efforts like that of Oregon's have the potential to alleviate medical debt, especially in light of federal policy changes that are likely to exacerbate the medical debt crisis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Clearance of HIV-1 Broadly Neutralizing Antibody VRC07-523-LS During Viremia: Influences on Trial Design and Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Broadly neutralizing antibodies (BNAb) are capable of neutralizing multiple HIV-1 strains through the targeting of conserved epitopes. This study's objective was to quantify the pharmacokinetic (PK) parameters describing the distribution and elimination of the BNAb VRC07-523-LS in people with HIV (PWH), and to identify the influence of viral load on VRC07-523-LS elimination. The PK of VRC07-523-LS was assessed in participants with and without HIV after intravenous or subcutaneous administration....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Electrocatalytic Nitrate Reduction to Ammonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrocatalytic nitrate reduction reaction (NO(3) ^(-)RR) offers a sustainable and energy-efficient alternative for green ammonia synthesis, with the added benefit of environmental remediation and resource recovery. In recent years, it has attracted significant attention. However, the challenges of achieving high selectivity and maintaining catalyst stability have substantially restricted its practical applications. To address these issues, researchers have proposed a variety of catalytic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered antibacterial and remineralization strategies for efficient dental caries management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dental caries, one of the most prevalent oral diseases among adults and children, is caused by oral microorganisms and diet and involves a complex, multi-step process of biofilm formation and tooth decay. The existing clinical treatment modalities are not satisfactory due to the disadvantages of incomplete eradication of pathogens, poor material compatibility and susceptibility to secondary caries. In recent years, there has been a growing interest in treating dental caries, with various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Brexpiprazole in Participants with Agitation Associated with Dementia Due to Alzheimer's Disease: Pooled Analysis of Randomized Controlled Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Brexpiprazole 2 or 3 mg/day reduced agitation symptoms compared with placebo over 12 weeks in this large, pooled sample of participants with dementia due to Alzheimer's disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of a Discrete Choice Experiment to Inform De-implementation of Mammography Overscreening: A US-Based National Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In the first DCE for de-implementation strategies, we found that women express clear preferences for how and with whom information is relayed, but do not have strong preferences for calculators/checklists.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Related Medication Nonadherence Among Adults with Stroke in the United States: Insight from the 2020-2023 National Health Interview Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarcopenic obesity increases the risk of falls in early-onset type 2 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with EOT2D are more prone to developing sarcopenic obesity, and visceral obesity contributes to the elevated risk of falls in this population. Therefore, interventions to preserve muscle mass and strength while reducing visceral fat accumulation are critical in mitigating fall risk among patients with EOT2D.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Drug Stent with Sirolimus and WKYMVm Promotes Endothelialization and Limits Hyperplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The sirolimus-WKYMVm dual-drug stent enhances re-endothelialization and inhibits neointimal hyperplasia, thereby offering a promising strategy for improving the efficacy and long-term safety of cardiovascular stents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bowel Preparation Quality for Optimal Sessile Serrated Lesions Detection: Is Excellent the Enemy of Good?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Excellent bowel preparation did not translate into a higher SSLDR compared to good preparation. Instead, SSL detection may be primarily driven by endoscopist expertise, inspection time, and the clinical context of the patient.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on: "Personalized Medicine in Cystic Fibrosis: Characterization of Eight Rare CFTR Variants in Intestinal Organoids and Cellular Models"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction to the Proceedings of the CNS*2025 Meeting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitigation of fine migration in low salinity water flooding of clay-rich sandstones Using Fe₃O₄/Saponin/Cu(II) nanocomposite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fines migration is a major cause of formation damage in clay‑rich sandstones, particularly under low‑salinity waterflooding where electrostatic double‑layer expansion destabilizes clay-mineral adhesion and causes severe permeability loss. This study investigates, at the laboratory scale, the potential of a Fe₃O₄@saponin/Cu nanocomposite to mitigate fines release and permeability loss during simulated low-salinity water flooding of clay-rich sandstone. The nanocomposite was synthesized by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atopic Comorbidities and Topical Steroids in Early Childhood Atopic Dermatitis: Are We Missing a Piece of the Puzzle?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diabetes-induced Multiorgan Damage: Can Magnesium Delay the process?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Diabetes mellitus is a leading cause of morbidity and mortality worldwide. Despite the widespread use of oral antidiabetic agents and insulin therapy, the global incidence of diabetes continues to rise at an alarming rate. Human studies have demonstrated an association between magnesium deficiency and both insulin resistance and impaired glucose tolerance. This review, which is based on information collected from human and experimental studies from existing databases,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using the Framework for Reporting Adaptation and Modifications-Expanded (FRAME) to Adapt an Evidence-Based HIV-Prevention Intervention for Zambian Adolescent Girls and Young Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite substantial global efforts, adolescent girls and young women (AGYW) in Southern Africa remain disproportionately affected by HIV. In Zambia, the HIV prevalence among AGYW is nearly three times that of their male peers. The Informed Motivated Aware and Responsible Adolescents and Adults (IMARA) program, an evidence-based HIV/STI prevention intervention initially developed in the United States and later adapted in South Africa, demonstrated promising reduction in HIV risk through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of candidate genes associated with mitotic-origin aneuploidy: a genome-wide association study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this study, we performed genome-wide association analysis on embryonic sequencing data and identified EMP2 on chromosome 16 as a potential gene implicated in mitotic-origin aneuploidy. Further verification experiments are required to confirm the functions of candidate genes during embryogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public Health Impact and Cost-Effectiveness of Routine and Catch-Up Human Papillomavirus Vaccination in Girls and Women in Selected Regions of China: A Model-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The routine 9vHPV strategy may be cost-effective compared with the 2vHPV strategy in China. However, a 9vHPV catch-up strategy varies in cost-effectiveness by regional socioeconomic development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in CMR-derived ventricular strain, fibrosis progression and outcomes in hypertrophic cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy (HCM) is a major health concern, with cardiac magnetic resonance (CMR) playing a crucial role in risk assessment. We investigated for the first time the utility of sequential CMR, particularly strain analysis, for tracking HCM progression. We retrospectively evaluated HCM patients undergoing two CMR scans over a 10-year period. We measured changes in left ventricular (LV) strain parameters and examined their yearly changes as predictors of a composite of sudden...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Schizophrenia: from mechanism to therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Schizophrenia is a multifaceted psychiatric disorder characterized by hallucinations, delusions, cognitive deficits, and social dysfunction. Its etiology involves a complex interplay of neurochemical, neurodevelopmental, genetic, and immune responses. Despite extensive research, its precise etiology remains elusive. Multiple hypotheses have been proposed to explain its onset and progression. Neurochemical hypotheses focus on dysregulation of the dopamine and glutamate systems, leading to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Latent Profiles of Suicide Risk in University Students: a Multidimensional Model Integrating sleep, mood, interpersonal, and Behavioral Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Suicidal ideation is prevalent among university students and is associated with a complex interplay of psychological, interpersonal, and behavioral factors. While prior research has examined individual predictors such as sleep disturbances, depressive symptoms, and impulsivity, less is known about how these factors co-occur in clinically distinct profiles. This study aimed to identify latent profiles of suicide risk using a multidimensional model.We conducted a secondary data analysis using the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Portrayed the development of activated T cell to exhausted T cell based on the ratio of CD28 to CTLA4]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[T cell exhaustion, to some extent, limits the clearance of viruses and tumor cells and accounts for the poor effectiveness of immune therapy. The generally accepted classification of exhausted T cells assigns them as progenitor and terminal statuses. However, the outcome of immune therapy benefits little from this classification. In this study, we constructed a new indicator with the ratio of CD28 to CTLA4 (ccRatio) to continuously characterize the development of T cell from activation to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pannexin-1 is present in a subpopulation of bovine milk-derived small extracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pannexin-1 (Panx1) is a large-pore membrane channel protein implicated in diverse physiological and pathological processes, yet its presence in extracellular vesicles has not been fully characterized. In this study, we investigated small extracellular vesicles derived from bovine milk to determine whether they contain Panx1. Using multiple complementary approaches, we show that Panx1 is present in a distinct subpopulation of milk-derived vesicles. Panx1 immunoreactivity was detected by Western...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FAP expression as a marker of malignant transformation enabling in vivo characterization in peripheral nerve sheath tumors: a multimodal and translational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Malignant peripheral nerve sheath tumors (MPNSTs) are aggressive sarcomas and a major cause of mortality in neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF-1). Distinguishing MPNSTs from benign neurofibromas remains challenging. We investigated fibroblast activation protein alpha (FAP) as a malignancy biomarker and theranostic target in peripheral nerve sheath tumors. Therefore, we integrated publicly available bulk transcriptomics, spatial transcriptomics, and single-cell RNA sequencing with immunohistochemistry...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic component of thermal stress in Jersey crossbred cows using test day production records and NASA POWER meteorological data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rab24 protein levels show dynamic changes in mouse tissues and human cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rab24 is an unusual member of the Rab family of small GTPases, implicated in autophagy, endocytosis and cell division. In order to elucidate possible organ and age-specific roles of Rab24, we investigated tissue-specific levels of Rab24 in mice by western blotting and immunohistochemistry from postnatal day one to 9 months of age. In adult mice, the highest protein levels were found in the brain followed by the kidney, whereas lower levels were detected in the pancreas, spleen, liver, lung,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic circulating biomarkers for predicting adverse events in PRaG therapy: a pooled analysis and model construction from PRaG series clinical trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study successfully delineated the real-world safety profile of PRaG therapy and identified a distinct set of dynamic circulating biomarkers strongly associated with moderate-to-severe AEs. The established non-invasive prediction model offers an effective tool for clinical early warning and proactive management in PRaG patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuity of long-term follow-up in patients with chronic hepatitis C after sustained virologic response following direct-acting antiviral therapy: a nationwide real-world multicenter cohort study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Within Japan's core-center network, long-term continuation after SVR is high but not universal. Follow-up was generally maintained for patients with severe comorbidities, while disengagement was more likely among those with lower perceived risk. Strengthening low-intensity, structured support for such patients may improve the continuity and equity of post-SVR care. These findings provide a foundation for optimizing post-SVR care pathways in national liver disease networks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adherence to a paleolithic diet and paleolithic-like lifestyle is associated with lower colorectal cancer risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A phase 2 study of orally administered live biotherapeutic salmonella-IL2 with FOLFIRINOX for stage IV pancreatic cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salmonella-IL2 is an attenuated Salmonella Typhimurium strain carrying the human gene for IL-2. When orally administered in preclinical trials, the bacterium colonizes tumors and locally releases IL-2, triggering immunologically-mediated tumor cell killing without untoward side effects. A non-randomized, phase 2 study evaluated the combination of Salmonella-IL2 with standard of care (SOC) chemotherapy where patients received Salmonella-IL2 plus FOLFIRINOX (FFX). Overall survival (OS),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiotherapy dose may not affect prognosis in ESCC patients receiving first-line chemoradiotherapy-immunotherapy: A multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multicenter data from China showed that higher radiotherapy doses provide no survival benefit for ESCC patients receiving first-line triple therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: "Dozing off" in the car and excessive daytime sleepiness (EDS) in parkinson's disease: a survey of 125 patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESR Essentials: Perfusion MRI-practice recommendations by the European Society for Magnetic Resonance in Medicine and Biology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perfusion MRI techniques-including dynamic susceptibility contrast (DSC) MRI, dynamic contrast-enhanced (DCE) MRI, arterial spin labeling (ASL) MRI, and intravoxel incoherent motion (IVIM) MRI-hold strong potential as imaging techniques for diagnosing, staging, and monitoring disease across a range of clinical applications. However, clinical adoption, especially of quantitative parameters, remains variable across techniques. Key barriers to broader implementation include a lack of standardized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unleashing CAR-T potential in solid tumors: overcoming intrinsic and extrinsic hurdles to improve therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cell therapy has shown transformative success in hematologic malignancies, yet its application in solid tumors remains limited by a combination of intrinsic and extrinsic barriers. Intrinsically, CAR-T cells face challenges such as CAR instability, T cell exhaustion, insufficient tumor infiltration, and poor persistence. Extrinsically, the tumor microenvironment (TME) acts as a formidable obstacle, with physical barriers, metabolic constraints, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of biocompatible novel multi-tailed indole-based resorcinarene for effective delivery of quercetin against multidrug-resistant S. aureus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Resorcine-based macrocycles have received significant attention in drug delivery applications owing to their tunable functional groups, well-defined cavities, and inherent self-assembly behavior, considering essential for encapsulation and controlled release of loaded drug candidates. However, existing resorcinarene derivatives face certain limitations in drug loading, physiologic stability, and compatibility with structurally complex natural therapeutics, necessitating the development of novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of modality compatibility on dual-task performance in a more naturalistic environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural MRI Biomarkers of Intracranial Pressure in IIH: Linking Optic Nerve Sheath, Pituitary Morphology, and Hormonal Changes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our exploratory findings suggest potential interactions between ICP, endocrine markers, and structural MRI measures. However, due to the limited sample size and variability in endocrine parameters, the results should be interpreted cautiously and considered hypothesis generating rather than clinically directive. Larger studies are needed to determine whether endocrine MRI associations hold true and whether they have diagnostic or clinical relevance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local-regional therapy plus ICIs, chemotherapy, and lenvatinib versus ICIs plus chemotherapy in advanced intrahepatic cholangiocarcinoma: a multicenter study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with the ICI-Chemo regimen, the LRT-ICI-Chemo-Len regimen significantly improved the prognosis of patients with advanced ICC. There was no significant difference in the incidence of grade 3-4 AEs between the two treatment regimens, and all AEs were manageable. This indicates that the LRT-ICI-Chemo-Len combination regimen is a feasible approach for the first-line treatment of advanced ICC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and prognostic model development of immune checkpoint inhibitor rechallenge in recurrent or metastatic nasopharyngeal carcinoma: a real-world study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provided a comprehensive assessment of the efficacy and prognostic factors of ICI rechallenge in RM-NPC patients who failed prior anti-PD-1 immunotherapy, and developed a prognostic model which could identify candidates for ICI rechallenge. Further prospective trials are warranted to confirm and expand these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards an international learning network for CAP Training- a Delphi study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A learning network of clinician-educators and stakeholders provides a sustainable approach to co-creating best practices in child and adolescent psychiatry (CAP) training. This study assessed the feasibility and relevance of developing such a network in Europe. Participants (n = 137) from 28 European countries-trainees (n = 58), trainers (n = 50), and experts by lived experience (n = 27)-rated the importance of potential topics (areas of learning) and activities (ways of sharing) for an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Organogel-AFPT System for Encapsulation and Cryopreservation of <em>Yarrowia lipolytica</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Encapsulation of microorganisms is a promising strategy in biomedical and industrial applications to enhance stability, reusability, and functionality. However, the cryopreservation of microorganism-encapsulated materials still represents a formidable challenge because of the mechanical and osmotic damage caused by inevitable ice formation at subzero temperatures. In this study, we developed a hydrophobic antifreeze material (organogel-AFPT) specifically for oleaginous microorganisms, following...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41591409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260127143403&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>