<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:21:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Dynamics-Based Optimization of Glyme Electrolytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the demand for high-energy-density lithium-ion batteries has increased, lithium metal batteries have emerged as promising alternative. Glyme-based electrolytes are attractive candidates for lithium metal systems due to their high ionic conductivity and improved electrochemical stability compared to conventional carbonate-based electrolytes. In this study, we employed atomistic molecular dynamics simulations to optimize glyme electrolytes with the goal of enhancing the ionic conductivity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231393/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic Surgery for Obese Type 2 Diabetes: Korean Multicenter Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: After adjusting for baseline differences, no statistically significant difference in T2DM remission was observed between SG and RYGB at 1 and 2 years in Korean patients with BMI ≥ 30 kg/m². These findings should be interpreted with caution given the modest sample size and limited follow-up. Prospective studies are needed to validate these findings and support clinical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-cancer single-cell RNA sequencing analysis refines multi-origin monocyte and macrophage lineages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) play crucial and important role in cancer dynamics by affecting homeostasis, immunosuppression, and angiogenesis within the tumor microenvironment. Using single-cell transcriptomics, we constructed a comprehensive atlas of myeloid cell populations across healthy and pan-cancer tissues that revealed heterogeneity. Our analysis suggested that TAMs may arise from two distinct origins: C1QC+ TAMs, which likely are derived from resident tissue macrophages, SPP1+...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bevacizumab plus erlotinib in advanced solid cancers with Krebs cycle gene mutations: A multicenter phase II study (BRISK; KCSG AL22-16)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Bevacizumab plus erlotinib demonstrated promising efficacy in tumors with Krebs cycle gene mutations, warranting further investigation beyond FH-deficient RCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MALDI mass spectrometry analysis of <em>N</em>-glycans through DMTMM-mediated benzylamidation and Girard's reagent P labeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glycosylation is one of the major post-translational modifications of proteins and plays important roles in diverse biological processes, including cell signaling and recognition. Matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization mass spectrometry (MALDI-MS) has been widely used to analyze glycans formed through glycosylation because it generates mainly singly charged ions and offers relatively high ionization efficiency for glycans. In this study, we present a method for MALDI-MS-based N-glycan...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncovering elusive ultrafast charge transfer-driven structural changes in 4,4'-bis(9-carbazol-9-yl)-1,1'-biphenyl, a paradigmatic molecular triad]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic semiconductors have attracted significant attention for their potential in flexible, lightweight, and tunable optoelectronic applications. Among them, 4,4'-bis(9-carbazol-9-yl)-1,1'-biphenyl (CBP) is one of the most widely employed host materials. However, despite its extensive applications, its intrinsic excited-state dynamics and subsequent structural evolution remain underexplored. In this study, we combined femtosecond transient absorption (fs-TA) spectroscopy and nonadiabatic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>In Silico</em> Target Discovery of Kaempferol: Therapeutic Effect of Kaempferol on Atopic Dermatitis through Regulation of Aryl Hydrocarbon Receptor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AhR) is known to bind several exogenous ligands such as natural plant flavonoids, synthetic polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons, and dioxin-like compounds, but its association with kaempferol (KF) is unknown. Therefore, in this study, AhR was explored as an atopic dermatitis (AD)-regulating target of KF for AD regulation using in silico prediction, and pharmacological prediction and various AD-induced models confirmed that KF exhibited pharmacological activity through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A CMOS Voltage Reference with PTAT Current Using DIBL Compensation for Low Line Sensitivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a low-power CMOS voltage reference with low supply sensitivity, designed and verified in a 180 nm standard CMOS technology. A DIBL-based line-sensitivity (LS) compensation path is incorporated into the conventional PTAT generation circuit to simultaneously provide a reference voltage and a bias current with improved LS. The proposed circuit achieves LS values of 0.01%/V for the voltage reference and 0.07%/V for the bias current reference over a supply voltage range of 1.4 V...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transmit-Receive Module Diagnostic of Active Phased Array Antenna Using Side-Lobe Blanking Channel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article presents a diagnostic method for transmit-receive modules (TRMs) in an airborne active phased array antenna (APAA). Given the spatial constraints of airborne radar systems, the diagnostic functionality was implemented using the peripheral probe method. To minimize the space, cost, and time required for modifications to the existing APAA, the side-lobe blanking (SLB) channel was employed as the probe. To prevent TRM saturation and to determine the fault detection threshold, an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SH003 as a Redox-Immune Modulating Phytomedicine: A Ferroptosis Induction, Exosomal Crosstalk, and Translational Oncology Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Redox dysregulation, ferroptosis evasion, and immune suppression are major barriers in cancer therapy. SH003, a multi-herbal formulation standardized under GMP conditions and evaluated in early-phase clinical studies (NCT03081819; KCT0004770), demonstrated a favorable safety profile supporting its translational potential. Preclinical studies reveal that SH003 disrupts mitochondrial homeostasis, triggers endoplasmic reticulum stress apoptosis, and sensitizes resistant tumors to ferroptosis via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-World Evidence on the Use of Traditional Korean Medicine in Managing Intervertebral Disc Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Korean medicine healthcare (KMHC), a form of traditional medicine including acupuncture and herbal medicine, is widely utilized by patients with intervertebral disc disease (IVDD). With the increasing use of real-world evidence (RWE) in the medical field, this study aims to derive RWE on KMHC utilization and its associated factors in patients with IVDD. Methods: Data from 495 individuals who received outpatient healthcare for IVDD regardless of the purpose such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ligand-Assisted Purification of Mixed-Halide Perovskite Nanocrystals with Near-Unity PLQY for High-Color-Purity Display Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cesium halide perovskite nanocrystals (PNCs) have emerged as promising materials for application in high-color-purity displays due to their exceptional optoelectronic properties, which include narrow emission linewidths, tunable bandgaps, and high photoluminescence quantum yields (PLQYs). However, preserving these characteristics during purification remains a major challenge as surface ligand detachment during the washing process can lead to increased defect states, reduced quantum efficiency,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227933/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expert Perspectives on Enhancing Analytical Methods for Multi-Ingredient Dietary Supplements (MIDS): A Qualitative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing demand for multi-ingredient dietary supplements (MIDS), driven by diverse consumer health needs, has introduced analytical challenges in product testing and quality control. These challenges stem from complex ingredient interactions, formulation variability, and the diverse physicochemical properties of the individual components. To examine these issues and explore practical solutions, this study employed semi-structured focus group interviews with 33 industry professionals and 10...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Analysis of Gene Networks Associated with Adipose and Muscle Traits in Hanwoo Steers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to characterize tissue-specific expression patterns in Hanwoo steers by identifying co-expression modules, functional pathways, and hub genes related to fat and muscle traits using Weighted Gene Co-expression Network analysis (WGCNA). RNA-Seq data were generated from three muscle tissues (longissimus muscle, tenderloin, and rump) and two fat tissues (back fat and abdominal fat) collected from six 30-month-old Hanwoo steers. Quality control of raw sequencing reads was performed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of Expression Quantitative Trait Loci (eQTL) for Adipose-Specific Regulatory Mechanisms in Hanwoo (Korean Cattle)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the genetic regulatory mechanisms of fat accumulation is crucial for improving beef quality. Hanwoo (Korean native cattle) is renowned for its high intramuscular fat (marbling), yet the genetic regulation of adipose gene expression remains insufficiently understood. In this study, we performed expression quantitative trait loci (eQTL) analysis using RNA-Seq data and genotype data from backfat tissue of 75 Hanwoo steers to identify regulatory variants associated with adipose...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effects of Vibration Therapy on Activities of Daily Living After Stroke: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Activities of daily living (ADL) are critical for independence after stroke, yet many survivors remain functionally limited. Vibration therapy (VT), including whole-body and focal modalities, has been proposed as an adjunct to enhance recovery, but effects on ADL remain unclear. This study aimed to evaluate the overall effectiveness of VT on ADL and to identify moderating factors. Methods: A systematic review and meta-analysis were conducted following PRISMA 2020...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Obstructive Sleep Apnea Management: Recent Trends from Conventional to Innovative Therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) is a common disorder characterized by recurrent upper airway collapse during sleep, leading to intermittent hypoxemia and sleep fragmentation. Untreated OSA is associated with increased risks of cardiovascular, metabolic, and neurocognitive comorbidities, as well as considerable socioeconomic burden. Positive airway pressure (PAP) remains the gold standard therapy; however, limited long-term adherence underscores the need for alternative, patient-centered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Cariogenic Organic Acid Concentrations According to Combined Use of Sucrose and Sugar Alcohols]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: This study involves a quantitative analysis of organic acids (lactate, acetate, propionate, formate, butylate, pyruvate, and valeric acid) concentrations after applying sucrose and sugar alcohols such as xylitol and erythritol in the oral cavity. Methods: Saliva samples were obtained from five volunteers before and up to 60 min after oral washing with sucrose and sugar alcohol (xylitol and erythritol). Concentrations of seven organic acids (lactate, acetate, propionate, formate,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long Noncoding RNA Lnc-MTPAP-1 Overexpressed by Particulate Matter Suppresses Apoptosis in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung cancer remains one of the most common and lethal malignancies worldwide, with poor prognosis largely due to late-stage diagnosis and resistance to therapy. Emerging evidence indicates that long non-coding RNAs (lncRNAs) play critical roles in cancer development, metastasis, and treatment resistance. Particulate matter (PM), a major environmental pollutant and recognized Group 1 carcinogen, has been linked to lung cancer through mechanisms that may involve dysregulation of lncRNA expression....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Technologies for Monoclonal Antibody Discovery and Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monoclonal antibodies (mAbs) represent one of the most successful classes of biopharmaceuticals, with more than 100 approved for treating oncological, immunological, and infectious diseases. Antibody discovery and development have been driven by diverse methodologies. Classical strategies such as mouse hybridoma technology, phage display, transgenic mouse models, and single B cell isolation have enabled the generation of high-affinity therapeutic antibodies. Beyond binding affinity, recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exosomal microRNA Panels for Detecting Early-Stage Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Early diagnosis of lung cancer requires lung nodule biopsies, which can lead to severe complications. This study aimed to identify optimized panels of exosomal microRNAs (miRNAs) for non-invasive diagnosis of early-stage non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC). Materials and Methods: This study comprised four phases: discovery, validation, optimization, and confirmation. In the discovery phase, next-generation sequencing profiled 2656 exosomal miRNAs in serum samples (n = 76) from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seaweed Foliar Biostimulants Improve Growth and Phytochemicals of Thai Basil (<em>Ocimum basilicum</em> L.) in a Plant Factory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify the optimal concentration of seaweed extract (SE) for enhancing growth, photosynthetic traits, antioxidant activity, and bioactive compound accumulation in Thai basil (Ocimum basilicum L.) plants cultivated in a fully controlled plant factory. Basil plants were foliar-sprayed twice weekly with five SE concentrations (0.5, 1.0, 1.5, 2.0, and 2.5 mL·L^(-1)), while untreated plants served as controls. After 28 days of transplanting, plant growth parameters,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing multi-task in vivo toxicity prediction via integrated knowledge transfer of chemical knowledge and in vitro toxicity information]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of potential drug toxicity is a crucial step in early drug development. in vivo toxicity assessment represents a key challenge that must be addressed before advancing to clinical trials. However, traditional in vivo experiments primarily rely on animal models, raising concerns regarding cost, time efficiency, and ethical considerations. To address these challenges, various computational approaches have been developed to support in vivo toxicity evaluations, though these methods...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KLC3 regulates axonemal glutamylation via RAB11/FIP5 in polycystic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[KLC3 was identified as a novel ciliary gene in a previous study that caused cyst formation due to abnormal ciliary defects in cyst-lining cells of polycystic kidney disease (PKD) models. RAB11FIP5 is a regulator of tubulin post-translational modification (PTM) in primary cilia and is located on basal bodies. Here, we determined the relationship between KLC3 and RAB11FIP5 mediated tubulin PTM, which may be involved in cyst progression in patients with PKD. KLC3 co-localizes and interacts with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41225582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultraprocessed Food Consumption and Risk of Early-Onset Colorectal Cancer Precursors Among Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, higher UPF intake was associated with increased risk of early-onset colorectal conventional adenomas. These data highlight the important role of UPFs in early-onset colorectal tumorigenesis and support improving dietary quality as a strategy to mitigate the increasing burden of EOCRC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disparities in the Diagnosis and Treatment of Breast Cancer Among People With Disabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study of women with breast cancer, those with disabilities experienced significant disparities in stage at diagnosis, treatment access, and survival outcomes compared with those without disabilities. These findings highlight the critical need for targeted interventions to address disability-related barriers and ensure equitable health care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With Patient Safety Activities of Clinical Nurses: A Cross-Sectional Secondary Data Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide a basis for educational programs to improve nursing skills and highlight the need to build an open and collaborative organizational culture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes after coronary angiography in individuals with elevated lipoprotein(a)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated Lp(a) levels are associated with increased burden of coronary atherosclerosis and significant residual risk for adverse outcomes following ICA, highlighting a need for targeted risk-reduction strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of transjugular and transfemoral approaches for leadless pacemaker implantation in Asian patients: an exploratory study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The transjugular approach for leadless pacemaker implantation demonstrated comparable procedural efficacy and pacing performance, with significantly lower rates of both puncture site bleeding and overall complications, as well as shorter hospitalization. These findings support its use as a safe and effective alternative access route, particularly in Asian patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic concordance and added value of doppler ultrasound and extended histopathologic features in primary Sjögren disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SGUS and MSGB demonstrate only fair diagnostic concordance and reflect complementary aspects of glandular involvement. Doppler ultrasound and extended histologic features provide limited incremental value. Key Points • In suspected primary SjD, SGUS and MSGB demonstrate modest agreement (κ = 0.334), with a 32.8% discordance rate. • MSGB with focus score ≥ 1 demonstrated the highest diagnostic accuracy, while extended histologic features (fibrosis, atrophy, LEL) did not provide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Description of Albimonas marina sp. nov., isolated from sea sand on the Yellow Sea Coast]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A Gram-stain-negative, anaerobic, short rod-shaped bacterium, designated as CAU 1670^(T), was isolated from a sea sand sample collected from Masiran Beach, Republic of Korea. Optimal growth conditions for the bacterium were identified as growth media containing 0-3% (w/v) NaCl at 30 °C and pH 5.5. Strain CAU 1670^(T) exhibited high 16S rRNA gene sequence similarity with Albimonas pacifica CGMCC 1.11030^(T) (97.8% similarity) and Albimonas donghaensis DSM 17,890^(T) (94.8% similarity). The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early response rates with adjunctive cenobamate in uncontrolled focal seizures: Prospective analysis of a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled study in a multinational Asian population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: To examine early responses to cenobamate therapy using prospective data from a dose-response study in Asian patients with focal seizures (YKP3089C035, C035) that employed a titration regimen starting at 12.5 mg/day.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orbital Rim Removal in Endoscopic Transorbital Approaches: Unveiling Indications and Technical Nuances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study establishes ORR as a pivotal advancement in ETOA, demonstrating its capacity to significantly enhance surgical outcomes, particularly in specific tumor scenarios. The anatomic study convincingly demonstrated the inclusion of ORR significantly expanded the surgical exposure during the ETOA. The combination of clinical insights and the feasibility of anatomic study demonstrates ORR as a valuable tool, augmenting outcomes and expanding the surgical armamentarium for complex...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trimerization-Enhanced NIR-II/Photoacoustic Nanoprobes for Precision Osteosarcoma Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of photoacoustic imaging (PAI) and near-infrared II (NIR-II) fluorescence imaging holds transformative potential for cancer diagnostics but faces challenges in developing high-performance dual-modal contrast agents. We report tH7@CT8, an organic nanoprobe engineered through fluorophore trimerization to address the photothermal conversion efficiency limitations of small-molecule agents. Trimerization of the [1,2,5]thiadiazolo[3,4-g]quinoxaline fluorophore derivative H7 induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-derived vesicles extruded from adipose mesenchymal stem cells attenuate intestinal inflammation and augment epithelial regeneration in a colitis model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adipose-derived stem cell (ADSC) cell-derived vesicles (CDVs) have been developed to overcome the limitations of ADSCs and ADSC extracellular vesicles (EVs). This study aims to analyze the characteristics and therapeutic effects of ADSC CDVs compared to ADSCs and ADSC EVs through ex vivo organoid and in vivo colitis experiments. ADSC CDVs were generated from ADSCs through serial extrusions using polycarbonate membrane filters. The characteristics and regenerative efficacy of ADSC CDVs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-resolved nonlinear microspectroscopy with Gaussian beams: Spatial coherence dynamics in quantum materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a theoretical framework for time-resolved nonlinear microspectroscopy using structured light to probe spatial coherence transfer in condensed-matter systems. Unlike traditional photon echo (PE) spectroscopy, our method employs Laguerre-Gaussian (LG) modes to encode and track quantum coherence migration spatially. By expanding the diffusion propagator in LG modes, we reveal radial mode mixing and conservation of orbital angular momentum during coherence migration. Analytical formulas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entropy and Human Aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Entropy, a measure of disorder and randomness, is an essential feature of thermodynamics, chemistry, and information theory, but there has been little study of entropy in human aging. Entropy arises from random molecular interactions or other forms of damage and will manifest at all levels of human biology. It should also progress in concert across many systems and increase the risk of numerous aging-related conditions. Illustrating these principles, research by Hong in this issue of Aging Cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Assessment of Fine-Tuned Open-Source LLMs in Cardiology: From Progress Notes to Discharge Summary]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The generation of accurate discharge summaries from clinical progress notes represents a critical challenge in healthcare documentation, particularly in specialized domains like cardiology where limited annotated data and complex medical terminology pose significant barriers to automation. To address this challenge and improve clinical workflow efficiency, we developed a comprehensive approach combining synthetic data generation with fine-tuned large language models (LLMs), specifically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between erectile dysfunction and relative fat mass in adult men in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that RFM is associated with ED among adult men in the United States, with significant mediation effects via hypertension and cholesterol levels. Prospective longitudinal studies are warranted to further elucidate the role of RFM in ED development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230175/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allyl nonanoate as a novel bile-derived biomarker in metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Bile metabolomic profiling in MASLD revealed distinct clustering patterns, with several fibrosis-associated metabolites demonstrating a stepwise increase with hepatic fibrosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparative study on stevioside- and rubusoside-assisted micellar solubilization of clofazimine for physicochemical and <em>in vitro</em> release properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study compares the micellization and encapsulation abilities of stevioside (STE) and rubusoside (RUB) for enhancing the solubility, stability, and bioavailability of clofazimine (CFZ), a poorly water-soluble antibiotic. CFZ-loaded micelles were prepared and characterized by FT-IR, XRD, DSC, SEM, and NMR. RUB showed a lower critical micelle concentration and significantly improved CFZ solubility (up to 2.06 mg/mL) compared to STE. CFZ-RUB complexes offered greater protection against UV and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of resection margin status on survival in gastric cancer: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: R1 resection significantly impairs survival across all stages of gastric cancer, with the extent and depth of microscopic involvement influencing prognosis. When R1 status is discovered postoperatively, subsequent resection should be considered to improve survival outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based fatigue classification using heart rate variability and cortisol: A multimodal approach to wearable health monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that a fatigue prediction model based on cortisol and HRV can maintain significant predictive power with a reduced number of variables. These findings suggest the potential for practical implementation in wearable devices, enabling accurate fatigue monitoring while minimizing sensor count and computational burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of preoperative percutaneous transthoracic needle biopsy on pleural recurrence in clinically early-stage non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative PTNB was statistically correlated with an increased pleural recurrence in clinical stage I NSCLC, even among patients without conventional high-risk pathological features. Careful consideration is warranted when deciding on PTNB for early-stage disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of OM-85 (Broncho-Vaxom) for prevention of acute exacerbations in patients with chronic airway diseases or chronic bronchitis: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that OM-85 therapy provides some benefits in improving exacerbation outcomes compared with placebo in patients with COPD or chronic bronchitis. Additional research is required to verify these findings due to the small number of trials and between-study heterogeneity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current lung cancer screening: a call for comprehensive reassessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive analysis of antihypertensive medications and their impact on lung cancer incidence and all-cause mortality: a population-based study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CCB use may increase the risk of lung cancer incidence and all-cause mortality compared with ARB use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of sarcopenia on early surgical outcomes in elderly patients following lung cancer surgery: a prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This is the first large prospective study to evaluate sarcopenia according to international guidelines for lung cancer surgery. In this prospective study applying AWGS criteria, sarcopenia was not associated with increased early postoperative complications in elderly patients undergoing lung cancer surgery. However, sarcopenia was linked to poorer mental health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of pleural metastasis in non-small cell carcinomas undergoing intraoperative frozen section examination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pleural nodularity in operative field strongly indicated pleural metastasis in NSCLC. Additionally, ADC and SqCC exhibited distinct microscopic characteristics, with sclerotic fibrosis frequently accompanying pleural metastasis in ADC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structured training and early outcomes in major pulmonary resections by a junior thoracic surgeon: a retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A structured, stepwise approach-including assistantship, gradual case complexity, and cognitive preparation-enabled safe and efficient early-career outcomes in major pulmonary resections. These findings highlight the value of combined technical training and institutional perioperative support in facilitating the transition to independent surgical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bronchodilator response as an independent predictor of severity in bronchiectasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In bronchiectasis, BDR is associated with poorer lung function, more frequent exacerbation, and increased disease severity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of how sarcopenia affects functional outcomes in acute ischaemic stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia, a common geriatric condition characterized by the loss of skeletal muscle mass and function, can negatively affect functional outcomes in acute ischaemic stroke; however, the underlying mechanisms remain unclear. We hypothesized that sarcopenia affects post-stroke outcomes, mediated through its impact on dysphagia, early neurological deterioration, or post-stroke recovery, particularly in patients with motor deficits. To explore this hypothesis, we included 600 consecutive elderly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonographic Measurement After Multilayer Stimulation for Body Fat Reduction and Muscle Strengthening: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Combined electrical muscle stimulation, radiofrequency, and vacuum therapy produced significant reductions in abdominal fat and waist size, increased muscle thickness, and improved perceived contour with favorable tolerability. These findings support this multimodal, noninvasive approach as a promising option for abdominal shaping.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pertuzumab enhances the antitumor activity of T-DXd in HER2-positive gastric cancer cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For HER2-positive advanced gastric cancer (GC), a recent major therapeutic advancement is the development of trastuzumab deruxtecan (T-DXd), a HER2-directed antibody-drug conjugate. In this disease, simultaneously targeting HER2 and HER3 pathways has the potential to be a promising therapeutic strategy. However, the therapeutic approach of combining T-DXd with pertuzumab, which disrupts HER2-HER3 heterodimerization, has not yet been explored in GC, making this study a pioneering effort. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229221/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LiDAR-Based Long-Term Mapping in Snow-Covered Environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving systems encounter various uncertainties in real-world environments, many of which are difficult to represent in maps. Among them, accumulated snow poses a unique challenge since its shape and volume gradually change over time. If accumulated snow is included in a map, it leads to two main problems. First, during long-term driving, discrepancies between the actual and mapped environments, caused by melting snow, can significantly degrade localization performance. Second, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Defect Identification in Automotive Brake Calipers Using PCA-Optimized Feature Extraction and Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to develop a non-contact automated impact-acoustic measurement system (AIAMS) for real-time detection of manufacturing defects in automotive brake calipers, a key component of the Electric Parking Brake (EPB) system. Calipers hold brake pads in contact with discs, and defects caused by repeated loads and friction can lead to reduced braking performance and abnormal vibration and noise. To address this issue, an automated impact hammer and a microphone-based measurement system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRTSC: Channel-Wise Recalibration and Texture-Structural Consistency Constraint for Anomaly Detection in Medical Chest Images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised medical image anomaly detection, which does not need any labels, holds a pivotal role in early disease detection for advancing human intelligent health, and it is among the prominent research endeavors in the realm of biomedical image analysis. Existing deep model-based methods mainly focus on feature selection and interaction, ignoring the relative position and shape uncertainty of the anomalies themselves, which play an important guiding role in disease diagnosis, hampering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning-Enabled Diagnosis of Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm Using Pulse Volume Recording Waveforms: An In Silico Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the feasibility of diagnosing abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) via deep learning (DL)-enabled analysis of non-invasive arterial pulse waveform signals. We generated arterial blood pressure (BP) and pulse volume recording (PVR) waveform signals across a diverse synthetic patient cohort using a systemic arterial circulation model coupled with a viscoelastic model relating arterial BP to PVR while simulating a range of AAA severity levels. We confirmed the plausibility of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydroelectricity Generation from Fiber-Oriented Waste Paper via Capillary-Driven Charge Separation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydroelectricity energy harvesting has emerged as a promising, eco-friendly alternative for addressing the growing demand for sustainable energy solutions. In this study, we present a hydroelectricity energy harvester fabricated from shredded waste printing paper (WPP), offering a novel waste-to-energy conversion strategy that requires neither material purification nor complex processing. The device leverages the randomly entangled fiber network of WPP to facilitate capillary-driven moisture...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensor-Efficient Estimation of Roll Misalignment via Side-to-Side Tension Differences in Roll-to-Roll Polymer Film Processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Roll misalignment in roll-to-roll (R2R) processes is a critical cause of lateral displacement and tension imbalance, leading to dimensional instability and surface defects in polymer films. Conventional analyses based on beam or camber models often require complex calibration and additional sensing, which can limit their applicability in real-time production environments. This study introduces a diagnostic approach that estimates web misalignment directly from side-to-side tension differences...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hardness and Surface Roughness of 3D-Printed ASA Components Subjected to Acetone Vapor Treatment and Different Production Variables: A Multi-Estimation Work via Machine Learning and Deep Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper analyzes the combined effects of acetone vapor treatment and 3D printing process parameters (layer thickness and infill rate) on the hardness and surface roughness of acrylonitrile styrene acrylate (ASA) components by using different machine learning and deep learning strategies for the first time in the technical literature. Considering the high-performance materials and aesthetic requirements of manufacturers, post-processing operations are highly critical for 3D-printed samples....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Review of Plasma-Synthesized/Modified Polymer and Metal Nanoparticles for Biomedical Applications Using Cold Atmospheric Pressure Plasma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review presents recent advancements in cold atmospheric pressure (AP) plasma (CAP) processes for the synthesis and surface treatment of polymer films and metal nanoparticles (NPs) in biomedical applications. We discuss the properties and applications of atmospheric pressure plasma (APP) processes, including dielectric barrier discharge (DBD) and plasma jet methods, highlighting their effectiveness in controlling surface characteristics such as wettability and functionalization.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Rosa canina</em> Extract Attenuates Muscle Atrophy in L6 Myotubes and Immobilized Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Skeletal muscle is essential not only for structural integrity but also metabolic homeostasis. Muscle atrophy, the loss of muscle mass and function, is closely linked to chronic and metabolic disorders and is driven by chronic inflammation, oxidative stress, impaired myogenesis, and disrupted protein homeostasis. The present study aimed to evaluate the protective effects and underlying mechanisms of Rosa canina extract (RCE), a polyphenol-rich plant known for its antioxidant and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mediterranean Diet Adherence and One-Year Metabolic Changes in Patients with Papillary Thyroid Cancer: An Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The Mediterranean diet (MD) has been associated with favorable metabolic outcomes in the general population. However, evidence of these associations among thyroid cancer survivors remains limited. This study examined whether higher MD adherence at diagnosis is associated with longitudinal changes in insulin resistance and lipid profiles in patients with papillary thyroid cancer (PTC). Methods: We analyzed 345 Korean patients aged ≥20 years with histologically confirmed PTC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Utilization and Research Status of the Herbal Medicine Guibi-Tang and Its Variants for Cognitive Impairment: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Guibi-tang (GBT) and its variant Kami-guibi-tang (KGBT) are traditional East Asian multi-herb formulas prescribed for memory loss, insomnia, and fatigue. Preclinical data suggest multimodal neuroprotective actions, including cholinergic signaling modulation and activation of the cAMP response element-binding protein (CREB)/extracellular signal-regulated kinase (ERK) pathway; however, clinical evidence for cognitive disorders remains scattered. This scoping review aimed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Dietary Vitamin D Levels on Markers Related to Amyloidogenesis and Neuroinflammation in db/db Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that vitamin D may exert neuroprotective effects on the hippocampus and PFC in diabetic mice by mitigating neuronal damage and suppressing amyloidogenic and inflammatory gene expression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monoterpenoids from the Roots of <em>Liquidambar formosana</em> (Formosan Sweet Gum) Exhibit Senomorphic Activity Against Cellular Senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that cinnamic acid-conjugated monoterpenoids may serve as interesting lead structures for the development of agents targeting the p16^(INK4A) pathway for the treatment of aging-associated diseases. Further studies will be required to clarify the mechanisms of action of this compound and to evaluate its in vivo efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-Obesity Effects of Acid-Processed <em>Citrus reticulata</em> Blanco Peel Extract Enriched in Highly Bioactive Polymethoxyflavones: Inhibition of 3T3-L1 Adipocyte Differentiation and Therapeutic Efficacy in <em>ob</em>/<em>ob</em> Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Chronic diseases linked to obesity represent a major global health challenge. Although pharmaceutical treatments show efficacy, their use is often limited by side effects. Methods: This study investigated the anti-obesity effects of acid-processed Citrus reticulata Blanco peels extract (CRBE) prepared through reflux extraction with 50% ethanol, followed by acid treatment using 3 M hydrogen chloride and neutralization. Results: Following acid treatment, the composition of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Multi-Omics Analysis Uncovers Immune-Metabolic Interplay in Hepatocellular Carcinoma Tumor Microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is one of the most common malignant liver tumors worldwide and is associated with a high mortality rate. Methods: In this study, we performed an integrated multi-omics analysis to characterize the immune and metabolic features of the tumor microenvironment (TME) in HCC. Tumor samples from 60 HCC patients were stratified into two groups based on immune activity score, and differentially expressed genes as well as differentially methylated regions were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Threshold-Based Overlap of Breast Cancer High-Risk Classification Using Family History, Polygenic Risk Scores, and Traditional Risk Models in 180,398 Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Breast cancer polygenic risk scores (PRS) and traditional risk models (e.g., the Gail model [Gail]) are known to contribute largely independent information, but it is unclear how the overlap varies by ancestry, age, disease type (invasive breast cancer, DCIS), and risk threshold. Methods: In a retrospective case-control study, we evaluated risk prediction performance in 180,398 women (161,849 of European ancestry; 18,549 of Asian ancestry). Odds ratios (ORs) from logistic regression...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing Cytoreductive Nephrectomy with Tumor Thrombectomy Between Open, Laparoscopic, and Robotic Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: For surgical candidates with metastatic renal cell carcinoma with a tumor thrombus (mRCC-TT), surgery is cytoreductive nephrectomy with tumor thrombectomy (CN-TT). This is carried out through an open (OCN-TT), laparoscopic (LCN-TT), or robotic (RCN-TT) approach. The purpose of this study was to compare survival outcomes to CN-TT by operative approach. Methods: This was a retrospective analysis of all patients with a diagnosis of mRCC-TT, who underwent CN-TT from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Impact of Postoperative Systemic Immune-Inflammation Index Changes in Epithelial Ovarian Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative SII monitoring, easily obtainable from routine blood tests, may help identify high-risk patients who could benefit from intensified surveillance or adjuvant treatment. Prospective multicenter studies are warranted to validate these findings and explore whether perioperative modulation of systemic inflammation can improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Esophageal and Gastric Cancer by Histologic Subtype in Steatotic Liver Disease: A UK Biobank Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Upper GI cancer risk in SLD patients is significantly modified by alcohol consumption, with combined metabolic dysfunction and alcohol exposure conferring the highest risks for esophageal adenocarcinoma and intestinal-type gastric cancer. Clinically, these findings suggest that SLD patients with any level of alcohol consumption require heightened cancer surveillance. Even minimal alcohol intake substantially increases cancer risk in metabolically compromised individuals, supporting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Federated Learning in Public Health: A Systematic Review of Decentralized, Equitable, and Secure Disease Prevention Approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Public health needs collaborative, privacy-preserving analytics, but centralized AI is constrained by data sharing and governance. Federated learning (FL) enables training without moving sensitive data. This review assessed how FL is used for disease prevention in population and public health, and mapped benefits, challenges, and policy implications. Methods: Following PRISMA 2020, we searched PubMed, Scopus, Web of Science, IEEE Xplore, and Google Scholar for peer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidental Findings on Abdominopelvic CT in Young Korean Soldiers: Prevalence, Clinical Relevance, and Healthcare System Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: This retrospective case series examines incidental findings (IFs) detected on abdominopelvic CT (APCT) among young Korean soldiers presenting with acute abdominal pain. APCT is a frontline test for acute abdominal pain but frequently reveals incidental findings (IFs) unrelated to the presenting complaint. While many IFs are benign, some require structured follow-up. In military settings with constrained access and frequent personnel transfers, IFs pose challenges for health-system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Chewing Difficulty and Number of Remaining Teeth with Anxiety (GAD-7) Among Korean Adults: Evidence from the 2023 KNHANES]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Oral health is increasingly recognized as a determinant of overall well-being, but its role in mental health remains underexplored. Chewing difficulty and tooth loss can impair nutrition, social interaction, and quality of life, thereby contributing to psychological distress. Objectives: This study examined the association between oral health indicators and anxiety among Korean adults. Methods: Data were obtained from 4746 adults aged ≥19 years who participated in the 2023 Korea...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurse-Led Microsurgical Free Flap Monitoring: A Scoping Review and Evidence-Based Framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Postoperative free flap monitoring, traditionally performed by surgical residents, has shifted toward nurse-led models due to global workforce constraints. While this practice is widespread, its implementation is fragmented, creating a "standardization gap" between successful outcomes and reproducible protocols. This scoping review aimed to comprehensively map all available evidence on nurse involvement in free flap monitoring and synthesize the findings into an evidence-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Superconductivity near the Pressure-Tuned Quantum Critical Point of Charge-Density-Wave Order in Cu<sub>1-δ</sub>Te (δ = 0.016)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We have investigated the evolution of CDW states and structural phases in a Cu-deficient Cu(1-δ)Te (δ = 0.016) by employing high-pressure experiments and first-principles calculations. Raman scattering results reveal that the vulcanite structure at ambient pressure starts to change into the Cu-deficient rickardite (r-CuTe) structure from 6.7 GPa, which then becomes fully stabilized above 8.3 GPa. Resistivity data show that T(CDW1) (≈333 K) is systematically suppressed under high pressure,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Supported Polyhedral-like Co<sub>3</sub>S<sub>4</sub> Nanostructures Enabling Efficient High Current Hydrogen Evolution Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The advancement of overall water-splitting technologies relies on the development of earth-abundant electrocatalysts that efficiently produce H(2) as a chemical fuel while offering high catalytic efficiency, structural robustness, and low-cost synthesis. Therefore, we aim to develop a cost-effective and durable non-noble electrocatalyst for overall water splitting. A straightforward hydrothermal approach was employed to fabricate freestanding polyhedral Co(3)O(4) on a microporous Ni foam...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental Study on the Role of Bond Elasticity and Wafer Toughness in Back Grinding of Single-Crystal Wafers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Grinding semiconductor wafers with high hardness, such as SiC, remains a significant challenge due to the need to maximize material removal rates while minimizing subsurface damage. In the back-grinding process, two key parameters-the elastic modulus (Eb) of the grinding wheel bond and the fracture toughness (K(IC)) of the wafer-play a critical role in governing the behavior of diamond and the extent of wafer damage. This study systematically investigated the effect of Eb and K(IC) on diamond...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Branched Hyaluronic Acid for Reduced Viscosity and Enhanced Moisturization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite its remarkable moisturizing properties, the inherently high viscosity of high-molecular-weight hyaluronic acid (HA) restricts its practical application in skincare products, cosmetic formulations, and skin-contact medical devices. To overcome this limitation, we propose the incorporation of branched structures into HA to create a branched HA hybrid (bHH) by chemically coupling low-molecular-weight HA (200 kDa) with high-molecular-weight HA (700-2500 kDa). The introduction of branched...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vegetables and Glycemic Index: Exploring Their Correlation and Health Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Comparative evaluation revealed that DF exerts a buffering effect on glycemic response (GR) and supports the use of fiber ratios as a more stable and intrinsic parameter for predicting GI than standard estimation methods. Traditional approaches that rely on net carbohydrates may overlook important factors affecting glycemic impact, particularly the buffering effects of dietary fiber. This study advocates for the incorporation of carbohydrate-to-fiber ratios into GI estimation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Analysis and Risk Assessment of Polycyclic Aromatic Hydrocarbons Using Gas Chromatography-Mass Spectrometry from Herbs and Spices Distributed in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, four polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (4PAHs: benz[a]anthracene, chrysene, benzo[b]fluoranthene, and benzo[a]pyrene (BaP)) were quantified in 110 herb and spice products marketed in South Korea. A validated gas chromatography-mass spectrometry (GC-MS) method achieved high sensitivity with limits of detection (LOD) ranging from 0.08 to 0.18 µg/kg and limits of quantification (LOQ) ranging from 0.24 to 0.55 µg/kg, with recoveries consistent with the Association of Official...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation of Biofilm-Forming Bacteria from Food Processing Equipment Surfaces and the Biofilm-Degrading Activity of <em>Bacillus licheniformis</em> YJE5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Food processing environments are prone to microbial contamination, where biofilm formation by persistent bacteria reduces hygiene and food safety. In this study, 27 biofilm-forming bacterial strains were isolated from processing equipment surfaces, with the dominant strains identified as B. cereus LE3, B. cereus YJBR3, and P. cibi F25. An environmental isolate, B. licheniformis YJE5, exhibited no hemolytic activity and demonstrated strong enzymatic potential. Intracellular substances (ICS)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Total Eosinophil Counts, Serum Allergen-Specific IgE and Related Cytokines in Dogs with Atopic Dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Canine atopic dermatitis (AD) is a chronic allergic skin disease in which various immunological markers have been investigated. While peripheral eosinophil counts, serum allergen-specific immunoglobulin E (IgE), and cytokines have each been evaluated in allergic disorders, their simultaneous assessment in dogs with AD has rarely been reported in Korea. This study aimed to evaluate the diagnostic and clinical utility of these parameters in affected dogs. A total of 93 dogs were included between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Adaptation of Wintering Water Birds to Man-Made Weirs in Relation to the Freeze-Thaw Process in Tancheon Stream, Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The roles of man-made weirs in flood control during the summer monsoon are well-known, but the function of habitats for wintering water birds has not been explored. This study examined the effects of man-made weirs on the wintering distribution of water birds in Tancheon Stream, Korea, with a focus on the impact of the freeze-thaw process. Data collected from January to February 2003 included thawed water surface ratios, water depths, sandbar areas, and bird distribution under different weather...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Calling Phenology of Two Frog Species in South Korean Rice Paddies Using Automated Call Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amphibian breeding phenology provides key insights into species' sensitivity to climatic and anthropogenic drivers. We used passive acoustic monitoring (PAM) with automated call detection to examine the calling activity of Dryophytes japonicus and Pelophylax nigromaculatus in South Korean rice paddies across five breeding seasons (2018-2022). Both species exhibited distinct seasonal patterns: D. japonicus showed a synchronous and concentrated calling peak in mid-June (GAM deviance explained =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glymphatic Dysfunction in Neuro-Pulmonary Complications Following Subarachnoid Hemorrhage: A New Perspective on Brain-Lung Axis Disruption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Subarachnoid hemorrhage (SAH), often resulting from aneurysmal rupture, remains a life-threatening cerebrovascular disorder with high morbidity and mortality. While previous research has focused primarily on cerebral damage and neurological outcomes, growing evidence suggests that SAH also causes systemic complications, including pulmonary dysfunction. The underlying mechanisms linking SAH to lung injury, however, are not fully understood. The glymphatic system, a perivascular network that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six1-Eya1 Axis Governs Myofiber Remodeling and Fibrosis in Extraocular Myopathy: Insights from Single-Cell RNA Sequencing and Mesenchymal Stem Cell Therapy in Thyroid Eye Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thyroid eye disease (TED) is an autoinflammatory condition characterized by fibrosis in orbital fat and extraocular muscles, primarily driven by TSH receptor antibodies and inflammatory cytokines. While research has predominantly focused on the involvement of fat tissue, the understanding of myopathy in TED remains limited. This study developed a TED mouse model and isolated myoblasts from both control individuals and TED patients for analysis. Single-cell RNA sequencing was used to investigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroptosis in Oral Cancer: Mechanistic Insights and Clinical Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death characterized by lipid peroxidation, has emerged as a pivotal vulnerability in oral squamous cell carcinoma (OSCC). This review provides an overview of ferroptosis mechanisms and their implications for OSCC pathobiology and therapy. OSCC cells exhibit heightened reliance on anti-ferroptotic defenses such as GPX4, SLC7A11, FSP1, and Nrf2, and disrupting these pathways suppresses tumor growth and restores sensitivity to chemotherapy,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erythropoiesis-Stimulating Agent Protects Against Kidney Fibrosis by Inhibiting G2/M Cell Cycle Arrest]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: G2/M cell cycle arrest of proximal tubular epithelial cells following acute kidney injury results in maladaptive repair and promotes chronic kidney disease. We investigated whether erythropoiesis-stimulating agents (ESA) regulate G2/M arrest and mitigate kidney fibrosis. Methods: Human kidney 2 (HK-2) cells were stimulated with TGF-β or paclitaxel, treated with darbepoetin alfa (DARB) at 0.5 ug/mL or 5 ug/mL, and cell cycles were analyzed using flow cytometry. In vivo experiments...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum Phosphorus Is a Fast and Highly Sensitive Marker Predictive of a Complete Cure of Tumor-Induced Osteomalacia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Tumor-induced osteomalacia (TIO) is a rare acquired paraneoplastic syndrome caused by phosphaturic mesenchymal tumors (PMTs). FGF23, which is overproduced by PMTs, causes hypophosphatemia and osteomalacia, ultimately leading to multiple insufficiency fractures, which are the cause of TIO symptoms. Therefore, recovery from TIO symptoms often takes several months. Due to its paracrine effects, even minuscule amounts of residual PMT can cause treatment to fail. To further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogel Drug Delivery Systems and Liposomal Bupivacaine: Innovations and Future Perspectives in Pain Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pain management remains a major clinical challenge, as conventional opioids and local anesthetics suffer from short analgesic duration, systemic toxicity, and dependence risks. Advanced drug delivery systems, particularly hydrogels and liposomal bupivacaine, have emerged as promising solutions to address these limitations. Hydrogels, composed of cross-linked hydrophilic polymer networks, enable biocompatible, biodegradable, and sustained drug release, while liposomal bupivacaine encapsulates the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postmenopausal Obesity and Dyslipidemia as Risk Factors for Breast Cancer in Korean Women: Analysis of a National Health Screening Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Over the past two decades, the incidence of breast cancer has been increasing in Korea, which is potentially attributable to longer life expectancies, Westernized lifestyles, and declining fertility rates. However, the contributions of modifiable metabolic and behavioral risk factors in Asian populations remain underexplored. This study aimed to assess the associations between health-related factors and incidence of breast cancer in a large Korean cohort. Methods: We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tacrolimus-Sirolimus Combined Exposure and Acute Rejection in Kidney Transplant Recipients Undergoing Early Conversion to Sirolimus: A Multicenter Retrospective Cohort Threshold Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Combining calcineurin inhibitors (CNIs) with mTOR inhibitors has been explored to reduce CNI exposure. However, the safety of this early conversion approach remains uncertain, and the optimal therapeutic targets for tacrolimus and sirolimus trough concentrations in patients have not been clearly established. Method: In this retrospective multicenter cohort, we analyzed 8027 kidney transplant recipients and compared a standard group (tacrolimus + MMF) with an early...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Downstream Occlusion During Mechanical Thrombectomy: Clinical Implications and Endovascular Trajectory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Downstream occlusion (DOC) is a commonly observed, yet frequently overlooked, angiographic event during mechanical thrombectomy (MT) for acute large vessel occlusion (LVO). This phenomenon has the potential to complicate procedures and influence outcomes. However, its prevalence, predictors, and endovascular trajectories remain poorly understood. Methods: A retrospective analysis of 703 patients who underwent MT for acute intracranial LVO between 2010 and 2021 at a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Flow Restriction Training Improves Cardiac Structure and Diastolic Function in Runners with Exercise-Induced Hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Exercise-induced hypertension (EIH) in runners predisposes them to cardiovascular diseases, including myocardial hypertrophy, arrhythmias, and coronary artery disease. Blood flow restriction (BFR) training has been reported to exert non-pharmacological benefits in runners with EIH by improving blood pressure, myocardial workload, and cardiorespiratory fitness. The purpose of this study was to investigate whether changes in myocardial structure and function accompany these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogel-Based Delivery Systems for Non-Opioid Analgesics: Advances, Challenges, and Clinical Prospects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review focuses on hydrogel-based systems specifically designed for non-opioid analgesics, aiming to improve efficacy, safety, and translational applicability. The opioid crisis has intensified the need for safer and more effective alternatives in pain management. Non-opioid analgesics including NSAIDs, acetaminophen, gabapentinoids, antidepressants, anticonvulsants, NMDA receptor antagonists, topical agents, and cannabinoids offer promising options but are limited by rapid clearance, short...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards an Improved Standard in Penile Duplex Doppler Ultrasonography: A Randomized Crossover Trial of 3D Virtual Glasses for Audiovisual Sexual Stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: We compared the efficacy of audiovisual sexual stimulation (AVSS) using 3D virtual glasses with a desktop monitor. Methods: In this randomized crossover study, 60 patients with ED underwent two penile duplex Doppler ultrasound sessions 1 week apart, each after intracavernosal prostaglandin E1 injection. Patients were randomly assigned to receive AVSS via 3D virtual glasses or a desktop monitor in the first session, with crossover in the second. We measured the resistive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Trends and Prognostic Impact of Pacemaker-Associated Heart Failure: Insights from a Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Pacemaker-associated heart failure (PaHF) is a recognized complication of chronic ventricular pacing, yet its long-term incidence and prognostic impact remain incompletely defined. Previous studies on PaHF have been largely limited by small sample sizes, single-center designs, and insufficient long-term or time-dependent analyses. We aimed to evaluate the incidence, clinical predictors, and mortality risk of PaHF in a nationwide real-world cohort. Methods: Using the Korean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Related Differences in Surgical and Biochemical Outcomes Following Parathyroidectomy for Primary Hyperparathyroidism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Despite its increasing incidence in older patients, parathyroidectomy for primary hyperparathyroidism (PHPT) is frequently deferred owing to risks and age-related comorbidities and the limited evidence of age-specific surgical safety and biochemical outcomes. We evaluate age-related differences in clinical characteristics, perioperative outcomes, postoperative complications, and biochemical responses, including bone turnover markers, after parathyroidectomy for PHPT....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptual Discrepancies of Opioid Analgesics and Psychotropic Drugs: A Cross-Sectional Study of Korean Patients and Physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Opioid analgesics and psychotropic drugs (medical narcotics) are essential for treating pain and psychiatric disorders. Unlike tiered classification systems used globally, Korea uniformly classifies these medications with illicit drugs under a single narcotics category. This creates misunderstandings among patients and physicians. This study investigates perceptions of medical narcotics, assesses awareness of the Narcotics Information Management System (NIMS), and proposes strategies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227131/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Breathing Exercises and Stabilization Techniques on Patients with COVID-19: Quasi-Experimental Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: To evaluate the effects of respiratory exercises and stabilization techniques on patients with coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19). Methods: This is a quasi-experimental study and a single community-based hospital. Thirty-nine patients with COVID-19 completed the study, of which 20 underwent respiratory exercises and stabilization techniques, while the rest (19 patients) did not. Respiratory exercises and stabilization techniques comprised diaphragmatic breathing, pursed-lip...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local Control and Vertebral Compression Fractures After Stereotactic Body Radiotherapy for Spinal Metastases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: This study aimed to evaluate the efficacy and toxicity of stereotactic body radiotherapy (SBRT) for spinal metastases, focusing on pain control, local tumor control, and the incidence of vertebral compression fractures (VCF). Materials and Methods: We retrospectively analyzed 179 patients with 217 spinal metastatic lesions who underwent SBRT between July 2020 and April 2022. The prescribed doses for SBRT were 18 or 20 Gy for one fraction, ≥24 Gy for three fractions, ≥20 Gy for four...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term and Heavy Smoking as a Risk Factor for Lumbar Spinal Stenosis: Evidence from a Large-Scale, Nationwide Population-Based Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: Lumbar spinal stenosis (LSS) is a leading cause of disability in older adults, but the role of cigarette smoking in its development remains unclear. This study aimed to clarify the association between smoking and the incidence of LSS, with a focus on dose-response relationships and subgroup variations by age and sex. Methods: We conducted a nationwide, population-based cohort study using the Korean National Health Insurance Service database. A total of 2,123,268 adults...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Detection of Lumbosacral Transitional Vertebrae on Plain Lumbar Radiographs Using a Deep Learning Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Lumbosacral transitional vertebra (LSTV) is a common anatomical variant, but its identification on plain radiographs is often inconsistent. This inconsistency can lead to clinical complications such as chronic low back pain, misinterpretation of spinal parameters, and an increased risk of wrong-level surgery. This study aimed to develop and validate a deep learning-based artificial intelligence (AI) model for the automated detection of LSTV on plain lumbar radiographs....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhaled Corticosteroids and the Risk of Lung Cancer in Patients with Bronchiectasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Prescribing inhaled corticosteroids (ICS) to patients with bronchiectasis may be controversial. Studies investigating the association between ICS and the risk of lung cancer in patients with bronchiectasis are rare. Methods: Patients with bronchiectasis were enrolled from the National Sample Cohort Data of the National Health Insurance Service (NHIS-NSC) in Korea. Among them, patients with lung cancer were selected as the case group, and the control group was selected by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Advanced Airway Management and Clinical Outcomes in Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest: A Nationwide Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Out-of-hospital cardiac arrest (OHCA) has persistently low survival rates. While advanced airway management (AAM) is crucial during cardiopulmonary resuscitation, optimal timing remains unclear. This study examined the association between early AAM and clinical outcomes in adult OHCA patients. Methods: This retrospective study analyzed Korean nationwide OHCA registry data (August 2019-December 2022). Adult patients with emergency medical service-treated OHCA of presumed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liver Abscess Caused by <em>Klebsiella pneumoniae</em> Originating from a Peri-Implant Abscess Following Dental Implant Surgery in a Patient with Diabetes: Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Clinicians should be aware of the potential occurrence of liver abscesses caused by K. pneumoniae if signs of systemic infection persist along with peri-implant infection after dental implant surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Sensitivity Cardiac Troponin as a Predictor of Atrial Fibrillation Detected After Stroke: Implications for Subsequent Cerebrocardiovascular Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Atrial fibrillation (AF) may be detected at the time of ischemic stroke or newly detected after stroke. While AF detected after stroke (AFDAS) is associated with poor outcomes compared to sinus rhythm, its prognostic implications relative to known-AF are inconsistent. High-sensitivity cardiac troponin (hs-cTn) is a biomarker of myocardial injury, but its role in predicting AFDAS in stroke patients is unclear. We aimed to evaluate hs-cTn as a predictor for AFDAS and to compare...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HMGB-1 Increases Proinflammatory Reaction via TLR4 in Human Granulosa Cells of Endometriosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Oxidative stress is a critical factor in the development and progression of endometriosis. Granulosa cells, which reside near oocytes in follicles, exhibit steroidogenic activity, and, consequently, influence oocyte quality. Increased oxidative stress may induce the danger signal such as HMGB-1 in granulosa cells and eventually change the follicular environment of patients with endometriosis. This study aimed to demonstrate that HMGB-1 and its receptors, TLR4 and RAGE,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring a Possible Link Between Tinnitus and the Risk of Obstructive Sleep Apnea-A National Population-Based Cohort Study Using Propensity Score Matching Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: The association between tinnitus and obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) has received attention; however, the mechanisms linking both conditions with diverse outcomes are still unclear. This study aimed to evaluate the association between OSA risk and tinnitus, including the OSA-related characteristics affecting tinnitus. Methods: We included participants aged 40-65 years with auditory examinations and STOP-BANG questionnaire between 2019 and 2021 from the Korean National Health and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Kim et al. BRD4 Inhibition Enhances the Antitumor Effects of Radiation Therapy in a Murine Breast Cancer Model. <em>Int. J. Mol. Sci.</em> 2023, <em>24</em>, 13062]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the original publication [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic Modulation of the Nox2-Hv1-ROS Axis by Botulinum Neurotoxin A Confers Protection Against CoCl<sub>2</sub>-Induced Retinal Hypoxic Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroinflammation and oxidative stress are key drivers of various ocular diseases. Experimental hypoxia, modeled using cobalt chloride (CoCl(2)), induces hypoxia-inducible factor 1-alpha (HIF-1α) stabilization, mitochondrial dysfunction, and excessive reactive oxygen species (ROS) production, primarily via the NADPH oxidase 2 (Nox2)-voltage-gated proton channel Hv1 axis. Although Botulinum neurotoxin type A (BoNT/A) is classically recognized for SNAP-25 cleavage, recent studies suggest broader...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence in Histopathological Analysis for Predicting Immunotherapy Response in Cutaneous Melanoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has emerged as a transformative tool in histopathology, offering new opportunities to enhance prognostic accuracy and guide immunotherapy in cutaneous melanoma. The prognostic significance of tumor-infiltrating lymphocytes (TILs) is well established, yet their manual assessment remains subjective, labor-intensive, and often confined to selected tissue regions. Recent AI-based approaches enabled automated and reproducible quantification of TIL density and spatial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of microRNA-Related Target Genes for the Development of Otic Organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mammalian hearing loss is typically permanent due to the inability to replace damaged cochlear hair cells. However, the neonatal mice inner ear demonstrates regenerative capacity, with cochlear floor cells proliferating and differentiating into organoids containing new hair cells and supporting cells, yet the governing molecular mechanisms remain poorly understood. Here, we isolated extracellular vesicles (EVs) from inner ear organoids at proliferation and differentiation stages, characterized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial and Functional Roles of Syndecans in Skin Wound Healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wound healing is a complex, multi-phase process involving hemostasis, inflammation, proliferation, and tissue remodeling. Syndecans (SDCs), a family of transmembrane heparan sulfate proteoglycans, serve as co-receptors for growth factors, cytokines, and ECM components, playing critical roles in cell adhesion, migration, proliferation, and angiogenesis. Among them, SDC-1 and SDC-4 are key regulators of skin wound healing. Due to their distinct spatial and temporal expression across various cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of Novel Predictive Biomarkers for Preeclampsia in Second-Trimester Amniotic Fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preeclampsia (PE) is a major cause of maternal and perinatal morbidity, and early prediction is critical for timely intervention. This study aimed to identify predictive biomarkers for PE through transcriptomic analysis of second-trimester amniotic fluid supernatant (AFS) collected prior to clinical symptom onset. AFS samples from women who later developed PE (n = 7) and matched controls (n = 7) underwent RNA sequencing to identify differentially expressed genes (DEGs). Candidate genes were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41226568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Robust 2.5D Stereo Multi-Object Tracking with Lightweight Stereo Matching Algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multi-object tracking faces persistent challenges from occlusions and truncations in monocular vision systems. While stereo vision provides depth information, existing approaches require computationally expensive dense matching or 3D reconstruction. This paper presents a real-time 2.5D stereo multi-object tracking framework combining lightweight stereo matching with resilient tracker management. The stereo matching module employs Direct Linear Transform-based triangulation using only bounding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between [<sup>18</sup>F]PSMA-1007 PET parameters and biochemical recurrence-free survival in high-risk prostate cancer patients receiving neoadjuvant hormonal treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results indicate that [^(18)F]PSMA-1007 PET might be used to aid in patient stratification for determining which patients would benefit from additional (neo)adjuvant treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported oral adverse events during cancer chemotherapy: longitudinal evaluation using patient-reported outcomes version of the common terminology criteria for adverse events (PRO-CTCAE) and concordance with clinician assessments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patient-reported oral adverse events, as assessed by PRO-CTCAE, were frequently mild but persistent throughout outpatient chemotherapy, suggesting a cumulative impact on quality of life. Concordance between PRO-CTCAE and clinician-reported CTCAE was limited, indicating that clinician assessments may underestimate symptoms such as dry mouth. These findings underscore the need to integrate patient-reported outcomes into routine oral care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of reconduction after cavotricuspid isthmus ablation based on computed tomography anatomy and procedural factors with emphasis on catheter stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A prominent ER was associated with reduced catheter stability during ablation, leading to greater catheter displacement and increased RF applications. This anatomical feature may contribute to chronic-phase CTI reconduction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association of anticoagulant use and hospitalization for hemorrhagic stroke among older adults aged 75 or older: A propensity score-matched study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings of this study highlight the need for careful consideration when prescribing anticoagulants, particularly warfarin, to older adults to minimize the risk of hemorrhagic stroke.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Total Synthesis of the Kikai Island Polybrominated C3'-N1 Bisindole Alkaloid by a Directed Metalation Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The first total synthesis of one out of four Kikai Island polybrominated C3'-N1 bisindole alkaloids from red alga Laurencia brongniartii is described. The key steps involve both dehydration of trans-hemiaminal and a C2'-methylthiolation of bisindole using dimethyl disulfide through directed metalation, followed by C3-methylthiolation using a N-SMe succinimide reagent.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2D nanoarchitectonics for exfoliated nanosheets: tailoring surface roughness of thin-film coatings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liquid-phase exfoliation is a general route to obtain two-dimensional (2D) materials. Manipulation of colloidally dispersed nanosheets including monolayers, few-layers, and multi-layers is required for their applications. The exfoliated nanosheets are used in the assembled states with coating on substrates. However, the significant factors controlling the surface morphologies of the coatings are not fully elucidated in previous reports. In the present work, the morphologies are studied by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41231062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Adhesion Barrier Use During Ladd Procedure for Intestinal Malrotation on Postoperative Midgut Volvulus and Postoperative Small Bowel Obstruction: A Retrospective Cohort Study Using a National Inpatient Database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Use of adhesion barrier during Ladd procedure can prevent rehospitalization due to postoperative small bowel obstruction without increasing the incidence of postoperative midgut volvulus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly efficient Nile red staining for the rapid quantification of microplastic number concentrations using flow cytometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorescent staining of microplastics (MPs) with Nile red (NR) improves the sensitivity of optical techniques, including microscopy and flow cytometry (FCM), and is commonly employed to quantify MP number concentrations. However, staining efficiency varies depending on the polymer type and surface characteristics, often resulting in insufficient fluorescence intensity. This study presents an improved protocol using a swelling-mediated NR staining method, which enables NR to be encapsulated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance direct thrombus imaging to distinguish acute pulmonary embolism from chronic thromboembolic pulmonary hypertension: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Acute pulmonary embolism and chronic thromboembolic pulmonary hypertension are both pulmonary thrombotic diseases. However, it is difficult to differentiate between them in some cases, complicating the choice of suitable treatment. Computed tomography pulmonary angiography and D-dimer measurement are helpful for diagnosing these conditions; however, these examinations cannot estimate the efficacy of anticoagulants in the pulmonary artery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Step-by-step bailout for MitraClip lock line stuck due to a knot]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41230356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transient π-coordination enables nucleophilic borylation of simple arenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Borylation of an arene typically proceeds via transition-metal-catalyzed C-H activation. We report here that transient π-coordination to chromium activates 1 equiv. of a simple arene towards nucleophilic borylation with B(2)(pin)(2) in the presence of an additive such as K(2)CO(3) or KF. The transient activation of the substrate is achieved via in situ ligand exchange with a naphthalene chromium complex, followed by borylation of the resulting arene chromium complex. Electron-rich and sterically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ambroxol displaces α-synuclein from the membrane and inhibits the formation of early protein-lipid coaggregates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Parkinson's disease (PD) is a neurological disorder characterized by neuronal loss and the deposition of α-synuclein-lipid coaggregates in the brain of patients as well as disruptions in lipid metabolism. Mutations in the gene GBA, which encodes the lysosomal glycoprotein Glucocerebrosidase, are together the most important genetic risk factor for PD and have been associated with lysosomal dysfunction, accumulation of pathological α-synuclein as well as major changes in both the levels and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When the Diaphragm Fails: Visual Hallucinations Due to Isolated Respiratory Muscle Weakness as a First Manifestation of Late-Onset Pompe Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case illustrates the diagnostic challenge of isolated respiratory failure due to LOPD when early signs are masked by comorbidities and metabolic disturbances. Nocturnal hypoventilation may cause atypical symptoms such as hallucinations. Systematic neuromuscular evaluation is essential to enable timely ventilatory support and disease-specific treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of streptozocin-based regimen and capecitabine-temozolomide therapy in advanced pancreatic neuroendocrine neoplasms: influence of tumor grade and Ki-67 index]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both STZ-based regimen and CAPTEM therapy are safe and effective treatment options for advanced Pan-NENs. STZ-based regimen was more beneficial in NET-G1/G2 patients, suggesting Ki-67 index and tumor grade may serve as indicators for treatment selection. Further prospective studies are warranted to validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Neuromuscular and biomechanical alterations in chronic ankle instability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[European Respiratory Society and European Society of Thoracic Surgeons clinical practice guideline on fitness for curative intent treatment of lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A multidisciplinary panel of lung cancer experts with a special interest in functional evaluation of lung cancer patients, and lung cancer patient representatives, has been facilitated by the European Society of Thoracic Surgeons and the European Respiratory Society to provide healthcare professionals with practical and up-to-date recommendations for the assessment of patients' fitness for curative intent treatments for lung cancer. The panel formulated four PICO (population, intervention,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periodic Precipitation in Hele-Shaw Cells: Mechanism Insights from Experiments and Numerical Simulation Considering Layer Thickness Effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liesegang patterns are self-organized macroscopic structures formed by precipitates. Traditional methods for producing these patterns rely on gel phases, which inhibit flow but introduce complications, such as undesired chemical interactions. This study presents a strategic approach utilizing a "Hele-Shaw cell", consisting of two glass plates that create a narrow gap (30-225 μm). This setup prevents flow due to friction between glass surfaces without the use of a gel. We identified two critical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A pilot study on midazolam sedation for murine echocardiography: A potential alternative to isoflurane anesthesia and awake imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Isoflurane anesthesia is often used to facilitate murine echocardiography, but can suppress cardiac function. Awake imaging avoids pharmacological interference, but can induce sympathetic activation. In this Midazolam sedation. Parameters were compared using repeated-measures ANOVA. Midazolam enabled imaging without overt stress behavior. Compared to midazolam, heart rate was similar under isoflurane and higher while awake (p ≤ 0.01). End-systolic volume was larger under isoflurane and smaller...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41229313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation Method for Resin Mold Using Reflective Wavefront Sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in molding technology have enabled the fabrication of plastic molded components with complex geometries. In contact lens (CL) manufacturing, a double-sided molding process using resin molds is employed, in which the front and back surfaces of the lens are replicated through injection molding. However, thermal deformation during polymerization can alter the mold shape, thereby affecting the optical characteristics of the final lenses. This study proposes a high-precision optical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-Contact Fatigue Estimation in Healthy Individuals Using Azure Kinect: Contribution of Multiple Kinematic Features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monitoring exercise-induced fatigue is important for maintaining the effectiveness of training and preventing injury. We evaluated a non-contact approach that estimates perceived fatigue from full-body kinematics captured by an Azure Kinect depth camera. Ten healthy young adults repeatedly performed simple, reproducible whole-body movements, and 3D skeletal coordinates from 32 joints were recorded. After smoothing, 24 kinematic features (joint angles, angular velocities, and cycle timing) were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Enhance-Fuse-Align Principle: A New Architectural Blueprint for Robust Object Detection, with Application to X-Ray Security]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Object detection in challenging imaging domains like security screening, medical analysis, and satellite imaging is often hindered by signal degradation (e.g., noise, blur) and spatial ambiguity (e.g., occlusion, extreme scale variation). We argue that many standard architectures fail by fusing multi-scale features prematurely, which amplifies noise. This paper introduces the Enhance-Fuse-Align (E-F-A) principle: a new architectural blueprint positing that robust feature enhancement and explicit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of 3D-Stacked 1Megapixel Dual-Time-Gated SPAD Image Sensor with Simultaneous Dual Image Output Architecture for Efficient Sensor Fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sensor fusion is crucial in numerous imaging and sensing applications. Integrating data from multiple sensors with different field-of-view, resolution, and frame timing poses substantial computational overhead. Time-gated single-photon avalanche diode (SPAD) image sensors have been developed to support multiple sensing modalities and mitigate this issue, but mismatched frame timing remains a challenge. Dual-time-gated SPAD image sensors, which can capture dual images simultaneously, have also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Silica Nanoparticles on Mechanical Properties and Self-Healing Performance of PVA Hydrogels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogels are three-dimensional polymeric networks capable of retaining large amounts of water. Polyvinyl alcohol (PVA)-based hydrogels exhibit autonomous self-healing through reversible physical interactions within the hydrogel matrix, including hydrogen bonding, crystallite formation, and dynamic crosslinking. However, their long self-healing times and low strength limit practical application. Herein, we propose an effective strategy to simultaneously achieve excellent self-repairing and high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Poly(ethylene glycol)-<em>graft</em>-Hyaluronic Acid Hydrogels for Angiogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyaluronic acid (HA) hydrogels are promising biomaterials for tissue engineering and drug delivery due to their biocompatibility and biodegradability. The objective of this study was to develop a novel HA-based hydrogel for the controlled release of basic fibroblast growth factor (bFGF) to promote angiogenesis. A series of PEG-grafted HA hydrogels with varying PEG grafting ratios were synthesized and characterized. We evaluated their physicochemical properties, including swelling ratio,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diet, Exercise, and Lifestyle in Glaucoma: Current Evidence and Future Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glaucoma is a major ocular neurodegenerative disease and a leading cause of irreversible blindness worldwide, with prevalence projected to exceed 110 million by 2040. Although lowering intraocular pressure (IOP) remains the only proven treatment, glaucoma arises from a complex interplay of genetic, local, and systemic factors-including oxidative stress, vascular dysregulation, mitochondrial dysfunction, and neuroinflammation. Emerging evidence suggests that modifiable lifestyle factors may...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cheese Consumption and Incidence of Dementia in Community-Dwelling Older Japanese Adults: The JAGES 2019-2022 Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Dementia is a growing public health concern in rapidly aging Japan. Dietary factors, including dairy products, have been proposed as modifiable influences on cognitive health, although findings across studies remain inconsistent. This study aimed to examine the association between habitual cheese consumption and incident dementia in a large, population-based cohort of older Japanese adults, and to provide epidemiological evidence regarding its potential preventive role in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Oncology: Cross-Sectional Single-Cell Transcriptomic Profiling of the Tumor Microenvironment Across Seven Human Cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: To elucidate the differential transcriptional and intercellular signaling features of tumor components across various cancers, we conducted a comparative analysis using single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq). This technology enables detailed characterization of tumor ecosystems and may explain variations in tumor behavior among distinct cancer types. Methods: We analyzed publicly available scRNA-seq datasets (GEO) from seven cancer types-pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Brain Metastases (Secondary Brain Tumor)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brain metastases, the most common intracranial neoplasms in adults, remain a major cause of cancer-related mortality and morbidity [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Clustering of Lifestyle Risk Factors for Chronic Diseases Among Middle-Aged Migrants in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides preliminary evidence of the high prevalence and clustering of modifiable NCD risk factors among middle-aged migrants in Japan. Findings highlight the need for comprehensive, multi-behavioral interventions tailored to migrant populations, while considering gender roles and occupational contexts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41228148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All-Solution-Processable Robust Carbon Nanotube Photo-Thermoelectric Devices for Multi-Modal Inspection Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While recent industrial automation trends emphasize the importance of non-destructive inspection by material-identifying millimeter-wave, terahertz-wave, and infrared (MMW, THz, IR) monitoring, fundamental tools in these wavelength bands (such as sensors) are still immature. Although inorganic semiconductors serve as diverse sensors with well-established large-scale fine-processing fabrication, the use of those devices is insufficient for non-destructive monitoring due to the lack of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Acoustic Absorbent Materials Using Pine Needles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acoustic absorbing materials made from waste plants or trees represent a sustainable source for noise reduction products and applications such as home acoustic insulation and/or traffic road noise reduction barriers. The primary aim of this work is hence to demonstrate the potential application of pine needle waste as the main constituent in acoustic absorbing materials while resin is used as binder. Once the samples have been manufactured, their different physical (density and porous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41227937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251113142125&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>