<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 07:37:59 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive study of the crystal structure and dynamics of [N(C<sub>3</sub>H<sub>7</sub>)<sub>4</sub>]<sub>2</sub>Cd<sub>2</sub>Cl<sub>6</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single crystals of the organic-inorganic hybrid compound [N(C(3)H(7))(4)](2)Cd(2)Cl(6) were synthesized by an aqueous solution method, and their structural and dynamic properties were systematically investigated. Thermal analyses revealed phase transitions at 321 K (T(C1)) and 445 K (T(C2)), followed by melting at 476 K. Single-crystal X-ray diffraction indicated that the compound crystallizes in a triclinic system with space group P[Formula: see text], showing variations in lattice parameters...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable production of battery-grade nickel via hydrogen reduction of saprolite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nickel production from saprolite-a major laterite source-is critical for the electric vehicle battery supply chain but is currently constrained by the high carbon footprint of the conventional Rotary Kiln-Electric Furnace (RKEF) process. Hydrogen-based reduction offers a sustainable alternative; however, optimizing the reaction kinetics and phase separation efficiency remains a challenge for industrial application. In this study, we investigated the hydrogen reduction behavior of saprolite ore...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of left ventricular systolic dysfunction in left bundle branch block using a fine-tuned ECG foundation model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Left bundle branch block (LBBB) is an important electrocardiographic (ECG) finding strongly associated with left ventricular systolic dysfunction (LVSD), a condition linked to poor clinical outcomes. Although early LVSD detection is crucial, standard diagnosis via echocardiography may not always be immediately accessible. In this study, we propose a fine-tuned ECG foundation model (FM) to enhance LVSD detection specifically in patients with LBBB. We conducted a retrospective multicenter analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances, challenges and prospects of origami and kirigami optoelectronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Switchable between 2D and 3D forms, origami and kirigami have emerged as a versatile platform for deformable optoelectronic devices. Unlike electronic devices, whose electrical properties remain largely unchanged during transformation, the optoelectronic properties of these systems can vary significantly, offering opportunities for optical tunability but also introducing design challenges. Developing such devices requires careful consideration of electrical, mechanical, and optical factors. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oleanolic acid prevents ferroptosis and enhances oocyte competence during in vitro maturation in a porcine model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The in vitro production of porcine embryos is a valuable model for livestock biotechnology and human reproductive research. However, oocyte quality is often compromised during culture by ferroptosis, which is an iron-dependent form of cell death driven by lipid peroxidation and redox imbalance. This study induced ferroptosis using RSL3 during porcine oocyte maturation to evaluate the protective potential of oleanolic acid (OA), an antioxidant triterpenoid compound. Exposure to RSL3 increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acupuncture as adjunctive treatment for schizophrenia: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Acupuncture combined with standard-dose antipsychotics may provide pragmatic benefits, though lack of superiority over sham acupuncture indicates uncertainty about specific effects. High-quality trials are needed to establish definitive clinical recommendations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hierarchical approach reveals site-scale drivers of nematode assemblages on the west coast of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study was performed to assess the spatial variability of free-living marine nematode assemblages in tidal flats along the west coast of Korea to understand natural and anthropogenic factors shaping nematode community structures. Sediment and nematode samples were collected in August and September 2023 using a hierarchical sampling design comprising three regions, each with three sites (W1-W9), and three patches within each site. Significant differences in nematode density, diversity, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Point-Deeponet: Predicting nonlinear fields on non-Parametric geometries under variable load conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonlinear structural analyses in engineering often require extensive finite element simulations, limiting their applicability in design optimization and real-time control. Conventional deep learning surrogates often struggle with complex, non-parametric three-dimensional (3D) geometries and directionally varying loads. This work presents Point-DeepONet, an operator-learning-based surrogate that integrates PointNet into the DeepONet framework to learn a mapping from non-parametric geometries and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Material-Independent Film Formation of Zr<sup>4+</sup>-Trimesic Acid Metal-Organic Complexes and Their Antifouling Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Interface-active, metal-organic complexes (MOCs) have been extensively exploited for interface engineering due to their material-independent coating properties. However, the MOC-based films often face some challenges, such as dark coloration and synthetic difficulty in organic-ligand derivatives, limiting their functional potential and expandability. This paper reports the fabrication of transparent MOC films, composed of Zr^(4+) ions and trimesic acid (BTC), under mild aqueous conditions and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circadian and Diurnal Regulation of Plant Lipid Metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circadian rhythms, driven by an endogenous biological clock, align physiological processes with the Earth's 24-hour light-dark cycle, enabling organisms to adapt to diurnal environmental changes. In plants, the circadian clock regulates key physiological and metabolic processes, such as photosynthesis, nutrient uptake, and stress responses, thereby optimizing growth and development. Recent studies reveal that lipid metabolism is significantly influenced by the circadian clock and diurnal rhythm,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3-Dimensional Microlens Printing of Quantum Dot/Siloxane Hybrid Color-Converter for Highly Efficient and Stable Full-Color Micro-Light-Emitting Diode Display]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum dots (QDs) are promising color-converting materials for full-color micro-light-emitting diode (micro-LED) displays, but have poor stability and poor scalability, which hinder their practical application. We report a hybrid color-converting layer (CCL) composed of QDs, fumed silica nanoparticles (FSNs), and siloxane matrix that exhibits high optical performance and long-term stability under various environmental conditions. The QD-FSN/siloxane incorporates uniformly dispersed QDs within a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A new alkaloid glycoside and antifungal metabolites from the aerial parts of <em>Argemone mexicana</em> Linn. collected in Vietnam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new benzophenanthridine alkaloid glycoside (1), named nitrotyrasanguinarinoside, together with twelve known compounds (2 -13), was isolated from the dichloromethane extract of the aerial parts of Argemone mexicana Linn. Their structures were elucidated using IR, HR-ESI-MS, 1D and 2D NMR, and ECD spectroscopy, as well as by comparison with the published data. The dichloromethane extract exhibited in vivo antifungal activity against Colletotrichum coccodes with 80% inhibition at a concentration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of extraction solvents on cytotoxicity and high-resolution LC-MS profiling of red yeast rice extracts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With increasing public interest in health-promoting foods, appropriate safety assessment of functional food ingredients is essential. In vitro toxicity testing typically requires extraction of food materials, and the choice of solvent can substantially influence the resulting chemical composition and toxicological profile. This study investigated the effects of solvent polarity on extraction yield, cytotoxicity, and also the chemical composition of red yeast rice (RYR) extracts. Using ten...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rewiring Steroidal Metabolic Pathways for Diosgenin Production in Solanum nigrum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diosgenin is a key starting material for the synthesis of steroidal drugs, such as corticosteroids and sex hormones. While the primary commercial source of diosgenin is the tubers of Dioscorea spp., identifying alternative plant hosts capable of diosgenin biosynthesis could enhance its production. In this study, we present Solanum nigrum, a widely distributed species of the Solanum genus, as a novel platform for diosgenin production. S. nigrum naturally accumulates high concentrations of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Experimental Evidence for Reverse Internal Conversion in the Relaxation Pathway of the Excited Anions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report here direct experimental evidence of reverse internal conversion taking place in the excited nitrobenzene anion, revealed by photoelectron spectra acquired by electron detection at the much-delayed time with respect to the laser-anion interaction time along the time-of-flight. Especially, autodetached photoelectrons from the dipole bound states which are in quasi-equilibrium with vibrationally hot anions have been clearly observed concurrently with thermionic emission at the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing technofunctional properties of an emulsion-type meat analog formulated with mealworm and TVP: mushroom incorporation at the optimal concentration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mushrooms are commonly used as functional additives in meat products and show promise in alternative protein development. This study evaluated the impact of five mushroom species-Ganoderma lucidum, Pleurotus eryngii, Pleurotus ostreatus, Agaricus bisporus, and Lentinula edodes-at 3% concentration on the quality of emulsion-type meat analogs made with textured vegetable protein and mealworm. Quality parameters including pH, color, viscosity, proximate composition, water holding capacity (WHC),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive review on mycoprotein-based meat analog production: nutritional, functional, physicochemical, and safety aspect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycoproteins derived from filamentous fungi have emerged as alternative meat proteins. This study reviews mycoprotein production and nutritional and functional characteristics. The quality properties of mycoprotein-based meat analogs and meat products are compared, and their safety is addressed. Fusarium spp., Aspergillus spp., and Neurospora spp. are safe, edible fungi capable of producing mycoproteins. Mycoprotein nutritional properties vary with the fungal strain, production substrate, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Panorama: a database for the oncogenic evaluation of somatic mutations in pan-cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Somatic mutations, key alterations in cancer development, exert differential effects across tissues and biological layers, such as transcriptomes, proteomes, and post-translational modifications (PTMs). Although previous pan-cancer studies have characterized the molecular landscape of cancer, the effects of individual somatic mutations across different tissues remain insufficiently explored. Here, we developed Panorama to evaluate the oncogenic potential of single somatic mutations across all...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Randomized, Double-Blind, Active-Controlled, Parallel, Phase 3 Clinical Trial for Evaluating the Efficacy and Safety of Zastaprazan in Patients with Gastric Ulcers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An 8-week therapy involving zastaprazan 20 mg demonstrated noninferiority to lansoprazole 30 mg in the cumulative rate of healing of gastric ulcers at 8 weeks, and the two demonstrated similar safety profiles. (ClinicalTrials.gov identifier NCT05448001).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Mechanism-Based Multi-Level Population PK/PD Model for Potassium-Competitive Acid Blockers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Potassium-competitive acid blockers (PCABs) are emerging alternatives to proton pump inhibitors for the treatment of acid-related diseases. However, due to the complex, nonlinear interaction between drug exposure, food intake, and physiological rhythms, optimizing dosing strategies remains challenging. A multi-leveled population analysis was conducted using published pharmacokinetic and pharmacodynamic data on four representative PCABs: tegoprazan, YH4808, fexuprazan, and vonoprazan. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stress Shielding Effects of Short Stem Alignment and Bone Density in Reverse Shoulder Arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Short-stem humeral implants in reverse total shoulder arthroplasty (rTSA) are increasingly adopted because they preserve bone stock and reduce stress shielding. However, their shorter length raises the risk of malalignment, and outcomes may be further affected by osteoporosis, which is common in rTSA patients. This study investigated how humeral stem alignment (neutral, varus, valgus) and bone mineral density simultaneously influence stress distribution in the proximal humerus using finite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-performance photothermal GA-MoSe<sub>2</sub> nanosheet for rapid and sensitive point-of-care detection of C-reactive protein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the global COVID-19 pandemic, there is a critical need to develop rapid and sensitive diagnostic devices for point-of-care testing (POCT). Despite the numerous benefits of paper-based colorimetric lateral flow immunoassays (LFAs) in rapid onsite diagnosis, their sensitivity and quantitative analysis capability are limited. To overcome the limitations of the current assays, we developed a new rapid diagnostic method that utilizes glycyrrhizic acid-molybdenum diselenide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FGF12 induces aberrant mechanosignaling in aortic smooth muscle cells during thoracic aortic aneurysm formation in Marfan syndrome mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Marfan syndrome (MFS), caused by mutations in the FBN1 gene, predisposes individuals to thoracic aortic aneurysm (TAA), a life-threatening complication. Recent studies have suggested that dysregulated mechanosignaling in aortic smooth muscle cells (SMCs) plays a pivotal role in TAA pathogenesis in MFS. However, the key molecular drivers remain largely undefined. Here we identify fibroblast growth factor 12 (FGF12) as a novel mediator of aberrant mechanosignaling in aortic SMCs during TAA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NGO ameliorates psoriasis by modulating mitochondrial function and suppressing pSTAT3-IL-17-expressing CD8<sup>+</sup> TRM cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psoriasis is a chronic autoimmune skin disorder characterized by keratinocyte hyperproliferation, persistent inflammation, and frequent relapse. Tissue-resident memory T (TRM) cells, particularly IL-17- and phosphorylated STAT3 (pSTAT3)-expressing CD8^(+) subsets, have been established as central drivers of disease persistence and recurrence. These pathogenic TRM cells maintain local inflammatory circuits that are poorly targeted by current therapies, which helps to explain the limited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of lumbar spinal epidural abscess using biportal endoscopic approach: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immediate effects of upper cervical spinal manipulation on cervical sensorimotor control in individuals with chronic primary cervical pain: an exploratory randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Activation of the pituitary adenylate cyclase-activating polypeptide type I receptor promotes neuroblastoma proliferation and migration through distinct G protein pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative visual and refractive analysis of two enhanced monofocal intraocular lenses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported health utility of stroke and gastrointestinal bleeding related to DOACs in atrial fibrillation: a vignette-based substudy of a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global burden of amphetamine, cannabis, cocaine and opioid use in 204 countries, 1990-2023: a Global Burden of Disease Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug use disorders (DUDs) are emerging global public health challenges. Here we investigated the global and regional estimates of the prevalence and burden of DUDs, including amphetamine, cannabis, cocaine and opioid use disorders, from 1990 to 2023 for 204 countries and territories by using the Global Burden of Disease Study 2023. Overall, trends in global age-standardized disability-adjusted life-years of DUDs increased from 169.3 (95% uncertainty interval (95% UI), 134.4-203.9) per 100,000...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of choroid plexus volume with brain atrophy and glucose metabolism in multiple system atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The choroid plexus (CP), a component of the glymphatic system, is essential in homeostasis and producing cerebrospinal fluid. Role of CP in multiple system atrophy (MSA) remains unclear. This study aimed to investigate the implication of the CP in MSA. This retrospective cross-sectional study included 87 MSA patients who underwent the Unified MSA Rating Scale (UMSARS), brain MRI, and^(18)F-fluorodeoxyglucose PET scan, along with 84 healthy controls (HCs). Multivariate linear regression analyses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and safety of minimally invasive distal pancreatosplenectomy in resectable and borderline resectable pancreatic cancer following neoadjuvant chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Minimally invasive distal pancreatectomy is a safe and oncologically sound option for selected patients with advanced PDAC after neoadjuvant chemotherapy. With careful patient selection, MIS may be effectively applied even in technically challenging cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DrugBank mining with machine learning reveals novel candidates for BCL-2 inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Apoptosis, also known as programmed cell death, is a fundamental biological process essential for development and cellular homeostasis. An imbalance in the levels of pro- and antiapoptotic proteins of the BCL-2 family can inhibit apoptosis and contribute to tumor formation. Although small-molecule inhibitors targeting BCL-2 proteins have been developed, their clinical efficacy remains limited, highlighting the need for new approaches to discover effective inhibitors. In this study, we used a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence based prediction of first recurrence in neovascular age related macular degeneration with validation by 19 experts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the value and difference in predictive performance between ophthalmologists and a previously developed and validated artificial intelligence (AI) model, and to evaluate how AI assistance influences expert decision-making in reliably assessing recurrence prediction of neovascular age-related macular degeneration (nAMD) after anti-vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF) treatment. 19 experts (nine retinal specialist ophthalmologists and ten non-retinal specialist...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative ketorolac use and postoperative acute kidney injury in elderly patients undergoing noncardiac surgery: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, particularly ketorolac, in elderly patients is not recommended due to concerns about acute kidney injury (AKI). However, the effect of perioperative ketorolac use on postoperative AKI in elderly patients remains uncertain. We retrospectively reviewed patients aged ≥ 60 years who underwent noncardiac surgery lasting ≥ 1 h and were hospitalized for more than 2 days after surgery between January 2011 and June 2019. The ketorolac group included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cultural memory semiotics and function behavior structure model for digital inheritance and innovation in AI generated Huizhou woodcarving images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asthma-mediated control of optic glioma growth via T cell-microglia interactions: A mathematical model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optic glioma, a slow-growing tumor, is associated with Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1) mutations and increased midkine (MDK) production. A connection between asthma and optic glioma has previously been observed, but the mechanisms are unclear. To elucidate the role of asthma in the regulation of glioma formation, we investigated the role of T cells and the subsequent pathways in the regulation of microglia, a key player in the glioma tumor microenvironment (TME). While asthma is often linked to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A compact dual-band antenna using a gap-coupled monopole branch for Wi-Fi 6/6E/7 applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spin-state engineering of single titanium adsorbates on ultrathin magnesium oxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single atomic adsorbates on ultrathin insulating films provide a promising route towards building bottom-up quantum architectures based on atomically identical yet individually addressable spin qubits on solid surfaces. A key challenge in engineering quantum-coherent spin nanostructures lies in understanding and controlling the spin state of individual adsorbates. In this work, we investigate single titanium (Ti) atoms adsorbed on MgO/Ag(100) surfaces using a combined scanning tunneling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional evaluation of wax-based oleogels as solid fat replacers for designing low saturated fat plant-based meat analogues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meat analogues have gained global attention as consumer demand increases for healthier and more sustainable food products. However, research aimed at replacing solid fats in meat analogues to lower saturated fat content remains very limited. Canola oil was structured with three natural waxes (candelilla wax, carnauba wax, and beeswax) and their potentials as solid fat replacers were evaluated for low saturated fat meat analogues. The wax-based oleogels retained solid fat at higher temperatures...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduction of RAD23A extends lifespan and mitigates pathology in a mouse model of TDP-43 proteinopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein misfolding and aggregation are cardinal features of neurodegenerative disease (NDD) and they contribute to pathophysiology by both loss-of-function (LOF) and gain-of-function (GOF) mechanisms. This is well exemplified by TDP-43 which aggregates and mislocalizes in several NDDs. The depletion of nuclear TDP-43 leads to reduction in its normal function in RNA metabolism and the cytoplasmic accumulation of TDP-43 leads to aberrant protein homeostasis. A modifier screen found that loss of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Associations of Total and Added Sugar Intake With Frailty in Older Adults: Analysis From a National Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: Higher total sugar intake and moderate added sugar intake were associated with lower frailty risk in older Korean adults. These findings highlight the importance of considering both the amount and source of dietary sugars when developing nutritional guidelines for healthy aging. Future policies should focus on nuanced dietary recommendations rather than universal restriction for the elderly population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution and microstructure of the endothelial glycocalyx in the blood-brain barrier]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urban Soils Encounter More Severe Per- and Polyfluoroalkyl Substance Contaminations and Associated Exposure Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFASs), as persistent hazardous contaminants, have been increasingly identified in diverse environmental media. To date, however, information regarding the distribution and risks of PFASs in soils, particularly across urban-rural gradients, remains scarce. Therefore, this study performed high-resolution monitoring of PFASs at 119 sampling sites in the Qinhuai River Basin. The findings revealed that 18 targeted PFASs were identified in all soil samples, except...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean Dioxin Risk Patterns: Modulation by Dietary-Socio-Demographic and Behavioral Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Socio-demographic and behavioral factors may play an important role in modulating the non-carcinogenic risk associated with dietary dioxin exposure. Changes in dioxin risk patterns across such factors warrant further examination through additional investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Comparison of Health-Related Quality of Life at 3 and 12 Months Post-Stroke Using Patient-Reported Outcome Measures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Predictors and trajectories differed between PH and MH groups, supporting separate assessment. PROMIS-10 exhibited better discriminatory capacity of milder disability at 12 months by distinguishing physical and mental dimensions, supporting tailored care basis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid microneedle patch for administration of measles and rubella vaccine with an on-patient medical record]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decentralized on-patient medical record (OPMR) storage would enable medical staff to access patients' medical information on demand, especially in low-resource settings lacking centralized recordkeeping infrastructure. We incorporated near-infrared (NIR) microparticles into microneedle patches (MNPs) to invisibly encode medical information in the skin for OPMR using a specialized reader. NIR particles were co-encapsulated with inactivated polio vaccine in the same microneedles without loss of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[C2-Involving Cervical Ossification of the Posterior Longitudinal Ligament (OPLL): Dome-like Laminoplasty Versus Laminectomy With Fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectivesTo compare the outcomes of C2 dome-like laminoplasty (C2-Dom LP) and C2 laminectomy with fusion (C2-LF) in patients with C2-involving ossification of the posterior longitudinal ligament (OPLL) and to identify radiological predictors that guide optimal surgical selection.MethodsA retrospective analysis of 143 patients (C2-Dom LP, 71; C2-LF, 72) was performed. Radiological evaluations were C2 cross-sectional area (CSA), cervical range of motion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-series evaluation of an ED-based syndromic alarm system before and during the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ED-based SyS can offer timely and specific early warning for seasonal respiratory outbreaks, particularly in pediatric populations. However, its utility is limited during sustained pandemic waves. Future surveillance systems must incorporate adaptive models, dynamic thresholds, and multiple data streams to remain effective under evolving epidemiological baselines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing practical predictors of collection efficiency for optimized chimeric antigen receptor T-cell apheresis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CE2 during CAR-T apheresis is strongly influenced by pre-apheresis hematologic parameters, particularly WBC. Establishing CE2 predictors may refine estimation of processing volumes and improve planning for centers initiating CAR-T manufacturing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D-printable, heat-resistant polycaprolactone-based polymer scaffold for sustained NO release in tissue engineering applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study entailed the development of a nitric oxide (NO)-releasing, 3D-printable, heat-resistant polymer scaffold to support angiogenesis and osteogenesis for tissue engineering applications. A scaffold synthesized with poly(nitrocarbonate)-poly(ε-caprolactone) random copolymer (PNC-ran-PCL) enabled controlled NO release, addressing the rapid diffusion limitations found in conventional NO delivery systems. The thermoplastic properties of PNC-ran-PCL facilitate the creation of biomimetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment preferences and values in chronic tinnitus patients: A cross-sectional survey study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tinnitus patients strongly prefer non-invasive treatments while harboring unrealistic expectations for cure. These findings underscore the importance of structured education and shared decision-making to align clinical care with patient values and promote more effective tinnitus management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution and prognostic impact of LymphGen subtypes in Korean diffuse large B-cell lymphoma using clinical NGS panel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several molecular subclassifications of diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) with prognostic and therapeutic potential have been proposed; however, their validation in diverse populations and real-world clinical settings remains limited. We investigated the genetic subtypes of Korean DLBCL using the LymphGen classifier and an institutionally developed targeted NGS panel for clinical use comprising 121 lymphoma-related genes. We further assessed quality control (QC) metrics, copy-number...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CiFGNA: Comprehensive information-based functional gene network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous gene networks capture coordinated gene activities and systemic disruptions in complex biological processes and diseases, but extracting biologically meaningful insights from these large-scale networks remains challenging due to limited interpretability of existing methods. To address this gap, we have developed comprehensive information-based functional gene network analysis (CiFGNA), a novel computational methodology that systematically detects functional pathways enriched with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Grouped-Bath Configuration Interaction for Transition-Metal Complexes by L-Edge X-ray Spectra Calculations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We assess the accuracy and limitations of the grouped-bath configuration interaction (GBCI), formerly termed the grouped-bath ansatz for the spin-flip nonorthogonal configuration interaction (SF-GNOCI), by calculating L-edge X-ray absorption spectroscopy (XAS) spectra and 2p3d resonant inelastic X-ray scattering (RIXS) spectra of transition-metal complexes. We compare the computed GBCI spectra with those from the spin-flip complete-active-space (SF-CAS) method and experiment. These comparisons...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Evaluation of the Hemostatic Efficacy and Safety of a Biodegradable Hemostatic Agent, Hemogram: A Comparative Study with Arista™ AH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundHemogram is a novel biodegradable powdered hemostatic agent developed by binding calcium ions (Ca²^(+)) to carboxymethyl starch (CM-starch) and applying granulation technology to enhance blood absorption and hemostatic efficacy. This study aimed to evaluate the clinical efficacy and safety of Hemogram compared with the commercially available agent Arista™ AH in patients undergoing gastrectomy.MethodsThis randomized controlled trial was conducted at Samsung Medical Center and included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indirect Associations of Perceived Stress and Sleep Quality in the Relationship Between Andropause Symptoms and Quality of Life Among Middle-Aged Men: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the associations between andropause symptoms, perceived stress, and sleep quality, and determined the indirect pathway of perceived stress and sleep quality in the relationship between andropause symptoms and quality of life (QoL) among middle-aged men. This cross-sectional study employed a quantitative mediation analysis design. In total, 186 middle-aged men completed questionnaires, including the Androgen Deficiency in Aging Males Scale, Perceived Stress Scale, Pittsburgh...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Lymphoscintigraphy and SPECT/CT After Vascularized Lymph Node Transfer in Lymphedema Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lymphoscintigraphy with SPECT/CT may serve as a valuable prognostic tool for evaluating surgical outcomes following VLNT in lymphedema treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Invisible Text Injection and Peer Review by AI Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Quality of Evidence of and Engagement With Video Medical Claims]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this quality improvement study, a substantial credibility-evidence gap was found in physician-generated video-sharing content, where medical authorities often legitimized claims lacking robust empirical support. These findings emphasize the need for evidence-based content guidelines and enhanced science communication training for health care professionals to maintain scientific integrity in digital health information.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Selective Growth of Bi<sub>2</sub>SiO<sub>5</sub> for Uniform UV-B Photodetector Arrays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce Bi(2)SiO(5) (BSO), an intrinsically UV-B selective oxide with a 4.17 eV bandgap (297 nm), and present a cost-effective, scalable conversion approach for its synthesis. A single-step reaction between Bi(2)O(3) vapor and SiO(2) in fused silica converts the glass directly into crystalline BSO. To enable scalable integration, SiO(2) is first patterned on Al(2)O(3); the same conversion then proceeds exclusively within those patterns, yielding pixel-defined BSO films with sharply...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gynostemma pentaphyllum Hydrodistillate and Damulin B Prevent UVB-Induced Photoaging In Vitro and In Vivo via ROS Suppression and Restoration of MAPK/AP-1 and TGF-β/Smad Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoaging of the skin, driven by ultraviolet B (UVB) radiation, is characterized by the upregulation of matrix metalloproteinases (MMPs), accelerated collagen degradation, diminished hyaluronic acid (HA) content, and disruption of extracellular matrix (ECM) integrity, culminating in wrinkle formation, and structural damage. Nutritional and plant-derived compounds have garnered increasing attention as promising therapeutic agents for skin aging. In this study, we explored the anti-photoaging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viscoelastic Phase Transition of Polyborodimethylsiloxane (PBDMS) for Mechanical Pass Filters and Noise Fading Sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous monitoring of physiological signals is inevitably disrupted by motion artifacts and ambient mechanical noise. Signal processing is typically required to extract genuine physiological signals from motion artifacts, yet the signals can be distorted and classified incompletely. Previously, we presented a noise-selective damper based on gelatin hydrogel and chitosan, however, the hydrogel is unstable due to dehydration. In addition, various types of mechanical filters, such as high-pass,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standardization of MR Electrical Properties Tomography: A Guideline From the ISMRM Electro-Magnetic Tissue Properties Study Group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to discussion forum: Prognostic implications of moderate aortic stenosis with concomitant aortic regurgitation in degenerative aortic valve disease: insights from a multicentre cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into promoter recognition by Aca7]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CRISPR-Cas systems provide adaptive immunity to bacteria, although bacteriophages counter these defenses with anti-CRISPR (Acr) proteins. Acr expression is frequently regulated by anti-CRISPR associated (Aca) proteins, which repress transcription by binding inverted repeat (IR) sequences in operon promoters. Here, we report the first identification of an IR motif within the AcrIF11-Aca7 operon promoter from Halomonas caseinilytica and present the crystal structure of Aca7 bound to this IR DNA....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering delivery platforms for controlled nitric oxide release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitric oxide (NO) is a versatile gaseous signaling molecule with broad therapeutic potential in cardiovascular regulation, immune modulation, oncology, antibiotics, and tissue regeneration. However, its clinical application is severely constrained by physicochemical limitations, including poor aqueous solubility, rapid degradation, and the lack of spatiotemporal control over its release. To address these challenges, a diverse array of NO donors, ranging from spontaneous-release compounds to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JAK Inhibition Restores Epidermal Homeostasis and Modulates Immune Responses in Dermatomyositis Skin: A Spatial Transcriptomic Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure preserving t-SNE of matrix framed data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Across various fields, we can align data elements into a matrix frame with both row and column indices, forming what we refer to as matrix-framed data. These elements can take various forms, such as scalars, vectors, time series, matrices, or arrays. Existing data visualization methods aim to represent data elements of different groups without considering the underlying two-dimensional structure present in matrix-framed data. To address this limitation, we introduce a novel visualization method...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between Fish Consumption and Undernutrition among Young Indian Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Encouraging fish consumption through public initiatives like the National Nutrition Mission could be a valuable strategy for mitigating the burden of anemia among young children. Further research utilizing detailed food consumption data, including fish intake, is warranted to investigate its impact on child health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cannula is safer than needle in filler injection?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The choice between cannulas and needles for dermal filler injection has direct implications for safety, efficacy, and patient experience. This narrative review synthesizes evidence from randomized controlled trials, observational studies, cadaveric/anatomical work, and expert consensus to compare complication profiles and practical use-cases. Across multiple studies, cannulas-by virtue of their blunt tips and gliding technique-are associated with lower rates of bruising and a reduced signal for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-guided injection of ankle contouring with botulinum neurotoxin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ultrasound-guided botulinum toxin injections appear to be a safe and effective minimally invasive approach for ankle contouring, achieving clinically meaningful reductions in muscle bulk with high patient satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing a strategic action plan for reducing the burden of stroke in Africa: report of the first African Stroke Leaders' Summit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sustained reduction of stroke burden in Africa requires the adaptation of best practices to the African context, building the capacity of African stroke care professionals and using available resources with political support. Improving stroke literacy in African communities is a complementary strategy to reinforce healthy lifestyle choices and improve screening and detection of hypertension and other modifiable stroke risk factors. This process will culminate in a strategic African...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of stroke in adolescents and young adults (aged 15-39 years) in South East Asia: a trend analysis from 1990 to 2021 based on the global burden of disease study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study highlights significant progress in managing ICH and SAH, especially among younger populations and females. However, ischemic stroke remains a growing challenge, particularly for males, necessitating targeted interventions to reduce the overall stroke burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Povetacicept for IgA Nephropathy and Primary Membranous Nephropathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Povetacicept had substantial, sustained UPCR reductions with stable eGFR, significant Gd-IgA1 reductions, hematuria resolution, clinical remission, with favorable safety in IgAN. Similar results were observed in pMN. By inhibiting both BAFF and APRIL, povetacicept targets the underlying cause of disease and has potential to provide a significant therapeutic advancement for autoimmune glomerular diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of soy protein isolate-soybean oil emulsion-aggregated gels with enhanced elasticity and structural stability using vacuum-autoclave treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the structural and functional characteristics of soy protein isolate (SPI)-based emulsion-aggregated gels produced at different SPI-to-oil ratios with or without vacuum-assisted (VA) treatment. VA treatment markedly enhanced gel cohesion, reduced porosity, and produced denser, smoother microstructures, as confirmed by SEM analysis. Optimal formulations (S3O7 and S4O6) exhibited balanced textural properties, superior freeze-thaw stability, and higher absolute zeta...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary interactions of emulsification and gelation in aggregated pea protein-soybean oil emulsion gels: insights for developing plant-based cream cheese analogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to develop a plant-based cream cheese analog using pea protein isolate (PPI) and soybean oil by adjusting the protein-to-oil ratio to assess the impact of balancing interactions between emulsification and gelation. Emulsion gels with varying PPI-to-oil ratios were prepared and evaluated, with commercial dairy cream cheese as the control. Formulations with intermediate PPI-to-oil ratios exhibited optimal characteristics, including balanced spreadability, minimal fluid loss, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering meat-like performance in plant-based burger patties: focusing on structural, cooking, and textural properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the structural, cooking, and textural properties of beef and plant-based burger patties to identify factors governing meat-like behavior. Commercial and experimental plant-based burger patties were compared, and modified variants were developed by adjusting the particle size and content of textured vegetable protein (TVP) and by varying starch-based binders (potato starch, tapioca starch, and glutinous rice flour). Finer TVP particles increased cooking loss but improved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of external hand force modeling on validity of inverse analysis of lifting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Manual lifting tasks pose the risk of musculoskeletal injury, including damage to lumbar intervertebral discs. To assess the risk, spinal joint reaction forces are often estimated using musculoskeletal simulations. However, such analyses require information of external hand force and moment (EHF&M), which has mostly been estimated using simplified models without sufficient validation. This study evaluates the validity of two common EHF&M models by comparing their analysis outcomes to those...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide regulon of NtrC reveals genetic regulation under nitrogen limitation in <em>Methylomonas</em> sp. DH-1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogen is an essential element, but its scarcity often leads to growth constraints, driving the development of metabolic pathways and regulatory mechanisms. Here, we employed an integrated multi-omics approach to analyze the transcription factor NtrC and its regulon, elucidating the transcriptional adaptive response of Methylomonas sp. DH-1 to nitrogen limitation. An integrative analysis of ChIP-exo and RNA-seq revealed that 19 genes are directly regulated by NtrC. The NtrC regulon includes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controlled high-yield assembly of gold nanoparticles <em>via</em> amide bond formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Assembly of gold nanoparticles (AuNPs) enhances their plasmonic properties, including visible coloration, local electric field generation, hot-carrier production, and photothermal heating. While assembling AuNPs through chemical reactions that create solid, well-defined covalent linkages is highly desirable, achieving such assemblies with high efficiency remains challenging. During surface functionalisation and interparticle reactions, AuNPs are prone to aggregation, which compromises colloidal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unusual Presentation of Hyponatremia: Persistent Hiccups]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyponatremia is a common electrolyte disturbance with well-recognized neurological and gastrointestinal symptoms. However, it rarely presents with atypical manifestations, such as persistent hiccups. We report a case of a 36-year-old woman with necrotizing tonsillitis who developed persistent hiccups 3 days prior to hospitalization. Laboratory evaluation revealed severe hyponatremia (serum sodium [Na] 122.4 mEq/L), consistent with the syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comparative Analysis of GPT-3.5, GPT-4, GPT-4 Omni, Gemini Advanced, and Gemini 1.5 in Answering Total Knee Replacement-Related Questions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that GPT-3.5, GPT-4, GPT-4 Omni, and Gemini 1.5 can provide highly accurate and relevant responses to TKR-related queries, while Gemini Advanced underperforms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current issue on special topic: robotic single-port system in general surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current status of single-port robotic surgery in hepatobiliary and pancreatic surgery: technical aspects of review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-port robotic surgery is emerging in hepatobiliary and pancreatic procedures. Current studies demonstrate safety and feasibility in cholecystectomy, distal pancreatectomy, pancreaticoduodenectomy, and selected liver resections. Although evidence remains limited and indications conservative, ergonomic advantages, stable visualization, and learning-curve improvement suggest expanding applicability as technology and instrumentation mature.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined in-person and home-based circuit exercise improves body composition and hormonal profiles in patients with post-bariatric weight regain: a genotype-stratified single-arm interventional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A structured hybrid exercise and dietary program was effective in reversing early weight regain and improving hormonal profiles after MBS. The FTO risk allele was associated with greater baseline obesity but did not attenuate response to the intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-port robotic gastrectomy in gastric cancer: a narrative review on the state of the art and outlook]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Minimally invasive surgery for gastric cancer has progressed from conventional laparoscopy to reduced-port and single-incision techniques, and further to robotic systems that address ergonomic and technical constraints. Reduced-port laparoscopic gastrectomy and single-incision laparoscopic gastrectomy demonstrated feasibility and cosmetic advantages but faced inherent limitations-restricted triangulation, instrument collisions, and unstable visualization-resulting in steep learning curves and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in single-port robotic thyroidectomy: evolution, techniques, and clinical outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robotic thyroidectomy has progressed from multiport to single-port (SP) platforms to minimize invasiveness and improve cosmesis. The da Vinci SP system (Intuitive Surgical) combines a flexible 3-dimensional endoscope with 3 wristed instruments in a single 2.5-cm cannula-enabled concealed remote access route and mitigates external arm collisions. This review synthesized PubMed-indexed reports (2020-2025) on SP robotic thyroidectomy using the following approaches: transaxillary variants, SP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cutting-edge trends in da Vinci single-port robotic approaches to breast surgery: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The da Vinci single-port (SP) platform (Intuitive Surgical, Inc.) has catalyzed a new phase of remote-access breast surgery by delivering multi-jointed, wristed instrumentation and stable 3-dimensional optics through a single trocar. This narrative review synthesizes contemporary evidence and practice patterns for SP-assisted procedures, drawing on a recent series of robotic nipple-sparing mastectomies (NSMs). Indications parallel conventional NSM with patient selection favoring...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of atorvastatin, methylene blue, and lidocaine as chemical antiadhesion agents in preventing postoperative remote adhesions: a randomized controlled experimental study in a rat model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Intraperitoneal administration of lidocaine, methylene blue, and atorvastatin effectively reduced remote adhesion formation, macroscopic and microscopic adhesion scores, and inflammatory cytokine levels in a rat adhesion model.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRES-based RNAs expressing co-stimulatory molecules: Promising candidates for cancer immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optimizing co-stimulatory signaling to enhance T cell responses is central to effective antitumor immunity. In this study, we developed single-stranded RNAs (ssRNAs) utilizing the internal ribosome entry site (IRES) of encephalomyocarditis virus (EMCV) to express OX40L, 4-1BBL, and ICOSL and evaluated their efficacy. Co-culture of splenocytes with tumor cells transfected with these ssRNAs resulted in increased cytokine production and proliferation, along with altered T helper (Th) subsets. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparation of Internal Mammary Vessels Using Ultrasonic Energy: A Technical Note]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response: Risk of cancers in women with polycystic ovary syndrome: Cohort study based on health insurance database in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Body Mass Index-Adjusted Body Cell Mass and Lean Body Mass with Metabolic Syndrome and Insulin Resistance in Middle-Aged and Older Adults: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results suggest that BCM(bmi) is independently associated with metabolic markers and demonstrates comparable predictive power to LBM(bmi) for MetS and IR, particularly in males.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Effectiveness of a Prophylactic Application for the Prevention of Postpolypectomy Bleeding in Pedunculated Colonic Polyps: A Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This network meta-analysis supports the use of endoloops with epinephrine as the most effective strategy for preventing immediate bleeding after resection of pedunculated colonic polyps, while current measures remain insufficient for delayed bleeding.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Long-Term Outcomes between Curative and Non-Curative Resection after Endoscopic Submucosal Dissection for Superficial Esophageal Squamous Cell Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ESD followed by appropriate treatment can yield acceptable long-term outcomes, even when CR is not achieved. These findings suggest that ESD may be a viable first-line treatment strategy for SESCC, even in patients who are unlikely to achieve CR, particularly high-risk surgical patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visuospatial dysfunction indicates an increased risk of rapid dementia conversion in Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The aim of this study was to define cognitive subtypes of early-stage Parkinson's disease (PD) based on temporal evolutionary patterns of domain-specific decline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the Letter on "Role of ALBI Grade as a Predictive Factor for Long-Term Mortality in Patients With Hepatocellular Carcinoma (HCC) Undergoing Transarterial Chemoembolization (TACE)"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polarization-Selective Efficient Hydrogen Evolution Reactions via Chiral Photocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing demand for sustainable energy solutions has stimulated the development of advanced photocatalysts with enhanced efficiency of solar-driven hydrogen production. However, the intrinsic challenges of hydrogen evolution reaction (HER), including rapid electron-hole recombination, and insufficient light absorption of conventional semiconductors, underscore the need for innovative catalytic strategies beyond conventional semiconductors. Here, a chirality-integrated plasmonic photocatalyst...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing team mindsets: Development and validation of a scale for team learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Team mindsets are the collective beliefs of team members regarding their ability to enhance each other's capacity by sharing knowledge, learning from failures, and collaboratively addressing challenges. This study developed and validated the Team Mindset Scale (TMS) to measure individuals' perceptions of teamwork in relation to learning. The initial study revealed that the developed 48-team mindset items represented a two-factor structure encompassing team growth and fixed mindsets. We conducted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ORY1001 enhances anti-tumor immunity via CXCL10-mediated macrophage modulation in EBV-positive DLBCL]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A survey on the clinical practice of herpes zoster and postherpetic neuralgia management by Korean medicine doctors: towards the development of Korean medicine clinical practice guidelines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This first large-scale study addresses a critical gap, establishing a strong clinical consensus among KMDs prioritizing pain relief using a multimodal strategy (acupuncture, herbal medicine, and pharmacopuncture). The findings highlight the urgent need to standardize objective diagnostic protocols and provide an evidence-informed foundation for developing KM-CPGs, which can effectively complement WM in improving patient outcomes for HZ and PHN.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of synthetic protein-binding non-genetic DNA systems in living cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Life's development and adaption to fluctuating environments are underpinned by DNA-protein interactions, which have also spurred the development of artificial systems ranging from genetic circuits to nanoarchitectures. Nonetheless, in cellulo there remains an untapped design space for DNA-protein systems that are incompatible with the role of DNA as genetic material. Here we engineer retrons to intracellularly express non-genetic small DNAs embedding specific protein-binding sequences. These DNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Destabilization of cardiac myosin acetylation and sequestration with type 2 diabetes mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Human T2DM myocardium exhibits early, site‑specific myosin acetylations that destabilize myosin structural OFF‑state. This myosin 'preload' remodeling occurs at no energetic cost and may constitute a potential early marker of latent myocardial vulnerability in T2DM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546080/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative voltage mapping-assisted resection of a giant right ventricular giant tumor: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intraoperative voltage mapping proved to be a valuable adjunct in the surgical management of right ventricular tumors, enabling effective tumor resection while preserving myocardial tissue and maintaining postoperative cardiac function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of Upadacitinib in elderly patients with IBD: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of SGLT2 inhibitors on NSAID-associated acute kidney injury in type 2 diabetes: a claims-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene-body DNA methylation of ONECUT2 predicts its expression and prostate cancer aggressiveness in needle biopsies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between preoperative interruption of antiplatelet therapy and postoperative thrombotic risk after minimally invasive surgery for abdominopelvic cancer in patients treated with P2Y12 inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Discontinuing antiplatelet therapy in patients receiving P2Y12 inhibitors more than 5 days before MIS was associated with an increased risk of postoperative coronary artery disease, without providing any benefit in terms of bleeding control or mortality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment resistance factors associated with Talaporfin sodium photodynamic therapy for local control after chemoradiotherapy for esophageal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Esophageal stenosis before Talaporfin-PDT was associated with resistance to local control and poor survival. The indications for the use of Talaporfin-PDT in patients with stenosis should be considered carefully.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral Lentinula edodes mycelia extract enhances the antitumor effect of radiotherapy via gut-associated activation of dendritic and cytotoxic T cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral administration of Lentinula edodes mycelia extract (L.E.M.) has been shown to stimulate systemic T cell-mediated antitumor immunity and inhibit tumor growth in mice, suggesting its potential to modulate host immune responses. However, the route of this systemic antitumor effect remains unclear. This study focused on gut-associated immune mechanisms by analyzing mesenteric lymph nodes (MLNs), a major component of the gut-associated lymphoid tissue (GALT), and examined whether oral L.E.M....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of local anesthetics on yield and differentiation of synovial mesenchymal stem cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human synovial mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs) demonstrate high chondrogenic capacity for regenerative medicine. While ultrasound-guided collection procedures utilize local anesthetics for patient comfort, their effects on synovial MSCs remain unclear despite their known cytotoxicity to other MSC types. This study investigated whether clinically relevant concentrations of lidocaine and ropivacaine affect synovial MSC proliferation and differentiation. Human synovial tissue from eight donors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laparoscopy is preferred for small bowel obstruction in pregnancy after Roux-en-Y gastric bypass: a 10-year, single center study of 32 cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Laparoscopy is a suitable therapeutic approach for pregnant patients with suspected small bowel obstruction following bariatric surgery. Surgical intervention during pregnancy did not negatively impact outcomes. Early recognition of atypical presentations by clinicians, together with patient education on warning signs, is essential to prevent diagnostic delays and improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyperactivity is linked to elevated cortisol levels: comprehensive behavioral analysis in the prenatal valproic acid-induced marmoset model of autism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyperactivity is frequently observed in individuals with autism spectrum disorder (ASD) and significantly affects various aspects of life. This underscores the critical need for effective intervention methods tailored to the needs of individuals with ASD. Non-human primate models offer a promising avenue for elucidating the intricate interplay between ASD characteristics and developing individualized therapeutic strategies. This study examined the activity levels and behavioral dynamics in a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of the putative transcription factor Rim101 in pH/oxidative stress response and cell wall structure formation in the white-rot fungus Pleurotus ostreatus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The transcription factor Rim101 regulates various cellular functions in fungi, including maintaining cell homeostasis, regulating redox processes, and transmembrane transport, in response to environmental pH changes and redox stress. White-rot fungi encounter various environmental stresses during wood degradation. In this study, the role of Rim101 in the stress response of white-rot fungi was investigated by analysing the phenotype of rim101-disrupted strains of Pleurotus ostreatus. The Δrim101...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Loss of transcription factor ATOH8 activates TGF-β signaling and exacerbates glomerulosclerosis in podocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atonal BHLH transcription factor 8 (ATOH8) is a basic helix-loop-helix (bHLH) transcription factor; however, its role in glomerular epithelial cells (podocytes) remains unclear. This study aimed to elucidate the function of ATOH8 in podocytes. First, ATOH8 expression in the mouse kidney was confirmed in podocytes by immunofluorescence staining and in situ hybridization. In cultured human podocytes, transforming growth factor-beta (TGF-β) treatment significantly reduced ATOH8 mRNA expression. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shaping the Future of Respiratory Care: A look into the next decade and strategic recommendations by EUFOREA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic respiratory diseases (CRDs) remain one of the leading causes of preventable morbidity and disability worldwide, and affect up to one-third of the total Western population in 2025. Recognising the substantial burden of inflammatory airway diseases such as asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD), chronic rhinosinusitis (CRS) and respiratory allergy, the European Forum for Research and Education in Allergy and Airway Diseases (EUFOREA) organised the symposium "Shaping the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tetanus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tetanus, although preventable by a highly effective vaccine, continues to cause 30 000-50 000 deaths annually. Global mortality has fallen substantially since the 1980s due to widespread vaccination efforts, yet adult disease persists, especially among those with weakened immune response, diabetes, and people who inject drugs. Diagnosis is still clinical, and management combines wound debridement, antibiotics, and antitoxin. However, key questions about prevention, diagnosis, and management...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient recruitment strategies of the Belgian plastic surgeon: A national anonymous survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Referrals and word of mouth are the most important recruitment strategies among Belgian plastic surgeons. Social media is increasingly relevant, particularly for younger, international patients and aesthetic surgery. Its growing use raises professional, legal, and ethical challenges, highlighting the need for clearer legislation, awareness, and enforcement strategies with patient safety as central priority.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary and nonprimary auditory cortex connectivity with brain regions involved in cognitive and emotional processing: in mouse and human]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Auditory cortex connectivity extends beyond the processing of acoustic stimuli, playing a crucial role in cognitive and emotional regulation through its interactions with higher-order brain regions. Although the neural mechanisms underlying acoustic information processing along the auditory pathway are well-documented, the connections supporting auditory-related cognitive and emotional processing, particularly in comparative studies between mice and human adults, are not yet fully clarified. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human parainfluenza virus type 3 viruses with the furin-susceptible motif at the cleavage site of the fusion protein arose from original wild strains during their propagation in vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human parainfluenza virus type 3 (HPIV3) requires proteolytic cleavage of its fusion proteins by either exogenous serine proteases or a ubiquitous intracellular protease, furin, for replication in vitro. Viruses that utilize furin possess furin-susceptible amino acid sequence motifs at the cleavage site of the fusion protein when they infect host cells; without the motif, the virus cannot replicate in cultured cells without the aid of serine proteases such as trypsin. While HPIV3 isolates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-based discovery of novel TAOK3 inhibitor via virtual screening, molecular dynamics simulations, and MM/GBSA analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer persists as a leading cause of global mortality, and the mitogen-activated protein kinase (MAPK) pathway plays a pivotal role in tumor progression and drug resistance. Among MAPK regulators, TAOK3 has emerged as a promising therapeutic target due to its oncogenic role in various cancers. Despite its significance, no clinically approved TAOK3 inhibitors exist. In this study we implemented a structure-based virtual screening approach to identify potential TAOK3 inhibitors from a library of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global molecular epidemiology of <em>Mycoplasma pneumoniae</em> and its association with macrolide resistance and disease severity: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The global molecular epidemiology of Mycoplasma pneumoniae (MP) and its associations with macrolide resistance and disease severity remain unclear. Studies reporting MP genotypes distribution by P1 typing, multiple locus variable number tandem repeat analysis (MLVA), or multilocus sequence typing analysis (MLST) among MP-infected patients were included. Data quality was assessed using the Joanna Briggs Institute tool and the Newcastle-Ottawa scale. Random-effects models were used to calculate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FLIPs: Genetically encoded molecular biosensors for functional imaging of cell signaling by linear dichroism microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetically encoded fluorescent biosensors convert specific biomolecular events into optically detectable signals. However, imaging biomolecular processes often requires modifying the proteins involved, and many molecular processes are still to be imaged. Here, we present a biosensor design that uses a hitherto overlooked detection principle: directionality of optical properties of fluorescent proteins. The biosensors (termed FLIPs) offer an extremely simple design, high sensitivity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International guideline on genetic testing of children with short stature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Short stature may be caused by a multitude of conditions including genetic and non-genetic causes. Over the last decade, advances in genetic sequencing technologies have revolutionized our understanding of the underlying physiology of growth and greatly increased our ability to identify genetic etiologies of short stature. The current guideline provides a general overview of the approach to the evaluation of a child with short stature followed by recommendations identifying factors in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[De novo discovery of bicyclic cysteine-rich peptides targeting gasdermin D]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gasdermin D (GSDMD) is the principal executor of pyroptosis, a form of proinflammatory programmed cell death misregulation of which is associated with numerous diseases. Despite significant interest, no specific GSDMD inhibitors have been developed for clinical use so far. Here, we developed a strategy to generate mRNA-displayed libraries of bicyclic cysteine-rich peptides (bCRP), and utilized these libraries to develop potent peptide ligands to full-length GSDMD using a two-stage discovery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolution of environmental sex determination via juvenile hormone-induced gene co-option in <em>Daphnia</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Juvenile hormone (JH) exerts pleiotropic effects in insects, regulating not only metamorphosis and reproduction but also caste differentiation, morphogenesis, and diapause. How such diverse functions evolved from the ancestral role of JH remains poorly understood. The water flea, Daphnia, provides a striking case in which JH governs environmental sex determination (ESD) by inducing male production. Nonetheless, the molecular pathway linking maternal JH signaling to sex determination has remained...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor Regarding "Advanced Liver Disease Events in People with HIV and Hepatitis B Virus Coinfection Initiating Antiretroviral Therapy in the United States"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical effects of taper angles in implant-abutment connection: a finite element study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Taper angle differences affect press-fit, abutment axial displacement, screw loosening, stress distribution, and microgap formation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>18</sup>F-PSMA-PET/CT in comparison with whole-body MRI and combination of conventional CT and bone scintigraphy for detection of recurrent disease in prostate cancer patients with rising PSA levels after initial definitive treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ^(18)F-FSU-880 PSMA-PET/CT showed a more favorable diagnostic performance, especially in terms of sensitivity, than WB-MRI and CT/BS in detecting recurrent disease in patients with prostate cancer after definitive treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of exercise interventions on cardiorespiratory fitness in childhood cancer survivors: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Exercise interventions significantly improved CRF in CCS. Due to the limited amount and heterogeneity of included studies, optimal FITT parameters to increase CRF in CCS could not be identified. More randomized controlled trials with large sample sizes are needed to complement existing evidence and increase the robustness of the findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictors of arrhythmia recurrence after cryoballoon ablation in paroxysmal atrial fibrillation: a comparative analysis from the CONTRAST-CRYO trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimized selection of specific antibodies against rodent ESR1 proteins and their application for immunohistochemistry and dual immunohistofluorescence with the specific anti-ESR2 antibody PPZ0506]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of immunohistochemical and immunohistofluorescence assays is essential for investigating the tissue and cellular distribution of target proteins. In this study, we identify specific anti-ESR1 antibodies against rodent ESR1 proteins and evaluate their applicability for immunohistochemistry and dual immunohistofluorescence with the specific anti-ESR2 antibody PPZ0506. We assessed the specificity and cross-reactivity of six commercially available anti-ESR1 antibodies (Clones MC-20,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do 6-9-year-old children in Denmark adhere to national dietary recommendations and are there sociodemographic disparities? The Generation Healthy Kids study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Possible functional origin of TPO-like genes in chordates revealed by their pleiotropic expression and disturbed phenomena in protochordates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mammalian thyroid peroxidase (TPO), a thyroid-specific peroxidase involved in thyroid hormone synthesis, has a characteristic hydrophobic region in the C-terminus (HRC) that anchors peroxidase to the apical membrane of epithelial follicle cells. Protochordates (lancelets and ascidians) have TPO-like (TPOL) peroxidases with or without HRC, and their expression has been reported in the endostyle. We herein investigated the molecular structures of TPOL in protochordates and TPO relatives in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retina-like Vascular Architecture in Persistent Fetal Vasculature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physiological cerebrospinal fluid interactions between brain and eye structures are altered after long-duration spaceflight]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Long-duration spaceflight represents an extreme challenge, triggering adaptive responses including spaceflight-associated neuro-ocular syndrome, characterized by diminished visual acuity and ocular changes, which is a significant health risk for Mars missions. Concurrently, spacefarers experience brain adaptations, including ventricular expansion and CSF redistribution; however, the integrative physiological mechanisms linking these brain-eye responses remain unestablished. We applied automated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SmI<sub>2</sub>/Sm-Induced Reductive Silacyclization of Alkene/Diene Derivatives Using Dichlorosilanes or 1,2-Dichlorodisilanes via Reductive Radical-Polar Crossover]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of efficient strategies for constructing cyclic organosilicon frameworks is considered of great importance because of their structural diversity and synthetic utility. Herein, we report a SmI(2)/Sm-mediated silacyclization of unsaturated organic compounds with readily available dichlorosilanes and -disilanes, enabling convenient access to 4-7-membered silacyclic compounds. Mechanistic investigations indicate that the reaction involves silyl radical intermediates and proceeds via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Circ72309 modulates gemcitabine metabolism and gemcitabine sensitivity in pancreatic cancer: Serum Circ72309 levels as a potential predictor of treatment response&lt;/p&gt;]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Circular RNAs (circRNAs) are associated with various biological features of cancer, including chemosensitivity and the structural characteristics of circRNAs indicate their potential as liquid biomarkers. Gemcitabine is a cornerstone treatment for pancreatic cancer (PC). A deeper understanding of gemcitabine sensitivity and the exploration of clinically valuable liquid biomarkers that are predictive of gemcitabine sensitivity may contribute to the development of improved‑tailored treatment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel model to study the impact of gender-affirming therapy on bone in young male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transgender individuals are increasingly seeking gender-affirming therapy. For children and adolescents, this typically involves puberty suppression followed by hormone treatment. However, potential long-term adverse effects on the growing skeleton remain poorly characterized, largely due to the lack of appropriate preclinical animal models. Existing models often rely on surgical puberty suppression and, in the case of estradiol (E2) administration, cause a high bone mass-phenotype that is not...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrahigh mobility and Rashba spin splitting in Sb-substituted bismuth telluride and bismuth selenide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topological insulators (TIs) such as Sb-doped Bi(2)Te(3) and Bi(2)Se(3) exhibit promising phenomena for advanced spintronics. While previous studies explored isolated doping levels; a systematic understanding of how Sb concentration influences topological behavior, Rashba-type spin splitting, and surface state formation is lacking. Here, we use density functional theory to investigate the structural, electronic, topological and transport properties of (Bi(1-x)Sb(x))(2)Te(3) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extensive phenotyping and genome-wide analysis of grain number-related traits in a diverse wheat core collection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bread wheat (Triticum aestivum L.) is one of the most important staple crops globally. Grain number per spikelet (GPS) is an important yield component in wheat. It is influenced by floret number per spikelet (FPS) and floret fertility. Through three consecutive years of observation of FPS, GPS, and floret fertility per spikelet (FFPS) in a globally collected hexaploid wheat core collection and using an improved genotyping dataset, we identified 42 marker-trait associations (MTA) for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bayesian reanalysis to assess consistency of TALAPRO-2 results in the Japanese subgroup with metastatic castration-resistant prostate cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Using Bayesian evidence synthesis with prespecified borrowing levels, the Japanese subgroup results were compatible in direction and magnitude with the overall TALAPRO-2 effect. These findings reduce uncertainty around local extrapolation; a dedicated randomized study would be required to establish efficacy independently in Japanese patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-stratified outcomes of radical cystectomy for muscle-invasive bladder cancer: a nationwide multicenter study of 1867 patients in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients aged ≥80 years had significantly worse oncological outcomes after RC. NAC may improve OS in selected older patients with good performance status.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quinone-Based Mediator Immobilized Mesoporous Electrodes for Bioelectrocatalysis of Glucose Dehydrogenase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bioelectrocatalysis, which couples enzymatic catalytic and electrode reactions, is the basic principle behind enzyme electrochemical biosensors, biofuel cells, and bioelectrosynthesis systems. Electron mediators facilitate the transfer of electrons between electrodes and oxidoreductases during catalytic reactions, so ideally the mediator remains near the electrode for higher catalytic efficiency. Additionally, electrode materials with three-dimensional space at the enzyme volume mesoscale are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gold-Catalyzed Cyclization of Pyrrole-Tethered Allenynes for the Synthesis of 4-Acylindoles and Its Application to the Ergot Alkaloid Scaffold]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gold-catalyzed cyclization of pyrrole-tethered allenynes produces 4-acylindoles, accompanied by oxidative benzene ring formation. This reaction would proceed via the activation of the allene by a gold catalyst, nucleophilic attack of the alkyne in a 6-endo-dig manner, and trapping of the resulting vinyl cation by an oxygen nucleophile. This methodology was successfully applied to construct the core structure of the ergot alkaloids.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the multifaceted nature of quality of life in dementia using a transdiagnostic network analysis approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: QOL in dementia is inherently multidimensional and differs when assessed from the viewpoint of the person living with dementia versus their carer. Network approaches offer the granularity required to ensure that targeted interventions can be tailored toward these complementary perspectives.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elucidating Leader Peptide-Enzyme Dynamics in Lactazole Biosynthesis Using mRNA Display]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thiopeptides are a class of ribosomally synthesized and post-translationally modified peptides (RiPPs) that show promise for drug discovery. Their biosynthesis depends on leader peptide recognition, whereby multiple enzymes are recruited to process a core region into the mature natural product. Here, we identify sequence determinants of the leader peptide-enzyme dynamics in a thiopeptide biosynthesis. Using the flexible in vitro (FIT)-Laz translation platform, we examined how leader mutations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ISUOG Consensus Statement on sonographic assessment of the endometrium: how to perform a gynecological ultrasound scan and report the findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle Metal Mass Uptake Correlates with Radiosensitizing Efficacy across 2D, 3D, and In Vivo Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite extensive efforts to develop nanoparticle-based radioenhancers, clinical translation remains limited, partly due to the lack of physiologically relevant preclinical models. To address this gap, we developed a 3D spheroid model of head and neck cancer using FaDu cells and compared it directly to a corresponding in vivo model in a radiotherapy setting. The spheroids exhibited key tumor-like features, including the formation of a hypoxic core and growth kinetics similar to those of in vivo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117023755&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>