<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:41:33 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic-scale 3D structural dynamics and functional degradation of Pt alloy nanocatalysts during the oxygen reduction reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pt-based electrocatalysts are the primary choice for fuel cells due to their superior oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) activity. To enhance ORR performance and durability, extensive studies have investigated transition metal alloying, doping, and shape control to optimize the three key governing factors for ORR: geometry, local chemistry, and strain of their surface and subsurface. However, systematic optimization remains incomplete, as it requires an atomic-scale understanding of these factors...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Chronic Administration of a Standardized Rice Bran Supplement on Sleep Architecture and Profiles in Mice: A Comparative Study with a Hypnotic Drug Zolpidem]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the effects of chronic administration of rice bran supplement (RBS) on sleep and to compare these effects with those of the hypnotic drug zolpidem (ZPD). During the three-week treatment period, ZPD initially reduced sleep latency, but that reduction effect of sleep latency gradually diminished over time and significantly decreased non-rapid eye movement sleep (NREMS). In contrast, RBS reduced sleep latency and increased NREMS on the first day, and these effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protopine Exerts Anti-Leukemic Effects by Promoting ROS-mediated Inhibition of Survival Signals in Acute Myeloid Leukemia Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Protopine represents a promising candidate for differentiation-based therapy in AML.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Phase II Trial of Pemetrexed Plus Oxaliplatin in Patients With Advanced Biliary Tract Cancer After Failure of Gemcitabine Plus Cisplatin-based Chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PemOx showed modest efficacy and manageable TRAEs in patients with aBTC after the failure of first line GP-based chemotherapy, although the primary endpoint was not met.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combinations of <em>Salmonella typhimurium</em> A1-R, Recombinant Methioninase, and Chloroquine, Each Targeting Fundamental Cancer Hallmarks, Are Selectively Effective on Colon Cancer Cells Compared to Normal Fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tumor-targeting with A1-R combined with methionine restriction (rMETase) or autophagy inhibition (CQ) resulted in selective and synergistic cytotoxicity against colon-cancer cells compared to normal fibroblasts. The present findings support the clinical potential of the combination of A1-R, rMETase, and CQ for recalcitrant colon cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring bacteriophages to combat gut dysbiosis: A promising new frontier in microbiome therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dysbiosis is the imbalance in the composition and function of the microbial community in the human body that leads to various multifactorial diseases, including autoimmune diseases, Alzheimer's disease, and rheumatoid arthritis. To address this problem, numerous research has demonstrated the potential of bacteriophages as therapeutic agents to regulate dysbiosis in the human body. Furthermore, phage-based products such as endolysins, proteins, and peptides have also been demonstrated to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of metaverse-based nursing education on operating room patient safety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both training methods demonstrated comparable educational outcomes. These findings suggest that metaverse-based education has the potential to be a viable alternative to traditional clinical training in operating room patient safety nursing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-Woven Stem Cells as Innovative Building Blocks for Enhanced 3D Bone Development and Tissue Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several major issues in conventional 3D spheroid systems include cellular heterogeneity, uncontrolled cell differentiation, and batch-to-batch variations. In this study, mesoporous silica nanoparticles (mSiO(2) NPs), human adipose-derived mesenchymal stem cells (hADMSCs), and boronate-phenolic interactions are applied for the first time to address these issues. Stable attachment of the NPs to hADMSCs via boronate-phenolic interactions produced nanobiohybrids, a novel building block for 3D...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Innovative Didactic Learning Formats: Have They Improved Dental Education? A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Innovative strategies lead to superior knowledge acquisition in comparison with traditional methods. Subgroup analyses favoured synchronous blended learning, but both asynchronous independent learning and synchronous learning formats, whether implemented in large-group settings via blended approaches or in small-group environments, are more effective than traditional instruction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide association and fine-mapping analyses identify novel candidate genes affecting serum cortisol levels using imputed whole-genome sequencing data in pigs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In swine breeding programs, it has now become critically important to emphasize selection for resilience to external environmental stress factors that have negatively impacted the productivity of pigs, such as those due to climate change induced temperature increases, or the intensification of housing environments. Secretion of cortisol, a neurophysiological change mediated by the hypothalamic-pituitary-adrenal axis, is a central mechanism in the biological stress response. This hormone is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alternative nutritional evaluation of black soldier fly with various substrates in cat diets and its effects on fecal microbiota]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to examine the effects of proper substitution ratios and organic substrates of black soldier fly larvae (Hermetia illucens larvae; HIL) on cats. A total of 30 mixed-sex domestic cats (Felis domestica) with an initial body weight of 5.06 ± 0.89 kg were used in this experiment, which used an incomplete 5 × 5 replicated Latin square design. The experimental period was 10 d, with 7 d of diet adaptation followed by 3 d of dietary treatment. The dietary treatments were provided: 1)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of red yeast rice on the growth of male SD rats: a 90-day feeding study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Red yeast rice (RYR) is commonly used as colouring and flavouring agent in foods throughout East Asia. RYR contains monacolin K, a compound known to lower blood lipids level, which has led to its use as a health functional food in Korea. Additionally, RYR is frequently used as a food ingredient and is incorporated into processed foods such as bread and makgeolli, a traditional Korean alcoholic beverage. However adverse effects associated with RYR have been reported by several regulatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hair Growth and Health Promoting Effects of Standardized <em>Ageratum conyzoides</em> Extract in Human Follicle Dermal Papilla Cells and in C57BL/6 Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Hair loss, driven by disrupted hair cycles, age-related hormonal imbalances, and oxidative stress, poses significant psychological challenges, necessitating the development of safe and effective therapies. This research investigates the trichogenic potential and underlying mechanisms of a standardized Ageratum conyzoides extract (ACE) using human follicle dermal papilla cells (HFDPCs) and C57BL/6 mice as models. Methods: HFDPCs were treated with ACE to assess its effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioactive Phenolics from Vinegar-Egg Accelerates Acute Wound Healing by Activation of Focal Adhesion and Mitogen-Activated Protein Kinase Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings demonstrate that 4-hydroxybenzoic acid (1) and vanillic acid (2) accelerate wound healing through the activation of focal adhesion and mitogen-activated protein kinase (MAPK) signaling pathways. These results highlight vinegar-egg as a promising therapeutic candidate for wound healing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-Wavelength Infrared Hyperspectral Imaging and Spectral Unmixing Techniques for Detection and Distribution of Pesticide Residues on Edible Perilla Leaves]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40870776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pesticide residue analysis of agricultural produce is vital because of associated health concerns, highlighting the need for effective non-destructive techniques. This study introduces a method that combines short-wavelength infrared hyperspectral imaging with spectral unmixing to detect chlorfenapyr and azoxystrobin residues on perilla leaves. Sixty-six leaves were treated with pesticides at concentrations between 0 and 0.06%. The study utilized multicurve resolution-alternating least squares...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40870776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Spatial Distribution of Pulse Blue Butterfly (<em>Lampides boeticus</em>), Pest of Legume Crops, in Response to Climate Change]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40870627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The potential distribution of the pulse blue butterfly, Lampides boeticus (Lepidoptera: Lycaenidae), was determined using MaxEnt, random forest, and ensemble models. The results indicate that most tropical, subtropical, and some temperate regions are suitable habitats. Climate change is projected to expand the species' habitat northward in the Northern Hemisphere. Predicted distributions aligned well with the known occurrence records for the species. The minimum temperature of the coldest month...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40870627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Three New Species of Nolidae (Lepidoptera) from Palawan Island, the Philippines, with Checklists of the Genera <em>Wittonola</em>, <em>Aeneanola</em>, and <em>Evonima</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40870576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper contains three newly recorded genera (Wittonola László, Ronkay & Ronkay, 2015; Aeneanola László, Ronkay & Ronkay, 2013; and Evonima Walker, 1865) and each new species (W. bicyanasp. nov., A. crassasp. nov., and E. palawanensissp. nov.) from Palawan, the Philippines. We provide illustrations of three new species and their genitalia, photographs of collecting sites, and checklists of the three genera.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40870576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Changes in Trends of Nationwide Incidence of Glaucoma and Associated Visual Impairment in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40869519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: We analyzed recent changes in the incidence of glaucoma and associated visual impairment (VI) in Korea over a 16-year period. Methods: We utilized nationwide, longitudinal cohort data from the Korea National Health Insurance System (KNHIS) National Health Screening Cohort from 2004 to 2019 to evaluate the age-standardized incidence rate (SIR) of glaucoma and glaucoma-related VI. VI was determined based on KNHIS health examinations and the National Registry for Visual...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40869519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing Japanese Encephalitis Virus as a Veterinary Infectious Disease Through Animal Surveillance and One Health Control Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40868908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Japanese encephalitis virus (JEV) is a mosquito-borne zoonotic flavivirus that circulates primarily within animal populations and occasionally spills over to humans, causing severe neurological disease. While humans are terminal hosts, veterinary species such as pigs and birds play essential roles in viral amplification and maintenance, making JEV fundamentally a veterinary infectious disease with zoonotic potential. This review summarizes the current understanding of JEV transmission dynamics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40868908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Antioxidant and Biological Activities of <em>Quercus Fructus</em>: Synergistic Role of Inner Shell and Extraction Methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40867872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study comprehensively evaluated how the inclusion of the inner shell and the choice of extraction method influence the antioxidant activity of Quercus Fructus (QF). Eight QF extracts were prepared with or without the inner shell using stirring (S) and ultrasonication (U) with 80% ethanol, boiled water (B) and autoclave (A) with distilled water. Among them, the ultrasonication extract with inner shell (IU) exhibited the highest antioxidant capacity, showing strong DPPH radical scavenging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40867872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Synthetic Tag Induces Palmitoylation and Directs the Subcellular Localization of Target Proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40867521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Proper subcellular localization is essential to exert the designated function of a protein, not only for endogenous proteins but also transgene-encoded proteins. Post-translational modification is a frequently used method to regulate the subcellular localization of a specific protein. While there are a number of tags that are widely used to direct the target protein to a specific location within a cell, these tags often fail to emulate the dynamics of protein trafficking, necessitating an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40867521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Activation of G Protein-Coupled Estrogen Receptor Induces p53 and ADAMTS1 to Inhibit Tumor Growth and Suppress Liver Cancer Metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40867252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Liver cancer is a common cause of cancer-related deaths among men and women globally. A disintegrin and metalloproteinase with thrombospondin motif 1 (ADAMST1) has been associated with various cancers, including prostate, esophageal, renal, and breast cancers. However, its role in liver cancer remains unclear. The aim of this study was to investigate the relationship between G protein-coupled estrogen (GPER) activation via its agonist, G1, and ADAMTS1 in suppressing liver...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40867252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250829034127&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal Faecalibacterium pathobionts and low-fiber diets synergize to impact offspring health: implications for atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide compelling evidence that maternalFaecalibacterium pathobionts play a critical role in the development of systemic conditions in offspring, offering valuable insights into the etiology of AD. Furthermore, the synergistic effect of gut microbiota dysbiosis and low fiber intake highlights the potential impact of modern dietary trends on the rising prevalence of AD and other chronic conditions. Video Abstract.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retrosynthetic crosstalk between single-step reaction and multi-step planning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retrosynthesis-the process of deconstructing complex molecules into simpler, more accessible precursors-is a cornerstone of drug discovery and material design. While machine learning has improved single-step retrosynthesis prediction, generating complete multi-step retrosynthetic routes remains challenging. In this study, we explore the integration of single-step retrosynthesis models with various planning algorithms to improve multi-step retrosynthetic route generation. We expand the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping interconnectivity of digital twin healthcare research themes through structural topic modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital twin (DT) technology is revolutionizing healthcare systems by leveraging real-time data integration and advanced analytics to enhance patient care, optimize clinical operations, and facilitate simulation. This study aimed to identify key research trends related to the application of DTs to healthcare using structural topic modeling (STM). Five electronic databases were searched for articles related to healthcare and DT. Using the held-out likelihood, residual, semantic coherence, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of Nanotube-Shaped mRNA Vehicles Using Self-Assembling Peptides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mRNA delivery vehicle technology is one of the key factors in developing mRNA-based therapeutics and vaccines. The delivery vehicle must protect the mRNA from degradation, accurately deliver it across body barriers into the target tissue or cell, and properly regulate expression of the protein. Even though the stability and performance of mRNA delivery vehicles is highly dependent on their nanostructure, most vehicles were irregular spherical shapes. In this chapter, we describe a detailed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-model approach for accurate chest disease detection using GViT and swin transformer V2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The precise detection and localization of abnormalities in radiological images are very crucial for clinical diagnosis and treatment planning. To build reliable models, large and annotated datasets are required that contain disease labels and abnormality locations. Most of the time, radiologists face challenges in identifying and segmenting thoracic diseases such as COVID-19, Pneumonia, Tuberculosis, and lung cancer due to overlapping visual patterns in X-ray images. This study proposes a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum geometry in hexagonal circuit QED lattice with triple leg stripline resonators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate various geometric aspects of a photonic hexagonal lattice made of triple-leg stripline resonators (TSRs) in a circuit QED system. The inherent two-fold degenerate spatial modes of the TSR act as two distinct orbitals in our 2D lattice system. Remarkably the energy spectra of the system exhibits the dispersive quadratic band-touching to the top and bottom flat bands. Our analysis reveals how the system harnesses destructive interference to establish flat bands via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular and morphological insights into the taxonomic classification and introduction pathways of Vespa crabro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The classification of the European hornet, Vespa crabro, into subspecies based on thoracic and abdominal color patterns remains controversial. This study combined morphological assessments and mitochondrial genetic analyses to critically evaluate subspecies delimitation and introduction pathways of V. crabro, focusing on two traditionally recognized subspecies in Korea: V. c. crabroniformis and V. c. flavofasciata. Morphological examination of 163 Korean specimens identified 27 distinct color...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of retinal layer thickness with brain volume and cortical thickness in older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study explored associations between macular retinal nerve fiber layer (RNFL) thickness, brain volume, and cortical thickness in older adults. A total of 166 community-dwelling participants over 65 years old (mean 75.2 ± 5.3; 61.4% women) without dementia or ocular pathologies underwent 3D T1 MRI and macular RNFL thickness measurements using spectral-domain optical coherence tomography. Voxel-based morphometry, adjusting for age, sex, and total intracranial volume (uncorrected p < 0.001,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Next-generation graph computing with electric current-based and quantum-inspired approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graph data is crucial for modeling complex relationships in various fields, but conventional graph computing methods struggle to handle increasingly intricate and large-scale graph data. Electric current-based graph computing and Quantum-inspired graph computing offer innovative hardware-based solutions to these challenges. Electric current-based graph computing has progressed from Euclidean graph data to non-Euclidean ones using the memristive crossbar arrays. This Perspective introduces...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ACTL6A depletion induces KLF4-mediated anti-tumorigenic effects in colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ACTL6A, a subunit of the SWI/SNF and INO80 chromatin remodeling complexes, is frequently overexpressed in various cancers, and its depletion attenuates cell proliferation in colorectal cancer (CRC). However, the epigenetic mechanisms underlying ACTL6A function remain poorly understood. Here, we aimed to elucidate how ACTL6A regulates chromatin accessibility and gene expression in CRC. Integrated multi-omics analyses revealed that ACTL6A deficiency alters chromatin accessibility and upregulates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of High-Throughput Screening Protocol Based on Isomerase Using <em>Geobacillus</em> sp. L-Rhamnose Isomerase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Directed evolution is a powerful tool in protein engineering that generates diverse variant libraries to enhance enzyme functionalities. However, the identification of desirable variants from large mutant libraries requires an efficient high-throughput screening (HTS) technique. In this study, we established a robust HTS protocol for selecting high-activity isomerase variants, specifically using L-rhamnose isomerase (L-RI) consistently; avoid switching between L-RI and L-RhI. L-RI catalyzes the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Basis for Tetramerization of <em>Klebsiella pneumoniae</em> <em>N</em>-Acetylglucosamine-6-Phosphate Deacetylase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[N-acetylglucosamine-6-phosphate deacetylase (NagA) is a conserved enzyme involved in bacterial amino sugar metabolism, catalyzing the conversion of GlcNAc-6-phosphate to GlcN-6-phosphate and acetate. While NagA typically function as dimers, its quaternary diversity across species remains underexplored. Here, we present the crystal structure of Klebsiella pneumoniae (kpNagA), which forms a homotetrameric assembly both in crystal and in solution, as confirmed by SEC-MALS. Each monomer adopts a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progression of Thoracic Kyphosis After Lower Thoracic Fusion in Lumbar Flatback Deformity: Analysis of Risk Factors and Clinical Consequences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectivesTo investigate the risk factors and clinical impact of progression of thoracic kyphosis (PTK) in who underwent lower thoracic fusion for lumbar flatback deformity (LFBD).MethodsThe study included 170 patients (mean age 70.2 years; 90.6% female) who underwent fusion from the lower thoracic spine (T9 or T10) for LFBD with a minimum follow-up of 2 years. PTK was defined as a final thoracic kyphosis (TK) ≥ 40° and ΔTK ≥10°. Multivariate logistic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Gas Exchange in ECMO: Key Insights for Clinical Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review examines the role of extracorporeal membrane oxygenation (ECMO) in the management of severe acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS), emphasizing its contribution to lung-protective ventilation by optimizing oxygenation and ensuring optimal decarboxylation. Key determinants of oxygen delivery during ECMO include circuit blood flow, cannula size and positioning, and hemoglobin concentration. Strategies for troubleshooting oxygenation issues, including recirculation, increased oxygen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of urinary creatinine concentration and specific gravity correction in exposure assessment: Comparison between chronic kidney disease patients and general population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Urine is a favored matrix for biomonitoring of several important classes of chemicals. Because of variations in concentration, however, urine is often adjusted for dilution. Urinary creatinine (Cr) and specific gravity (SG) have been frequently employed for this purpose. The filtration function of the kidneys may influence the excretion of Cr and SG into the urine; their influences on urinary exposure biomarker levels are well-characterized. We hypothesized that dilution adjustment of urine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Evaluation of AI-Based Three-Dimensional Dental Implant Planning: A Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The AI-based 3D implant planning tool demonstrated potential as a decision-support system by providing valuable guidance in clinical scenarios. However, discrepancies between AI-generated and actual implant positions indicate that further research and development are needed to enhance its predictive accuracy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developmental toxicity of microplastics in human stem cells using adverse outcome pathway based Integrated Approaches to Testing and Assessment approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Micro/nanoplastics (MNPs), detected in human tissues including the placenta, raise significant concerns regarding their potential impact on early human development. However, the mechanisms underlying their developmental toxicity remain poorly understood. To address this, we applied an Integrated Approaches to Testing and Assessment (IATA) framework to evaluate the developmental toxicity of polystyrene (PS) MNPs by combining adverse outcome pathway (AOP) development, experimental testing within...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suicide trends and patterns in young adults across global regions and selected major countries worldwide from the World Health Organization mortality database, 2001-2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Suicide trends among young adults varied by sex, method, and country, with concerning increases or persistently high rates observed in some countries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LUNAR: Periodicity-aware time-series analysis framework for LUNg Auscultation Respiratory detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate detection of respiratory cycles in lung sound auscultation is crucial for diagnosing respiratory diseases such as asthma, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease, and pneumonia. Traditional auscultation methods rely heavily on clinician expertise, creating diagnostic inconsistencies particularly in resource-constrained settings where access to specialists varies. While recent artificial intelligence approaches have advanced abnormal breath sound classification and respiratory disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of driving pressure and mechanical power with postoperative pulmonary complications in one-lung ventilated surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this OLV surgery population, a DP-Pplat-limited mechanical ventilation strategy of 15 cmH(2)O or DP-PIP of 18 cmH(2)O was associated with lower risk of PPC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two different domain swapped dimer structures were revealed by crystal structure of EPIC1 from Phytophthora nicotianae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cysteine protease inhibitors such as cystatins are crucial regulators of proteolytic activity involved in immunity, host-pathogen interactions, and cellular homeostasis. EPIC1, a cystatin-like inhibitor secreted by plant pathogen, such as Phytophthora nicotianae, suppresses host immunity by targeting papain-like cysteine proteases. Here, we report the high-resolution crystal structure of EPIC1, revealing a domain-swapped dimer architecture in which structural elements are exchanged between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of accuracy of three intraoral scanners for different types of tooth preparations: A laboratory study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To evaluate the laboratory accuracy of three intraoral scanners (IOSs) across three types of tooth preparations, using a laboratory scanner as the reference.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876021/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors for Typhoid Fever: Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This review identifies demographic and socioeconomic factors as key drivers of typhoid transmission, underscoring the need for targeted interventions. Strengthening street food regulation in urban Asia and investing in water infrastructure in rural Africa can significantly mitigate risk. Integrating water, sanitation, and hygiene interventions with typhoid vaccines can reduce immediate exposure while enhancing long-term immunity. Prioritizing these strategies in schools and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FRET Materials for Biosensing and Bioimaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Förster resonance energy transfer (FRET) spectroscopy and microscopy are constantly expanding sensing techniques for analyzing biomolecular interactions. In addition to the biological recognition molecules and biological or chemical analytes, the most important components for designing FRET biosensing systems are the materials that constitute the FRET donor-acceptor pair. These FRET materials consist of small molecules, biological or chemical nanoscaffolds, or nanomaterials that function in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Curtail North Korea's illegal wildlife trade]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Architecture of the UBR4 complex, a giant E4 ligase central to eukaryotic protein quality control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eukaryotic cells have evolved sophisticated quality control mechanisms to eliminate aggregation-prone proteins that compromise cellular health. Central to this defense is the ubiquitin-proteasome system, where UBR4 acts as an essential E4 ubiquitin ligase, amplifying degradation marks on defective proteins. Cryo-electron microscopy analysis of UBR4 in complex with its cofactors KCMF1 and CALM1 reveals a massive 1.3-megadalton ring structure, featuring a central substrate-binding arena and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knee arthroplasty can preserve cognitive function in patients with severe knee osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Knee arthroplasty can reduce the decline in cognitive function in patients with severe knee OA of K-L grade 4 who do not respond to conservative treatment. Even if pain is controlled with conservative treatment, the decline in cognitive function in patients with OA is faster than the age-related decline observed in the general population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The critical effects of self-management strategies on predicting cancer survivors' future quality of life and health status using machine learning techniques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the significance of enhancing the quality of life (QoL) and overall health status (including physical, mental, social, and spiritual well-being) among individuals who have survived cancer, the existing prediction model for QoL and health status lacks sufficient interpretation. Our primary objectives were to develop and validate simple prediction models for QoL and secondary health statuses. Additionally, we aimed to interpret these prediction models using explainable artificial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visualization of multidrug-resistant bacterial infection trends in the intensive care units]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Graph transformation allowed the observation of MDR Gram-negative bacterial infection trends in ICUs. Further studies should aim to confirm whether our arrow indicators are useful for infection control and in identifying factors for reducing infections.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the lung: Distinct recurrence patterns of mucinous and non-mucinous lung adenocarcinoma after surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Invasive mucinous adenocarcinoma group demonstrate better recurrence-free survival and a lower risk of extrapulmonary recurrence compared to non-mucinous group following surgical resection. These findings highlight the need for further research aimed at developing tailored surveillance and treatment strategies based on tumour histological characteristics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wedge resection versus segmentectomy in early-stage lung cancer considering resection margin and lymph node evaluation: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with clinical stage IA1-IA2 lung adenocarcinoma, RFS did not differ significantly between wedge resection and segmentectomy when a sufficient surgical margin and adequate LN evaluation were achieved.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Traumatic liver injury increases susceptibility to bacterial pneumonia in swine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We have developed a novel, clinically relevant, reproducible porcine model of abdominal injury with subsequent A. pleuropneumoniae pneumonia for the study and development of therapeutics against immune dysregulation induced by trauma. Additionally, a novel finding is that plasma from traumatized pigs provides a permissive environment for bacterial growth.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic application of canine adipose tissue-derived mesenchymal stromal cells in a dog with refractory immune-mediated thrombocytopenia, with diabetic ketoacidosis, and gastrointestinal bleeding induced by immunosuppressive treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Refractory immune-mediated thrombocytopenia (ITP) in dogs is a condition with a poor prognosis due to the poor response to immunosuppressive therapy and the adverse effects of long-term drug administration. This case report describes the successful management of refractory ITP using stem cell therapy in a dog that experienced severe side effects from immunosuppressive treatment. The patient experienced recurrent relapses when prednisolone (PDS) tapering was attempted during conventional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40875161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical Preservation of Pancreatic Ducts in Partial Pancreatectomy: A Case Report of Canine Insulinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report describes partial pancreatectomy in a dog with insulinoma, emphasizing the role of pancreatic ductal anatomy on surgical planning and postoperative management. A 13 yr old castrated male poodle was evaluated for a pancreatic mass with signs indicative of insulinoma. Imaging showed the mass occupying most of the right pancreatic limb, with its cranial margin just adjacent to the minor duodenal papilla. Although intraoperative visualization was limited by duodenal adhesions,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying potential miRNA-disease associations through an accurate matrix completion approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exploring latent microRNA (miRNA)-disease associations (MDAs) is vital for early screening and treatment. Compared with traditional experiments, computational methods enhance efficiency and lower costs in predicting MDAs. We trained the Accurate Matrix Completion for predicting potential MiRNA-Disease Associations (AMCMDA) model in this work, utilizing truncated nuclear norm minimization to improve the prediction accuracy. In AMCMDA, we begin by constructing a heterogeneous network incorporating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the economically justifiable price of nirsevimab to prevent respiratory syncytial virus infection in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The current standard-of-care prophylaxis for respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) is primarily administered to high-risk infant populations. We conducted a cost-effectiveness analysis to determine the economically justifiable price of nirsevimab compared with the standard of care in preventing medically attended RSV-associated lower respiratory tract infections from all infants and palivizumab-eligible children <2 years in South Korea. A month-age-specific static decision-tree model was used from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Significance of Inflammation Marker of Radionecrosis in Laryngopharynx Cancer Treated With Radiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with an advanced tumor status and elevated mid-radiation NLR should be closely monitored for radionecrosis. This suggests that early intervention with HBO therapy may enhance the rate of organ preservation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between weekend catch-up sleep and health-related quality of life using a generalized additive model and sex and chronotype sub-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tailored sleep interventions based on individual characteristics and specific WCUS durations may serve as an effective strategy to improve HRQoL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing the validity of social measures on human rights awareness: a dual-method approach integrating exploratory factor analysis and latent profile analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Licensed caregivers (LCs) are crucial in Korea's long-term care systems, ensuring the well-being of older adults. This study examines the human rights awareness of 1,050 LCs against a backdrop of increasing elder abuse in residential facilities. The study employed Exploratory Factor Analysis (EFA) and Latent Profile Analysis (LPA) to assess multi-dimensional human rights awareness - spanning self-determination, anti-discrimination, individualized care, anti-abuse, and advocacy. We identified...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current status and future perspectives of minimally invasive liver surgery for hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of laparoscopic liver resection has rapidly increased. According to two international consensus meetings, certain resection methods are already considered standard procedures for liver resection, especially for small malignant tumors located on the liver surface or in the anterolateral segments of the liver. However, further studies and international consensus meetings are required for laparoscopic procedures to be accepted as standard procedures for highly complex hepatectomies, major...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between Possible Sarcopenia and Fall Risk, Depression, and Quality of Life in Middle-Aged and Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to identify the associations between possible sarcopenia (p-sarcopenia) and fall risk, depression, and quality of life (QOL) in middle-aged (age ≥ 45 years) and older (age ≥ 65 years) adults. In this study, we analyzed a total of 10,181 men and women aged 45-85 years from the initial survey sample of the 2006 Korean Longitudinal Study of Aging. Among middle-aged men (women) adults, fall risk and depression were 4.09 (1.34) and 2.25 (2.05) times higher in the p-sarcopenia group...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Ultrasonographic and computed tomographic features of presumed gastric plasmacytoma (plasma cell tumor) with ulceration in two dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric plasmacytoma is rare in dogs, with only four previous reports providing limited descriptions of abdominal ultrasound (AUS) and computed tomography (CT) findings. This study presents the AUS and CT imaging features of two histopathologically suspected gastric plasmacytomas. Combining the four previous and two new cases, these tumors predominantly occurred in the greater curvature and pyloric antrum as solitary round masses connected to the submucosal or transmural layers. Pre- and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical evaluation of a novel fixed-dose combination tablet (Sentorphil<sup>®</sup> ForteGold) versus compounded powdered medications in dogs with myxomatous mitral valve disease: a randomized, double-blind study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Myxomatous mitral valve disease (MMVD) is a prevalent cardiac condition in older, small-breed dogs, often managed with multiple medications. Traditional administration involves compounded powdered mixtures, which may lead to dosing inaccuracies and reduced compliance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarkers of type 2 inflammation as predictors of response to biologics for severe eosinophilic asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with SEA treated with anti-IL-4Rα antibodies, pre-treatment F (ENO) may be a good predictor for certain treatment response domains.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874166/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatable traits in chronic cough: a prospective evaluation for predicting cough persistence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that cough hypersensitivity symptoms are associated with long-term outcomes of chronic cough. Further studies are needed to validate the role of treatable traits in chronic cough management and to better understand factors associated with cough persistence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Visible light-driven photocatalytic degradation of rhodamine B and 5-fluorouracil using ZIF-8/GO: unveiling mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The removal of pharmaceutical and organic contaminants from wastewater remains a pressing challenge for conventional treatment technologies. In this study, a novel photocatalyst composed of Zeolitic Imidazolate Framework-8 (ZIF-8) nanocrystals integrated with a graphene oxide (GO) matrix was developed via a facile interfacial synthesis approach. The structural and morphological properties of the resulting ZIF-8/GO composite were characterized using X-ray diffraction, X-ray photoelectron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commonly observed sex differences in direct aggression are absent or reversed in sibling contexts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decades of research support the generalization that human males tend to be more aggressive than females. However, most of that research has examined aggression between unrelated individuals. Data drawn from 24 societies around the globe (n = 4,013) indicate that this generalization does not hold in the context of sibling relationships. In retrospective self-reports, females report being at least as aggressive as males toward their siblings, often more so. This holds for direct as well as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth performance of broiler chickens fed diets containing granulated L-methionine compared with DL-methionine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel granulated L-methionine (Met) has been developed using a simplified purification process, however its replacement with DL-Met has not yet been explored. The objective of the present study was to investigate the growth performance of broilers fed diets containing granulated L-Met (90% purity) compared to a diet containing DL-Met (99% purity). A total of 192 one-day-old broilers were allocated in four dietary treatments with six replicates (eight birds/cage) in a randomized complete block...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feeding of reduced vitamin premix negatively affects laying performance and vitamin contents in chicken eggs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study was conducted to investigate effects of diets with varying levels of vitamin premix on egg production, eggshell quality, and vitamin contents in eggs of commercial laying hens. A total of 144 Hy-line Brown layers at 45 weeks old were randomly divided into four groups (six replicates, 6 birds for each group) and fed diets containing different levels of vitamin premix for eight weeks. Laying hens in the control group received diet containing 100% vitamin premix (0.1% in experimental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bovine colostrum-derived exosomes alleviate muscle degeneration by modulating gut microbiota and metabolic homeostasis in atrophy models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia, a condition characterized by chronic systemic inflammation and a significant decline in the quality of life, is primarily associated with aging and degenerative diseases. Several studies have shown that milk exosomes contain a substantial number of miRNAs that are involved in immunity, inflammation, osteoporosis, and gut microbiota regulation. This study aimed to evaluate the potential functional role of bovine colostrum-derived exosomes (BCE) in reducing muscle atrophy. BCE...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antimicrobial activity of <em>Pediococcus pentosaceus</em> strains against diarrheal pathogens isolated from pigs and effect on paracellular permeability of HT-29 cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate lactic acid bacteria with antimicrobial activities against infectious diarrheal pathogens in pigs and their genetic characteristics. Acid-resistant lactic acid bacteria were examined for bile resistance, pancreatic enzyme resistance, gelatinase and urease activities, and antibiotic resistance. Subsequently, selected isolates were examined for antimicrobial activities against Campylobacter coli, Clostridium perfringens, Escherichia coli, and Salmonella Typhimurium,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete genome sequence of <em>Lactiplantibacillus plantarum</em> strain GA_C_14 with potential characteristics applicable in the swine industry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, the complete genome of Lactiplantibacillus plantarum strain GA_C_14 was sequenced and analyzed. We isolated the L. plantarum strain GA_C_14 from gajami sikhae, the Korean traditional food purchased from a local market in Gangneung, Korea. The genome of the L. plantarum strain GA_C_14 consisted of one circular chromosome (3,196,348bp) with a guanine + cytosine (GC) content of 44.7% and one circular plasmid (40,211bp) with a GC content of 38.9%. The genome annotation revealed 3,083...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of polyphosphates with different chain lengths on digestive organ weight, carcass quality, and immune response, and intestinal microflora in broilers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physiological effects of polyphosphates with different chain lengths were unknown in poultry. The effect of 0.05% concentration of short chain polyphosphates (SCPP), medium chain polyphosphates (MCPP) and long chain polyphosphates (LCPP) was observed in broilers. MCPP and LCPP produced bacteriostatic properties against four pathogenic bacteria, Shigella sonnei, Pseudomonas aeruginosa, Salmonella enterica serovar. Pullorum, and Escherichia coli O157:H7. SCPP reduced the level of triglycerides in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local gyrification index and sulcal depth as imaging markers of cognitive decline in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results indicate that certain changes in cortical shape features are associated with particular cognitive function scores. Surface-based morphometric features of SD and LGI provided complementary results to CT analyses. Region-specific changes in SD and LGI could be useful imaging markers to predict cognitive decline in AD patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pigment epithelium detachment with thickened choroid in a preterm infant at term-equivalent age: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pigment epithelial detachment (PED) is well-documented in adult retinal diseases but is rarely reported in neonates. This case describes a preterm infant, born at 31 weeks, who developed PED with thickened choroid at term-equivalent age, detected using handheld OCT. The PED emerged at 39 weeks postmenstrual age, coinciding with inhaled steroid treatment for respiratory distress, and resolved by 41 weeks after steroid discontinuation without structural damage. The temporal relationship suggests...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of extracellular vesicles carrying bacterial DNA in urine and serum from a Korean population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Bacteria-derived extracellular vesicles (BEVs) are emerging as key biomarkers of host-microbiota interactions. However, little is known about how BEV profiles differ across different biofluids or how these differences relate to clinical phenotypes. We aimed to examine the BEV distribution and site-specific and shared associations with host phenotypes, and evaluated the clinical relevance of microbial distance between sampling sites.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancements in Understanding Catalyst Reconstruction During Electrochemical CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical CO(2) reduction reaction (CO(2)RR) has received great attention to solve CO(2)- induced global warming and carbon neutrality. It is essential to enhance the electrochemical CO(2)RR selectivity, activity, and long-term stability for sustainable manufacturing of specific chemicals via CO(2)RR. To produce multi-carbon (C(2+)) chemicals, Cu-based heterogeneous catalysts have been developed in terms of defect engineering, morphological design, and facet control. Despite the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[15-Deoxy-Δ<sup>12,14</sup>-prostaglandin J2 induces apoptosis in human microvascular endothelial cells (HMEC-1)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[15-Deoxy-Δ^(12,14)-prostaglandin J2 (15d-PGJ2) plays an important role in cell proliferation and apoptosis with various inhibitory effects. We investigated whether 15d-PGJ2 influence proliferation and apoptosis of human microvascular endothelial cells (HMEC-1), and suppression of the nuclear factor (NF)-κB activity and PI3K/AKT/mTOR signal pathway. Cell proliferation was analyzed using the MTS/PMS and colony formation assays. We analyzed the cell cycle using flow cytometry, while quantitative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exposure and health effects follow-up study of residents near a former smelter site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Seo-Cheon Janghang Smelter in South Korea closed in 1989 owing to its contribution to environmental pollution. The emissions from the smelter likely affect various environmental media and also pose significant health risks to nearby residents, particularly in relation to exposure to heavy metals such as lead, cadmium, and arsenic. Although the environmental impacts of the smelter are known, long-term follow-up studies on heavy metal exposure in nearby residents remain limited, especially...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pupillary responses to masked and gaze-averted faces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Face masks, a common practice during COVID-19, remain important in various cultural and medical contexts. Studies have shown how face masks affect our ability to recognize emotions, highlighting the role of facial features. Gaze direction plays a key role in modulating the identification of emotions, particularly in the presence of masks. So far, little is known about how gaze and masks influence emotion processing via physiological measures like pupil size. Here, we used pupillometry with 40...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Analysis of Chest Radiographs for Predicting Major Adverse Events in Patients Visiting the Emergency Department With Acute Cardiopulmonary Symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI analysis of CXRs showed greater accuracy than the KTAS did in predicting major adverse cardiopulmonary events in patients visiting the ED with acute cardiopulmonary symptoms. AI analysis may enhance the efficacy of patient triage in the ED.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Deep-Learning Model for Estimating Newborn Gestational Age via Lumbar Vertebral Segmentation on Plain Radiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our deep learning model showed promising performance in lumbar vertebral body segmentation and GA estimation using plain radiographs, suggesting its potential utility as a supportive tool for neonatal maturity assessment in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accuracy of Large Language Models in Detecting Cases Requiring Immediate Reporting in Pediatric Radiology: A Feasibility Study Using Publicly Available Clinical Vignettes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multimodal LLMs may achieve overall accuracy comparable to or exceeding that of human readers in identifying cases requiring immediate radiology reporting, supporting their potential use for pediatric radiology worklist prioritization. However, the models' sensitivity in detecting such cases was not reliable.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiparametric MRI Features of Plasmacytoid Urothelial Carcinoma of the Urinary Bladder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PUC demonstrates notable mpMRI features, including localized or diffuse wall thickening (often with a linitis plastica-like appearance), muscle-invasive and advanced disease, progressive and prolonged enhancement patterns, and mild hyperintensity or isointensity on high b-value DWI. These features, which are potentially linked to the myxoid stromal composition of the tumor, suggest that mpMRI may serve as a noninvasive diagnostic tool for this aggressive malignancy. However, further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large Language Models for CAD-RADS 2.0 Extraction From Semi-Structured Coronary CT Angiography Reports: A Multi-Institutional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: LLMs demonstrated high accuracy in automated extraction of CAD-RADS 2.0 components from semi-structured CCTA reports, particularly when used with CoT prompting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Academic Journal Podcast and Generative Artificial Intelligence: Introducing KJR SummaryCast]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When Leader's Forgiveness Backfires: Consequences on Trust and a Potential Mitigation Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[When leaders forgive, does it influence follower trust? This study examines whether forgiveness creates an integrity-benevolence dilemma for leaders, potentially reducing follower trust. Across three studies (N = 1,235), findings reveal that forgiveness has a dual impact: it decreases integrity-based trust while enhancing benevolence-based trust. These findings were consistent across studies with controlled scenarios depicting typical organizational misconduct and a behavioral experiment with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent-onset atrial fibrillation: challenges and opportunities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atrial fibrillation (AF) is increasingly diagnosed early, close to its first occurrence due to: (i) increased public awareness with self-screening; (ii) health care initiatives including population screening and opportunistic case finding; and (iii) increased use and surveillance of implantable cardiac devices. At its onset, AF is often low burden, and cardiovascular co-morbidities may be absent or at an early stage. Thus, the management of recent-onset AF has become an issue of growing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated with the Utilization of Out-of-Region Medical Institutions for Brain Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings provide valuable insights into among-group differences in the utilization of medical institutions. Identifying factors that may influence regional concentration in these medical utilization behaviors can provide clues to identifying and improving problems in the allocation of medical resources.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trajectories of Alzheimer's Disease Prevalence among National Health Insurance and Medical Aid Beneficiaries from 2010 to 2019]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this study, we identified significant differences in AD prevalence between NHI and MA recipients, with a notable increase in the MA group, especially among those under 60 years of age.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors for Heterotopic Ossification in Traumatic Brain Injury: An Analysis of the Korean National Health Insurance Service Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In conclusion, middle-age range, female sex, obesity, comorbidities, injury severity, systemic inflammation, and bony metabolism-affecting medications appear to increase the risk of HO in patients with TBI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Transplant Surgeon-Innovated Ex Vivo Machine Perfusion: Validation in a Porcine Donation after Circulatory Death-Simulated Liver Transplant Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study successfully demonstrated the stability of the transplant surgeon-innovated normothermic EVMP protocol, validating its efficacy in improving organ preservation and reducing IRI in a porcine DCD sLT model.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between Benzodiazepine and Dementia Risk in Treating Depression after Breast Cancer Diagnosis: A Nationwide Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study underscores the importance of cautious benzodiazepine use in breast cancer patients diagnosed with depression, given its potential to significantly increase dementia risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Child Abuse Cases Referred to a Hospital-Based Child Protection Teams in Korea and the Role of Psychiatric Intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CPTs have enhanced the reporting and management of child abuse cases in Korean hospitals. Psychiatric intervention within CPT plays a crucial role for subsequent psychiatric outpatient visits. Since the infant and toddler group is more vulnerable to severe injuries, psychiatric intervention within the CPT should be conducted for all age groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Implication of LDL-C Variability and Its Association with Lipid-Lowering Strategies: Insights from the RACING and LODESTAR Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared to high-intensity statin therapy, LDL-C variability was not increased with the moderate-intensity statin plus ezetimibe combination therapy; however, it was increased in the treat-to-target strategy. Even among those treated with moderate- or high-intensity statins or statins with a target LDL-C levels of 50-70 mg/dL, increased LDL-C variability was associated with higher risk of adverse cardiovascular outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Left Atrial Appendage Characteristics Assessed with Cardiac Computed Tomography in Patients with Atrial Fibrillation and Severe Mitral Valve Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Due to advanced LAA remodeling in AF patients with severe MV disease, the morphologic distribution of LAA types differs from that established in patients without MV disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-degron-mediated ATG8 isoform switching controls plant thermotolerance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macroautophagy/autophagy is a highly conserved catabolic pathway in eukaryotes that mediates the selective degradation and recycling of cellular components through the formation of double-membrane autophagosomes. ATG8 is a core component of autophagy and determines cargo selectivity through interactions with specific cargo receptors. Higher plants harbor multiple ATG8 isoforms, implying potential functional diversification; however, the biological significance of this isoform expansion remains...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Heterologous Vaccination Using Virus-Like Particles and Vaccinia Virus Containing MIC8 and AMA1 Proteins of <em>Toxoplasma gondii</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background:Toxoplasma gondii (T. gondii) infection causes serious diseases in immunocompromised patients and causes congenital toxoplasmosis in infants. T. gondii microneme protein 8 (MIC8) and apical membrane antigen 1 (AMA1) are essential proteins involved in parasitic invasion. Methods: In this study, we generated virus-like particles (VLPs) and recombinant vaccinia virus (rVV) containing MIC8 or AMA1 proteins. Vaccine efficacy was evaluated in mice (BALB/c) upon challenge infection with T....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872947/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protective Efficacy Induced by Virus-like Particles Expressing Dense Granule Protein 5 of <em>Toxoplasma gondii</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background:Toxoplasma gondii (T. gondii) causes severe disease in immunocompromised individuals and pregnant women, underscoring the urgent need for effective vaccines against toxoplasmosis. The dense granule protein 5 (GRA5) of T. gondii plays a key role in parasitic cyst formation. Methods: This study evaluated the protective immune responses induced by a virus-like particle (VLP) vaccine expressing the T. gondii-derived antigen GRA5 in a mouse model challenged with the ME49 strain of T....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Year-Long Antibody Response to the EuCorVac-19 SARS-CoV-2 Vaccine in Healthy Filipinos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: We previously reported an interim safety and immunogenicity analysis of a Phase 3 trial in the Philippines of the EuCorVac-19 (ECV-19) COVID-19 vaccine with the COVISHIELD^(TM) (CS) comparator (ClinicalTrials.gov identifier NCT05572879). Here, we present full-year humoral immunogenicity analysis. Methods: Healthy adults over 18 years of age received two injections of ECV-19 or CS vaccines, with 4 weeks between prime and boost. Analysis was carried out in individuals with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Guinea Pig X Virus Is a Gammaherpesvirus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Guinea Pig X Virus (GPXV), a newly identified gammaherpesvirus, provides an opportunity to study viral evolution and host-virus dynamics. This study characterizes the GPXV genome and investigates its phylogenetic relationships and divergence from related viruses through comparative genomic and phylogenetic analyses. Virus propagation was conducted in Vero cells, followed by genomic DNA extraction and pan-herpesvirus nested PCR. Sanger sequencing filled gaps in the initial genome assembly,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacologic Potential of Statins in Cancer Prevention: Colo-Rectal Cancer Risk in Dyslipidemic Patients from a Korean Nationwide Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Colorectal cancer (CRC) is a growing public health concern in South Korea, with incidence rising alongside dyslipidemia. Statins, widely prescribed for lipid control, have been proposed to reduce CRC risk, but evidence remains inconsistent, particularly in Asian populations. Methods: Using Korean National Health Insurance Service data (2002-2019), we conducted a nested case-control study of 9920 CRC patients and 39,680 matched controls. To reduce confounding, we applied a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing the Hepatoprotective and Nephroprotective Potential of <em>Nigella sativa</em> Fractions via per os Administration in CCl<sub>4</sub>-Intoxicated Wistar Rats: A Mixed Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background:Nigella sativa, known as black cumin, is traditionally used to treat various illnesses. Objective: The current study aims to investigate the potential hepatoprotective and nephroprotective effect of black cumin fractions via per os route in CCl(4)-intoxicated Wistar rats. This study used a computational approach to assess the interaction of bioactive compounds with key proteins (CYP P450 3E1, TNF-α, and Cox-2). Methods:Wistar rats were treated with CCl(4) to induce liver injury and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunoenhancing Effects of Jeju <em>Agastache rugosa</em> Extracts on NK Cell Activity and Lymphocyte Proliferation in Cyclophosphamide-Induced Immunosuppression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/objectives: This study evaluated the immunoenhancing effects of Agastache rugosa extract in a cyclophosphamide-induced immunosuppressed mouse model. Methods: Jeju A. rugosa was processed via hot water extraction and 20% ethanol extraction. For immunosuppression induction, 7-week-old male BALB/c mice received intraperitoneal CPA injections (150 mg/kg, day -3; 110 mg/kg, day -1), followed by oral administration of hot water extract (ARE-W) and ethanol extract (ARE-E) at 100 and 300...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative In Silico and In Vivo Analysis of Banhasasim-Tang for Irritable Bowel Syndrome: Mechanistic Insights into Inflammation-Related Pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Banhasasim-tang (BHSST) is a traditional herbal formula commonly used to treat gastrointestinal (GI) disorders and has been considered a potential therapeutic option for irritable bowel syndrome (IBS). This study aimed to explore the molecular targets and underlying mechanisms of BHSST in IBS using a combination of network pharmacology, molecular docking, molecular dynamics simulations, and in vivo validation. Methods: Active compounds in BHSST were screened based on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laser-Based Selective Removal of EMI Shielding Layers in System-in-Package (SiP) Modules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the increasing complexity and integration density of System-in-Package (SiP) technologies, the demand for selective electromagnetic interference (EMI) shielding is growing. Conventional sputtering processes, while effective for conformal EMI shielding, lack selectivity and often require additional masking or post-processing steps. In this study, we propose a novel, laser-based approach for the selective removal of EMI shielding layers without physical masking. Numerical simulations were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graphene-Based Gas Sensors: State-of-the-Art Developments for Gas Sensing Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gas sensors based on graphene have gained considerable attention because of graphene's remarkable properties, such as its extensive surface area, impressive electrical conductivity, and exceptional mechanical strength. This review critically analyzes recent developments in functionalization strategies designed to enhance the sensitivity, selectivity, and stability of graphene-based sensors. It discusses various chemical, physical, and hybrid functionalization methods, illustrating how surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanostructure Engineering by Oblique Angle Deposition for Photodetectors and Other Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oblique angle deposition (OAD) holds significant potential for diverse applications, including energy harvesting devices, optoelectronic sensors, and electronic devices, owing to the creation of unique nanostructures. These nanostructures are characterized by their porosity and nanoscale columns, which can exist in numerous forms depending on deposition conditions. As a result, the engineering of nanostructures using OAD achieves the successful modulation of optical properties such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Wideband Magneto-Electric (ME) Dipole Antenna Enabled by ME Resonance and Aperture-Coupled Excitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel wideband aperture-coupled magneto-electric (ME) dipole antenna that achieves enhanced bandwidth by simultaneously leveraging ME resonance and aperture-coupled excitation. Building upon the conventional ME dipole architecture, the antenna integrates a pair of horizontal metal patches forming the electric dipole and a pair of vertical metal patches forming the magnetic dipole. A key innovation is the aperture-coupled feeding mechanism, where electromagnetic energy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vitro Propagation of Variegated <em>Cymbidium lancifolium</em> Hooker]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variegated Cymbidium lancifolium is a highly valued ornamental plant sought after in local and international markets. The commercial production of variegated C. lancifolium through traditional propagation methods faces significant challenges, such as low propagation rates and prolonged growth periods. This study aims to develop effective in vitro propagation techniques for variegated C. lancifolium through asymbiotic seed germination to enhance production efficiency and meet market demand. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive Image Deblurring Convolutional Neural Network with Meta-Tuning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Motion blur is a complex phenomenon caused by the relative movement between an observed object and an imaging sensor during the exposure time, resulting in degradation in the image quality. Deep-learning-based methods, particularly convolutional neural networks (CNNs), have shown promise in motion deblurring. However, the small kernel sizes of CNNs limit their ability to achieve optimal performance. Moreover, supervised deep-learning-based deblurring methods often exhibit overfitting in their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Spatiotemporal Seismic Fragility Assessment of Structures Based on Site-Specific Seismic Response and Sensor-Integrated Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Earthquake hazards, such as strong ground motion, liquefaction, and landslides, pose significant threats to structures built on seismically vulnerable, loose, and saturated sandy soils. Therefore, a structural failure evaluation method that accounts for site-specific seismic responses is essential for developing effective and appropriate earthquake hazard mitigation strategies. In this study, a real-time assessment framework for structural seismic susceptibility is developed. To evaluate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an Interactive Digital Human with Context-Sensitive Facial Expressions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the increasing complexity of human-computer interaction scenarios, conventional digital human facial expression systems show notable limitations in handling multi-emotion co-occurrence, dynamic expression, and semantic responsiveness. This paper proposes a digital human system framework that integrates multimodal emotion recognition and compound facial expression generation. The system establishes a complete pipeline for real-time interaction and compound emotional expression, following a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capillary Flow Profile Analysis on Paper-Based Microfluidic Chips for Classifying Astringency Intensity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Astringency, a complex oral sensation resulting from interactions between mucin and polyphenols, remains difficult to quantify in portable field settings. Therefore, quantifying the aggregation through interactions can enable the classification of the astringency intensity, and assessing the capillary action driven by the surface tension offers an effective approach for this purpose. This study successfully replicates tannic acid (TA)-mucin aggregation on a paper-based microfluidic chip and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871931/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Micro Orthogonal Fluxgate Sensor Fabricated with Amorphous CoZrNb Film]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We successfully fabricated micro orthogonal fluxgate sensors using amorphous CoZrNb films. The sensor, measuring 1.5 mm × 0.5 mm, consists of three main parts: the conductor for excitation current flow, the magnetic layer sensitive to an external magnetic field, and the detection coil for measuring output voltage dependent on an external magnetic field. The magnetic layer forms a magnetically closed-circuit in the cross-section, which reduces reluctance and power consumption. Key fabrication...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Serum High Sensitivity C-Reactive Protein Levels and Low Muscle Strength Among Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher hsCRP levels were independently associated with low muscle strength in middle-aged women and older adults. Downregulating inflammation through nutritional strategies could help prevent muscle decline with aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemical Profiling and UPLC-qTOF-MS/MS-Based Metabolomics of Three Different Parts of <em>Edgeworthia chrysantha</em> and Identification of Glucose Uptake-Enhancing Compounds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings provide a comprehensive chemical and metabolomic characterization of E. chrysantha and highlight its potential as a functional food ingredient for glucose-lowering effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250829034124&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Semiconducting Nanomaterials for Intrinsically Stretchable Field-Effect Transistors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing intrinsically stretchable field-effect transistors (FETs) is critical for enabling next-generation flexible, wearable, and bio-integrated electronic systems. Unlike conventional stretchable devices that rely primarily on geometric engineering of rigid materials, intrinsically stretchable FETs involve materials that inherently withstand large mechanical deformation while preserving their electronic performance. Although significant progress is achieved in the field of stretchable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a capacitance measurement for pulsed magnetic fields]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capacitance measurements are crucial for probing the electrical properties of materials. In this study, we develop and implement a capacitance measurement technique optimized for pulsed magnetic fields. Our approach employs an auto-balancing bridge method, leveraging a high-bandwidth transimpedance amplifier to mitigate parasitic contributions from coaxial cables. This technique enables precise capacitance measurements in rapidly changing magnetic fields, as demonstrated in experiments on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A monotone single index model for spatially referenced multistate current status data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Assessment of multistate disease progression is commonplace in biomedical research, such as in periodontal disease (PD). However, the presence of multistate current status endpoints, where only a single snapshot of each subject's progression through disease states is available at a random inspection time after a known starting state, complicates the inferential framework. In addition, these endpoints can be clustered, and spatially associated, where a group of proximally located teeth (within...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40874356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Thermal Interface Materials: Insights into Low-Temperature Sintering and High Thermal Conductivity of MgO]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The escalating frequency of electric vehicle (EV) fires has underscored the critical importance of effective thermal-management in battery package (TMBP). A key challenge in current TMBP lies with the low thermal conductivity (TC, 3 W m^(-1) K^(-1)) of commercial alumina-polymer composite (thermal interface materials, TIM). While magnesia (MgO) TIMs, which show high TC (8-10 W m^(-1) K^(-1), this study) and low cost, are emerging as an alternative heat-dissipation material (HDM), their full...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40873067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Symmetry-Forbidden Rectification via Dynamic Phase Transitions in the Weyl Metallic State of ZrTe<sub>5</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Weyl metals, known for their topological structure and chiral anomaly, exhibit nonlinear transport that defies conventional theory. In this study, ZrTe(5), an inversion-symmetric Dirac semimetal tunable to a Weyl state by magnetic field, is investigated, and rectification (alternating current (AC) to direct current (DC) conversion) and third harmonic generation in longitudinal configurations is revealed. Despite its bulk inversion symmetry, symmetry-forbidden rectification and a dynamic phase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40872996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Next-Generation Wound Healing Materials: Role of Biopolymers and Their Composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The progress in biopolymers and their composites as advanced materials for wound healing has revolutionized therapeutic approaches for skin regeneration. These materials can effectively integrate their inherent biocompatibility and biodegradability with the enhanced mechanical strength and customizable properties of polymers and functional additives. This review presents a detailed investigation of the design principles, classifications, and biomedical applications of biopolymeric composites,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40871190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Histopathological characterisation of omphalitis in piglets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Omphalitis in piglets was characterized by inflammation and presence of bacteria in the umbilical arteries and to a lesser extent the umbilical vein. Inflammation in urachus was not present.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunophenotyping and Mutation Analysis of Canine Intestinal T-Cell Lymphoma: A Comparative Pathological Study of Human Enteropathy-Associated T-Cell Lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human enteropathy-associated T-cell lymphoma (EATL) is a rare primary aggressive intestinal T-cell lymphoma associated with celiac disease and is considered to be a neoplasm of intraepithelial lymphocytes (IELs) with an innate lymphoid cell (ILC)-like immunophenotype. The lack of an animal model has delayed the elucidation of its pathogenesis. In dogs, the histopathological and immunophenotypic features of intestinal large T-cell lymphoma (ILTCL) are similar to EATL; however, its cell of origin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward equitable parenting in surgery: a response to commentary on the "Daddy Surgeon" case study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pancreatic head clockwise devascularization technique during robotic pancreaticoduodenectomy to minimize intraoperative bleeding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The pancreatic head clockwise devascularization technique may be an effective technique to systematically devascularize the pancreatic head.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877624/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical evaluation of the perinephric vein as a surgical landmark in minimally invasive distal pancreatectomy for pancreatic cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Perinephric vein was identified as a novel landmark vein in more than half of patients who underwent MIDP. This vein can facilitate safe access to the left renal vein and ensure adequate posterior surgical margin, contributing to improve surgical precision.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary cilium disappearance in podocytes during vertebrate phylogeny revealed by array tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Podocytes are a type of epithelial cells that form the kidney nephron and are essential for ultrafiltration in the glomerulus. The majority of nephron constituent cells have primary cilia, which play an important role in the maintenance of normal tubular architecture of nephron. However, whether podocytes have primary cilia was only partially understood. In general, immunohistochemistry with an anti-acetylated α-tubulin antibody is often used to visualize primary cilia. α-Tubulin is highly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevention of catheter-related bladder discomfort and agitation by intravesical lidocaine administration during awake craniotomy: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A longitudinal study examining determinants of essential health services during the COVID-19 pandemic in regional referral hospitals across Uganda]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic disrupted essential health services worldwide. In sub-Saharan Africa, lockdowns initially controlled virus transmission but later negatively affected non-COVID-19 healthcare. In Uganda, government policies evolved from strict movement restrictions to moderate restrictions with consideration for socioeconomic activities. This study assessed the impact of COVID-19 measures on hospital access in Uganda. We performed a longitudinal observational study using monthly outpatient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Horse model of spontaneous atrial fibrillation share proteomic changes with humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Horses and humans are among the few mammals susceptible to spontaneous atrial fibrillation (AF), both suffering from high recurrence rates after treatment. Treatment resistance is often attributed to progressive atrial remodeling, but current treatment options fail to effectively address this aspect. Here, we introduce a novel horse model of spontaneous AF to investigate the biological pathway changes in early stages of the disease. Through data-independent acquisition mass spectrometry on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regulation of divergent epithelial-to-mesenchymal transition responses via the CDK4/6-USP51 pathway through ZEB1 protein stabilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epithelial-to-mesenchymal transition (EMT) is a cellular process important for numerous developmental processes, wound healing and cancer progression. In the context of heterogenous nature of cancer, EMT occurs at the forefront of tumor invasion, although the precise molecular mechanisms governing its spatial dynamics remain unclear. This study aimed to explore the diverse responses to EMT in monolayer cell cultures of MCF10A epithelial cell with induction of Zinc-finger E-box binding homeobox 1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic origins of temperature scaling in the early embryonic cell cycle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Temperature strongly influences physiological and ecological processes, particularly in ectotherms. While complex physiological rates often follow Arrhenius-like scaling, originally formulated for single reactions, the underlying reasons remain unclear. Here, we examine temperature scaling of the early embryonic cell cycle across six ectothermic species, including Xenopus, Danio rerio, Caenorhabditis, and Drosophila. We find remarkably consistent apparent activation energies (75 ± 7 kJ/mol),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chelation-based iron uptake mitigates the effects of prolonged high-temperature stress in cool-season grasses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-temperature stress poses a significant threat to agricultural productivity and ecological diversity. Here, we show the effects of prolonged high-temperature stress on wheat (Triticum aestivum) and the model grass Brachypodium distachyon and demonstrate that heat stress induces iron deficiency in newly emerged leaves. Quantitative trait locus analysis of B. distachyon reveals a genomic region associated with heat resilience that includes the transporter of mugineic acid family...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gram-scale selective telomerization of isoprene and CO<sub>2</sub> toward 100% renewable materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon dioxide (CO(2)) is an ideal chemical feedstock due to its abundance, low cost, low toxicity and its role as a greenhouse gas. Telomerization with butadiene give rise to functional small molecules and polymers with significant CO(2) content, but the fossil origin of the olefin offsets sustainability benefits. Here, we present a palladium-catalyzed telomerization of CO(2) with isoprene, two of the most prevalent organic compounds in the atmosphere, yielding "COOIL", an ideally 100%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40877237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcome of a FODMAP restriction diet with subsequent blinded reintroduction in functional dyspepsia/postprandial distress syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A LFD significantly improved PDS symptoms, but this was not associated with altered mucosal integrity. Powder reintroduction identified a large variety in individual FODMAPs and glucose as triggers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental illness knowledge and the intention to seek psychiatric treatment among college athletes: use of a two-axis matrix to assess a new method of mental health support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Mental illness knowledge does not necessarily lead to the intention to seek psychiatric treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of musculoskeletal conditions with remotely delivered physiotherapy versus face-to-face physiotherapy: process evaluation of the REFORM trial using the Realist Evaluation and the RE-AIM Framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Remotely delivered physiotherapy has the potential to be rolled out across Australian clinical settings to participants similar to the REFORM trial. However, further research involving participants with different types and severity of musculoskeletal conditions is needed to improve the generalisability of our findings. Adoption might be improved with a hybrid model of care where physiotherapists' and patients' preferences are met.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vivo and in vitro evaluation of the protective effects of osthole against ototoxicity using the zebrafish model and HEI-OC1 cell line]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osthole, a coumarin derivative with potent antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties, has demonstrated promising therapeutic potential in protecting against ototoxicity. This study investigated the protective effects of osthole through both in vitro and in vivo experimental models. A high-content screening of 1,505 natural compounds in HEI-OC1 cells identified osthole as the most effective compound in alleviating gentamicin-induced cellular damage. Our results indicate that osthole confers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating biosolutions for sustainable food systems: A review of safety, quality, regulatory and sustainability considerations within the European Union]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biosolutions, such as food cultures and fermentates, are emerging alternatives to classical food preservation methods, offering multiple benefits, including food quality and safety enhancement, and waste reduction, with limited sensory and nutritional modification of the product and higher consumer acceptance. This study explores the potential of biosolutions to address critical challenges in sustainable food systems through their application in food production. Evaluation criteria of focus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated with Respiratory Syncytial Virus-Neutralizing Antibody Titers in Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RSV-neutralizing antibody titers showed age-dependent variation, with notably lower levels among individuals in their 30s. Higher titers were associated with chronic conditions and living with younger children, highlighting the role of exposure history in shaping immunity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consistency in treatment effects and statistical significance between early-stage pregnancy endpoints and live birth in randomized controlled trials of infertility: a systematic meta-epidemiological study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION(S): A strong correlation was observed between clinical or ongoing pregnancy and live birth, supporting the rationale for using clinical or ongoing pregnancy data to assess treatment effectiveness when live birth data are limited or unavailable. However, the risk of intervention-related pregnancy loss must be considered during the assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic characterization and serotype distribution of dengue virus circulating in Pakistan during 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dengue virus (DENV) remains a significant public health concern in Pakistan, with recurrent outbreaks necessitating continuous genomic surveillance. The 2024 dengue outbreak prompted an investigation into circulating serotypes and genomic diversity. The National Institute of Health (NIH), Pakistan, received 524 NS-1 confirmed dengue samples across multiple districts in 2024. Serotyping via real-time PCR confirmed DENV-2 in 93 % (n = 361) and DENV-1 in 7 % (n = 27) of 388 positive samples, with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between serotonin and vascular dysfunction and the impact of 5-HT<sub>2A</sub> receptor blockade by sarpogrelate on vascular function in diabetes mellitus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetes mellitus affects the functions of large and small vessels, leading to complications broadly classified as macro-vascular complications, including peripheral arterial disease, heart disease, and stroke, and microvascular complications, including neuropathy, retinopathy, and nephropathy. Moreover, vascular dysfunction, including abnormal reactivity to endogenous substances, is often observed in patients with diabetes mellitus. Among various vasoactive substances, serotonin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intravitreal Aflibercept 8 mg in Neovascular Age-related Macular Degeneration: 96-Week Results from the Randomized Phase 3 PULSAR Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Aflibercept 8 mg delivered sustained disease control in patients with nAMD, maintaining improvements in visual and anatomic outcomes through Week 96 with extended dosing intervals and similar safety profile to aflibercept 2 mg.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cgm1 is a β-galactoside α-(1→4)-mannosyltransferase involved in the biosynthesis of capsular glucuronoxylomannogalactan in Cryptococcus neoformans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capsular polysaccharides are present in the outermost layer of the cell wall of Cryptococcus neoformans. The capsule consists of glucuronoxylomannan (GXM) and glucuronoxylomannogalactan (GXMGal), both of which are major virulence factors that enable immune evasion. This study aimed to identify a novel glycosyltransferase involved in the biosynthesis of capsular polysaccharides in C. neoformans. While GXM is the predominant capsule component and plays a broad role in immune evasion, GXMGal,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of losing control over threat on the acquisition, extinction, and renewal of conditioned fear]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncontrollable situations are often experienced as more challenging than those within our control. Recently, it has been proposed that threat (un)controllability also affects fear learning processes. Most studies compare two variants of threat control - lacking versus having control. However, the impact of a sudden loss of control remains understudied. The current study investigated the impact of loss of control over threat on conditioned fear. We randomly assigned 80 participants to a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40876386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250829034125&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>