<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 07:42:40 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative separation of planar Nernst effects in harmonic Hall measurements of spin-orbit torques in Pt/Co/HfO/Ta multilayers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spin-orbit torques (SOTs) provide a promising pathway for efficient magnetization switching in magnetic random-access memory (MRAM) devices, but their quantitative evaluation is complicated by thermal artifacts. While increasing the resistivity of heavy metals can enhance the spin Hall angle through scattering mechanisms, high-resistivity systems also exhibit sizable thermoelectric signals that obscure reliable SOT extraction. In this study, we investigate SOTs in Pt/Co/HfO/Ta multilayers with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive machine learning for postoperative pain using biosignals: a retrospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conformation-driven reversibility control in ring-opening metathesis polymerization of non-bicyclic cyclooctenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reversible ring-opening metathesis polymerization (ROMP) of cyclooctene (COE) derivatives remains a challenge due to their high ring strain energies (RSEs). While previous strategies rely on fused bicyclic systems to reduce RSEs, depolymerization of non-bicyclic COE polymers has proven difficult. Here, we demonstrate efficient reversible ROMP of non-bicyclic COE derivatives by introducing conformational constraints via geminal tert-butyl and hydroxy substituents. These tailored monomers enable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398164/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive discovery of m<sup>6</sup>A sites in the human transcriptome at single-molecule resolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA modifications (RMs) are critical for diverse biological processes, but the lack of accurate, quantitative detection methods has limited their study. A large-scale and high-quality training dataset is an essential component for accurate deep learning, but such dataset has been absent for RM detection, resulting in low accuracies. We developed DeepRM (Deep learning for RNA Modification), a sophisticated deep learning framework powered by Nanopore sequencing. DeepRM dataset is a massive-scale,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skin-conformal MHz-speed organic photodetectors for angle-free and long-range near-infrared communication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Near-infrared (NIR) organic photodetectors (OPDs) offer a promising platform for skin-integrated optical communication systems, but achieving high-speed operation under mechanical stress remains a central obstacle. Here, we report a skin-conformable OPD with a 3 μm total thickness that achieves a specific detectivity calculated from noise-equivalent power of 0.84 × 10^(14) Jones at 790 nm and a - 3 dB cut-off frequency exceeding 1 MHz, maintained under 66% compressive strain and sub-5 μm bending...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Enavogliflozin as Add-on in Adults with Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus Inadequately Controlled with Insulin or Insulin with Other Antidiabetic Drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Enavogliflozin 0.3 mg/day is an efficacious and safe add-on treatment option in T2DM patients controlled inadequately with insulin alone or combined with OADs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of stiffness on cell behavior and drug resistance in patient-derived breast cancer organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC) accounts for 10-15% of breast cancer cases and is characterized by its high aggressiveness, influenced by extracellular matrix (ECM) proteins such as collagen IV and laminin. Creating a cancer microenvironment that mimics these conditions could enhance the clinical relevance of breast cancer models for patient-specific treatments. In this study, a Segmented Organoids with Agile Reassembly (SOAR) printing was established by compartmentalizing TNBC spheroids...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design, synthesis, and applications of Naphthalimide-based Mechanofluorophores for multimodal security encryption and anti-counterfeiting technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two novel donor-acceptor (D-A) type naphthalimide-based π-conjugated mechanofluorophores, NMF1 and NMF2, exhibiting solvatochromic, aggregation-caused quenching (ACQ), and reversible mechanofluorochromic (MFC) properties, were designed and synthesized. A systematic investigation of their solvatochromic behavior revealed bathochromic shifts in absorption maxima (λ(abs) from 411 to 441 nm (NMF1) and 415 to 444 nm (NMF2)) across a series of solvents of increasing polarity. Correspondingly,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and Efficacy of Hairy Scalp Donors in Thick Split-Thickness Skin Grafting: Complications and Outcomes of Grafts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All donor sites achieved successful regenerative healing. Thick scalp grafts demonstrated reduced contracture and superior color matching. These findings support the use of the hairy scalp as a safe and effective donor site for thick STSGs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Band and Field Coengineered Charge Trap Memristor via Au Nanoparticle Layer for Programming Speed Enhancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Charge trap memristors (CTM) are promising candidates for nonvolatile analog units in crossbar array platforms, offering a pathway to next-generation high-density memory and synaptic arrays, due to their low-current operation and self-rectifying characteristics. However, the charge trapping process is inherently slow, posing a significant challenge to achieving high-speed operation. In this study, a CTM device incorporating a gold nanoparticle (Au NP) layer, referred to as NP-CTM, is proposed....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hazard identification and characterization of leachable chemicals from plastic products - a new PARC project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A recent study has suggested that plastics may contain more than 16,000 chemicals, including additives, processing aids, starting substances, intermediates and Non-Intentionally Added Substances. Plastic chemicals are released throughout the plastic life cycle, from production, use, disposal and recycling. Most of these chemicals have not been studied for potential hazardous properties for humans and in the environment. To refine the risk assessment of these leachable chemicals, additional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tissue-Specific HGF and Soluble c-MET Levels in Gestational Diabetes Mellitus: Insights into Maternal-Endocrine Crosstalk and Fetal Metabolic Adaptation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings indicate tissue-specific dysregulation of HGF/c-MET signaling in GDM, potentially linking maternal insulin resistance with fetal metabolic stress through visceral-fat-derived HGF. The associations between maternal HGF and neonatal lactic-acid levels suggest an endocrine interaction influencing fetal adaptation. Further studies are needed to clarify underlying mechanisms across heterogeneous GDM phenotypes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392932/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunable Multimetallic Single-Atom Catalysts for Efficient Hydrogen Evolution Reaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Designing single-atom catalysts (SACs) with various metal atoms can significantly expand their range of applications. In this study, a scalable strategy is developed to synthesize a series of transition metal (TM = Mn, Fe, Co, Ni, and Cu) SACs with widely tunable compositions, progressing from unitary to binary (CoNi), ternary (MnCoNi), quaternary (MnFeCoNi), and quinary (MnFeCoNiCu) atoms. High loadings of TM atoms (>10 wt%) are successfully embedded in porous N-doped carbon nanoparticle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photocatalysis-Assisted Silver Reduction via ZnO Nanoparticles for High-Resolution, Flexible, and Etch-Free Printed Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, the development of environmentally friendly etch-free micro-printed circuit boards with fine-line traces has garnered significant attention. A novel photonic-assisted fabrication method is introduced that utilizes ultraviolet (UV) light and intense pulsed light (IPL) to produce highly conductive silver films on flexible substrates. Although silver organometallics can be reduced by the heating effect from localized surface plasmons (LSPs), this process alone is inefficient. Introducing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rising burden of myopia among South Korean young adults based on 13-year trends, associated factors, and projections to 2050]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To investigate long-term and projected trends of myopia and high myopia among young South Korean males and to evaluate associated sociodemographic risk factors. A repeated cross-sectional analysis was conducted using medical records from 4,063,091 19-year-old conscripts between 2011 and 2023. Logistic regression identified myopia risk factors, while linear regression assessed temporal trends. Projection modeling estimated future prevalence through 2050. Myopia prevalence increased from 50.6% in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous Glucose Monitoring for Pancreatogenic Diabetes After Total Pancreatectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Proactive CGM use may improve postoperative glycemic management in PDM after TP by increasing awareness of glycemic patterns, resulting in lower HbA1c and greater time in the target range.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural basis of dimerization and cascade formation by Cas5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CRISPR-Cas systems are essential for prokaryotic adaptive immune mechanisms; however, the structural details of many subtype-specific components remain unclear. Herein, we report the crystal structure and biophysical characterization of Cas5 from Moraxella bovoculi (MboCas5), a component of the type I-C CRISPR-Cas system. We found that M. bovoculi encodes both type I-C and type III-B systems, and that MboCas5 forms a dimer that is stabilized by key interactions, including a salt bridge between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Film cooling performance analysis of different multi-row cooling hole configurations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates film cooling flow over a flat plate with five different cooling hole configurations. These configurations include a combined arrangement of cylindrical and fan-shaped holes. Numerical simulations are performed using the open-source computational fluid dynamics (CFD) platform OpenFOAM. The study is performed at two different mainstream Mach numbers ([Formula: see text] and [Formula: see text]) and three different blowing ratios ([Formula: see text], [Formula: see text],...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398192/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a deep learning-based automatic segmentation and classification of cerebral white matter hyperintensities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results demonstrate the high segmentation and classification performance of our models and their potential for deployment as accurate diagnostic support tools for quantified evaluation of WMH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and neuroimaging correlates of disease related gait patterns in patients with multiple system atrophy cerebellar type]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiple system atrophy-cerebellar type (MSA-C) is a rapidly progressive neurodegenerative disorder, yet objective digital biomarkers for disease severity remain scarce. This cross-sectional study aimed to identify disease-relevant gait patterns using a 2D video-based gait analysis algorithm and examine their clinical and neuroimaging correlates. Gait features were extracted from videos of patients with MSA-C using Gaitome, and an MSA-C gait pattern score was derived. This score significantly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chemotherapy-driven intestinal dysbiosis and indole-3-propionic acid rewire myelopoiesis to promote a metastasis-refractory state]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The contribution of chemotherapy-induced tissue injury to individual susceptibility to metastasis remains largely unexplored. We report that chemotherapy indirectly prevents colorectal cancer (CRC) liver metastases by inducing a lasting systemic "chemomemory". Chemotherapy-induced intestinal mucositis alters nutrient availability, promoting the expansion of tryptophan-metabolizing bacteria and production of the microbial metabolite indole-3-propionic acid (IPA). IPA reprograms bone marrow...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inertial Agitation in an NMR Magnet: Real-Time Monitoring of Protein Aggregation at High Resolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a simple and efficient method to agitate NMR samples and thereby induce protein aggregation directly inside an NMR magnet. In this approach, termed inertia NMR, the rotational inertia of an eccentric floater within the sample tube generates agitation during acceleration and deceleration of tube spinning. This method enabled the aggregation of multiple disease-associated proteins under near-physiological conditions while allowing real-time monitoring by NMR spectroscopy. By combining...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions and Readiness for Generative AI Implementation among Oncology Nurses: A Qualitative Study in a Specialized Cancer Hospital]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Based on the research findings, academic and practical implications for the application of generative AI in nursing and strategies to enhance nurses' readiness for its implementation are presented.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring factors affecting oral health changes among community-dwelling older adults: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Study findings highlight the need for multi-level actions in clinical care, community health promotion, and policy to expand dental insurance. Future research should extend longitudinal analyses, address unmet oral health needs, and draw cross-national insights to inform strategies and policies for healthy aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world effectiveness of recombinant zoster vaccine in allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplant recipients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RZV demonstrated substantial effectiveness in reducing HZ risk among allo-HCT recipients in real-world clinical practice. These findings provide compelling evidence for incorporating RZV into after transplantation preventive care as a valuable complement to, or alternative to, traditional antiviral prophylaxis strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Methylation Profiling Uncovers IL10RB Hypomethylation as a Mediator between Environmental Heavy Metal Exposure and Lung Cancer Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Residents living in areas exposed to environmental hazards, such as abandoned mines and refineries, are hypothesized to exhibit distinct omics profiles compared with those in unaffected regions. In this article, we aimed to identify the differentially methylated regions (DMRs) affected by these hazards using Forensic Research via Omics Markers in Environmental Health Vulnerable Areas (FROM) cohort. We then evaluated the potential effects of these DMRs on 23 human diseases by using data from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Six-Month Outcomes of a Nurse Home Visiting Program in Korea: A Randomized Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: KECHI improved the home environment and maternal mental health at 6 months postpartum. The upcoming 2-year results will offer further insight into KECHI's impact and support its national scale-up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Excellent defluorination performance in defective CoNiO<sub>2</sub> based asymmetric flow capacitive deionization system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High concentration fluoride ions (F^(-)) in industrial fluorine-containing wastewater unavoidably impose tremendous hazards on environmental safety and public health. In comparison to traditional techniques, flow electrode capacitive deionization (FCDI) has attracted significant attention due to the advantages of easy operation, low operational cost, and lack of secondary pollution. However, FCDI with the same electrode materials, always accompanies with mismatched response to anions and cations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting emerging viruses with phage display-driven engineered antibodies: Bridging molecular design and clinical application]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phage display (PD) is a powerful platform that accelerates the discovery and engineering of therapeutic antibodies across diverse diseases, including emerging and re-emerging viral infections. The COVID-19 pandemic highlighted the urgency for rapid and adaptable antibody development against highly mutable pathogens, including severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2). PD technology enables the rapid and high-throughput identification, optimization, and efficient reformatting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asciminib Demonstrates Superior Efficacy and Safety in Newly Diagnosed Chronic Myeloid Leukemia in the ASC4FIRST Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many patients receiving frontline tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs) for chronic phase chronic myeloid leukemia (CML-CP) experience inadequate disease control and/or adverse events (AEs) that impair quality of life. Treatments offering optimal efficacy, safety, and tolerability will support long-term therapy. In the primary analysis from ASC4FIRST, a phase 3 randomized trial comparing asciminib with investigator-selected TKIs (IS-TKIs) in newly diagnosed CML-CP, asciminib demonstrated superior...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Utility Analysis and Value-Based Pricing of Digital Therapeutics for Pulmonary Rehabilitation in Chronic Respiratory Disease: Economic Evaluation Based on a Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DTx for pulmonary rehabilitation demonstrated the cost-effectiveness compared with standard treatment. These findings support its potential for improving outcomes in patients with chronic respiratory disease and provide a pricing framework to facilitate its integration into health care systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Injectable ABA Triblock Copolyether Hydrogel for Dental Implant-Mediated Drug Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, we present a novel implant-mediated drug delivery platform that integrates dexamethasone (DEX)-loaded injectable hydrogels with 3D-printed titanium implants. A hydrophobic monomer, (cyclohexyloxy)ethyl glycidyl ether, was designed and polymerized into ABA-type triblock copolymers via anionic ring-opening polymerization initiated by a poly(ethylene oxide) midblock. Tailoring the A block length optimized the viscoelasticity of the hydrogels, enabling shear-thinning flow for injectability...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ureteral Access Sheath Use and Infection-Related Hospitalizations: Practice Patterns and Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: UAS use in URS for renal stones varies across Michigan and was not associated with lower infection-related hospitalization. Prospective studies on the implications of intrarenal pressure are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decentralized trust optimization in VANETs: A blockchain-driven hybrid PoS-PBFT architecture for enhanced security and energy-efficient communication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vehicular Ad Hoc Networks (VANETs) are essential for the success of Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS), providing real-time communication between vehicles and infrastructure. However, the highly dynamic and decentralized nature of VANETs introduces significant challenges in ensuring trust and security across the network, including security threats, communication overhead, and energy inefficiencies. This paper presents a novel blockchain-based trust management framework that addresses these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of Pancreatic Cancer-Associated Ascites and Redefined Criteria for Bacterial Peritonitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PDAC-associated ascites exhibited distinct characteristics according to their etiology. Redefined diagnostic criteria could aid in a more specific diagnosis of bacterial peritonitis in patients with PDAC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to 'Methodological and statistical concerns in MINERVA microbiome-disease knowledge graph' by Salvatore Chirumbolo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Double Dermoglandular Reposition Mastopexy in Severely Ptotic and Flat Breasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severely ptotic and flat breasts pose significant reconstructive and aesthetic challenges due to poor skin elasticity and attenuated support structures, which limit the stability of upper pole projection. Augmentation mastopexy using implants may increase the risk of nipple-areola complex vascular compromise, and many patients prefer to maintain or reduce breast volume. Between 2022 and 2024, we performed vertical mastopexy with a double dermoglandular reposition technique in 31 patients (mean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complication Profiles of Immediate Implant-Based versus Deep Inferior Epigastric Perforator Flap Breast Reconstruction following Nipple/Skin-Sparing Mastectomy in Patients with Prior Breast-Conserving Surgery and Radiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with prior breast-conserving surgery and radiotherapy, choosing a DIEP flap as a breast reconstruction modality may reduce complication risk compared with implant-based methods. These findings provide valuable guidance for preoperative patient counseling and surgical planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anticoagulation Discontinuation After Catheter Ablation for Atrial Fibrillation-Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anhydrous Atomic Layer Deposition of HfO<sub>2</sub>: Mechanistic Analysis of the Tetrakis(dimethylamido)hafnium (TDMAH)-O<sub>2</sub> Process]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atomic layer deposition (ALD) is widely used to produce uniform hafnium oxide (HfO(2)) thin films with sub-nanometer thickness control. However, most studies on HfO(2) ALD have focused on ligand exchange reactions between surface hydroxyl (-OH) groups and Hf precursors. Here, we investigate the ALD reaction of HfO(2) on an OH-free HfO(2) surface using tetrakis(dimethylamido)hafnium (TDMAH) and molecular O(2). Theoretical approaches including machine learning interatomic potential (MLIP) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparisons of three-year outcomes according to the degree of left ventricular ejection fraction in patients with myocardial infarction with non-ST-segment elevation with and without chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Regardless of CKD status, the HFrEF subgroup showed higher mortality rates compared with the HFmrEF and HFpEF subgroups. However, the mortality rate differed between the HFmrEF and the HFpEF subgroups in both the CKD and the non-CKD groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the Letter Regarding "Dynamics of Oxygen Reserve Index and Arterial Oxygen Partial Pressure in Children"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete genome sequences of three <em>Geobacillus stearothermophilus</em> strains isolated from a Korean hot spring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present the complete genome sequences of three Geobacillus stearothermophilus strains-EF60063, EF60133, and EF60134-isolated from a Korean hot spring. S8 family serine peptidases and M4 family metallopeptidases were identified in all strains. Strain EF60063 harbors three plasmids. These findings advance understanding of the genus Geobacillus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Robust Strategy for High-Throughput and Deep Proteomics by Combining Narrow-Window Data-Independent Acquisition and Isobaric Mass Tagging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Data-independent acquisition (DIA) mass spectrometry systematically fragments all precursor ions within predefined isolation windows of a predefined mass-to-charge (m/z) range. Unlike data-dependent acquisition (DDA), which selects precursor ions based on intensity, DIA enhances identification and quantification opportunities for lower-intensity peptides, significantly improving proteome coverage. Nevertheless, standard DIA methodologies have limited application for isobaric-labeled peptides,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ovonic Switches Enable Energy-Efficient Dendrite-like Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, dendrites of neurons, which were previously thought to perform only information pooling and networking, have now been shown to express complex temporal dynamics, Boolean-like logic, arithmetic, signal discrimination, and edge detection. Mimicking this rich functionality could offer a powerful primitive for neuromorphic computing. Here, using Ovonic threshold switching in Sb-Te-doped GeSe, we demonstrate a single two-terminal component capable of self-sustained dynamics and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Early Pregnancy Isolated Leukocytosis With Adverse Pregnancy Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High first-trimester WBC counts (≥14 000/µL) are significantly associated with PTB, preeclampsia, SGA, and NICU admission and may serve as an early clinical predictor.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracranial stenosis and longitudinal progression of Alzheimer's disease pathologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The relationship between intracranial stenosis (ICS) and Alzheimer's disease (AD) pathologies remains unclear. We investigated whether baseline ICS is associated with longitudinal changes in amyloid beta (Aβ) and tau deposition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between steatotic liver disease subtypes and incident diabetes in young Korean adults: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: All SLD subtypes significantly increased the risk of type 2 diabetes in young adults, with the greatest risk in ALD, followed by MetALD and MASLD. Early detection and management of SLD are essential to reduce the future burden of diabetes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dimeric Acceptor with Small Singlet-Triplet Energy Gap Enables Suppressed Triplet Loss and 20.85% Efficiency of Organic Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The relatively high non-radiative energy loss has become a major limiting factor for improving the performance of organic solar cells (OSCs), with triplet exciton formation being a primary source. Narrowing the energy gap between the first singlet and triplet excited states (ΔE(ST)) in low-bandgap acceptors is considered an effective strategy to mitigate this issue. In this work, we design and synthesize a dimeric acceptor, DY-TXT, utilizing a thermally activated delayed fluorescence (TADF)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancements in Single-Atom Catalysts: Synthesis, Characterization, and Applications in Sensing Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-atom catalysts (SACs) have rapidly progressed from early proof-of-concept studies to high-performance sensing platforms. Their atomically dispersed active sites and tunable coordination environments, offer superior catalytic activity and selectivity compared with conventional nanocatalysts. Recent advances in support engineering, spanning carbon nanomaterials, metal oxides, and metal organic frameworks have enabled precise control over SAC composition, electronic structure, and stability...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Label-Free Electrochemical Impedance Spectroscopy for Biosensing: Evolving Interfaces and Mechanistic Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The evolution of label-free electrochemical biosensors has revolutionized the field of analytical detection by enabling rapid, direct, and sensitive detection of a wide range of analytes. Electrochemical impedance spectroscopy (EIS) provides mechanistic insight into the interfacial changes occurring at the electrode/electrolyte interface, thereby enabling real-time monitoring. Direct detection of molecular binding events at the electrode interface is made possible by sensing measurable shifts in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing Oxidized Alginate Microgels for Rapid and Self-Assembling Dental Tissue Organogenesis In Vitro and In Vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regenerating dental tissues for craniofacial reconstruction remains challenging due to inadequate tissue organization and poor intercellular connectivity, often caused by residual biomaterials. Recapitulating key developmental processes, such as spontaneous cellular condensation and epithelial-mesenchymal interactions (EMI), is essential for engineering functional tissue architecture. This study introduces an innovative system that utilizes oxidized alginate (OA) microgels laden with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction notice to "Three in-one fenestrated approaches of yolk-shell, silver-silica nanoparticles: A comparative study of antibacterial, antifungal and anti-cancerous applications" [Heliyon 9 (2023) e18034]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This retracts the article DOI: 10.1016/j.heliyon.2023.e18034.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395446/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction notice to "Advances in biodegradable materials: Degradation mechanisms, mechanical properties, and biocompatibility for orthopedic applications" [Heliyon 10 (2024) e32713]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This retracts the article DOI: 10.1016/j.heliyon.2024.e32713.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical standards for antimicrobial stewardship in TB care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These clinical standards aim to support clinicians, programme managers, and public health authorities in implementing effective, TB-specific AMS strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395320/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proceedings from the Third International Post-Tuberculosis Symposium: expanding the circle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In light of the recent growth in interest and knowledge of post-TB sequelae, there were high levels of engagement during the 3rd International Post-Tuberculosis Symposium held in Stellenbosch, South Africa. This multi-disciplinary symposium aimed to: 1) Advocate for greater global awareness of post-TB sequelae and empower TB-affected communities; 2) Advance knowledge by sharing current evidence and identifying key priorities; 3) Foster collaborations by strengthening research networks and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Retraction notice to "A mechanistic overview on green assisted formulation of nanocomposites and their multifunctional role in biomedical applications" [Heliyon 11 (2025) e41654]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This retracts the article DOI: 10.1016/j.heliyon.2025.e41654.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined intra- and extracapsular stabilization for CCL rupture in a toy-breed dog: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cranial cruciate ligament (CrCL) rupture is a frequent orthopedic condition leading to hindlimb dysfunction in dogs. While tibial plateau leveling osteotomy (TPLO) has become the predominant surgical choice in large breeds, its use in toy-breed dogs remains controversial due to anatomical constraints and implant limitations. This case report presents a 10-year-old, 2.0 kg Maltese with CrCL rupture and underlying cardiac disease, for whom osteotomy was contraindicated. A hybrid stabilization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and Implementation Process in a Pilot Project to Improve a Community Health Survey Using Mixed-mode Methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Pilot survey has been completed and the data are currently being refined. This report serves as interim documentation for design and implementation of a mixed-mode pilot project plan. Through this pilot project, we aim to establish a foundation to improve the overall survey system. The results of these analyses will be carefully reviewed and incorporated into community health surveys.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current Status and Directions for Improvement of the National Health Information Portal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In response to expanding AI-based search availability, the Portal has implemented a Generative Engine Optimization strategy and is exploring strategies to more effectively provide personalized health information in the future, including connectivity with national personal health record systems. The Portal will continue to strengthen its role as a leading public platform that improves health literacy and promotes healthy lifestyle practices in the population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Repeatable Photoactive Stent-Based Catheter to Enhance Therapeutic Efficacy for Esophageal Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Localized photodynamic therapy (PDT) using a photoactive stent-based catheter involves the direct delivery of reactive oxygen species to the mucosa in esophageal carcinoma; however, the damaged mucosa recovers within 2 to 4 weeks, which considerably limits the clinical application of PDT. Here, we used aluminum(III) phthalocyanine chloride tetrasulfonic acid (AlPcS4) as a photosensitizer due to its excellent photochemical durability, low photobleaching, and high quantum yield and investigated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of lifestyle change after H. pylori eradication with cardiovascular disease: a nationwide Korean NHIS cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Addressing ULS factors after H. pylori eradication may have a protective effect against posteradication CVD. Favourable changes in cholesterol levels, resulting from the direct effect of H. pylori eradication and the indirect effect of lifestyle modification, also contributed to CVD prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Habitual natto intake elevates serum MK-7 levels, enhances osteocalcin carboxylation, and supports bone density: a meta-analysis of Japanese evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Habitual natto consumption is associated with improved vitamin K status and bone metabolism markers. However, given the observational nature of the available evidence and its moderate-to-low certainty, these findings should be interpreted with caution. Natto may represent a culturally grounded dietary approach for supporting bone health and osteoporosis prevention, but its generalizability beyond Japanese populations warrants further investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncovering the genetic architecture of pungency, carotenoids, and flavor in <em>Capsicum chinense</em> via TWAS-mGWAS integration and spatial transcriptomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capsicum chinense (habanero pepper) exhibits substantial variation in fruit pungency, color, and flavor due to its rich secondary metabolite composition, including capsaicinoids, carotenoids, and volatile organic compounds (VOCs). To dissect the genetic and regulatory basis of these traits, we conducted an integrative analysis across 244 diverse accessions using metabolite profiling, genome-wide association studies (GWAS), and transcriptome-wide association studies (TWAS). GWAS identified 507...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide association and RNA-seq analyses reveal genes linked to salt stress in peanut (<em>Arachis hypogaea</em> L.)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salt stress adversely affects seed germination, seedling growth, and development, considerably impacting peanut (Arachis hypogaea L.) production. However, their genetic and genomic responses to salinity remain poorly understood. To identify candidate genes associated with salt tolerance, a genome-wide association study (GWAS) of 295 peanut genotypes and RNA sequencing (RNA-seq) analysis of two contrasting accessions (tolerant and susceptible) exposed to 200 mM NaCl at the seedling stage were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[User experience evaluation of Cogscreen for screening mild cognitive impairment: Formative and summative evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cogscreen demonstrated high usability as a digital screening tool for MCI, underscoring its promise for supporting early detection of cognitive decline. Future refinements should focus on enhancing error handling and improving demographic guidance. Expanding testing across diverse populations could further validate its potential clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic and Treatment Status of Severe Fever with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome in a Patient Cohort in 2022-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This multicenter cohort study characterized the diagnostic and therapeutic patterns of patients with SFTS in ROK. The findings provide essential data for the development of diagnostic tools and therapeutic strategies and highlight the importance of continued multicenter clinical research on SFTS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individual Malaria Case and Case Cluster Status in the Capital Region of the Republic of Korea, 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The post-coronavirus disease 2019 rise in malaria incidence is linked to resumption of social activities and enhanced surveillance. The capital region remains the focal point of domestic transmission, highlighting the need for regional and population-specific control measures. Targeted strategies for military personnel and outdoor workers are critical to achieve Korea's national malaria elimination by 2030 goal.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rational design and applications of piperazine and cyclohexane ionizable lipids for PKU and SSADH deficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A significant challenge of mRNA-based protein replacement therapies is the diminishing efficacy and escalating toxicity associated with repeated dosing of lipid nanoparticles (LNPs). Many existing lipid formulations were originally designed for vaccine and are not optimized for therapeutic applications. We developed two libraries of ionizable lipids-one based on piperazine and the other on a newly introduced cyclohexane structure-with variations in linker and tail groups to enhance molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Microbiome-based therapeutics for metabolic disorders: harnessing microbial intrusions for treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fmedt.2025.1695329.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implicit bias in digital health: systematic biases in large language models' representation of global public health attitudes and challenges to health equity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: As emerging instruments in digital health, large language models (LLMs) assimilate values and attitudes from human-generated data, thereby possessing the latent capacity to reflect public health perspectives. This study investigates into the representational biases of LLMs through the lens of health equity. We propose and empirically validate a three-dimensional explanatory framework encompassing Data Resources, Opinion Distribution, and Prompt Language, positing that prompts are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developmental Outcomes and Caregiving Burdens Among Children and Adolescents of Parents With Schizophrenia Spectrum Disorders: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this systematic review was to examine the developmental outcomes and caregiving burdens of the children and adolescents that have parents diagnosed with schizophrenia spectrum disorders. Following the Cochrane Handbook and the PRISMA guidelines, five electronic databases (PubMed, EMBASE, Cochrane Library, CINAHL, and PsycINFO) were systematically searched for studies published between January 2015 and December 2024. Eight quantitative studies met the inclusion criteria and were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ALS With and Without Upper Motor Neuron Signs: A Comparative Study Supporting the Gold Coast Criteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: The Gold Coast criteria permit diagnosis of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) even without upper motor neuron (UMN) signs. However, whether ALS patients with UMN signs (ALSwUMN) and those without (ALSwoUMN) share similar characteristics and prognoses remains unclear. This study compared clinical features, disease progression, electrophysiological findings, biomarker profiles, imaging parameters, and survival between these groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Persistent postoperative anaemia and 1-year mortality: re-examining time origin and sample selection - a reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Role of Heteroatom (N, Co) Co-Doped Ti<sub>3</sub>C<sub>2</sub>T<sub>x</sub> MXene in Hydrogen Evolution Reaction and Energy Storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene possesses remarkable properties for energy storage and electrocatalysis, yet its limited active sites and moderate catalytic activity restrict performance. This study explores nitrogen (N) and cobalt (Co) co-doping of Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene (MX-N-Co) as a strategy to enhance functionality, systematically comparing it with pristine and individually doped Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene with N and Co (MX-N, MX-Co) to elucidate the synergistic effects of dual doping on electrochemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boosting Hybrid Supercapacitor Performance with Molybdate Anions-Intercalated High-Entropy-Doped LDH Nanosheets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-entropy doping is now a powerful strategy to optimize the electrochemical properties of nanostructured materials for advanced energy storage. Here, a binder-free 2D high-entropy doped NiCoZnCrFe layered double hydroxide intercalated with molybdate anions (NCZCFM) is reported, and synthesized via electrodeposition. The cross-linked porous nanosheet network of NCZCFM provides abundant active sites, tunable composition, improved conductivity, enlarged interlayer spacing, rapid ion kinetics,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Multi-Channel Automatic Cellular Profiling (iMAP) System for Cholangiocarcinoma Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cholangiocarcinoma (CCA) is a highly lethal malignant tumor with a five-year survival rate below 10%. Clinical challenges include the absence of effective screening tools, the gradual progression until symptoms manifest, and the low diagnostic accuracy of CCA tissue due to the paucicellular nature of specimens obtained during an intervention. To address these challenges, an integrated multi-channel automatic cellular profiling (iMAP) system is developed for robust analysis of endoscopically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Interactions Between Single Atoms and Clusters/Nanoparticles on Nitrogen-Doped Carbon Supports for Electrocatalysis: A Critical Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Since the discovery of single-atom catalysts (SACs) in 2011, research has primarily focused on achieving atomic dispersion, which can lead to their remarkable catalytic activity, selectivity, and atom utilization. In parallel, nanoparticles (NPs)-based catalysts have a long-standing history and a proven track record in electrocatalysis. Integration of single atoms (SAs) and NPs within a single catalytic framework has recently emerged as a promising strategy to enhance electrocatalytic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Performance n-Type Thermoelectric Polymers via Ion-Exchange Tuning of Polaron-Cation Interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The thermoelectric (TE) properties of the n-type conjugated polymer (CP) polybenzodifuran-dione (PBFDO) are systematically modulated via counter-ion exchange, in which protons initially present as the counter-ion are replaced with various cations of increasing ionic radius. Ion exchange varied polaron-cation coupling, macroscopic conducting network, and macroscopic structural order, enabling purpose-oriented TE properties control, depending on the cation. In potassium-exchanged PBFDO film, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392739/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reassembly and improved annotation of the nearly complete mitochondrial genome of <em>Echinostoma caproni</em> (Digenea: Echinostomatidae) from an Egyptian isolate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a nearly complete mitochondrial genome (mitogenome) of Echinostoma caproni (Egyptian isolate), which was reassembled and thoroughly annotated from whole-genome sequencing data available from Sequence Read Archive (accession No. ERS055227). Although a mitogenome of E. caproni has previously been deposited in GenBank (accession No. AP017706), it represents a partial sequence lacking the transfer RNA (tRNA)-Ser2 and possessing only a short non-coding region. In contrast, the newly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tranexamic Acid Inhibits 17β-Estradiol-Induced Melanogenesis Through PKA-CREB-MITF Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tranexamic acid (TXA), a well-known anti-fibrinolytic agent, has been proven effective in the treatment of hyperpigmentation, particularly melasma. Oestrogen is known as an important cause of melasma and has been reported to induce pigmentation through the oestrogen receptor or the G protein-coupled oestrogen receptor. Although various mechanisms by which TXA improves skin pigmentation have been reported, its effect on oestrogen (17β-estradiol, E2)-induced pigmentation has not yet been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Cerebral Blood Flow With Near-Infrared Light Therapy in Mouse Model of a Chronic Hypoxia-Induced Bilateral Common Carotid Artery Stenosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transcranial photobiomodulation (PBM) was evaluated in a bilateral common carotid artery stenosis mouse model of chronic cerebral hypoperfusion. PBM enhanced cognitive performance and regional cerebral blood flow, particularly in hippocampal and cortical regions. Histological analysis revealed attenuated neuronal loss and smaller perivascular spaces, although residual necrotic foci persisted. PBM reduced BCL2 expression and modulated HIF-1 in a context-dependent manner, suggesting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alantolactone as a Bioactive Sesquiterpene Lactone: Molecular Mechanisms and Anticancer Potential for Pharmaceutical Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer remains a major global health challenge, responsible for millions of deaths each year. The limitations of current therapies, including adverse effects and drug resistance, have intensified the search for safer, more effective alternatives, particularly from natural sources. Alantolactone, a sesquiterpene lactone extracted from Inula helenium and related medicinal plants, has emerged as a promising anticancer candidate due to its diverse pharmacological actions. Although notable anticancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392518/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Foraminal Decompression Technique During ACDF for Cervical Radiculopathy that Provides a Better Outcome: Total Uncinatectomy vs Partial Uncoforaminotomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectivesAnterior cervical discectomy and fusion (ACDF) provides clinical improvement for cervical radiculopathy. Recently, it was determined that foraminal decompression via uncinate process resection could lead to faster and greater improvement of arm pain. Total uncinatectomy (TU) and partial uncoforaminotomy (PU) are commonly used for direct foraminal decompression. But the advantages and pitfalls of the two techniques remain unknown.MethodsConsecutive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Simple Fluorescence Spectrometry With Blue Emissive V<sub>2</sub>C MXene for Selective Detection of Rabeprazole Sodium in Pharmaceutical Samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Etching is a well-established method to create particles with nano-level precision. Herein, we have synthesized vanadium carbide (V(2)C) MXene fluorescent nanoparticles (FNPs) for the determination of rabeprazole sodium (R-Na) in drug samples. The prepared V(2)C MXene FNPs show blue emission under 365 nm of UV light with a good quantum yield of 9.70%. The synthesized V(2)C MXene FNPs showed the highest fluorescent intensity up on excitation at 350 nm, giving a maximum emission wavelength of 428...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SUPER: Upcycling Genetic Parts for Precise Gene Expression Control, Leakage Minimization, and Genetic Circuit Stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A long-standing goal of synthetic biology is to reprogram cells by rewiring genetic parts. Despite the expanding library of genetic parts, construction of integrated synthetic circuits with desired specifications remains challenging in part due to intricate dependence on sequence contexts, where unexpected narrow dynamic ranges and leaky expression can plague system performance. To provide an alternative approach to the screening process of iterative design-build-test cycles, SUPER (Synthetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Access to allyl-<em>gem</em>-difluorides <em>via</em> allylation and Cope rearrangement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fluorinated molecules play crucial roles in medicinal and materials chemistry, as the presence of fluorine profoundly alters molecular electronics and reactivity. Among them, allyl gem-difluorides have attracted growing attention as versatile synthetic intermediates, but their selective construction remains challenging. Here, we disclose an efficient strategy for synthesizing allyl gem-difluorides bearing (E)-vinyl boronic esters through a LiOtBu-mediated deborylative allylation/Cope...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Contact Property and Thermal Stability by Suppressing Oxygen Diffusion through Subnm Ultrathin Barrier for IGZO Devices Beyond Scaling Limits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We studied the effects of the interface oxide layer between amorphous indium-gallium-zinc oxide (IGZO) and metallic electrodes on contact resistance (R(C)). The reduction of R(C) has become imperative as IGZO devices are scaled down to achieve higher on current. Previous studies have reported the formation of low-resistance ohmic contacts, wherein oxygen vacancies generated by reactions between IGZO and metal supply free electrons. Nonetheless, such reactions inevitably lead to the formation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diabetogenic processes for insulin resistance-linked hyperinsulinaemia are associated with colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: Diabetogenic processes characterised by insulin resistance-linked hyperinsulinaemia were associated with increased odds of CRC, including early-onset disease. These findings offer new insights into diabetes-CRC pathogenesis, and may inform targeted prevention strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silent cerebral microvascular disease and the longitudinal risk of cognitive decline in atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The SKAF study aimed to investigate the incidence of asymptomatic cerebrovascular disorders and cognitive decline in patients with nonvalvular atrial fibrillation (NVAF). We enrolled patients with NVAF aged ≥ 60 years and those with sinus rhythm (SR) for comparison. We collected the head magnetic resonance imaging test and Montreal Cognitive Assessment (MoCA) data at baseline and 24 months follow-up. The primary endpoint was the composite of silent ischemic stroke and microbleeding, and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anxiety, depression and distress in family members of people who have experienced a critical care admission: a systematic review and Bayesian meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Levels of distress, anxiety and depression appear to be comparable between individuals who experience a critical care admission and their family members. An estimated 38% and 20% of family members have clinically important levels of anxiety and depression, respectively. PROSPERO registration: CRD42022302735.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ECG sonification methods for robust and generalizable clinical decision support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrocardiography (ECG) sonification has emerged as a complementary modality to visual waveform interpretation, enabling diagnostic cues to be conveyed through sound in real time. This review synthesizes evidence from the past decade to establish the current methodological landscape and gaps in ECG sonification research. A structured search identified eight peer-reviewed studies (2015-2025) that applied auditory transformation of ECG signals for diagnosis, monitoring, or therapeutic guidance....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polygenic and single-locus selection on BMI during Polynesian expansion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The 'thrifty' variant hypothesis, which posits that certain genetic adaptations promoting efficient energy storage during periods of food scarcity, has been invoked to explain the high prevalence of obesity in modern human populations. Although several candidate variants have been proposed, the timing and effects of these variants on body mass index (BMI) in specific populations remain poorly understood. In this study, we performed whole-genome sequencing of 22 Tongan individuals. A previous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Statins attenuate PD-L1 sorting to small extracellular vesicles dependent on ubiquitin-like 3 modification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Small extracellular vesicles (sEVs) mediate cell-to-cell communication by carrying RNAs and proteins. Ubiquitin-like 3 (UBL3) functions as a posttranslational modification factor, regulating protein sorting to sEVs. Programmed cell death ligand 1 (PD-L1) binds to programmed cell death 1 (PD-1) on immune cells, suppressing their function. Although immune checkpoint inhibitors, anti-PD-L1 and anti-PD-1 antibodies, have improved cancer treatment, efficacy remains limited (~ 25%). Per recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrinsic resistance to RAS inhibitors is driven by dysregulation of KRAS degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Activating mutations in KRAS occur in approximately 30% of lung adenocarcinomas. Despite advances in RAS-targeted therapies, intrinsic resistance limits their long-term efficacy. Here, we identify elevated levels of wild-type KRAS (WT-KRAS) protein as a key driver of intrinsic resistance in KRAS-mutant lung tumors. KRAS accumulation results from impaired LZTR1-mediated degradation, triggered either by LZTR1 loss or pharmacological RAS inhibition. Stabilized WT-KRAS activates the mTOR/HIF1α...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-neuron correlates of visual consciousness in human lateral occipital complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conscious perception, a critical aspect of human cognition, is assumed to emerge from a complex network of interacting brain regions that transmit information via feedforward and recurrent pathways. This study presents single- and multiunit recordings from the human lateral occipital complex (LO), a key region for shape and object recognition, during three distinct perceptual paradigms: backward masking, flash suppression and binocular rivalry. Stimulus awareness increased decoding accuracy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Guselkumab-mediated marked improvement in a case of refractory ulcerative colitis resistant to mirikizumab: evidence for switching between IL-23p19 inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-Linker Hydrophobicity Determines Microgel Nanostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In aqueous precipitation polymerization, which enables the synthesis of uniformly sized microgels, the monomers are dissolved and the polymer precipitates, leading to nucleation and growth process driven by hydrophobic interactions. Therefore, the (in)compatibility of chemical species used with aqueous solvents is expected to influence the nanostructure of the resulting microgels. In this study, several cross-linkers differing in the number of ethylene glycol units─hence varying in their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subthalamic Nucleus Deep Brain Stimulation Modulates Auditory Steady State Responses in Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deficits in auditory perception have been widely observed in Parkinson's disease (PD) patients and the literature attributes it, in part, to impaired central auditory processing. Deep brain stimulation (DBS) of the subthalamic nucleus (STN) is a well-established therapeutic option for patients with advanced PD. Analysis of auditory evoked potentials suggested a modulatory effect of DBS on central auditory processing. To better understand the latter, we investigated whether DBS modulates auditory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microsimulation modelling to predict the burden of CKD and the cost-effectiveness of timely CKD screening in Belgium: results from the Inside CKD study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Without changes to current practice, the disease burden of CKD in Belgium is predicted to remain substantial over the next few years. This highlights the need for timely diagnosis of CKD and demonstrates that, in line with guideline recommendations, implementing a CKD screening programme involving UACR and eGFR measurements followed by treatment would be cost-effective.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-[3-(4-(2-methoxyphenyl) piperazine-1-yl) propyl]-heteroaromatic carboxamide as selective α<sub>1A/1D</sub>-adrenoceptor antagonists: SAR study and metabolic stability evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual α(1A/1D)-adrenergic receptor (AR) antagonists are a mainstay treatment for lower urinary tract symptoms (LUTS) associated with benign prostatic hyperplasia (BPH). Building on the phenylpiperazine pharmacophore of naftopidil, our previous work identified the linker region as a critical structural determinant for subtype selectivity. However, we recognized that the secondary hydroxyl group within the previously employed linker (e.g., in lead R-17) could represent a potential metabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward a unified theory of ATP synthesis/hydrolysis: Integrating physics, chemistry, and biology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intercomparisons of computed epithelial/absorbed power density and temperature rise in anatomical human face models under localized exposures at 10 GHz and 30 GHz]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Epithelial/absorbed power density (EPD/APD) was recently introduced in the latest revision of international exposure guidelines as a dosimetric quantity associated with body surface temperature rise. To provide insight into their relationship, the intercomparison was organized by the IEEE Standards Coordinating Committee 95 Subcommittee 6 Working Group 5 and carried out by an international task force comprising eight governmental, academic, and industrial research institutions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smartphone App-Based Eating Behavior Monitoring and Feedback Intervention for Glucocorticoid-Induced Appetite Increase in Patients With Systemic Lupus Erythematosus: Protocol for a Pilot Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot trial will provide foundational data on the feasibility and efficacy of smartphone-based real-time feedback in managing glucocorticoid-induced appetite increase in patients with SLE. These findings may contribute to the growing body of literature on app-based interventions for medication-related adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-Surface Inter-Cytochrome Electron Transfer Limits Biofilm Electron Conduction Kinetics in <em>Shewanella oneidensis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrical conductivity of biofilms plays a critical role in advancing bioelectronics for energy and environmental applications, yet the underlying mechanisms remain poorly understood. Previous studies proposed interheme electron transfer between hemes 5 and 10 in the outer-membrane deca-heme cytochrome (OMC) MtrC as the rate-limiting step in the biofilm electron conduction of Shewanella oneidensis MR-1. However, the strong interheme electron coupling in MtrC suggests that interprotein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Air-Stable Tetrazene Radical Cation Salts: Structural Requirements and Oxidation Catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, stable tetrazene radical cation salts were synthesized and characterized for the first time. The radical cation derived from 1,2-di(2-azaadamantan-2-yl)diazene (DAD) was isolated as an air-stable solid, retaining its integrity for at least 120 days at ambient temperature (∼25 °C) and pressure. X-ray crystallography and electron spin-resonance spectroscopy revealed the delocalization of the unpaired electron over the tetrazene core and into the adamantane framework. DAD undergoes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41397181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of computed tomography short-axis diameter for supraclavicular lymph node metastasis after neoadjuvant chemotherapy for esophageal squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Esophageal squamous cell carcinoma (ESCC) often metastasizes to supraclavicular lymph nodes (SCLNs), which are potentially curable distant metastases by SCLN dissection during esophagectomy. Prophylactic SCLN dissection should be based on an accurate preoperative assessment of SCLN metastasis. We evaluated 199 patients who received neoadjuvant chemotherapy, followed by esophagectomy with three-field lymph node dissection for ESCC. For each patient, the largest SCLN was measured on the left and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of Transdermal Delivery and Vaccine Effect via Chemical Permeation Enhancers Integrated Solid-in-Oil Dispersions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Needle-free transdermal vaccination is an attractive alternative to hypodermic injection but its use remains limited because of the poor skin permeability of macromolecular antigens. Here, we integrated chemical penetration enhancers (CPEs) into solid-in-oil (S/O) dispersions to improve transdermal delivery and vaccine efficacy. The 24 different CPEs spanning five chemical classes were screened in fluorescein isothiocyanate-ovalbumin permeation assays using excised mouse skin. Fatty acids...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Detection of Pulmonary Edema in Dogs Using Wearable Monitoring of Daily Respiratory Variability: Two Case Reports]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing lens and organ dose evaluation in head CT examinations using monte carlo simulation: influence of gantry tilt and scan range]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subtraction-based Stepwise computed tomography post-processing with probabilistically adjusted thresholding for fat-ice demarcation: an in situ study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraprocedural visualization of the iceball boundary is often limited at the fat-ice interface, where frozen fat-despite increased computed tomography (CT) values-remains within the negative range, thus yielding limited contrast with non-frozen fat. This limitation is relevant in CT-guided renal cryoablation involving perirenal fat. We evaluated a stepwise CT post-processing method of subtraction and scaled addition with probabilistically adjusted thresholding, using an in situ fat-muscle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: Smoldering multiple myeloma: advances in diagnosis and risk stratification, and evolving therapeutic strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cytomegalovirus-induced intrahepatic cholestasis complicated by hemophagocytic syndrome in an immunocompetent adult]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reactivation of cytomegalovirus (CMV) remains a significant concern in patients receiving immunosuppressive therapy. Although CMV infection and reactivation is associated with intrahepatic cholestasis in infants and immunosuppressive adults, intrahepatic cholestasis caused by CMV infection is rare in immunocompetent adults. Here, we report a case with CMV-induced intrahepatic cholestasis in an immunocompetent adult complicated by hemophagocytic syndrome (HPS). We excluded CMV infection from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term remission of severe refractory scleritis associated with ulcerative colitis after proctocolectomy: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extraintestinal manifestations occur in up to 50% of patients with inflammatory bowel disease and can affect various organs, including the joints, skin, and eyes. Scleritis, one such extraintestinal manifestation, is associated with severe eye pain, vision impairment, and potential permanent vision loss. However, it is rare, and detailed descriptions of its characteristics and management are limited. We report the case of a 55-year-old man initially diagnosed with proctitis ulcerative colitis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative determination of suvorexant, lemborexant, and daridorexant in human plasma using a MonoTip C18 and gas chromatography-mass spectrometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MonoTip C18 utilizes a reduced amount of solvent, thereby eliminating the need for evaporation-to-dryness steps. As a result, the entire procedure, encompassing SPE to GC-MS detection, can be completed within 40 min. This single protocol is applicable to all ORAs currently available in Japan and is suitable for both clinical and forensic toxicological applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative analysis of toxicokinetic profiles of methamphetamine and its metabolites at toxic and therapeutic doses in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results obtained from this study suggest that the metabolism of AMP to OHAMP and NEP was saturated during intoxication. Furthermore, the determination of whether a toxic dose had been administered within 24 h or after 24 h would be possible through a joint evaluation of the urinary [AMP] / [MA] and [AMP] / [OHMA] ratios.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disparities in sleep medicine in Japan: association between CPAP prescriptions and the number of certified sleep medicine providers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The present study showed regional disparities in sleep medicine in Japan and a positive association between the number of sleep specialists and CPAP prescriptions, which highlighted the importance of enhancing the certification systems for sleep specialists to address regional health inequities in sleep medicine.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to comment on RE: Restricted morphological changes in infrapatellar fat pad during walking is revealed as a dynamics feature in symptomatic knee osteoarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Replicator dynamics and behavior-augmented multiscale epidemic modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study presents a multiscale modeling framework that integrates stochastic integrate-and-fire dynamics, networked replicator dynamics, and a behavior-augmented susceptible-exposed-infectious-recovered-susceptible model to simulate the interplay between agent behaviors and infection spread. Traditional compartmental epidemiological models often overlook behavioral adaptations and network complexity that underlie disease transmission. In contrast, our approach captures the stochastic acquired...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pressure-Induced Stabilization of 3D Hyperhoneycomb Li<sub>2</sub>(Sn<sub>1-<em>x</em></sub>Ru<sub><em>x</em></sub>)O<sub>3</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-ordered rock-salt oxides (e.g., AMO(2), A(2)MO(3), A(3)MO(4)) exhibit diverse functionalities arising from cation ordering, yet their structural evolution is difficult to predict due to the lack of systematic design principles. For A(2)MO(3) compounds, although two-dimensional (2D) honeycomb structures have been widely explored, the three-dimensional (3D) hyperhoneycomb phase is still rare, despite its appeal as a battery cathode and as a Kitaev spin-liquid candidate. Here, we report...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41396006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hidradenitis suppurativa patients exhibit a distinctive and highly individualized skin virome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hidradenitis suppurativa (HS) is a chronic inflammatory disease characterized by recurring skin lesions. Despite ongoing research, the exact cause underlying initiation and progression of disease remains unknown. While prior research has linked the skin microbiota to HS pathology, the role of viruses has remained unexplored. To investigate the skin virome, metagenomic sequencing of viral particles was performed on 144 skin samples from 57 individuals (39 HS patients and 18 controls). It was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular characterization of Candida boidinii GTS1 and its role in yeast proliferation in the phyllosphere]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gts1 is a pleiotropic regulator for stress response and metabolism in yeast. Here, we identified and characterized CbGTS1 from the methylotrophic yeast Candida boidinii. Deletion of CbGTS1 reduced yeast proliferation on plant leaves and decreased tolerance to high-salt stress. These findings demonstrate that CbGts1 contributes to yeast adaptation and survival under challenging phyllosphere environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibody-Drug Conjugates Using CD4 Mimics and a Neutralizing Antibody as HIV-1 Entry Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of new anti-HIV drugs with a novel mechanism of action is still required. A human cell surface protein, CD4, is a primary receptor for HIV-1 entry, and we have developed small-molecule CD4-competitive HIV-1 entry inhibitors, including CD4 mimics. CD4 mimics bind to a viral envelope protein, gp120, and cause a conformational change. Combinational use of CD4 mimics with CD4-induced antibodies, which recognize the exposed regions of gp120 induced by the CD4/CD4 mimic binding, shows...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decline in the mortality rate of children aged under 20 years with chronic conditions in Japan in 1995-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Mortality rates from diseases considered chronic in childhood in our analysis have declined for 27 years. Further investigation of disease prevalence is required to clarify the number of adolescents with chronic diseases who reach adulthood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of multiple gastric adenocarcinoma of fundic gland type accidentally found by additional gastrectomy following endoscopic submucosal dissection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An octogenarian male underwent upper gastrointestinal (UGI) endoscopy for an annual surveillance program, which identified a 12 mm type 0-IIa lesion on the posterior wall of the gastric fornix. An endoscopic biopsy was performed, raising suspicion for malignancy. Subsequent endoscopic submucosal dissection (ESD) was conducted, and the final histopathological diagnosis confirmed fundic gland-type gastric adenocarcinoma. The tumor exhibited submucosal invasion to a depth of 1000 μm. No evidence of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transanal minimally invasive surgery for rectal gastrointestinal stromal tumor using articulated forceps after neoadjuvant chemotherapy with imatinib mesylate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rectal gastrointestinal stromal tumors (GISTs) are rare, accounting for approximately 5% of all GISTs and 0.1% of all rectal malignancies. Radical resection without capsule violation is the standard treatment for localized GISTs. However, surgical resection of large rectal GISTs poses challenges because of the narrow pelvic anatomy and the need to preserve excretory function. Based on KIT mutation status, neoadjuvant imatinib therapy facilitates tumor shrinkage and improves surgical outcomes. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resistance mechanism to pembrolizumab in <em>DEK</em>-<em>AFF2</em> fusion-associated sinonasal squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, the first case of a novel DEK-AFF2 fusion has been identified in nonkeratinizing squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) of the sinonasal tract with an exceptional response to pembrolizumab. Here we present the case of a 71-year-old female with metastatic poorly differentiated SCC of the sinonasal cavity with a DEK-AFF2 fusion. She initially received pembrolizumab monotherapy as first-line treatment, but the disease progressed after two months. Subsequent treatment with paclitaxel plus cetuximab...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of primary ovarian clear cell carcinoma with <em>ETV6::NTRK3</em> fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the first documented case of primary ovarian clear cell carcinoma harboring an ETV6::NTRK3 fusion gene. A 49-year-old woman presented with a rapidly growing ovarian cyst that was diagnosed as stage IC1 clear cell carcinoma following primary debulking surgery. Molecular analysis revealed an ETV6::NTRK3 fusion gene, confirmed by RT-PCR and Sanger sequencing. The tumor also contained an ARID1A variant (p.P1326Rfs*155), exhibited low tumor mutation burden (3.7 Muts/Mbp), and showed stable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early detection of drug-induced interstitial lung disease using an electronic patient-reported outcome system: a report of two cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug-induced interstitial lung disease (DILD) is an adverse event associated with the use of various anticancer drugs. Although DILD is rare, it is a serious complication that can lead to treatment interruption and, in some cases, life-threatening outcomes. The early detection of DILD requires careful monitoring of subjective symptoms, regular computed tomography (CT) scans, and biomarker assessments. We present two cases in which electronic patient-reported monitoring by a pharmacist, utilizing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tirabrutinib rechallenge achieved complete response for recurrent primary central nervous system lymphoma: illustrative case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary central nervous system lymphoma (PCNSL) is an aggressive non-Hodgkin lymphoma with a poor prognosis, with a 5-year survival rate of 23-42%. Relapse occurs in 35-60% of patients within 1-2 years, and no standard treatment exists for recurrent PCNSL. Tirabrutinib, a second-generation BTK inhibitor, is used for recurrent PCNSL treatment in Japan, but its efficacy in rechallenge therapy remains uncertain. A 75-year-old man presented with gait disturbance, dysarthria, and ataxia. MRI revealed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-grade gliomas derived from an ovarian mature teratoma: clonal dynamics and genetic insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-grade glioma (HGG) arising from a mature ovarian teratoma is extremely rare and its genetic alterations remain largely unknown. We report a case of WHO Grade 4 HGG (HGG-G4) developing 3 years after cystectomy for ovarian mature teratoma, where a WHO Grade 3 HGG (HGG-G3) was identified upon pathological reevaluation. Whole-exome sequencing confirmed the clonal relationship between HGG-G3 and HGG-G4, revealing genome-wide copy-neutral loss of heterozygosity, copy-number alterations, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of long-term relief from bleeding due to fungating breast cancer in an elderly patient after 8-Gy single-fraction radiation therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fungating lesions in advanced breast cancer often affect the quality of life. Fractionated radiation therapy is the preferred treatment over single-fraction radiation therapy because of the relatively favorable prognosis for breast cancer. Therefore, limited literature is available regarding the effectiveness of short-course radiation therapy, especially 8-Gy single-fraction radiation therapy. Herein, we describe the case of an 85-year-old patient diagnosed with locally advanced breast cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful treatment of primary intramedullary spinal cord lymphoma based on the molecular diagnosis of a MYD88 mutation in the cerebrospinal fluid: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary intramedullary spinal cord lymphoma (PISCL) is a rare subtype of primary central nervous system lymphoma (PCNSL) that mimics other myelopathies, often leading to delayed diagnosis. Histopathological confirmation via spinal biopsy is the gold standard; however, spinal biopsies carry considerable risks. The myeloid differentiation primary response gene 88 (MYD88) L265P mutation is highly specific for PCNSL and can be detected in the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) by liquid biopsies. However,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hemostasis and life-saving by arterial embolization for a rupture of hepatic metastasis from choriocarcinoma after initiation of EMA/CO therapy: a case report and literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Choriocarcinoma occurs in the uterus and various other organs, including liver, lungs, and brain. Depending on the site of onset, early identification is difficult due to non-specific or an asymptomatic presentation. Moreover, choriocarcinoma may be detected when the tumor grows considerably or ruptures. We encountered a case in which hepatic metastasis ruptured, leading to hemorrhagic shock. The rupture occurred after the initiation of etoposide, methotrexate, actinomycin D, cyclophosphamide,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The first case of <em>GOLGA5-RET</em> fusion-positive malignant spindle cell sarcoma of the head and neck responsive to selpercatinib]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft-tissue sarcoma (STS) is a rare malignancy that accounts for less than 1% of all cancers, and recent advances in molecular biology have led to its classification based on genomic information. Some RET-rearranged neoplasms have been reported to present pathological features similar to Neurotrophic Tyrosine Kinase Receptor-rearranged spindle cell neoplasms. Here, we report the first case of head and neck spindle cell sarcoma with a GOLGA5-RET fusion that demonstrated a sustained clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Decade of Porcine Circovirus Type 2 (PCV2) in Thailand: Phylodynamic and Molecular Epidemiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porcine circovirus type 2 (PCV2) is a major swine pathogen causing significant economic losses in the swine industry worldwide. Continual monitoring of genetic and antigenic diversity is essential for the early detection of emerging variants. This study investigates the evolutionary dynamics and genetic variation of PCV2 circulating in Thailand and across Asia from 2007 to 2024, using integrated phylogenetic and phylodynamic analyses. Analysis of 2739 PCV2 genomes, after excluding 0.99%...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-inflammatory and skin-regenerative properties of Red Sea <em>Holothuria atra</em>: in vitro wound healing activity of the methanolic extract and in silico anti-Tumor Necrosis Factor-<em>α</em> evaluation of its bioactive metabolites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Marine-derived functional ingredients are gaining attention for their therapeutic potential in skin health and inflammation. The wound healing and anti-inflammatory properties of Holothuria atra, an edible sea cucumber, remain underexplored. This study aimed to evaluate the in vitro wound healing activity of H. atra methanol extract and the in silico anti-tumor necrosis factor-α (TNF-α) of its metabolites. Cytotoxicity on human keratinocyte (HaCaT) cells was assessed, followed by scratch assays...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the effectiveness of low-dose oral switch therapy for uncomplicated streptococcal or enterococcal bloodstream infection: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Low-dose OST may be effective for clinically stable patients with uncomplicated GP-BSI in settings with low obesity prevalence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41395130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Unveiling the role of sintering temperatures in the physical properties of Cu-Mg ferrite nanoparticles for photocatalytic application"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1016/j.heliyon.2024.e40771.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-cultural Comparison of Recovery College Implementation Between Japan and England: Corpus-based Discourse Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recovery Colleges (RCs) are mental health learning communities, operated in 28 countries across cultures. However, the RC operational model is informed by Western countries sharing similar cultural characteristics such as individualism and short-term orientation. How RC operational model needs to be adapted to non-Western culture remains unknown. We investigated how RCs are introduced to the public in two countries with contrasting cultural characteristics: Japan (collectivism, long-term) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41394523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-erythrocyte spectrin network preferentially stabilizes flat membrane and enhances cell stiffness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spectrin αII and βII, the predominant non-erythroid isoforms, assemble into cytoskeletal networks that shape the plasma membrane. However, how these networks interact with membranes of different curvatures remains unclear. Using microfluidic deformation cytometry, we show that spectrin βII overexpression increases the apparent stiffness of MDA-MB-231 breast cancer cells. Fluorescence microscopy further demonstrates that spectrin is excluded from highly curved regions and enriched on flatter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393207/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into endogenous agonist selectivity of aminergic receptors from the octopamine β<sub>2</sub> receptor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tyrosine-derived amines (TDAs), such as octopamine, noradrenaline, dopamine, and tyramine, are essential neurotransmitters that play diverse roles in various physiological processes. The distinct receptor selectivity of these structurally similar molecules is vital for their specific functions. However, all these receptors belong to the same subfamily of G-protein-coupled receptors and share high sequence homology within their orthosteric binding sites. The molecular basis of this selectivity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41393170/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma-Induced Amine-Modified PEEK Promotes Osteointegration via Multiple Osteogenic Pathways and Macrophage Modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyetheretherketone (PEEK) is a semicrystalline synthetic polymer commonly used in orthopedic devices because of its chemical stability, thermal elasticity, radiopacity, and mechanical moduli similar to that of bone. However, its inherent biological inertness results in poor initial fixation and insufficient bone bonding, which can compromise implant stability and long-term success. To overcome this limitation, various surface modification strategies, such as physical treatments (for example,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392887/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanointerface-Guided Pt Deposition on Co-Mn Oxide-SnO<sub>2</sub> Supports for High ORR Durability and Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen polymer electrolyte fuel cells (PEFCs) are key technologies for achieving a low-carbon society, but conventional oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) catalysts sucg as Pt/C suffer from degradadation of carbon supports during operation. To overcome this limitation, we developed a nanostructured catalyst support by coating tin oxide (SnO(2)) nanoparticles with cobalt-manganese oxide (CMO), enabling nanoscale interface engineering. The CMO layer was formed via electroless deposition of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Xrp1 drives damage-induced cellular plasticity of enteroendocrine cells in the adult Drosophila midgut]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellular plasticity, the ability of a differentiated cell to adopt another phenotypic identity, is restricted under basal conditions, but can be elicited upon damage. However, the molecular mechanism enabling such plasticity remains largely unexplored. Here, we report damage-induced cellular plasticity of secretory enteroendocrine cells (EEs) in the adult Drosophila midgut. Ionizing radiation induces EE fate conversion and activates stress-responsive programs in EE lineages, accompanied by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Chemically Switchable Synthetic Condensate Platform for Reversible Protein Sequestration and Release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Creating artificial organelles that sequester and release specific proteins in response to a small molecule in mammalian cells is an attractive approach for regulating protein function. In this work, by combining phase-separated condensates formed by the tandem fusion of two oligomeric proteins with a trimethoprim (TMP)-responsive nanobody switch for GFP (^(GFP)LAMA; ligand-modulated antibody fragment), we developed a synthetic condensate system that initially sequesters GFP-tagged proteins...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lateral size modulated structural color of aqueous dispersions of titanate nanosheets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Deionized suspensions of titanate nanosheets exhibit vivid structural colors arising from the formation of lamellar liquid-crystalline phases. We investigated the impact of lateral size on the resulting structural coloration. A decrease in average lateral size (aspect ratio) shifts the structural color toward a blue dominant tone and narrows the reflection bandwidth, indicating an improvement in structural regularity. This behavior can be attributed to the faster orientational relaxation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metal-Organic Framework Nanopores Identify Single Monomer Mutation on Synthetic Polymer Chain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we demonstrate that the nanopores of a metal-organic framework (MOF) can recognize even a single-monomeric difference within a long synthetic polymer chain comprising over 600 repeating units. Specifically, MOF-808, featuring three-dimensional pores with apertures of ca. 1.0 nm, does not adsorb polystyrene (PS) homopolymers from a toluene solution. Strikingly, it exhibits significant adsorption of PS chains bearing even only a single substitution within the polymer backbone. Furthermore,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41392460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling interactions of spatial-temporal information in tactile motion perception]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tactile perception is inherently dynamic, relying on active manual exploration to extract information about motion and surface properties. Spatiotemporal inputs facilitate tactile motion perception by conveying information both direction and speed perception. Although previous studies have examined these features separately, the interactions between spatial and temporal features in shaping perceptual outcomes remain poorly understood. To address this gap, we conducted two psychophysical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based mortality risk prediction model for elderly diabetic patients with non-ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction using MIMIC-IV database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-ST-elevation myocardial infarction (NSTEMI) in elderly diabetic patients presents unique challenges in risk assessment and prognosis prediction. This study aimed to develop and validate a machine learning-based mortality risk prediction model for this specific population using the MIMIC-IV database. We conducted a retrospective cohort study including 5,272 NSTEMI patients aged ≥ 55 years with diabetes from the MIMIC-IV database. Multiple machine learning models were developed using clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41398420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251216024236&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>