<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:40:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urban mental health: A position paper of the European Psychiatric Association]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250903034025&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250903034025&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Relative Roles of Inflammation in Kidney Allotransplantation and Xenotransplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250903034025&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nature and severity of the inflammatory response influences the outcome of organ allotransplantation and xenotransplantation. In allotransplantation, the source of the allograft, for example, from a living, brain-dead, or circulatory death donor, influences the inflammatory response, as do such factors as the preexisting comorbidities and the length of the period of chronic kidney disease in the recipient and the management he/she has received. There is also inflammation associated with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250903034025&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ATE1 promotes breast cancer progression via arginylation-dependent regulation of MAPK-MYC signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ATE1 promotes breast cancer progression by enhancing cell proliferation, survival, and migration through MAPK-dependent stabilization of MYC in a lineage-specific context. These findings identify ATE1 as a potential therapeutic target and highlight the relevance of protein arginylation in the molecular heterogeneity of breast cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully biocompatible, thermally drawn fiber supercapacitors for long-term bio-implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in implantable bioelectronic devices have increased the demand for biocompatible energy sources with long-term electrochemical and mechanical stability. Here, we present a tough hydrogel-based supercapacitor (THBS) fiber, fabricated via a thermal drawing process (TDP), that enables the integration of all components-electrodes, electrolyte, current collectors, and encapsulation-into a single, unified, and mechanically robust fiber-shaped architecture. Through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A reconfigurable piezo-ionotropic polymer membrane for sustainable multi-resonance acoustic sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sensorineural hearing loss is the most common form of deafness, typically resulting from the loss of sensory cells on the basilar membrane, which cannot regenerate and thus lose sensitivity to sound vibrations. Here, we report a reconfigurable piezo-ionotropic polymer membrane engineered for biomimetic sustainable multi-resonance acoustic sensing, offering exceptional sensitivity (530 kPa^(-1)) and broadband frequency discrimination (20 Hz to 3300 Hz) while remaining resistant to "dying". The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and interlaboratory validation of a linearized plasmid DNA certified reference material by single molecule direct counting and digital PCR]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital PCR (dPCR) technology is widely utilized for various applications, including the quantification of gene mutations and copy number variations. Certified reference materials (CRMs) play a critical role in improving the comparability of dPCR results, establishing SI-traceable copy number concentration values for dPCR calibration remains a key challenge due to the limited availability of CRMs value-assigned by higher-order, independent methods. To tackle this issue, a linearized plasmid DNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field application of a tiered TRIAD approach: Effects of soil extraction methods on site-specific soil ecological risk assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The TRIAD approach achieves site-specific soil ecological risk assessments by integrating three lines of evidence (LoEs): chemistry, ecotoxicology, and ecology. Although the various toolbox items within TRIAD should be analyzed according to the site characteristics, no studies have yet determined the effect of selecting different analytical items on the resulting ecological risk. In this study, we applied the tiered TRIAD system to two heavy-metal-contaminated sites and compared the ecological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal denaturation of porcine myofibrillar proteins at different heating temperatures: A focus on the surface hydrophobicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Changes in the hydrophobic interactions of porcine myofibrillar proteins (MPs) were investigated at various heating and internal temperatures (ITs). MP extracts were heated at 50, 60, 70, 80, or 90 °C until their ITs reached the same respective values (±2 °C) and were labeled IT50, IT60, IT70, IT80, and IT90. The intrinsic tryptophan fluorescence intensity (FI) of the MPs decreased after heating at all ITs (P < 0.05). FI(max) decreased significantly between IT50 and IT60 (P < 0.05) and increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modified Saengmaeksan, an herbal formula containing six herbs, improves hypertension through RhoA/Rho kinase-mediated vasorelaxation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: mSMS exhibits potent antihypertensive effects through the inhibition of the RhoA/Rho-kinase pathway, reduction of vascular remodeling, oxidative stress, and renal protection. These findings support the potential of mSMS as a novel therapeutic agent for hypertension, offering a multi-targeted approach with fewer side effects compared to conventional therapies. Further clinical studies are required to confirm its clinical efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A national survey on how to improve the integration of traditional Chinese medicine and artificial intelligence: Attitudes and perceptions from medical staff]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The integration of TCM and AI has a brilliant and promising future, prioritizing diagnostic accuracy while addressing cultural/clinical adaptation challenges in key applications, such as syndrome differentiation systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic effects of Gunryeong-tang on the cardio-renal axis in an animal model of pulmonary hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: In the realm of cardiovascular and renal health, the modulation of oxidative stress and inflammation within the cardio-renal axis plays a pivotal role. This study investigates the therapeutic potential of Gunryeong-tang (GRT), a traditional Korean herbal formula combining Oryeongsan (Wulingsan) and Sagunza-tang (Sijunzi-tang), specifically in addressing cardio-renal axis dysfunction induced by pulmonary arterial hypertension (PAH-r). Methods: PAH-r models were induced through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A national survey on the integration of traditional Chinese medicine and artificial intelligence: attitudes and perceptions from the individuals with health needs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The integration of TCM and AI demonstrates promising acceptance among health-seeking individuals in China, with younger and educated populations who have health demands for TCM showing particularly high trust, and intelligent syndrome differentiation systems highlight a clear pathway for AI to modernize TCM practice by augmenting diagnostic accuracy and treatment personalization.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of core outcome set for healthy aging treatment in primary care settings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The COS provides a standardized set of outcomes for evaluating healthy aging interventions in primary care. Its application in primary care and health promotion programs may enhance comparability across studies and support evidence-based decision making. Future revisions are recommended based on clinical applications and emerging research findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-elution of <em>Cis</em>-NMIFAs in the 18:3t region: analytical approach in <em>trans</em> fatty acid identification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate identification of trans-18:3 fatty acid isomers remain challenging due to the co-elution of structurally diverse cis isomers, particularly non-methylene-interrupted fatty acids (NMIFAs). GC-FID analysis of pine nut using an SP™-2560 column revealed unusually high peak areas (> 13%) in the 18:3t region. However, a peak reduction in the 18:3t region after nitric acid-induced isomerization reaction, suggested the presence of cis isomers in native pine nut. GC-MS data identified the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The elucidation of the dual role of Beclin-1 in ischemic stroke through systems biology modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Beclin-1 plays a pivotal role in the interplay between autophagy and apoptosis in ischemic stroke, influencing both cell survival and death. We developed a mathematical model incorporating the dual role of Beclin-1 to simulate Beclin-1-induced autophagy and apoptosis under varying ischemic stress conditions. The model predicts a critical threshold of Beclin-1 expression, beyond which apoptosis is triggered, with this threshold decreasing as stress severity increases. To validate the model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring <em>murE</em> protein inhibitors of <em>Tropheryma whipplei</em> through pharmacoinformatic approaches incorporating solubility-enhancing formulation insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tropheryma whipplei the causative agent of Whipple disease, presents a diagnostic challenge due to its diverse symptomatology, including weight loss, abdominal pain, diarrhea, joint pain, fever, and occasionally neurological manifestations. Its resistance to fluoroquinolones complicates treatment further. Traditional methods for antibiotic susceptibility testing are ineffective as Tropheryma whipplei cannot be cultured in axenic media. To address this, we explored potential drug targets within...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective Green Colorimetric Liquid- and Solid-Based Determination of Furfural in Power Transformer Insulating Fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Furfural (FF), an intermediate aldehyde compound, can serve as an indicator of the extent of the Maillard reaction on heat-induced food processing and storage, as well as for the aging assessment of the solid insulation of oil-immersed transformers because it is formed by the degradation of cellulosic insulation. By considering the concepts of green analytical chemistry, a new furfural-bis-(4-aminophenyl) disulfide (APDS) colorimetric chemosensory assay, based on the Stenhouse reaction between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phloridzin Mitigates Gorham-Stout Disease by Dual Inhibition of Osteoclastogenesis Related to the Ca<sup>2+</sup> Signaling Pathway and Vascular Proliferation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phloridzin, a natural compound derived from Malus doumeri, exhibits a wide range of biological activities, making it a promising candidate for the development of functional foods aimed at promoting health and preventing disease. Gorham-Stout disease (GSD) is an orphan rare disorder defined by gradual bone resorption and vascular proliferation, with fewer than 400 cases documented, leading to severe pathological consequences. This study aims to examine the mechanisms underlying two key features...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Zero-Field Overhauser Dynamic Nuclear Polarization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overhauser dynamic nuclear polarization (O-DNP) enables the production of hyperpolarization in liquids via the dissolution of nitroxide radicals. However, the application of magnetic fields has been inevitable. In the present study, we experimentally demonstrate that water can be hyperpolarized through O-DNP at effectively zero magnetic field. Selective saturation induced by circularly polarized RF fields, generated by two orthogonal RF coils, effectively circumvents the concurrence of positive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the relationship between digital competency and life satisfaction Among the elderly]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Improving digital skills alone may not suffice to enhance well-being in older adults. Programs should also boost self-efficacy and emphasize personal relevance to increase satisfaction with digital transformation. These findings inform future interventions aimed at reducing digital inequality and supporting more inclusive digital aging policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of repeated intratracheal instillation of incense smoke condensate in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Incense smoke condensate (ISC) can have harmful mutagenic and genotoxic effects. Epidemiological and experimental studies have reported the negative effects of incense use on humans. We investigated the toxicological effects of the incense smoke condensate ISC in a 2-week repeated intratracheal instillation model in mice. Twenty-five male mice were divided into four treatment groups and one control group (n = 5 per group). The treatment groups received daily intratracheal instillations of ISC at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Safety, Tolerability, and Pharmacokinetics of ALT-BB4 (A Novel Recombinant Hyaluronidase): A Randomized, Double-Blinded, Placebo-Controlled, Phase 1 Study in Healthy Volunteers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both intradermal and subcutaneous injection of ALT-BB4 demonstrated excellent safety and tolerability, supporting its potential as a promising alternative to traditional animal-derived hyaluronidases. Future studies are warranted to confirm these findings in broader clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute-phase response- and inflammation-, but not extracellular matrix-related proteins in the amniotic fluid are associated with spontaneous preterm delivery in asymptomatic women with midtrimester short cervix]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: To determine whether (i) altered levels of acute-phase response (APR)-, inflammation-, and extracellular matrix (ECM)-related proteins in the amniotic fluid (AF) were associated with spontaneous preterm delivery (SPTD) in asymptomatic women with midtrimester short cervix (SCX) and (ii) if SPTD risk severity was related to the expression levels of inflammation-related proteins in the AF. Methods: This retrospective cohort study included 70 singleton pregnant women diagnosed with a SCX...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Representations of Neuropsychiatric Symptoms in Alzheimer's Disease Continuum Using Pathology-Based Functional Connectivity Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We identified the key regions specific to affective and apathy factors based on the areas with coexistence of amyloid-beta and tau pathologies and the accompanying altered functional connectivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Team Korea injury and illness surveillance at the 2024 Paris Olympic Games]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Team Korea athletes participating in the 2024 Paris Summer Olympic Games exhibited higher incidences of injury and illness than previous Olympic Games statistics. This single-delegation epidemiological research will contribute to our understanding of the true incidence of health problems in Olympians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of ECPR initiation time and age on survival in out-of-hospital cardiac arrest patients: a nationwide observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Platelet-rich plasma enhances local homing of umbilical cord-derived mesenchymal stem cells to articular cartilage by increasing the quantity and activation of integrin ꞵ1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This suggests that pre-conditioning MSCs and cartilage ECM with PRP synergistically enhanced MSC adhesion to the cartilage ECM by increasing both the quantity and activation of ITGB1 in MSCs, thereby enhancing the therapeutic effects of MSCs on articular cartilage regeneration in a rat osteochondral defect model.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overall survival following radical surgery and postoperative chemotherapy in colorectal cancer patients aged ≥ 70 years: a population-based retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In elderly CRC patients, comorbidity and frailty may play a dominant role in determining overall survival, potentially exceeding the impact of tumor-directed treatments such as postoperative chemotherapy. These findings highlight the need for comprehensive geriatric assessment and individualized treatment planning in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of physical activity interventions on physical fitness in preschool children: a meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials and dose-response study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PA interventions effectively improve physical fitness in preschool children. Optimal weekly doses range from 180 to 380 min, depending on the fitness component. Intervention effectiveness is further moderated by session frequency, duration, and total program length, highlighting the need for tailored PA strategies targeting specific physical fitness outcomes in early childhood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of a nurse-led online video intervention for mealtime assistance in dementia care: a quasi-experimental mixed-methods study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: YouTube-based multimedia learning interventions effectively improved the knowledge, attitudes, and behaviors of DCWs in mealtime assistance for older adults with dementia. Its accessibility and practicality suggest that this approach can be a useful educational model in long-term care settings. Further studies are needed to explore the role of opinion leaders in sustaining and expanding these effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: ES-UNet: efficient 3D medical image segmentation with enhanced skip connections in 3D UNet]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How place shapes genital herpes simplex distribution in South Korea: a Bayesian spatial analysis using National Health Insurance Service data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study reveals distinct geographic patterns in GHS incidence rates that are not fully explained by demographic composition alone. The significant associations with household structure and sexual violence risk suggest that place-specific social contexts influence GHS incidence rates. These findings highlight the importance of spatially targeted interventions to address contextual vulnerabilities in regions with high GHS incidence rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898057/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of intraoperative low-dose remimazolam as a third antiemetic agent for preventing early postoperative nausea in high-risk patient: A Randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Low-dose remimazolam infusion did not reduce the incidence of PONV at postoperative 24 h. It was associated with a lower incidence of nausea at postoperative 6 h and dizziness in the PACU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Bio-Stimulation Effects of Various Dermal Fillers: Hyaluronic Acid-Based Polynucleotides and Microparticle Fillers in Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provided comprehensive insights into the biophysical properties and efficacy of various dermal fillers in stimulating collagen production. PDO and HA-PDLLA initially demonstrated efficacy in promoting collagen synthesis, but limitations were noted in sustaining long-term collagen production. Understanding the dynamics of filler administration and its impact on tissue response is essential for optimizing outcomes in aesthetic surgery practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Final Report on the Safety and Efficacy of Poly-L-Lactic Acid Filler (Gana V) Injection for the Correction of Nasolabial Fold: A Double-Blind, Non-Inferiority, Randomized, Split-Face Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Through the final report of the trial, Gana V was non-inferior to Sculptra with respect to the NLF correction and safety profile. Gana V demonstrated its long-term efficacy through 24 months.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of total hip arthroplasty in patients with multiple epiphyseal dysplasia: a single centre study of eighty eight hips at a mean of sixteen year follow-up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: THA performed in patients with MED demonstrated excellent clinical outcomes with high implant survivorship at a mean follow-up of 16 years. Our findings suggest that THA is an effective and durable option for treating osteoarthritis secondary to MED.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced power structure for enhanced optical performance of AMOLED displays at low luminance levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To improve the image quality of active-matrix organic light-emitting diode (AMOLED) displays at low luminance levels, a novel power structure is proposed. Its effectiveness was validated by fabricating a 13-inch AMOLED panel with a tandem OLED and evaluating its optical performance. Compared to the conventional structure, the proposed structure reduced panel luminance deviation by 12% and color deviation by 41%, while also achieving a 41% reduction in hysteresis-induced color shift. As the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-sectional analysis of sociodemographic factors associated with self-reported and knowledge-based health literacy in Korea using data from KNHANES 2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Health literacy is a key factor influencing treatment adherence and outcomes. This study analyzed the 2023 Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (KNHANES) to explore the relationship between demographic and socioeconomic factors and health literacy. We examined associations between factors such as age, gender, residential region, education, and income with health literacy, which consisted of 10 questions and 1 knowledge assessment. Multiple linear regression was applied to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive outdoor UWB dataset: Static and dynamic measurements in LOS/NLOS environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study provides a comprehensive outdoor ultra-wideband (UWB) dataset to examine the multipath effects in line-of-sight and non-line-of-sight (NLOS) environments for real-time localization. Specifically, the dataset comprises static and dynamic datasets designed to capture discrete multipaths affected by antenna height, obstructions, and time-varying environments. A static dataset varies the antenna height and distance to analyze the multipath interference on the received signal strength and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tissue-specific iron levels modulate lipid peroxidation and the FLASH radiotherapy effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Iron is vital to living cells, playing a key role in cellular respiration, DNA synthesis, and various metabolic functions. Importantly, cancer cells have a higher dependency on iron compared to normal cells to support their rapid growth and survival. Due to this fact, tumors are more vulnerable to ferroptosis, an iron-dependent form of regulated cell death. Radiation therapy (RT), a standard treatment for many cancer patients, is known to induce ferroptosis. Ultra-high dose rate FLASH RT offers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the link between adolescent depression and precarious employment in adulthood: evidence from a sibling fixed effects analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight adolescent depressive symptoms as a significant early risk factor for employment precarity in adulthood. The results underscore the importance of early mental health interventions and suggest that improving emotional well-being and educational outcomes during adolescence may reduce long-term socioeconomic disadvantage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of bladder outlet obstruction on age-related changes in male bladder contractility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study revealed that BOO might act as a confounding variable in measuring the contractility of an aged bladder. Excluding the effect of BOO, bladder contractility significantly decreases with age. Therefore, when male LUTS are treated, changes in bladder contractility due to aging vary depending on BOO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antimicrobial resistance of <em>Mycoplasma genitalium</em> in Korea for two decades]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Currently, referred males exhibit a rapid increase in AMR, and the synergy between A2059G and S83I/R/N mutations raises concerns regarding the emergence of pan-drug-resistant M. genitalium, potentially leading to an irreversible crisis in treatment options in Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between truncal muscle mass index measured by bioelectrical impedance analysis and overactive bladder symptoms in men: A retrospective cross-sectional analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: sTMI, a BIA-based index reflecting truncal skeletal muscle normalized to BMI, is an independent predictor of moderate-to-severe OAB in men. This suggests a potential role of muscle composition in OAB pathophysiology and risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aquablation versus HoLEP: Propensity score matching analysis of functional outcomes and ejaculation preservation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Aquablation and HoLEP are both effective surgical options for BPH. Aquablation offers comparable symptom relief with significantly superior ejaculation preservation, making it particularly suitable for sexually active patients. HoLEP provides greater deobstructive efficacy, as evidenced by superior Qmax and PSA outcomes. These findings support individualized, patient-centered decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing consensus recommendations for metastatic hormone-sensitive prostate cancer in South Korea: A modified Delphi study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This Delphi consensus established local consensus on controversial areas of mHSPC management. The findings offer meaningful perspectives that may help shape future treatment strategies and encourage thoughtful reconsideration of reimbursement criteria to align evidence and clinical practice in South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of neoadjuvant chemotherapy on survival outcomes subsequent to radical cystectomy in pathological T0 bladder cancer patients: A multicenter large-scale analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with MIBC who achieved a pT0, NAC administration prior to RC has a positive impact on oncological prognosis. Although further prospective studies are needed for validation, the results of this study will confirm the importance of NAC in MIBC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contemporary management of metastatic urothelial carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Urothelial carcinoma, the most common malignancy of the urinary tract, presents a significant challenge, particularly in its metastatic stage, where prognosis remains poor despite advancements in treatment. Historically, platinum-based chemotherapy has been the standard first-line therapy, achieving moderate response rates but limited long-term survival. Recent breakthroughs have introduced immune checkpoint inhibitors, antibody-drug conjugates (ADCs), and targeted therapies as more effective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incorporating thermoreceptor responses in a local sensation model to account for setpoint adaptation during cold-to-warm transition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Berkeley comfort models are well-suited for addressing nonuniform, transient, and cold conditions owing to their comprehensible model structures. Integrating these models with thermoregulation models can aid in formulating energy-efficient local warming and heating, ventilation, and air conditioning (HVAC) operational strategies for occupant-centric winter conditioning in battery electric vehicles (BEVs)-a critical step toward their widespread adoption. However, the Berkeley local sensation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The lights and shades of the new treatment for rectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroprotective effects of Tanshinone IIA in an acrylamide-induced in-vivo zebrafish model: Behavioral, biochemical and molecular restoration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acrylamide is a neurotoxic chemical widely present in carbohydrate-rich foods due to thermal processing. Chronic exposure to acrylamide can lead to oxidative stress, neuroinflammation, and neurodegeneration, resulting in motor dysfunction and cognitive impairments. In this study, we evaluated the neuroprotective potential of Tanshinone IIA (TIIA), a bioactive compound derived from Salvia miltiorrhiza (Danshen), on an adult zebrafish model induced with acrylamide. Zebrafish were exposed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alterations in mitochondrial base editors enhance targeted editing efficiency for mouse model generation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) base editors are powerful tools for investigating mitochondrial diseases. However, their editing efficiency can vary significantly depending on the target site within the mtDNA. In this study, we developed two improved versions of the mitochondrial adenine base editor (Hifi-sTALED and αnHifi-sTALED) by modifying components other than the TadA8e-V28R deaminase variant. These enhancements significantly increased editing efficiency while preserving minimal off-target...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Young adult grandchildren's intergenerational and digital solidarity with grandparents and depressive symptoms during the pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Consequently, maintaining digital communication with grandparents compensated for the lack of in-person contact and contributed to the alleviation of depression among young adult grandchildren during the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insulin resistance and the risk of incident depression: the role of age, glycemic status, and adiposity in a prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Despite emerging evidence, the causal relationship between insulin resistance and depression remains controversial. This study aimed to investigate whether insulin resistance is associated with increased risk of incident depression and whether the association is affected by potential moderators.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progenitor cells, microglia, and non-coding RNAs: Orchestrators of glioblastoma pathogenesis and therapeutic resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma (GB) remains a major challenge owing to its extremely aggressive nature and resistance to conventional therapies. This review focuses on the intricate roles of progenitor cells, microglia, and non-coding RNAs (ncRNAs) in orchestrating GB pathogenesis and therapy resistance. Glioma stem cells (GSCs), derived from progenitor cells, are important drivers of tumor initiation and recurrence and exhibit remarkable plasticity and resistance to treatment. Microglia, the immune cells of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of LIPOSA-T pharmacopuncture on localized fat as a fat dissolving injection via regulation of fat metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Taken together, LIPOSA-T exerted the catabolic effects on fat deposition in obesity by regulating the glucose production, lipid synthesis and TAG hydrolysis in consistent with the prediction results. Based on the findings, LIPOSA-T pharmacopuncture is expected to be a dissolving injection for localized fat.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inverse-designed metasurfaces for wavefront restoration in under-display camera systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Under-display camera (UDC) systems enable full-screen displays in smartphones by embedding the camera beneath the display panel, eliminating the need for notches or punch holes. However, the periodic pixel structures of display panels introduce significant optical diffraction effects, leading to imaging artifacts and degraded visual quality. Conventional approaches to mitigate these distortions, such as deep learning-based image reconstruction, are often computationally expensive and unsuitable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896159/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mortality Related to Pneumonia and Diabetes Mellitus: A Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the need for integrated DM management and pneumonia prevention strategies. Targeted vaccination programs and early respiratory infection management could help reduce mortality in high-risk groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential Therapeutic Benefits of Pepper Fruit Extract on Hyperglycemia and Dyslipidemia in Obese Type 2 Diabetic Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Type 2 diabetes (T2D) is a complex metabolic disorder characterized by impaired glucose regulation and insulin resistance and frequently accompanied by obesity and dyslipidemia. The search for novel therapeutic agents to manage these metabolic parameters remains ongoing. Pepper fruit (cv. Meein) extract, a non-pungent Capsicum variant, has been proposed as a potential intervention for metabolic dysfunctions associated with T2D. Methods This study investigated the impact of pepper...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of different exercise prescription parameters on metabolic and inflammatory biomarkers in cancer patients: a systematic review, meta-analysis, and meta-regression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regular exercise confers modest but favorable effects on metabolic and inflammatory biomarkers in cancer patients. Meta-regression highlighted the importance of high-intensity aerobic exercise (HRR > 85%) in modulating IL-6, adiponectin, and IGF-1, as well as longer weekly exercise duration (>280 min/week) in improving TNF-α and IL-8. Mechanistically, high-intensity aerobic exercise may serve as a primary trigger for activating pathways that mediate metabolic and inflammatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Exercise preconditioning alleviates photothrombotic ischemic stroke in mice by orchestrating neutrophils]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fphys.2025.1580283.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting the Hippo/YAP Pathway: A Promising Approach for Cancer Therapy and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer represents a growing cause of death and a threat to public health worldwide; thus, there is an urgent need to understand its pathological mechanism and design effective therapies. The Hippo pathway regulates diverse cellular processes under physiological conditions; however, its dysregulation is associated with several types of cancer, including lung, pancreatic, colorectal, breast, and prostate cancer. Consequently, compounds targeting deregulated Hippo components represent potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of stroke in the United States of America, 1990-2021: a systematic analysis for the US burden of disease study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Despite improvements in age-standardized stroke incidence, mortality, and DALYs, the overall burden of stroke continues to increase owing to demographic shifts and the increasing prevalence of risk factors. There is a critical need for tailored and targeted interventions to address the evolving demographic and regional disparities and effectively reduce the US stroke burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel lipase-catalyzed synthesis of structured lipids from DHA-enriched glycerides and capric acid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structured lipids were successfully synthesized via a novel two-step enzymatic process. In the first step, docosahexaenoic acid (DHA) was enriched from tuna oil in the glyceride fractions by consecutive lipase-catalyzed reactions, hydrolysis, and ethanolysis. Following these processes, the DHA concentration increased from 26.7 mol% in the initial tuna oil to 66.2 mol% in the glyceride fraction. DHA-enriched glycerides were isolated from the reaction mixture obtained after the consecutive enzyme...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antioxidant addition to dough or frying oil: effects on the oxidative stability of deep-fat fried noodles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the oxidative stability of deep-fat fried noodles and frying oils when antioxidants were added either to the dough or to the frying oil. Hydrophilic and hydrophobic antioxidants, including α-tocopherol, ascorbyl palmitate, trolox, and ascorbic acid, were tested over 100 continuous frying cycles. Trolox showed the highest antioxidant activity when added to frying oil, while ascorbyl palmitate was more effective when added to dough. Ascorbic acid consistently exhibited low...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of small molecule surfactant type and oil phase composition on Ostwald ripening in model food emulsions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ostwald ripening destabilizes emulsified oils with significant water solubility, such as flavor oils, essential oils, and small triacylglycerols, by increasing oil droplet size over time. This study examined how small molecule surfactant types and oil phase composition affect Ostwald ripening rates in model oil-in-water emulsions. Emulsified n-decane was stabilized using two non-ionic surfactants with the different structures: polyoxyethylene (100) stearyl ether or poloxamer P407. The oil phase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of low-sodium mayonnaise using vegetable extract and high internal phase double emulsion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the physicochemical and sensory properties of mayonnaise formulated as a double emulsion (DE) with vegetable extracts and compared them with those of conventional oil-in-water (O/W) mayonnaise. A W(1)/O:W(2) ratio of 8:2 showed the highest stability, whereas a W(1):O ratio of 5:5 was selected as a balanced formulation with acceptable stability and reduced oil content. The polyglycerol polyricinoleate concentration was optimized at 2%, and the incorporation of vegetable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of emulsifier mixing and inhibitor type on Ostwald ripening of model food emulsions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined how the ability to inhibit Ostwald ripening varies with ripening inhibitor type and how interfacial composition affects inhibitor efficiency. Emulsions were stabilized using Brij S100 and S20, which differ in ethylene oxide unit numbers, while medium-chain triglyceride (MCT) and ester gum (EG), possessing distinct molecular structures, were incorporated as ripening inhibitors. Ostwald ripening rate decreased with a higher proportion of Brij S20 at the interfacial membrane....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prooxidative properties of aldehydes in oil-in-water emulsion on the aspects of physicochemical properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effects of aldehydes on the oxidative stability and physicochemical properties including oxygen solubility, surface tension, interfacial tension, and droplet sizes were evaluated in an oil-in-water (O/W) emulsion matrix. As amphiphilic aldehydes including propanal, hexanal, and nonanal added in O/W emulsion, headspace oxygen depletion and formation of conjugated diene and lipid hydroperoxides increased significantly (p < 0.05) compared to O/W emulsion without the addition of aldehydes, which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gene expression dynamics before and after zygotic gene activation in <em>Drosophila</em> early embryogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-transcriptional gene regulatory mechanisms are fundamental to the determination of gene expression dynamics and especially crucial for the earliest stages of animal development in which transcription is nearly silent. Here, we performed high-resolution total RNA sequencing and quantitative mass spectrometry analysis simultaneously on Drosophila maternal-to-zygotic transition (MZT). Further, this study is the first to report the proteome-wide quantitative changes in protein ubiquitination in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of chromatin accessibility associated with azacitidine response in higher-risk myelodysplastic neoplasms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Azacitidine, used in the treatment of higher-risk myelodysplastic neoplasms, is a DNA methyltransferase inhibitor that modifies epigenetic regulatory programs. The efficacy of azacitidine varies among patients, with approximately 50% of patients failing to respond. However, whether epigenomic factors affect responses to azacitidine has not been investigated. We examined chromatin accessibility in bone marrow cells from 23 treatment-naive patients with higher-risk myelodysplastic syndrome,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyaluronic acid filler injection for upper body aesthetic contouring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The demand for non-surgical upper body enhancement continues to grow, particularly among men seeking improved muscular definition without the risks of surgery or functional compromise. This case report presents a novel protocol using high G-prime hyaluronic acid (HA) fillers (Sedifill; Maypharm, Seoul, Republic of Korea) to contour the pectoralis major, deltoid, biceps, and brachioradialis in a 41-year-old male with moderate subcutaneous adiposity (BMI: 25 kg/m²; body fat: 21 %). A total of 134...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Environmental and genetic effects on phytochemical and nutritional composition of onion (<em>Allium cepa</em> L.) varieties in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Onions (Allium cepa L.) are widely recognized for their antioxidant properties, bioactive compounds such as flavonoids, organosulfur compounds (OSCs), and phenolics. This study evaluate the antioxidant activities, phytochemical composition, and nutrient variations of two onion varieties, Katamaru (KM) and Sunpower (SP), cultivated in two different locations, Muan and Changnyeong, Korea. The antioxidant activity was assessed through enzymatic and non-enzymatic parameters, including peroxidase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of body composition and cardiovascular fitness with hypertension in a middle-aged adults: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the significant association between abdominal obesity, reduced cardiovascular fitness, and hypertension in middle-aged Korean adults. Abdominal obesity and low cardiovascular fitness were identified as independent risk factors for hypertension in this population. These results suggest that weight management to reduce abdominal obesity and regular physical activity to promote cardiovascular fitness are key to the prevention and management of hypertension.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The longitudinal impacts of secondary caregiver networks on primary caregiver's social isolation and depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Caregiving for older adults often leads to increased social isolation and depression among primary caregivers. Secondary caregiver networks (SCNs) may provide crucial support, potentially mitigating these adverse outcomes. This study aimed to identify the SCN support patterns and examine their impacts on primary caregivers' social isolation and depression over 2 years, as well as potential differences in the associations by gender and race.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-eosinophilic esophagitis eosinophilic gastrointestinal diseases are more prevalent than eosinophilic esophagitis in Korean children: from a multicenter study based on new diagnostic criteria and nomenclature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights the distinctive epidemiology of pediatric EGIDs in Korea, where non-EoE EGIDs are more prevalent than EoE, contrasting with Western reports. Peripheral eosinophil counts and fecal calprotectin levels were significantly higher in non-EoE EGIDs with EI than in EoE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepBiome: A Phylogenetic Tree Informed Deep Neural Network for Microbiome Data Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Evidence linking the microbiome to human health is rapidly growing. The microbiome profile has the potential as a novel predictive biomarker for many diseases. However, tables of bacterial counts are typically sparse, and bacteria are classified within a hierarchy of taxonomic levels, ranging from species to phylum. Existing tools focus on identifying microbiome associations at either the community level or a specific, pre-defined taxonomic level. Incorporating the evolutionary relationship...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoelectrocatalytic Reduction of <mml:math xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"> <mml:mrow><mml:msub><mml:mi>CO</mml:mi> <mml:mstyle><mml:mn>2</mml:mn></mml:mstyle> </mml:msub> </mml:mrow> </mml:math> to Formate Using Immobilized Molecular Manganese Catalysts on Oxidized Porous Silicon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The selective reduction of CO 2 to formate using molecular catalysts immobilized on high surface area porous silicon is described. Manganese complexes of the form (^(R)bpy)Mn(CO)(3)Br (bpy = 2,2'-bipyridine) were prepared with silatrane groups on the bpy ligand for attachment to oxide-coated porous silicon (SiO(x)-porSi). SiO(x)-porSi wafers were formed by heating hydrogen-terminated p-type porous silicon wafers under air and the manganese complexes were immobilized on SiO(x)-porSi by heating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypokalemic Periodic Paralysis in a Patient With Primary Sjögren's Syndrome and Distal Renal Tubular Acidosis: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: An accurate diagnosis of HPP secondary to dRTA and Sjögren's syndrome requires high clinical suspicion. Prompt recognition and intervention, including immunotherapy and balanced electrolyte replacement, can prevent profound neuromuscular complications and improve patient outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40894112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A butyrate-producing synbiotic mitigates intestinal inflammation in a murine colitis model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) is a chronic condition characterized by intestinal inflammation and gut dysbiosis, with limited treatment options primarily focused on immune-modulating therapies. Among potential therapeutic agents, butyrate has emerged as a promising candidate due to its anti-inflammatory and gut-restorative properties. However, direct administration of butyrate poses significant challenges, including its rapid absorption, uneven distribution within the intestinal tract, and an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to improve the care of decompensated cirrhosis: the intervention model for chronic disease management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating the complexity of colorectal liver metastasis: molecular profiling and tumor sidedness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The risk of hepatocellular carcinoma recurrence after liver transplantation increases with locoregional therapies in patients initially within Milan criteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The optimal timing of transplantation for hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is still under debate regarding the tumor biology and locoregional control with various treatments. We designed this study to find out what kind of factors affect the post-transplantation outcome focusing on the timing of transplantation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to: Germline and Somatic <em>BRCA1/2</em> Mutations in Breast Cancer Treatment Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing Nature: Computational and Experimental Insights Into Ipomoea obscura Metabolites for Bladder Cancer Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ipomoea obscura (L.), a medicinal plant from the Convolvulaceae family, has been traditionally used to treat various ailments. This study evaluated the in vitro cytotoxicity of its ethanolic leaf extract against human bladder cancer T24 cells and investigated its phytochemical constituents through computational methods. The extract exhibited dose-dependent cytotoxicity with an IC(50) of 82.10 µg/mL, comparable to doxorubicin (75.04 µg/mL). Among 35 screened phytocompounds, kaempferol, oleic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893046/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in antiviral treatment rate for hepatitis B virus before hepatocellular carcinoma diagnosis: a nationwide Korean study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AVT rate before HCC diagnosis significantly increased over the past 10 years in Korea. Further efforts are needed to improve the AVT rate in elderly patients with HBV-related HCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis, Radiolabeling, and Evaluation of a Dimeric Fibroblast Activation Protein Inhibitor with a Triazine Linker]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dimeric fibroblast activation protein inhibitor (FAPI) radioligands are promising candidates for theranostic applications because of their enhanced tumor uptake and prolonged retention compared to monomeric radioligands. Several linker strategies have been investigated to connect two FAPI motifs and a radiometal chelator in a dimer design. In this study, we report the development of a novel dimeric FAPI radioligand, [^(68)Ga]Ga-1, which utilizes a triazine core as a trifunctional linker. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40893020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gel-Based Ionic Circuits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionic circuits have emerged as a promising candidate to bridge the gap between biological and artificial systems by applying the mechanically compliant and adaptive nature of gels as ionic conductors. Gel-based ionic circuits exploit the intrinsic characteristics of ions, such as their mass, diversity, and local accumulation, to achieve selectivity, hysteresis, and chemical-electric signal transduction. Their dynamic and nonlinear behaviors not only emulate traditional solid-state electronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How PARTHENOPE Charts the Course Toward Precision DAPT: Navigating Future Science in Antiplatelet Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Powered High-Performance WS<sub>2</sub> Photodetector via a Monolithic p-i-n Homojunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lateral homojunction photodetectors (PDs) offer high responsivity and fast response, yet challenges in tailoring carrier concentrations in two-dimensional transition-metal dichalcogenides (TMDs) have limited their implementation. Here, we demonstrate a high-performance self-powered monolithic lateral p-i-n homojunction PD using multilayer WS(2). To our knowledge, this study is the first report of achieving tunable, multilevel compensation doping via WO(X) formation using only time-controlled and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of body composition on prognostic stratification and survival in periampullary carcinoma after pancreatoduodenectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative body composition is associated with OS in patients with periampullary carcinoma. Integrating preoperative SMI status and postoperative SMI changes provide a more nuanced prognostic stratification. Gender-specific body composition analysis may improve prognostic accuracy and postoperative management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genomic and Phenotypic Evaluation of the Gliadin-Degrading Probiotic Bacillus amyloliquefaciens EG025 from Cheonggukjang for Celiac Disease Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacillus amyloliquefaciens EG025 was isolated from cheonggukjang, a traditional Korean fermented soybean paste. Among multiple isolates from diverse fermented foods, B. amyloliquefaciens EG025 uniquely exhibited potent gliadin-degrading activity, a trait with the potential to attenuate the immunogenicity of gluten peptides implicated in celiac disease. B. amyloliquefaciens EG025 maintained robust enzymatic activity across a wide pH spectrum (neutral to alkaline) and, remarkably, retained over...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging renal mitochondrial dysfunction in chronic kidney disease: a repurposed role for [<sup>99m</sup>Tc]Tc-MIBI SPECT/CT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: [^(99m)Tc]Tc-MIBI kidney SPECT/CT effectively detected renal mitochondrial dysfunction in patients with CKD, suggests its potential as a noninvasive imaging biomarker. SUV may serve as a quantitative parameter for assessing renal mitochondrial dysfunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling of kidney allograft rejection using hiPSC-derived kidney organoids and HLA-mismatched PBMCs: an in vitro co-culture system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study is to establish an in vitro co-culture system to model allograft rejection using kidney organoids system derived from human induced pluripotent stem cells (hiPSCs). We co-cultured kidney organoids derived from wild-type hiPSCs with HLA-mismatched peripheral blood mononuclear cells (PBMCs) from healthy controls (HC) for 24 h. To assess allogeneic rejection modeling, we measured the expression of HLA molecules, (HLA-ABC and HLA-DR), and evaluated cellular damage in the kidney...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An evaluation of zanidatamab, a novel, anti-HER2 biparatopic antibody, for the treatment of biliary tract cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Zanidatamab is a humanized biparatopic IgG antibody that selectively inhibits HER2 signaling pathway by targeting two distinct epitopes in the extracellular domains II and IV of HER2. Zanidatamab received accelerated approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration for the treatment of HER2-positive (immunohistochemistry [IHC] 3+) biliary tract cancer (BTC) in November 2024. Additionally, zanidatamab received approval for the treatment of HER2 IHC 3+ BTC from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Exosome-Augmented Microneedling and Laser Therapies in Full-Face Skin Rejuvenation: A Split-Face Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Exosomes enhanced skin rejuvenation with microneedling and CO2 laser. Picosecond laser showed strong results overall, though exosome benefit was less distinct. Larger studies are warranted to optimize delivery and confirm long-term regenerative effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40892048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Node Reporting and Data System Evaluation of Axillary Nodes in Invasive Ductal and Lobular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Although the Node Reporting and Data System (Node-RADS) offers a standardized method for assessing lymph node metastasis, its performance may vary according to the histologic type of breast cancer. Purpose To evaluate the applicability of the Node-RADS score in assessing axillary lymph node involvement in patients with invasive ductal carcinoma (IDC) or invasive lobular carcinoma (ILC). Materials and Methods In this retrospective study, data from consecutive women with pathologically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Quantitative and Qualitative Visual Feedback on Motor Learning in Male Novices During a Badminton Underhand-Clear Striking Task]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the biomechanics of striking tasks, different types of visual feedback for the upper extremities influence motor learning and control in distinct ways. Quantitative feedback (QN), which provides precise numerical data, and qualitative feedback (QL), which offers descriptive or interpretive guidance, may facilitate different aspects of motor skill acquisition. Given that ballistic motor skills, such as the badminton underhand-clear stroke, require not only rapid and coordinated movement...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cryogen-free variable-temperature Kelvin probe force microscopy for probing local chemical potential in van der Waals heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the development of a variable-temperature Kelvin probe force microscopy (KPFM) system based on a Gifford-McMahon cryocooler, which enables stable and highly sensitive operation across a broad temperature range. The system integrates a custom-designed phase-locked loop, automatic gain control, and compact passive vibration isolation stages, effectively suppressing mechanical vibrations intrinsic to cryostats. We demonstrate the system's performance using a monolayer graphene (MLG)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acquisition phase-specific contribution of climbing fiber transmission to cerebellum-dependent motor memory in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climbing fiber (CF) transmission from the inferior olive (IO) triggers complex spikes (Cs) in Purkinje cells (PCs) driven by a burst of calcium spikes. In the context of motor learning, especially the compensatory optic response, CF transmission serves as an instructive signal selectively conveyed to PCs. While the significance of CF input in motor memory formation is widely acknowledged, a comprehensive understanding of its distinct contribution across different temporal windows, spanning from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal conductivity of individual single-crystalline F<sub>16</sub>CuPc nanoribbons]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic semiconductors are widely used in flexible electronics, optoelectronic devices, and thermoelectric systems. Among them, copper hexadecafluorophthalocyanine (F(16)CuPc), an n-type organic semiconductor, exhibits excellent chemical and thermal stability, making it suitable for a range of device applications. As device architectures scale down to the nanoscale, understanding the intrinsic thermal transport properties of such materials becomes critical for effective thermal management. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nkx3.2 Inhibits Retinal Degeneration by Modulating Inflammation and Cell Death in RPE]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Nkx3.2 can suppress inflammatory responses and necroptic cell death in RPE. By employing these mechanisms, Nkx3.2 may play a significant role in inhibiting retinal degeneration caused by aging and oxidative stress.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-volatile resistive switching characteristics in Cu<sub>2-<em>x</em></sub>S-based memristor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memristors have emerged as promising candidates for high-density non-volatile memory and neuromorphic computing due to their simple structure and low power operation. However, conventional memristive switching devices often require a lot of energy for fabrication processes and high operating voltages, which not only hinder integration with flexible substrates but also impose substantial limitations on overall energy efficiency. In this study, we demonstrated a memristive switching device based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vibrational asymmetry across heptad positions in coiled-coil IR spectra: A simulation study of isotope-labeled amide I modes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Isotope-edited infrared (IR) spectroscopy is a powerful tool for probing site-specific structures and dynamics within proteins. However, the interpretation is often complicated by spectral congestion and environmental heterogeneity. In this study, vibrational exciton models combined with molecular dynamics simulations are employed to examine the frequency distributions and IR spectra of isotope-labeled local modes (ILMs) in parallel coiled-coil dimers. Based on the difference spectra obtained by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidation State Manipulation of NiO<sub>x</sub> for High Performance and Light-Soaking Stability of Perovskite Solar Modules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NiO(x) is widely used for hole-transporting layers in p-i-n-type perovskite solar cells (PSCs) due to its stability, wide bandgap (≈3.5 eV), and solution processability. However, during solution processing, oxygen exposure can induce non-stoichiometry, forming Ni^(≥3 +). While Ni^(≥3 +) enhances hole mobility, it also promotes redox reactions at the interface, undermining long-term stability. To utilize the improved mobility without sacrificing stability, bilayer NiO(x) films with controlled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Review of Electrochemical Metallization and Valence Change Mechanisms in Filamentary Resistive Switching of Halide Perovskite-Based Memory Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Halide perovskites (HPs) are gaining significant attention in data storage, particularly for their application in resistive random-access memory (ReRAM) systems. Their exceptional electrical and light absorption properties position them as potentially revolutionary materials for the memory industry. The use of HPs as resistive switching (RS) materials in ReRAMs is driven by their observed current-voltage hysteresis. This hysteresis is linked to the formation of defects within the HP crystals and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative delirium and quality of recovery in older patients undergoing gastrectomy under general anaesthesia: a reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vessel segmentation for <mml:math xmlns:mml="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML"> <mml:semantics><mml:mrow><mml:mi>χ</mml:mi></mml:mrow> <mml:annotation>$$ \chi $$</mml:annotation></mml:semantics> </mml:math> -separation in quantitative susceptibility mapping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed method has the potential to facilitate various applications, offering reliable analysis through the generation of a high-quality vessel mask.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Exacerbation of Allergic Inflammation by Combined Exposure to Air-pollutants in a Murine Model of Allergic Rhinitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Coexposure to PM2.5, formaldehyde, and zinc aggravated allergic inflammation in an OVA-induced murine model, with PM2.5 + zinc showing the strongest synergistic effects. These findings highlight the importance of pollutant-pollutant interactions in allergic airway diseases and underscore the need for further studies to elucidate longterm health impacts and human relevance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative Full Thickness Macular Hole Formation after Vitrectomy for the Removal of Epiretinal Membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ERM with LH was a significant factor for MH formation, while thin preoperative CMT showed a marginal association. At the time of MH detection, ERM and CME were observed in most cases, suggesting that tangential traction caused by postoperative ERM or, postoperative CME may represent possible etiologies for MH formation. In patients with ERM with LH or thin CMT, the possibility of MH formation after ERM surgery should be taken into account and careful monitoring is needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adaptive Strategies in Expertise: Optimizing Movement Trajectory for Perception Accuracy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the traces of movement trajectories for perception accuracy in expert performance, focusing on table tennis. Twenty participants (10 experts and 10 novices) performed self-generated movements for extended haptic accuracy tasks, and their performance was analyzed for absolute error and movement trajectory. The results reveal that the expert participants exhibited more movement entropy than novices, strategically sacrificing trajectory predictability to enhance haptic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modelling Assumptions in Cost-Effectiveness Analysis of Antiviral Therapy for High Viremic Indeterminate Phase Chronic Hepatitis B]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891217/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus statement on peri-implant disease from the Korean Academy of Periodontology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This consensus report presents the first official position statement of the Korean Academy of Periodontology on peri-implant diseases, issued in response to South Korea's rapidly aging population and the associated rise in peri-implant disease management. It reviews the prevalence, classification, and definition of peri-implant diseases, emphasizing that these conditions progress more aggressively and unpredictably than periodontal diseases. The report also identifies systemic and local risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging the gap: the essential collaboration between orthodontists and periodontists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Analysis of Growth and Neurodevelopmental Outcomes in Very Low Birth Weight Infants With Congenital Anomalies Over Three Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Congenital anomalies pose significant challenges to the growth and neurodevelopment of VLBWIs. Early and individualized interventions, structured neurodevelopmental follow-up, and multidisciplinary care are essential for improving long-term outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40891162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250903034026&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bench-Stable Copper Complex for Trifluoromethylation and <sup>18</sup>F-Labeling of Aryl Iodides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we report an efficient and highly active copper complex ([(TMPhen)(2)Cu(I)][O(2)CCF(2)Cl]) for the trifluoromethylation of aryl iodides. This bench-stable copper complex converts aryl iodides into their corresponding CF(3) derivatives in high yields within 1 h. The protocol is also well-suited for aromatic [^(18)F]trifluoromethylation, offering a rapid and efficient approach for the development of new radiopharmaceuticals within 20 min.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40890990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation of 222-nm ultraviolet C irradiation bactericidal effect on the surgical field in a rabbit model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultraviolet C (UV-C) not only has a bactericidal effect, but is also cytotoxic; however, UV-C at a wavelength of 222 nm with a high absorption coefficient for proteins is considered safe. We have previously reported the safety of 222-nm UV-C irradiation in humans and rabbits. This study evaluated the bactericidal effect of 222-nm UV-C irradiation on exposed surgical fields. Sixteen-week-old female rabbits were used, and the exposed area on their backs was sprayed with a bacterial solution from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lasting impact of undergraduate operating room shadowing on novice nurses: a ChatGPT-supported qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A single OR shadowing experience during undergraduate education can evoke deep emotional responses and support early professional identity formation among novice nurses. The integration of structured reflection or guided debriefing may enhance these effects. Findings support the inclusion of observational experiences, even brief ones, in undergraduate nursing curricula as a means to cultivate ethical sensitivity, interprofessional awareness, and reflective practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SDS-EDTA-treated chromatography paper strips for sampling and transportation of monkeypox virus, varicella zoster virus and herpes simplex 1 and 2 viruses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mpox is a viral zoonotic disease characterized by flu-like symptoms followed by rash, which can be difficult to distinguish from other rash-presenting infections. Laboratory diagnosis is essential for confirming monkeypox virus (MPXV) infection; However, challenges in specimen transport and storage in endemic regions, especially in rural areas with limited infrastructure, hinder timely diagnosis. This study evaluates the use of SDS-EDTA-treated chromatography paper strips for testing different...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A roadmap for navigating child health research data sharing across Canada and beyond - building on UCAN CAN-DU]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898230/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of the kakaritsuke-yakuzaishi (family pharmacist) system for underage individuals in Japan: a cohort study using a health insurance claims database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrated that the family pharmacist system improved TDDI prevention among underage individuals. However, its effectiveness was consistent regardless of the characteristics related to the utilization of the family pharmacist system, indicating that the trend of positively applying the system to those with these characteristics was not supported. The operation of the system may be reconsidered for the efficient allocation of medical resources.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Career advancement and fertility intention among working women in Japan: a cross-sectional survey study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Job stability, job type, career motivation, confidence, and proactive health management are associated with fertility intention among working women in Japan. Women assured of career advancement may also be more inclined to plan for childbearing, highlighting the importance of workplace policies supporting career development and family planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Loneliness and analgesic overuse among low-dose estrogen-progestin users in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To our knowledge, this is the first detailed study to investigate concomitant analgesic use and overuse among LEP users. Loneliness was found to be prevalent in this population and was associated with concomitant analgesic use, potentially reflecting underlying patterns of frequent or habitual analgesic intake. Furthermore, concomitant analgesic overuse was linked to conditions such as endometriosis and low back pain, underscoring the importance of medication monitoring that takes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QTL-seq identifies NAL1 and OsOFP19 as additive regulators of tiller number in rice (Oryza sativa L.)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Collectively, these findings advance our understanding of the genetic regulation of tillering in rice and provide molecular tools for improving plant architecture and yield in upland rice varieties cultivated under lowland conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel role of isosorbide as a biostimulant in enhancing plant growth and development in Arabidopsis thaliana]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sustainable agriculture faces growing challenges in boosting food production while minimizing environmental impact, highlighting the need for innovative solutions. The "plastics to fertilizers" concept, which converts poly(isosorbide carbonate) (PIC) derived from plastic waste into urea and isosorbide, presents a promising approach, as we have previously reported (Abe in Green Chem 23:9030-9037, 2021). While urea's role in plant nutrition is well established, the effect of isosorbide on plant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unintended metabolites in Monascus pilosus (beni-koji) cultures resulting from Penicillium adametzioides contamination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The health hazards, including kidney damage, were reported following the ingestion of a health food product, so-called "foods with functional claims (FFC)'', containing beni-koji (red yeast rice), a product of Monascus pilosus very recently in Japan. Puberulic acid (PA) was detected as an unexpected compound in FFC products, and further investigation was required to identify additional unintended compounds and determine the route of PA contamination. To date, we have reported the possibility...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of patients aged 70 years or younger with aggressive ATL at core hospitals for ATL treatment in Tokyo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adult T-cell leukemia-lymphoma (ATL) is one of the most intractable peripheral T-cell neoplasms caused by human T-cell leukemia virus type I (HTLV-1) infection. Recently, the incidence of HTLV-1 infection and ATL has increased in non-endemic metropolitan areas in Japan. This retrospective study evaluated the clinical features and outcomes of patients with aggressive ATL aged 70 years or younger treated at a core hospital in Tokyo between 2004 and 2016. The median follow-up was 124.4 months for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of venetoclax and ibrutinib in Japanese patients with relapsed/refractory mantle cell lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Long-term follow-up of ibrutinib plus venetoclax showed prolonged efficacy and a well-tolerated safety profile in Japanese patients with R/R MCL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real world efficacy of naltrexone/bupropion for weight management in obesity and after bariatric surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Real-world data show that NB treatment is equally effective in surgery-naive patients and in patients experiencing weight regain after bariatric surgery, regardless of the maximal dose administered.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning model for screening causes of activated partial thromboplastin time prolongation using clot waveform analysis at multiple wavelengths]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Activated partial thromboplastin time (APTT) prolongation occurs due to coagulation factor deficiencies/inhibitors, lupus anticoagulant (LA), and anticoagulant-taking, necessitating discrimination through further testing. Clot waveform analysis (CWA) can discriminate causes while measuring APTT, but conventional CWA exhibits moderate accuracy due to visual judgement and limited parameter use. We applied deep learning (DL) techniques to huge numerical data constituting clot waveforms and their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Indo-European Cognate Relationships dataset]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Indo-European Cognate Relationships (IE-CoR) dataset is an open-access relational dataset showing how related, inherited words ('cognates') pattern across 160 languages of the Indo-European family. IE-CoR is intended as a benchmark dataset for computational research into the evolution of the Indo-European languages. It is structured around 170 reference meanings in core lexicon, and contains 25731 lexeme entries, analysed into 4981 cognate sets. Novel, dedicated structures are used to code...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced antibody production in Chinese hamster ovary cell cultures supplemented with barley shochu distillation by-product supernatant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibody production in Chinese hamster ovary (CHO) cell culture was enhanced by supplementing the culture medium with barley shochu distillation by-product supernatant (BX2). To predict antibody production following BX2 addition, fed-batch culture experiments were conducted under varying BX2 conditions using a response surface methodology. BX2 supplementation was predicted to improve antibody production by 138 %, 146 %, 120 %, and 240 % in IgG-producing CHO-MK1, CHO-MK2, CHO-DG44, and Fc-fusion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Locus heterogeneity in the mechanism underlying the superior fermentation performances of phylogenetically distant sake yeasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sake yeasts, Saccharomyces cerevisiae strains isolated from Japanese sake fermentation tanks, exhibit superior fermentation performance to that of other yeast strains. Although the exceptional abilities of the modern sake yeast strain K701 have been extensively investigated, those of phylogenetically distant classical sake yeasts remain largely understudied. In this study, we aimed to clarify the mechanism underlying the superior fermentation ability of the classical sake yeast strain Km67 by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The myth of circularity: assessing vapour capture for volatile anaesthetics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FLASH-enabled Proton SBRT for a challenging case of spine metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: The FLASH effect, characterized by potential sparing of organs at risk (OAR) through ultra-high dose rate irradiation, has garnered significant attention for its capability to address indications previously untreatable at conventional dose rates (DR) with hypofractionated schemes. While considerable biological research is needed to understand the FLASH effect and determine the FLASH modifying factors (FMF) for individual OARs, treatment planning studies have also emerged. This study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40897368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Powdered camel milk production and changes occurring along the processing steps and storage conditions: A comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spray drying offers high-quality camel milk powder with a good nutritional and techno-functional profile. However, the thermal stress can cause whey protein denaturation, reducing the effectiveness of the bioactive components of the milk and compromising its health benefits. Camel milk caseins are more sensitive to heat, while its whey proteins exhibit greater resistance compared to those in bovine milk. The drying air temperature is crucial in determining the nutritional profile and dehydration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survival of patients with squamous cell carcinoma of the breast compared with invasive ductal carcinoma by biological subtype: A matched analysis of the Japanese national clinical database-breast cancer registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Within the triple-negative subtype, SCC histology was associated with a significantly worse prognosis than IDC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing a predictive model for rapid stroke diagnosis via blood using mid-infrared spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ATR-FTIR spectroscopy is a promising and minimally invasive approach for rapid stroke detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combining the antenatal risk questionnaire and the Edinburgh Postnatal depression scale as a psychosocial risk assessment tool in Danish antenatal care. A descriptive study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We identified women at increased risk of mental health problems who were not identified by the current triage process. Combining ANRQ and EPDS assessment may be an important part of a model for early identification of pregnant women with special needs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication and characterization of electrospun polycaprolactone/<em>Urechis unicinctus</em> derived-ECM composite scaffolds for small-diameter vascular grafts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Small-diameter vascular grafts (SDVGs; ≤6 mm inner diameter) often fail due to thrombosis, poor endothelialization, and low patency. To overcome these limitations, we developed electrospun composite scaffolds incorporating decellularized Urechis unicinctus ECM (UdECM), a marine invertebrate source rich in collagen, glycosaminoglycans, and elastin. UdECM was blended with polycaprolactone (PCL) at 1, 5, and 10 wt% and electrospun into fibrous matrices. We characterized scaffold hydrophilicity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bracing for scoliosis in children with cerebral palsy-a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Brace therapy offers temporary relief for physical and daily life challenges associated with cerebral palsy. However, its effects are not sustained, necessitating operative techniques for long-term management. This was a systematic review of Level-II studies or Level-I studies with inconsistent results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide association mapping for early maturity in kintoki bean (<em>Phaseolus vulgaris</em> L.)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Japanese red or white common bean (Phaseolus vulgaris L.) cultivars, used to make sweetened boiled beans, are called "kintoki" beans. Kintoki beans are planted to precede winter wheat for crop rotation in Hokkaido, northern Japan. Therefore, early maturity is an important trait for them. The aim of this study was to map the genomic region associated with days to maturity in kintoki beans by genome-wide association study (GWAS). Significant single nucleotide polymorphisms associated with days to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of DNA markers for assisted selection of cassava resistant to cassava mosaic disease (CMD)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cassava is an important staple crop in tropical and subtropical regions. Cassava mosaic disease (CMD) is one of the most dangerous diseases affecting cassava production in Africa. Since the first reported in Southeast Asia in 2015, the CMD prevalence has become a concern in Southeast Asia. To combat it, CMD resistance has been introduced from African cassava into Asian elite cultivars. However, efficient DNA markers for the selection of CMD resistance are not available. The CMD2 locus confers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Macrocycles composed of biphenylene and butadiyne units with antiaromatic character]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, we report the synthesis and characterization of π-conjugated macrocycles, with diameters over 2.4 nanometers, composed of biphenylene and butadiyne units. Specifically, biphenylene-2,7-diyl-butadiyne-1,4-diyl (BB) macrocycles were synthesized via the intermolecular Hay coupling reaction of a 2,7-diethynylbiphenylene derivative. The BB macrocycles exhibited absorption bands extending up to ∼600 nm and emitted red luminescence. Moreover, scanning tunneling microscopy observations revealed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision nutrition across climates: decoding diet, tradition, and genomic adaptations from South Asia to the Arctic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human populations have developed distinct genetic adaptations to diet in response to changes in lifestyle and environments in which they live. Particularly contrasting patterns of dietary adaptations are expected in populations living in tropical versus extreme cold environments. This article explores the genetic, dietary, and microbiome-related adaptations in populations of South Asia and the Arctic. We review adaptations related to high-carbohydrate, plant-based diets in South Asians and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40896188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examination of the gait evaluation index using shoes with built-in motion sensors: intra-rater reliability during comfortable walking and fastest walking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[Purpose] To determine the intra-rater reliability of gait evaluation data obtained using shoes equipped with built-in motion sensors. [Participants and Methods] Thirteen healthy adults were recruited and gait evaluation data (stride length, stride speed, stride duration, stance phase duration, and swing phase duration) were obtained during comfortable and fastest possible walking. Gait evaluation was repeated after a one-week interval. The intra-class correlation coefficients and systematic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between walking space and physical activity for hospitalized patients with stroke: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[Purpose] This study aimed to investigate the associations among physical activity, sedentary patterns, and walking spaces in patients hospitalized after stroke. [Participants and Methods] This cross-sectional observational study included 52 patients (mean age, 72.6 ± 11.3 years) hospitalized following stroke. A triaxial accelerometer worn at the waist on the nonparetic side was used to estimate the time spent in sedentary behavior, light intensity physical activity, and moderate-to-vigorous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of surface ligands on the surface chemical states and photoluminescence characteristics in cesium lead bromide perovskite nanocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the results of our study on the relationship between the surface chemical states, which are influenced by ligands, and photoluminescence (PL) characteristics in cesium lead halide perovskite nanocrystals (NCs). NCs were synthesized via the Ligand-Assisted Reprecipitation (LARP) and Ultrasonic-Assisted (URSOA) methods, which were able to produce NCs with and without ligands. Although both synthesis methods used similar precursor composition and processing steps, the resulting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pitfalls of a Drug-Dispensing Audit Support System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dispensing audit support systems that authenticate pharmaceuticals via barcodes have been introduced into clinical practice to prevent dispensing errors, yet they occasionally generate false warnings, complicating clinical usage. This study sought to identify drugs prone to weight-error false warnings in the C-correct II^(®) dispensing audit support system and to clarify its operational problems. We investigated the drugs that caused false weight-error warnings in the system, confirming that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of cardiac surgery in a patient with antiphospholipid syndrome using the heparin-activated clotting time titration curve and thromboelastography: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients with antiphospholipid syndrome undergoing cardiac surgery are at increased risk for thrombotic and hemorrhagic complications. We present here the management of a 68-year-old man with antiphospholipid syndrome who was scheduled for aortic valve replacement. A heparin sensitivity test was performed after anesthesia induction, and a calibration curve for blood heparin concentration and activated clotting time was created. We set a target activated clotting time of 444 s, corresponding to a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40895394/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250903034024&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>