<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:51:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroinflammatory and transcriptional dynamics during SARS-CoV-2 infection in KRT18-hACE2 mouse brain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Neurological complications are increasingly recognized as a significant consequence of COVID-19; however, time-resolved, brain-specific characterization of transcriptional alterations underlying SARS-CoV-2-associated neuroinflammation and neuronal injury remain limited. We hypothesized that brain transcriptional responses evolve dynamically during acute SARS-CoV-2 infection, resulting in temporal transcriptional programs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decoding the brain's ATG8 paralog code: LC3-GABARAP specialization at synapses and the astrocyte-neuron interface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macroautophagy is essential for the long-term health of neurons and astrocytes in the central nervous system (CNS). The six mammalian ATG8 paralogs (LC3A/B/C and GABARAP/GABARAPL1/L2) exhibit an emerging "ATG8 code"-a division of labor among these proteins that assigns specialized roles in the autophagy pathway to each paralog, enabling fine-tuned proteostasis at synapses and the astrocyte-neuron interface. This review synthesizes how LC3 versus GABARAP mediate distinct steps of autophagy (LC3...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational identification of natural inhibitors targeting GroEL in <em>Leptospira interrogans</em>: an integrative virtual screening and molecular dynamics approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Leptospirosis is a zoonotic disease caused by Leptospira interrogans and represents a major public health and veterinary concern. The persistence of the pathogen is closely associated with biofilm formation, yet targeted therapeutics are currently unavailable. The GroEL chaperonin, a conserved protein involved in biofilm formation and immunogenicity, was investigated as a potential therapeutic target.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and Future Challenges in Monolithic 3D Integrated Logic, Power, and Optoelectronics Technologies for Tightly Interconnected Intelligent Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The emergence of ultralarge-scale hardware systems for artificial intelligence is driving demand for high-performance heterogeneous integration. At the heart of these systems lies the maximization of computational capability through high data bandwidth, necessitating interconnects that either increase the number of links between tiers and chips or enhance the data transfer rate of each link. Monolithic three-dimensional (M3D) integration, particularly with two-dimensional (2D) materials, offers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Astragalus membranaceus sprouts and their unique constituents regulate reactive oxygen species production, inflammation-related senescence-associated secretory phenotype components, and extracellular matrix in fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging involves a gradual decline in physiological functions and increased susceptibility to damage and disease. Suppressing reactive oxygen species (ROS) production and inflammatory responses is critical for delaying age-related cellular decline. Astragalus membranaceus is one of the important health functional foods worldwide due to its health benefits, including antioxidant and immunomodulatory properties. While the root is the most commonly utilized part, other plant parts remain largely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>ERJ Open Research</em> in 2026: progress and future directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As we enter our 11th year, ERJ Open Research celebrates record interest. We are dedicated to becoming the best-open access respiratory journal, balancing high-quality research with inclusivity and speed to serve the community. https://bit.ly/4bqyvLh.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From coordination to function: Inorganic insights into metalloproteins and metallopeptides in biosystems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deubiquitinase USP2 promotes hepatic stellate cell activation via p300 stabilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatic stellate cell (HSC) activation is a central mechanism in liver fibrosis, with histone acetyltransferase p300 acting as a pivotal transcriptional cofactor. To define upstream regulators of p300 stability during HSC activation, we performed a deubiquitinase inhibitor screen in activated HSCs and identified ubiquitin carboxyl-terminal hydrolase 2 (USP2) as a p300 deubiquitinase. Single-cell RNA sequencing of fibrotic human liver tissues revealed USP2 as the most specifically expressed USP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plant-based oil composition modulates saltiness and bitterness in sodium-reduced double emulsions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of plant-based oil composition on the physicochemical properties, sensory perception, and digestive stability of sodium-reduced emulsions. Four edible oils (perilla, sesame, canola, and olive) were evaluated in both oil-in-water (O/W) and high internal phase double emulsion (HIPDE) systems. O/W emulsions contained either NaCl or KCl, whereas HIPDEs encapsulated KCl in the internal aqueous phase (W₁) and NaCl in the external phase (W₂). In O/W emulsions, oils...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma-driven oxidative modification of quercetin and its antibacterial application on cherry tomato]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quercetin, a widely distributed natural flavonol, is well known for its antioxidant properties, but can act as a pro-oxidant under certain conditions, promoting oxidative stress and generating reactive oxygen species (ROS). This transition to a pro-oxidant state enables quercetin to exert potent antibacterial activities. In this study, cold plasma treatment was employed to induce the pro-oxidant conversion of quercetin, and the antibacterial efficacy, underlying antibacterial mechanisms of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between Information and Communication Technology Use and Depression in Community-Dwelling Older Adults: The Potential Role of Social Participation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ICT use was associated with depression among older adults, with formal and informal social participation potentially being relevant factors, and associations varied by ICT use type.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Evaluation of Machine Learning Models for Spatio-Temporal Groundwater Quality Prediction and Classification in the Muvattupuzha River Basin, India]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Groundwater contamination has increased significantly due to population growth, land-use change, and unsustainable resource exploitation, necessitating advanced predictive tools for effective water governance. This study presents a multi-temporal, comparative machine learning (ML) to evaluate groundwater quality in the Muvattupuzha River Basin, Kerala, India, using datasets from 2003, 2013, and 2023. A total of five supervised ML models (i.e., decision tree [DT], logistic regression, support...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Förster resonance energy transfer-based anion-responsive nanoemulsion optodes: the importance of fluorescent dye liquid lipophilicity and ionophore-dye interaction for stable and background-free anion response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we fabricated and evaluated a highly sensitive Förster Resonance Energy Transfer (FRET)-based anion-responsive nanoemulsion optode (FRET-NE optode) using an originally developed lipophilic fluorescent dye liquid. When the donor (D) dye liquid, designed and synthesized for a previously developed poly(vinyl) chloride (PVC) film optode, was directly applied to the NE optode, it was found that the D dye liquid leaked into the aqueous phase upon anion response due to insufficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unravelling Voriconazole's Hepatic Metabolism: A Narrative Review on Factors Impacting Voriconazole-N-Oxide Exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: VRC dose, CRP, age and CYP2C19 genotype are the primary covariates affecting NOX or MR, and renal and liver function should also be considered in future population pharmacokinetic models and TDM protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colorless and Transparent Semialicyclic Polyimide Aerogels with Mechanical Durability for Thermal Insulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Visible-light transparency, low thermal conductivity, and high mechanical resistance are important properties for aerogel insulators. Achieving these properties in a single aerogel, however, is a significant challenge. While aromatic polyimide aerogels are known to demonstrate high mechanical resistance, improving both visible-light transparency and thermal insulation remains a challenge. Herein, we present colorless and transparent aerogels with low thermal conductivity and high mechanical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction and inter-species transmission dynamics of high pathogenicity avian influenza H5N1 viruses in Japan 2021-25]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High pathogenicity avian influenza virus impacts poultry and wild birds worldwide. Since the introduction of clade 2.3.4.4b H5N1 isolates in Japan in late 2021, new cases have been reported in domestic birds and poultry each winter. To understand the role of wild birds in introducing these viruses in Japan, a phylodynamic analysis based on geography and host species was conducted using H5N1 isolates in Japan from 2021 to 2025. A total of 892 hemagglutinin gene sequences of H5N1 viruses,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705171/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Machine Learning Applications in Lung Transplantation: A Narrative Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lung transplantation (LTx) offers life-saving therapy for patients with end-stage lung disease but remains limited by donor shortages, complex postoperative management and graft failure. Machine learning (ML) enables opportunities to address these challenges by identifying patterns in complex, high-dimensional data, thereby providing novel insights and improving outcomes. This review outlines ML studies in LTx and explains the methodologies. ML has demonstrated promising results in organ...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case report of J wave syndrome with abnormal potentials in both right and left ventricles and reversed J wave in lead V1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Abnormal epicardial potentials in J wave syndrome predominantly involve the right ventricular outflow tract (RVOT), while left ventricular (LV) involvement remains less characterized and associates with increased ventricular fibrillation (VF) risk. We report a case demonstrating an inverted J wave in lead V1, suggesting LV posterior wall substrate rather than typical RVOT involvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety, immunogenicity, and optimal dosing of VLPCOV-02, a SARS-CoV-2 saRNA vaccine with modified 5-methylcytosine base]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Variant-adapted vaccines are becoming increasingly important for continued COVID-19 prevention. Part 1 of the phase 1/2 study with VLPCOV-02, a lipid nanoparticle-encapsulated, self-amplifying RNA (saRNA) vaccine with a modified 5-methylcytosine (5 mC) base, demonstrated lower reactogenicity and incidence of adverse events, and induction of antibody responses. We report results of part 2 with an expanded number of participants (N = 323 [3 μg VLPCOV-02: 53 non-elderly and 54 elderly; 7.5 μg...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary intake characteristics in older adults: A systematic review of physical, social, psychological, and behavioral limitations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Older individuals generally have decreased food intake owing to physical, social, psychological, and behavioral limitations. However, the characteristics of food and nutrient intake resulting from these limitations are poorly organized. Organizing knowledge for practical application in older adults is necessary when considering nutrition care strategies. This review aimed to characterize food and nutrient intake according to these exposure factors in older individuals. This systematic review...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Voice Conversion System from Electrolarynx Speech to Preoperative Patient's Speech for Total Laryngectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Laryngectomy is a life-changing procedure typically performed as a surgical treatment for patients with head and neck cancer. Voice conversion (VC) is a technology that converts one voice into another without changing the linguistic information. Recently, "Save the Voice Project" for patients planning to undergo laryngectomy using our VC technique has been initiated. This study evaluated the speech converted from EL speech using the VC technique in a patient with head and neck cancer who had...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enthalpy-Entropy Trade-Off Underlies Geometric Isomer Selectivity in Histamine H<sub>1</sub> Receptor-Doxepin Interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the thermodynamic basis of ligand recognition by G-protein-coupled receptors (GPCRs) is crucial for rational drug design. Here, we directly characterized the binding thermodynamics of the histamine H(1) receptor (H(1)R) interacting with the geometric isomers of doxepin using isothermal titration calorimetry combined with molecular dynamics (MD) simulations. The Z-isomer binding to H(1)R_WT exhibited a larger enthalpic gain but a greater entropic loss than the E-isomer, whereas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of the particle size of wheat bran inclusions in feed on the precaecal gastrointestinal tract fibre particle size distribution, caecal digesta particle size and caecal fibre fermentation in young and growing broilers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Including additional dietary fibre fractions in broiler feed has gained renewed interest due to its potential for stimulating (gut) health and performance. The beneficial effects of fibre are mainly due to its fermentation in the caecal lobes, but the influx of digesta into these lobes seems restricted to small particles and solubles. To boost caecal fermentation via fibre inclusions, more knowledge on how fibre particle size in feed can affect the fibre particle size distribution along the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704251/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between climate change awareness-related psychological distress and mental health in people with psychiatric diagnoses or subclinical symptoms: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of arginine-enriched enteral nutrition on clinical outcomes with infectious events and muscle volume in critically ill patients: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Arginine-enriched EN may not exert beneficial effects on the incidence of infection or other outcomes. However, because no studies have examined the administration of arginine alone and few RCTs investigated physical outcomes, such as muscle volume and physical function, further research is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revealing the biological and genomic characteristics of Escherichia coli phages and their application in reducing biofilm formation and bacterial counts in contaminated meat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The meat industry is often confronted with bacterial contamination, particularly Escherichia coli (E. coli), which compromises food safety and poses significant public health risks. Conventional treatments for bacterial contamination can lead to undesirable outcomes, highlighting the need for alternative strategies. In this study, we characterized E. coli phages, including their genomic features to evaluate their safety, and assessed their potential as biocontrol agents for controlling E. coli...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does compassion affect shame emotions and mental health in individuals with ASD traits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The continuous net benefit: assessing the clinical utility of prediction models when informing a continuum of decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The magnitude of multimorbidity in childhood: a global systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Childhood multimorbidity poses significant health and social challenges, necessitating integrated care approaches and standardized definitions for cross-study comparability. Preventive strategies targeting social determinants and early-life interventions are crucial to mitigate its long-term burden. Future research should focus on longitudinal studies to explore progression and inform targeted interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fava bean and pea protein hydrolysates modulate stress responses in <em>C. elegans</em> through different mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing global demand for protein, combined with the urgent need for effective strategies to manage conditions such as obesity and diabetes, highlights legume proteins as valuable sources of derived bioactive peptides with health-promoting properties. In this study, we employed the Caenorhabditis elegans model to investigate the effects of supplementation with hydrolysates derived from fava bean and pea protein on healthspan. Supplementation with fava bean and pea protein hydrolysates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-Assembly with Donor-Acceptor Self-Assembled Monolayers to Enhance Interfacial Hole Extraction, Wettability, and Crystallization in Inverted Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Self-assembled monolayers (SAMs) are commonly employed as hole-selective layers in inverted perovskite solar cells. However, the widely used Me-4PACz (Me4) often faces issues such as solution aggregation, poor precursor wettability, insufficient interfacial contact, and suboptimal crystallinity at the perovskite buried interface, leading to non-radiative losses. This study proposes two newly designed donor-acceptor (D-A) SAMs, LYS-H and its fluorinated derivative LYS-F, and employs a co-assembly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social support and depressive symptoms among people living with HIV in Cambodia: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This cross-sectional study examined the prevalence of depressive symptoms, levels of social support, and their association among 4,089 clinically stable people living with HIV receiving antiretroviral therapy (ART) across 20 clinics in Cambodia. Depressive symptoms were assessed using the 10-item Center for Epidemiologic Studies Depression Scale (CES-D-10), and social support was measured using the Berlin Social Support Scale (BSSS). Overall, 19.5% of participants reported depressive symptoms,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncounted and Underserved: Housing Data and Programs Overlook Pregnant and Parenting Families]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Experiencing housing insecurity and homelessness while pregnant is associated with an array of adverse maternal and infant health outcomes. This study aims to describe how the federal and Illinois housing landscapes prioritize, fund, and collect data on pregnant and postpartum people.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cannabis dispensary exposure and smoked, vaped and edible cannabis use among young adults: Comparison of web-scraped and government-maintained registries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Living near a greater number of cannabis dispensaries within 1 mile of home appears to be associated with an increased risk of cannabis use. Web-scraped dispensary sources and United States government-maintained registry lists produce similar conclusions regarding the association of living near a greater number of dispensaries with young adult cannabis use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laser-Direct Printed 2D Material-Based Heterostructure for the Fabrication of Electronic Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Integrating two-dimensional (2D) materials into functional electronic devices remains a major challenge, requiring precise, defect-free deposition and patterning techniques. In this work, we present experimental results on the fabrication of heterostructures composed of graphene, PdSe(2), and MoSe(2) using the Laser-Induced Forward Transfer (LIFT) technique. This digital, maskless method enables accurate positioning and shape definition of 2D material pixels with micrometer-scale resolution. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Integrative Review of Community Health Volunteer-Led Training to Improve Water, Sanitation, and Hygiene Practices in Haiti]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Water, sanitation, and hygiene (WASH) are foundational determinants of public health and community development. Globally, approximately 2.3 billion people still lack access to safe drinking water and sanitation services. These disparities are most pronounced in low- and middle-income countries such as Haiti, and regions affected by conflict, political instability, or fragile health infrastructure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnitude of Response in Treatment and Control Groups within Psychedelic Trials for Psychiatric Disorders: A Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Natural History of Insomnia: Sleep Opportunity Extension Following a Poor Night of Sleep Is Not Related to the Transition From Acute to Chronic Insomnia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The behavioural tendency to expand sleep opportunity to compensate for prior sleep loss is referred to as 'sleep extension.' It is believed that sleep extension (here referred to as 'sleep opportunity extension' [SOE]) is the primary perpetuating factor explaining the transition from acute to chronic insomnia. Recently, this proposition was prospectively evaluated by assessing how sleep opportunity varied, week-by-week, relative to the incidence of acute and chronic insomnia. Significant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementing GPT-4 Learning Models in Dermatology: An Assessment of Medical Quality and Utility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overall, GPT-4 models produced dermatological content with few harmful recommendations. However, GPT-4-generated content performed poorly on the DISCERN instrument, and validation of LLM-generated responses remains challenging. Results suggest LLM parameters and query structures may be optimizable for dermatologic applications. If implemented alongside the professional judgement of certified dermatologists, future LLMs may serve as time-saving dermatologic tools, enhancing patient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shoulder morphology and throwing shoulder pain: Associations with humeral retroversion angle and posterior glenohumeral distance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Reduced humeral retroversion may be accompanied by morphological changes in the posterior glenoid rim, which may be associated with an increased risk of throwing shoulder injury. MRI‑based morphological assessment is useful as a research tool to understand the pathomechanisms of throwing‑related shoulder injury and to validate potential clinical markers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel spinel-type selenide semiconductor ZnSc<sub>2</sub>Se<sub>4</sub> and its solid solution with sulfide for photovoltaics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[It has recently been reported that the spinel-type sulfide (Zn,Mg)Sc(2)S(4) possesses optoelectronic properties, including both n- and p-type dopability and strong visible-light emission. Herein, we present a novel isomorphic selenide, ZnSc(2)Se(4), synthesized using a high-pressure synthesis technique, which exhibits n-type semiconducting behavior. Additionally, a solid solution between ZnSc(2)S(4) and ZnSc(2)Se(4) is realized over the entire composition range, enabling continuous tuning of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isolation and Comprehensive Characterisation of Edwardsiella anguillarum From Diseased Tilapia (Oreochromis niloticus) Cultured in Mexico: Biochemical, Genetic and Genomic Insights and Dose-Dependent Pathogenicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Edwardsiella anguillarum is an emerging aquaculture pathogen responsible for economic losses across several cultured fish species. This study reports the isolation, identification, and characterisation of four isolates recovered from two infectious outbreaks in farmed Nile tilapia (Oreochromis niloticus) in Mexico. In 2021 and 2022, mortalities events occurred at two aquaculture facilities located in Querétaro and Estado de México, where affected fish exhibited clinical signs including skin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid Eye Movement Sleep Behavior Disorder with Clinical Dementia with Lewy Bodies Phenotype but Lacking Postmortem Central Nervous System Synuclein Pathology: Alternate Etiologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RBD may arise independently of α-synuclein pathology. In the present case, RBD might be caused by dysregulation of the brainstem REM sleep-related structures due to age-related proteinopathies impairing the limbic system, and venlafaxine overactive monoaminergic transmission. In neuroprotective trials, CSF α-synuclein SAA may be useful to exclude IRBD patients without synuclein pathology. © 2026 International Parkinson and Movement Disorder Society.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacial Materialization Enabled by Cellulose Nanofibril Surfactants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biphasic liquid systems, serving as platforms with spatially directing functionality, achieve the integration of bio-mass nano-building blocks into advanced materials. Using liquid-liquid interfaces, a series of assemblies based on cellulose nanocrystals (CNCs) emerges, yet with limited application prospects, as the assemblies are mechanically fragile and thus incapable of withstanding processing-induced stresses. Here, we propose flexible cellulose nanofibrils (CNFs) as alternative assembling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Statistical methodologies for absolute and relative efficacy assessment based on single-arm trials: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regulatory decision-making on the marketing authorisation of Advanced Therapy Medicinal Products (ATMP) is challenging, in particular since the evidence that is provided in the marketing authorization application is frequently not from randomized controlled clinical trials, but based on single-arm trials (SAT). Additionally, if a conditional marketing authorisation is applied, cross-trial comparisons are often necessary against other authorised treatments in the same indication. While various...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[USP10 Deubiquitinates MTX2 to Suppress cGAS-STING Signaling in MI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identifies USP10 as a novel regulator of the cGAS-STING signaling pathway in MI. Moreover, our findings demonstrate that a decrease in USP10 in the BZ cardiomyocytes can be therapeutically targeted to mitigate cardiac injury in MI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Clinical Trial and Molecular Profiling Reveals Immune Drivers of Chronic Hand Eczema]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings confirmed the involvement of not only type 2 but also type 1 and type 3 immunity across all CHE patients, and demonstrate that IL-4Rα blockade may offer effective therapeutic perspectives for this highly burdensome condition, independent of an atopic dermatitis background.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-cultural adaptation and validation of the Suffering Pictogram for Brazilian cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The SP-BR is a validated, unidimensional Brazilian Portuguese instrument suitable for holistic suffering assessment in clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subcellular nanoparticle trafficking investigated with label-free, live cell imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanoparticle drug delivery systems have significant potential to transform precision medicine due to their ability to encapsulate a wide range of cargo, improve systemic circulation time, and enhance targeted delivery. These delivery properties can be further modified by altering the surface chemistry of the nanoparticle carrier. However, a gap remains in our understanding of the cellular mechanisms underlying nanoparticle uptake, in addition to the subcellular trafficking kinetics. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705321/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancement of Zn/Zn<sup>2+</sup> Reversibility Using Molecular Materials in Aqueous Zinc-Ion Batteries: A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Development of aqueous zinc ion batteries (AZIBs) is of recent interest for sustainable and scalable energy storage. This review focuses on the development of all components of AZIBs, namely, electrolytes, anodes, cathodes, and a separator, using molecular materials to enhance battery performance. It systematically categorizes different kinds of molecular materials based on their diverse functionalities, intrinsic properties, and applicability in different components of batteries. Each component...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient Perspectives on Psychiatric Polygenic Risk Scores in Reproductive Decision-Making and Polygenic Embryo Screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polygenic risk scores (PRS) estimate individuals' genetic risk for developing multifactorial conditions. Recent genome-wide association studies have enabled development of psychiatric PRS, which hold potential to streamline diagnosis and treatment of psychiatric conditions. As individuals with mental illness often identify concern about passing on psychiatric conditions as a key factor in family planning, some may also seek to use psychiatric PRS in reproductive decisions like childbearing or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences and Quality of Life Impacts Related to Urinary Tract Infections in Veterans With Neurogenic Bladder: A Mixed Methods Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Results suggest that people with NB may experience substantial QoL impacts from UTIs, and patient-centered interventions may be needed to decrease the impact of UTIs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trials of Improved Practices (TIPs) to Explore Caregivers' Practices for Childhood Nutrition and Acceptance of Novel Interventions for Moderately Wasted Children in a Dhaka Slum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The TIPs approach identified context-specific caregiver behaviours and feeding preferences. These findings will guide the upcoming trial and assist policymakers and program planners in developing culturally tailored interventions to address childhood malnutrition in urban slums.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interleukin-22 and Interleukin-18 as Potential Blood Biomarkers in Dupilumab-Treated Atopic Dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strengthening Respiratory Virus Surveillance in Sub-Saharan Africa: Integrated Epidemiological and Genomic Monitoring in Côte d'Ivoire]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Integration of RSV and SARS-CoV-2 into influenza sentinel surveillance has enabled continuous detection and genomic characterization, reinforcing the critical role of integrated sentinel surveillance for timely response to respiratory virus threats.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milk fat globule-EGF factor 8/ATP-binding cassette subfamily E member 1 axis maintains mitophagy flux homeostasis to suppress ferroptosis in acute pancreatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Endogenous MFG-E8 protects against AP by binding ABCE1 to sustain mitophagy flux and inhibit ferroptosis. Targeting this axis offers a promising therapeutic strategy for mitigating pancreatic injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decreased adipokine CTRP4 in CAD patients: CTRP4 attenuates atherosclerosis via inhibition of RAGE and TLR4]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Decreased CTRP4 levels in serum and epicardial adipose tissue are associated with CAD in patients. CTRP4 deficiency promotes the development of atherosclerosis in ApoE^(‒/‒) mice, whereas CTRP4 supplementation attenuates atherosclerosis via binding and inhibition of RAGE and TLR4. These results suggest that CTRP4 is a novel anti-inflammatory and anti-atherogenic adipokine inversely associated with CAD and a potential therapeutic target.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultra-Efficient Bamboo Microfiber Adsorbents for Formaldehyde Purification: Fabricated via In-Situ Growth of Dual Metal-Organic Frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An innovative strategy of heterointerface-driven formaldehyde capture was developed by dual metal organic framework (MOF) nanoarchitectures in-situ grown on bamboo microfibers (BMFs). The hierarchical BMF/MOF adsorbents were fabricated using steam-exploded BMFs as cores, followed by the sequential growth of indium-based MOF (MIL-68) on zeolitic imidazolate framework-8 (ZIF-8). This triggered a clear transition in adsorption behavior from physical adsorption to a chemisorption-dominated process,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HepAssis2<sup>®</sup> bioartificial liver system in treating acute-on-chronic liver failure patients: Findings from a phase 1 randomised, open-label clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the German version of the Subjective Scale to Investigate Cognition in Schizophrenia (SSTICS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Schizophrenia Spectrum Disorders (SSD) are characterized by cognitive deficits that can significantly impact daily functioning and quality of life. The Subjective Scale to Investigate Cognition in Schizophrenia (SSTICS) is a widely used self-report tool for assessing subjective cognitive impairments. This study validates the German version of the SSTICS. Data from N = 308 participants (38% female) with SSD were analyzed to evaluate factor structure, reliability, and convergent/discriminant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Digital and Remote Health Interventions in Pediatric Populations From Underserved or Rural Areas: A Systematic Review of Randomized Controlled Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Digital health interventions are effective and feasible for improving pediatric outcomes in underserved settings. Future research should emphasize long-term impact, cost-effectiveness, and equitable access to ensure sustainable and inclusive digital healthcare delivery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Risk Factors Affecting Cumulative Live Birth in Couples With Unexplained Infertility Undergoing IVF/ICSI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The prevalence of UI was 8.8% in our population, with 62.2% achieving CLB after one complete IVF/ICSI cycle. Female age and ovarian reserve indicators emerged as the main factors influencing oocyte yield, embryo acquisition, and CLB outcomes in UI patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced gelling properties in fish gelatin by refined and semi-refined κ-carrageenan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of semi-refined κ-carrageenan (SC) and refined κ-carrageenan (RC) on the gelling properties of fish gelatin (FG) and revealed the critical role of sulfate content in the modification process of FG. RC, with higher sulfate content (23.25%), enhanced FG more effectively than SC. A data model linked sulfate content to FG's gelling properties, showing a significant correlation. Structural analysis revealed that SC/RC formed aggregates with FG, increasing hydrogen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[METTL14 modulates the nasopharyngeal carcinoma microenvironment via m<sup>6</sup>A-modified YWHAH identified through single-cell and machine learning analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Integration of multi-omics data facilitated the identification of YWHAH as a METTL14-regulated gene, which plays a pivotal role in the NPC immune microenvironment. The elevated expression of YWHAH indicates its role in regulating immune balance. Together these findings suggest a potential regulatory link between TNF-α, YWHAH and METTL14 in the context of NPC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-associated neutrophils in renal cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Renal cell carcinoma (RCC) is an immunogenic tumor in which tumor-associated neutrophils (TANs) and neutrophil extracellular traps (NETs) represent a functionally important component of the tumor microenvironment. Recent studies have revealed pronounced phenotypic heterogeneity of RCC-infiltrating neutrophils, including interferon-responsive, immunosuppressive PMN-MDSC-like, pro-angiogenic, and NET-forming subsets that cannot be adequately described by the classical N1/N2 model. Their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complement activation and M2-like macrophage accumulation in anti-MDA5 monoclonal antibody-induced hepatic injury in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Complement activation and the accumulation of M2-like macrophages are associated with anti-human MDA5 monoclonal antibody-induced hepatic injury in mice. These findings provide mechanistic insight into antibody-complement-macrophage interactions and suggest that modulation of complement pathways may represent a potential therapeutic approach to limit liver and systemic involvement in this disorder.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and mechanistic basis of ADAR1-mediated RNA editing and immune regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adenosine deaminase acting on RNA 1 (ADAR1) is a central regulator of innate immunity. By binding to and catalyzing adenosine-to-inosine deamination within double-stranded RNAs, ADAR1 mitigates the immunogenicity of self-derived RNAs and preserves cellular homeostasis. In this review, we summarize recent structural and mechanistic advances that illuminate key features of ADAR1 architecture, including how its multi-domains engage dsRNA substrates and contribute to substrate selectivity....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Remote learning and physical activity in medical students from Latin America: a cross-sectional study during the first wave of the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fspor.2025.1684127.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune-modulatory biomimetic nanoparticles: Advances in design, mechanisms, and nanomedicine applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of biomimetic nanoparticles (NPs) represents an innovative approach to address the lacks of conventional drug delivery systems. This advancement demonstrates promising potential in immunotherapy. Biomimetic NPs imitate biological structures to improve the effectiveness of drug delivery and enhance interactions with cancer cells. Their beneficial features include biocompatibility, long circulation time, tissue specificity, enhanced drug absorption, and low toxicity. Recent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integration of gut microbiota, Stroke Dysbiosis Index, and inflammatory biomarkers in assessing prognosis of acute ischemic stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Gut dysbiosis, elevated dysbiosis indices, and inflammatory biomarker derangements were strongly associated with post-stroke infections and adverse prognosis. Integrating microbiota and biomarker profiles with clinical parameters may provide a robust framework for risk stratification and open avenues for microbiota-targeted therapies in AIS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The acute effect of sprint interval training on the immune system: a systematic review and meta-regression analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A single session of SIT elicits a potent acute systemic immune response, characterized by a highly conserved mobilization of circulating leukocytes, particularly neutrophils. This response is significantly modulated by individual training status: athletes exhibit a distinct immunometabolic profile characterized by a robust IL-6 release and stable mucosal immunity (sIgA), whereas untrained individuals show more variable responses. These findings provide critical evidence for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical practice guideline for female fertility preservation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Female fertility preservation (FFP) has become a clinical priority because gonadotoxic therapies for cancer and benign diseases are increasingly common and may cause irreversible ovarian failure. The current clinical practice guideline provides evidence-based recommendations on fertility assessment, oocyte/embryo cryopreservation, and ovarian tissue cryopreservation and transplantation for women at risk of iatrogenic infertility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution, extent, and calculated age of initiation of coronary artery calcification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Calcified plaque was most commonly identified in the LAD. CAC occurs earlier in the LAD than in other coronary arteries. The particular susceptibility to calcification of LAD is not related to gender.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resection combined with hyperthermic intraperitoneal chemotherapy in the treatment of spontaneously ruptured hepatocellular carcinoma: a multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HIPEC combined with resection for srHCC can effectively prolong survival time. Resection combined with HIPEC and targeted therapy may be a promising strategy for srHCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perspective: What is the Likely Impact of the Proposed Food and Drug Administration Front-of-Package Criteria on the Labeling of Foods?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The United States Food and Drug Administration (FDA) recently proposed a new rule on front-of-package (FOP) labeling. Focusing on added sugars, sodium, and saturated fat, the proposed FOP label would identify foods with low [<5% daily value (DV)], medium (6‒19% DV), and high (20% DV) concentrations of each nutrient, calculated per serving size. This study applied the proposed FDA criteria to food categories and subgroups as defined in the USDA Food and Nutrient Database for Dietary Studies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The protocol for mesoscopic wide-field optical imaging in mice: from zero to hero]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article provides protocols that enable researchers to master mesoscopic wide-field optical brain imaging from scratch. The protocols describe surgery for wide-field cranial window creation in mice, as well as the imaging process and setup. The protocols for components of the imaging system selection and assembly, creation of a headplate for fixation, and training mice are also provided. The final section briefly outlines methods for data processing. The described procedure can be used to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705132/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of interoception: the critical role of maternal affective touch in early attachment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite growing interest in interoceptive functioning, primarily due to its pivotal role in physical and mental health, little is known about its developmental origins and the factors that influence it. Interoception-the perception of one's internal bodily state-in which bottom-up sensory signals from receptors located in the body are integrated with top-down cognitive interpretations, is crucial for homeostatic and emotional regulation and overall wellbeing. Specific questions remain on how and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An integrated surveillance in Zhejiang Province: ecological and pathogen survey of vectors and reservoir hosts in 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This integrated surveillance established baseline metrics for important vectors and reservoir hosts, furnishing evidence-based support for the ongoing management and prevention of vector-borne diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Admixture-driven structural variation diversity and its functional implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Population admixture is a potent evolutionary force shaping genomic diversity, yet its influence on the dynamics and functional consequences of structural variation (SV) remains poorly understood. Here, we present a comprehensive whole-genome sequencing analysis of SVs in the Uyghurs, a model admixed Eurasian population with distinct Western and Eastern ancestral contributions. We identified 9965 high-confidence SVs, revealing that Uyghurs exhibit 32% novel SVs and 1.19-fold greater...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Malrotated lateral radiographs do not allow for proper assessment of patellar height using the Caton-Deschamps Index]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Malrotation significantly alters PHM using the CDI on lateral knee radiographs. A clinically relevant difference of ≥0.1 in ΔCDI occurred in over one-third of patients. Malrotated radiographs should be used with caution, and repeat imaging should be considered when CDI values approach clinical decision thresholds.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth Trajectories of Medication Adherence in Pediatric Organ Transplantation and Their Relationship to Posttransplant Health Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underscore the dynamic and heterogeneous nature of adherence across pediatric transplant populations. MLVI-based trajectory modeling offers a promising avenue for early risk identification and could inform the development of electronic medical record-integrated alerts or personalized adherence interventions. Future research should integrate psychosocial variables and expand to multicenter samples for enhanced generalizability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705091/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and validation of respiratory virus immunization using natural language processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Electronic health record (EHR)-based research often relies on structured data elements, such as ICD-10-CM and CPT codes, to identify clinical diagnoses and procedures. However, some information, such as the administration of immunizations, may be captured more reliably in the text-based narrative sections of the patient's record. We developed a rule-based natural language processing (NLP) algorithm to identify the administration of immunizations for COVID-19, influenza, and RSV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment of geriatric pelvis fractures - What are the knowledge gaps?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence of insufficiency fractures of the pelvis is rising in developed countries. The aim of this review is to summarize the current evidence regarding the classification, treatment, and surgical strategies for these fractures. Several classifications have been developed such as the AO Spine Sacral Injury Classification System, the Fragility Fractures of the Pelvis (FFP), and the OF pelvis classification. The treatment option consists of non-operative treatment, sacroplasty, ileosacral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FaXNet: a frequency-adaptive, explainable, and uncertainty-aware network for influenza forecasting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: FaXNet provides accurate, interpretable forecasts with calibrated prediction intervals across 1-4-week horizons, offering actionable lead time for region-specific risk assessment and resource planning. Performance may depend on surveillance data completeness and the limited set of exogenous covariates considered, motivating future extensions with additional drivers (e.g., mobility or vaccination) and broader external validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in the neurotoxicity of ecological pesticide maneb: mechanisms and implications for human health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maneb, a typical dithiocarbamate pesticide, is widely used in the control of agricultural fungi in lands. Its residues with main metabolites in environmental media pose risks to environmental safety and human health. This research summarized the research progress on the environmental residues, human exposure levels, neurotoxic effects and mechanisms of maneb. Epidemiological studies have shown that exposure to maneb is associated with an increased risk of neurodegenerative diseases such as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Critical Events in Anaesthetised Kids Undergoing Tracheal Intubation (CRICKET)-study protocol for an international multicentre prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Critical Events in Anaesthetised Kids undergoing Tracheal Intubation (CRICKET) is a prospective, international multicentre observational study with the objective of capturing, assessing, and analysing critical events associated with tracheal intubation in children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic Ce sites promote a four-electron pathway of Pt as NADH oxidase mimics for <em>in situ</em> coenzyme regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide (NAD^(+)) is a key coenzyme for human redox reactions, vital for cellular health and metabolic balance. Lots of NAD^(+)-dependent redox enzymes, like alcohol dehydrogenase (ADH) and lactate dehydrogenase, can catalyze both forward and reverse reactions. However, substrate accumulation and inadequate NAD^(+) replenishment hinder forward reactions, disrupting the proper metabolism of these substrates. In this work, we reported atomic Ce-doped Pt (Ce(1)Pt)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: Further correction: Reductive annulations of arylidene malonates with unsaturated electrophiles using photoredox/Lewis acid cooperative catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.1039/C9SC00302A.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital spatial profiling of α-PD-1 treated breast cancer bone metastases reveals region-specific signaling and enrichment of immune-suppressive markers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bone is the most common and preferential site for breast cancer metastasis. Upon dissemination to the bone, breast cancer cells engraft into multiple niches, but it is unclear whether there are region-specific differences that may drive breast cancer progression in bone. We used a proteomic digital spatial profiling (DSP) approach to investigate which proliferation, cell death, and immune-related markers and pathways are enriched in immune and cancer cells residing 1) in the bone marrow or 2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transarterial chemoembolization (TACE) combined with immunotherapy and anti-angiogenic agents in intermediate-stage hepatocellular carcinoma (CHANCE2202): a target trial emulation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: This study aimed to assess the clinical outcomes of transarterial chemoembolization (TACE) with immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs) plus vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF) inhibitors or tyrosine kinase inhibitors (TKIs) (combination therapy) versus TACE monotherapy as a first-line treatment for intermediate-stage hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wide-range High-precision Eye-tracking based on Purkinje Reflections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humans continually move their eyes to explore the visual world. Precisely measuring eye movements is, therefore, crucial for both understanding human vision and paving the way for the next generation of augmented and virtual reality devices. Imaging Purkinje reflections enables high-resolution eye-tracking over a limited range. Here we present an optical architecture that enables extension of the tracking range while maintaining 1 arcmin resolution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41705014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Different structural brain patterns and their association with executive function and general cognitive ability in cognitively normal elderly adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cognitively normal elderly adults exhibited different structural brain patterns, which were further associated with executive function and general cognitive ability. These findings shed light on the relationship between brain structural pattern changes and cognition in cognitively normal elderly adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensor-integrated hip and knee prostheses: advances, challenges, and future perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Total joint arthroplasty consistently alleviates pain and improves function in patients with end-stage joint disease. Nevertheless, up to 10% of hip and 20% of knee recipients remain dissatisfied after surgery, and registry data indicate that approximately one in five implants requires revision within 25 years, most commonly due to aseptic loosening, mechanical instability, or periprosthetic joint infection. Conventional postoperative surveillance relies on intermittent clinic visits and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704935/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transgender identity and psychiatric care in Italian prisons: a thematic analysis of systemic gaps and institutional challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Transgender and gender-diverse (TGD) individuals face high levels of stigma, discrimination, and psychological distress, which are amplified in carceral settings. Italian prisons have introduced specialized sections for TGD inmates; however, limited empirical evidence exists on their function and the psychiatric, social, and institutional challenges emerging within them.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A dual-path mediation model: associations between childhood psychological maltreatment and loneliness among Chinese college students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings support the proposed dual-path model, suggesting that the association between childhood psychological maltreatment and later loneliness may operate through eroded interpersonal trust and impaired development of adaptive coping strategies. This underscores the importance of integrated interventions targeting both trust reconstruction and coping skills training in mitigating the long-term impacts of early adversity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-sectional study on the relationship between sarcopenia indicators and lung function in a community-dwelling population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that sarcopenia indicators are closely associated with lung function in community-dwelling individuals. As a condition that significantly impacts healthy aging and is linked to both quality of life and longevity, enhancing the early identification and management of sarcopenia within community settings may yield multi-organ benefits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The associations between physical activity, microbiome and metabolic adaptation in sedentary overweight adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite well-established benefits of exercise on metabolic regulation and the gut microbiome (GM), its impact on body composition is inconsistent and often attenuated by metabolic adaptation. This compensation mechanism adjusts energy expenditure including total daily energy expenditure (TDEE) and resting metabolic rate (RMR). Intra-individual variation in exercise response remains unclear, but might be explained by the GM. In this well-controlled study, we investigated the relationship between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704904/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Access-Related Hand Dysfunction After Hemodialysis Access Placement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with CKD or ESKD, hemodialysis access surgery results in ARHD, which is associated with muscle atrophy, altered transcriptomic profiles, and higher incidence of access maturation failure. These findings underscore the need for early identification and targeted interventions to prevent ARHD and improve dialysis-access surgery outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Executive anosognosia in progressive supranuclear palsy versus Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Executive anosognosia is a marker of PSP, highlighting the need for objective neuropsychological assessments in clinical trials. PSP patients' reports of executive dysfunction are more associated with mood than actual impairment, which challenges the validity of patient-reported outcomes in PSP and related neurological diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-specific effects of fecal microbiota transplantation on TBI-exacerbated Alzheimer's disease pathology in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In 5xFAD mice, TBI drives sex-dependent worsening of amyloid pathology, neuroinflammation, and dysbiosis. Acute FMT partially restores microbial composition and plaque features in sham animals but fails to reverse TBI-induced neuroinflammation or motor deficits. These findings underscore the context- and sex-dependence of microbiome interventions and support longer-term, sex-specific strategies for AD with comorbid TBI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conditional generative diffusion model for 3D trabecular bone synthesis with tunable microstructure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed generative model is capable of generating realistic digital trabecular bone patches. The application of latent space diffusion using a dedicated VAE augmented with the shifting-slab mechanism effectively overcomes computer memory constraints to enable the synthesis of 3D volumes. The conditioning mechanism is effective in guiding the synthesis toward desired microstructural characteristics. Possible applications include virtual clinical trials of new skeletal image...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phenome-Wide Associations of Polygenic Scores for Schizophrenia and Major Depression in 100,000 Chinese Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study suggests the context specificity of relationships between mental disorders and other traits, highlighting a potential role of sociocultural factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Patterns of Biomarker Testing in Colorectal, Lung, and Prostate Cancers: Insights From the NIH <em>All of Us</em> Research Program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Despite national guidelines, biomarker testing remains underutilized and unevenly distributed across sociodemographic groups. These findings should be interpreted as exploratory, reflecting the fidelity of structured electronic health record (EHR) documentation rather than definitive utilization. Leveraging the scale and diversity of All of Us highlights both equity gaps and documentation limitations, positioning the program as a valuable platform for hypothesis generation in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704839/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of patient and site engagement in the SYNCHRONIZE™ phase 3 clinical trial program for survodutide in obesity through clinical trial simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest participant and site staff input from a CTS could help improve obesity clinical trial design, which may ultimately lead to more robust data and reliable clinical findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704810/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported outcomes after upper-extremity deep vein thrombosis due to compression syndromes: a multinational longitudinal retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: UEDVT can have lasting functional and psychosocial effects. Patient-reported outcomes reveal a burden that is not captured by traditional clinical metrics and should be integrated into routine care as well in the setting of interventional trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plant hormones and membrane transporters: integrating nutrient uptake, ion homeostasis, and stress responses through hormonal cross-talk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant membrane transporters are essential components in the regulation of nutrient uptake, ion homeostasis, and adaptive responses to environmental stress. These transport processes are tightly coordinated by complex phytohormonal signaling networks. This review provides an in-depth examination of the molecular mechanisms through which major plant hormones including auxins, cytokinins, brassinosteroids, ethylene, abscisic acid, gibberellins, jasmonates, strigolactones, melatonin, karrikins, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomic profiling identifies prognostic signature for Krukenberg tumor of gastrointestinal origin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Krukenberg tumor (KT) primarily originates from the stomach and colorectum, but reliable biomarkers for distinguishing KT from other tumors at the same sites and predicting ovarian metastasis remain lacking. Using pressure cycling technology (PCT) and data-independent acquisition (DIA) mass spectrometry, we analyzed 263 formalin-fixed paraffin-embedded (FFPE) samples, identifying 10,837 proteins. The results revealed distinct proteomic signatures from the primary gastrointestinal lesions of KT....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The succinate prodrug NV354 prevents brain lesions and late-stage motor dysfunction in mitochondrial complex I deficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leigh syndrome is a fatal pediatric neurodegenerative disease caused by mitochondrial dysfunction, which can be modeled in the Ndufs4 KO mouse with mitochondrial respiratory chain complex I (CI) deficiency. This study explores NV354, a prodrug of succinate with enhanced oral bioavailability and brain uptake, as a potential therapy to counteract this devastating condition. NV354 modulated whole-body respiration and metabolic flexibility, prevented late-stage motor dysfunction, delayed clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maimendong decoction suppresses non-small cell lung cancer growth by promoting dendritic cell maturation via the SIRT1/p65 acetylation pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maimendong Decoction (MMDD), a classical traditional Chinese medicine, has shown promising clinical efficacy against non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC), yet its immunological mechanisms remain unclear. Using a Lewis lung carcinoma (LLC) mouse model, we found that MMDD markedly suppressed tumor growth, enhanced CD8^(+) T cell infiltration, and promoted dendritic cell (DC) maturation. Mechanistic analyses revealed that MMDD inhibited SIRT1 expression, increased p65 acetylation, and elevated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Activation of SNr GABA neurons drives liver-brain-eye axis dysfunction in hepatic encephalopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatic encephalopathy (HE) is frequently accompanied by visual dysfunction, yet the mechanisms underlying the liver-brain-eye axis remain unclear. We established mouse models of acute hepatic encephalopathy (AHE) using thioacetamide and chronic hepatic encephalopathy (CHE) using bile duct ligation, confirming hyperammonemia and visual impairment by electroretinogram (ERG) and visual evoked potentials (VEPs). Retinal analyses revealed preserved structure in AHE, whereas CHE induced significant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERG phase separation attenuates cellular senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Centenarians, individuals who reach extreme old age, provide a valuable model for understanding mechanisms associated with healthy aging. Using ATAC-seq and transcriptomic profiling of peripheral blood mononuclear cells from centenarians, we identified a distinct chromatin accessibility landscape linked to exceptional longevity. Integrative analysis highlighted the E-26 transformation-specific (ETS)-related transcription factor ERG as a longevity-associated regulator. Functional studies in human...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoacoustic imaging-guided, synchronously targeted thrombolysis and neuroprotection of acute ischemic stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute ischemic stroke (AIS) is a major cause of disability and mortality worldwide, typically resulting from a thrombus that blocks cerebral blood flow. Current treatments focus on thrombolysis and neuroprotection, with recombinant tissue plasminogen activator (rt-PA) and edaravone (Eda) as key drugs. However, their therapeutic efficacy is constrained by poor targeting, leading to suboptimal drug delivery to the brain. Herein, we develop a biomimetic delivery system (PLEA, platelet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative analysis reveals the autoantibodyome neuroimmune signature of neurodegeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurodegenerative disorders, including Alzheimer's disease (AD), Parkinson's disease (PD), and multiple sclerosis (MS), are complex conditions driven by systemic dysregulation that transcends the central nervous system. An integrative systems immunology framework was applied to characterize the neuroimmune "autoantibodyome" across neurodegeneration through an individual participant data meta-analysis of five protein microarray datasets, comprising 596 samples from patients with AD, PD, or MS and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Aurkb</em> deficiency disrupts microglial development, homeostasis and hinders remyelination following cuprizone-induced demyelination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microglia are crucial for phagocytic clearance of myelin debris, which hinders remyelination and leads to neurological decline during aging and in multiple sclerosis (MS). However, the molecular mechanism enabling microglia to expand and function effectively in remyelination remains elusive. Here, we identified that mitotic kinase Aurkb was upregulated in microglia during early development and in MS. Neonatal deletion of Aurkb disrupted cell density, morphology, and proliferation, which is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ACTG1 facilitates proliferation and epithelial-mesenchymal transition-mediated metastasis via COL21A1 in gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer (GC) remains a lethal malignancy with limited therapeutic options. We investigated the role of γ-actin (ACTG1) in GC progression. Bioinformatics analyses revealed that ACTG1 is upregulated in GC tissues and correlates with poor patient prognosis. Functionally, the knockdown of ACTG1 suppressed GC cell proliferation and metastasis in both in vitro and in vivo models. Transcriptomic sequencing identified COL21A1 as a key downstream effector, and KEGG analysis indicated involvement...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomimetic hydrogel for the construction of patient-derived bladder cancer organoids with aggressive growth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In cancer, the extracellular matrix (ECM) reorganization, notably collagen, forming dense, thickened, and orderly structures, affects tumor traits. Bladder cancer organoids (BCOs) mimic tumor properties for personalized medicine. However, current organoid scaffolds lack tumor-such as collagen, crucial for cell growth and migration. Previous efforts to incorporate mesoscale collagen fibers extracted directly from tumors into scaffolds were limited by the size of the tumor tissue and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating thermal liquid biopsy, clinical data, and mass spectrometry for early diagnosis and biomarker discovery in colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early detection of colorectal cancer is essential to improving survival, where yet current diagnostic tools show limited performance. This study aimed to enhance diagnostic accuracy by integrating clinical variables with thermogram profiles obtained through serum-based thermal liquid biopsy and analyzed using machine learning models. We evaluated 328 patients with colorectal cancer and 355 symptomatic individuals with non-organ-specific cancer signs but negative diagnostic evaluations, to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of metabolic stability under environmental perturbations using a kinetic model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cells robustly maintain metabolic functions despite environmental fluctuations that broadly alter reaction kinetics. However, kinetic models of cellular metabolism often exhibit fragility, losing stability with minor parameter changes. This discrepancy suggests that cells possess metabolic regulations that preserve the stable state under environmental perturbations. To understand the principles of metabolic robustness, we investigated the effects of temperature changes on a kinetic model of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and treatment-related predictors of complete response after total neoadjuvant therapy for rectal cancer in a large multicenter analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: More intensive TNT protocols were associated with higher CR rates. Smoking cessation may be beneficial but requires external validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic biomarkers for idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis: findings from ISABELA clinical trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We provide new insights into the prognostic value of MMP-7 and CCL18 in identifying high-risk IPF patients in the largest cohort to date. The combination of high baseline MMP-7 and CCL18 levels, along with longitudinal changes in CCL18, has the potential to enhance risk stratification and support efficacy assessment and monitoring in clinical trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differentiating benign and malignant solitary pulmonary nodules through exhaled breath analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that breath analysis could improve nodule management by refining patient selection for CT screening and reducing unnecessary invasive procedures or follow-up scans. Further validation through larger multicentre studies is needed to confirm these results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upfront combination therapy with nintedanib and anti-inflammatory agents for progressive pulmonary fibrosis: a multicentre, single-arm phase 2 study (TOP-ILD)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Early combination therapy with tacrolimus, prednisolone and nintedanib was associated with improved pulmonary function and was well tolerated in previously untreated PPF patients. Our findings suggest the potential of this regimen as an initial treatment strategy, but further validation in larger randomised controlled trials is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Multi-sensory integration treatment for preschool children with intermittent exotropia and idiopathic scoliosis comorbidity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report evaluates a novel multi-sensory integration training (MSIT) protocol, combining binocular disparate vision perception training with physiotherapeutic scoliosis-specific exercises in two pediatric patients (aged 4 and 5 years) with comorbid non-syndromic strabismus and idiopathic scoliosis. Both patients presented with intermittent exotropia, amblyopia, and thoracic scoliosis (Cobb angles of 10° and 13°, respectively). Following the individualized MSIT intervention, marked...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antihypertensive therapy in diabetes mellitus: efficacy, safety, and metabolic impacts in type 1 and type 2 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severe pediatric hypocalcemia in Vietnam: etiologic profile, clinical outcomes and risk factors in 246 cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Severe pediatric hypocalcemia in Vietnam predominantly affects infants and young children and is largely attributable to preventable vitamin D deficiency. While vitamin D deficiency is globally recognized, this study provides novel region-specific insight into the high frequency of symptomatic presentations, including seizures and cardiac events, in a tropical setting with presumed adequate sunlight exposure. It also emphasizes distinct biochemical phenotypes that allow early...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The future of Asian biophysics built through Korea-Japan collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41704586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A trolamine-enabled shape-morphing poly(Vinyl Alcohol) hydrogel with adaptive adhesion and therapeutic function for burn wound healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Burn injuries are commonly treated using wound dressings; however, conventional materials often suffer from inadequate adhesion control, poor adaptability to irregular wounds, and secondary tissue damage during removal. Thus, this study reports a multifunctional hydrogel burn wound dressing composed of poly(vinyl alcohol) (PVA), borax, tannic acid (TA), trolamine (TrA), and xylitol (Xyl), designed to address these clinical challenges through interfacial and physicochemical modulation. Dynamic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peucedanum japonicum Thunb. ameliorates age-related muscle loss by improving mitochondrial function in aged mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41701439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peucedanum japonicum Thunb. (PJ), also known as costal hog fennel, is an edible medicinal plant recognized for its potential health benefits. We previously demonstrated the protective effects of PJ against muscle atrophy in young mice. In the present study, we investigated whether PJ also inhibits age-related muscle loss in aged mice. PJ treatment of primary myoblasts derived from aged mice attenuated myotube diameter reduction, suppressed the expression of atrogenes, and prevented the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41701439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-assembly networks of azobenzene with hydrogen and halogen bonds on Au(111)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41700764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The self-assembly of azobenzene, a prototypical photo-switchable molecule, has been extensively studied through hydrogen-bond-driven motifs. However, systems incorporating halogen bonds, which often compete with hydrogen bonds, remain rare. Here, we investigate the self-assembled structures of azobenzene derivatives terminated with hydroxyl and bromo groups on the Au(111) surface using scanning tunneling microscopy. Three distinct supramolecular motifs-triangular, hexagonal, and striped-were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41700764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A strategy for simulation-driven CT metal artifact reduction toward improving network generalizability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41699969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We proposed a self-supervised metal artifact reduction framework that combines MLP-based beam-hardening correction with a conditional latent diffusion model in the imaging physics framework. The MLP module provides physics motivated beam-hardening corrected CT images, while the residual artifact simulation strategy enables fully self-supervised training without the need for paired data. The proposed method demonstrated superior artifact suppression and structural preservation on both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41699969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shared white matter connectome-based correlates of self-reproach, response failure, spatial planning, and resilience in patients with subthreshold depression: a graph theory approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Social Determinants on Healthcare Transition Readiness Among Adolescent and Young Adult Childhood Cancer Survivors: A Mixed Methods Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: Healthcare transition readiness is crucial for adolescent and young adult childhood cancer survivors (AYA CCS) to ensure continuity of care as they move from pediatric to adult healthcare services. A systematic review of the evidence linking social determinants of health (SDoH) and healthcare transition readiness is needed to provide valuable insights into the impact of disparities on transition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entropy and thermal dynamics motivated by ternary nanocomposites and geometric influence of oblique channel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermal transport in converging/diverging channels finds applications in various engineering fields, including heat exchangers, microfluidics, and biomedical devices, due to their ability to enhance heat transfer and control fluid flow. The use of nanoparticles cannot be circumvented because of their promising characteristics. These materials widely used in applied thermal engineering, to enhance or control thermal transport in machinery, transformer, chemical engineering. The flow in tank...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explainable AI in education: integrating educational domain knowledge into the deep learning model for improved student performance prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning models, especially the Artificial Neural Network (ANN), are widely used for student performance prediction, their "black-box" nature often leads to unreliable learned relationships that contradict educational domain knowledge, limiting both trustworthiness and further performance improvement. Based on Shapley Additive Explanations (SHAP), this study developed an ANN using a public dataset containing 395 Portuguese high school students' mathematics performance records. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-incision robotic complete mesocolic excision for right-sided colon neoplasms: technical and oncologic feasibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Single-incision robotic right colectomy using the dVSP is technically feasible and safe approach, offering favorable perioperative results and has proven oncologic safety based on long-term outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and histological analysis of multi-hole versus fully covered self-expandable metallic stents in a porcine model of hilar biliary obstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional fully covered self-expandable metallic stents (FCSEMS) for hilar biliary obstruction (HBO) remains limited due to the potential for side branch obstruction. The multi-hole covered self-expandable metallic stent (MHSEMS) was designed to overcome the limitations of FCSEMS by incorporating side holes into the fully covered membrane. This preclinical study evaluated the feasibility and safety of MHSEMS compared to conventional FCSEMS in a porcine HBO model. HBO was induced via...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of gastrectomy on the risk of alcohol-associated liver disease in patients with gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41703013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptomic insights into polyketides and toxin biosynthesis genes in freshwater dinoflagellates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Freshwater dinoflagellates are typically considered non-toxic, and their polyketides and toxin biosynthesis genes are largely unexplored. Here, we generated and analyzed the transcriptome of freshwater dinoflagellate Palatinus apiculatus and compared it with the transcriptome data from Peridinium bipes and Ceratium furcoides to investigate the presence and diversity of polyketide synthases (PKS), fatty acid synthases (FAS), and saxitoxin (STX) biosynthesis genes (sxt). We identified 95, 117, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in macular structure after removal of epiretinal membrane in combined hamartomas of the retina and retinal pigment epithelium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the effect of epiretinal membrane (ERM) removal in the combined hamartomas of the retina and retinal pigment epithelium (CHRRPE) patients. In this retrospective, comparative case series, 15 CHRRPE patients were included. Six patients received ERM surgery (operation group) and 9 patients were observed (observation group). The differences of age at diagnosis and the severity of ERM were not statistically significant for the operation and observation group at initial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marginal effect of clean energy, nuclear energy-related R&amp;D investment, energy security risk, and policy uncertainty on the environment in the USA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Postoperative Complications in Patients With Lung Cancer and Idiopathic Pulmonary Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This novel scoring system consisting of six easily accessible clinical variables may help predict postoperative pulmonary complications and guide treatment decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of trivalent cation cross-linked quorum quenching beads for biofouling mitigation and phosphorus removal in a membrane bioreactor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study applied quorum-quenching cell-entrapping beads (QQ-CEB) to mitigate membrane fouling and enhance phosphorus removal in a membrane bioreactor (MBR). Instead of suspending QQ-CEB in the MBR, immobilising it on a recovery net maintained the effluent total phosphorus removal at approximately 50%. It extended the system's operational period by about 2.2 times compared to a conventional MBR. Membrane fouling mitigation was attributed to quorum-quenching activity, reducing microbial products...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Vocal Development in Young Children with Simultaneous Bilateral Cochlear Implants: A Short-term Longitudinal Acoustic Analysis of Spontaneous Speech]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Despite persistent group differences in certain acoustic measures, children with simultaneous bilateral CIs exhibited developmental patterns that were increasingly consistent with those of their TH peers. Therefore, early bilateral implantation might facilitate more age-appropriate vocal development in young children with CIs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pupil size as a predictor of visual outcomes with an enhanced monofocal intraocular lens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative and postoperative pupil size ≥4.0 mm, as measured by Anterion, was associated with better UCDVA with enhanced monofocal intraocular lenses. However, further research is needed to confirm if this results from the lens design or physiological confounders like diffraction. Measurement discrepancies between AS SS-OCT devices highlight the need for standardisation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proposal for Risk-Adjusted Surveillance Strategies in Extrahepatic Bile Duct Cancer with Cost-Effectiveness Validation: A Real World Multi-Institutional Cohort Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A risk-adjusted survival model tailored to prognostic factors and RT status enables individualized surveillance, improves recurrence detection, and reduces unnecessary visits supporting efficient and cost-effective survivorship care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The invasive non-typhoidal Salmonella vaccine landscape: Innovations and challenges ahead]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invasive non-typhoidal Salmonella disease represents a major public health challenge, particularly in sub-Saharan Africa, where it is a leading cause of community-acquired bloodstream infections. Despite its significant morbidity and mortality, no licensed vaccines exist. Recognizing this unmet need, multiple global health initiatives and targeted investments have advanced iNTS vaccine development. These efforts have advanced several promising candidates employing diverse platform technologies,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unique characteristics of pediatric sporadic vestibular schwannoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Children, particularly those under 14 years, experienced significantly poorer tumor control after surgery for sporadic VS compared with adults, despite similar tumor size and location. The higher recurrence and regrowth rates observed in the pediatric cohort suggest that a more aggressive treatment and surveillance approach may be warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct clinicopathologic features and efficacy of adjuvant therapy in intraductal papillary mucinous carcinoma compared with conventional pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Clinical features and prognosis differ considerably among colloid IPMC, tubular IPMC, and cPDAC. Unlike cPDAC, where systemic treatment significantly improves prognosis, favorable outcomes in IPMC depend primarily on early detection and R0 resection. Developing effective adjuvant treatment strategies tailored for IPMC is therefore essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702307/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrically controlled hyaluronic acid-based hydrogel for sustained and repeatable metronomic chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving sustained plasma drug concentrations within the therapeutic range is essential for effective metronomic chemotherapy, but poor dose control and patient noncompliance remain major clinical challenges. Existing electro-responsive drug delivery systems often have limited clinical utility due to biodegradability, cytotoxicity, or manufacturing complexity. In this study, we present HTZ@D, a biocompatible, biodegradable, and electro-responsive hydrogel composed of hyaluronic acid, tannic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mammalian AHR2 loss: Evolutionary patterns, mechanisms, and relevance of biological factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental contamination by dioxins and polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons threatens wildlife health, yet the molecular basis of interspecies variation in toxicological sensitivity remains poorly understood. The aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AHR) mediates dioxin-like responses and typically exists as two isoforms (AHR1 and AHR2) across vertebrates but mammals exhibit a unique evolutionary restructuring characterized by widespread loss of AHR2. To elucidate the evolutionary patterns and mechanisms...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41702107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260218145111&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>