<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 07:38:01 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in livestock manure biochar Development in Korea: A review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In Korea, livestock manure (LM)-derived biochar is emerging as a key solution for carbon neutrality and sustainable LM management. With LM generation reaching approximately 50 million tons annually, more than 70% has been treated through composting and applied to farmland. However, composting has caused environmental concerns, including emissions of greenhouse gases (CH(4) and N(2)O), ammonia (NH(3), a precursor of PM(2.5)), and non-point source pollution adversely affecting water and soil...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A colorimetric strategy for quantifying amino acids using E. coli auxotrophs displaying gold-binding proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a cell-based colorimetric assay for amino acid quantification using Escherichia coli auxotrophs engineered to grow exclusively in the presence of their corresponding target amino acids and to display gold-binding proteins (GBPs) on their surface. Upon the addition of gold nanoparticles (AuNPs), the surface-expressed GBPs mediate AuNP aggregation, resulting in a distinct color shift from pink to blue. This approach enables the detection of ten essential amino acids through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical Study With Clinical Significance of the Buccomandibular Space: A Complementary Ultrasonographic Study to Cadaveric Dissection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The buccomandibular space is a potential space located within the oral and maxillofacial regions. This morphological study aimed to provide a detailed anatomical description and ultrasonographic examination of the buccomandibular space and its adjacent structures, to discuss its clinical significance-particularly in relation to pathological conditions such as the spread of odontogenic infections, complications associated with antiaging injectables, and tumor invasion-and to offer valuable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Preoperative Metformin Use with Postoperative Mortality and Morbidity in Type 2 Diabetes Patients Undergoing Noncardiac Surgery: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative use of metformin is associated with reduced postoperative mortality and complications in diabetic patients undergoing noncardiac surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel cross-attentive network for classifying cervical metastatic lymph nodes on B- and D-mode ultrasound images in oral squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: LNM-Net demonstrates strong potential as a clinical decision-support tool for preoperative lymph node metastasis assessment in oral squamous cell carcinoma. Despite current limitations such as dataset size and cross-institutional variability, the model offers a promising supplementary aid, particularly in settings with limited radiological expertise.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Site-selective addition of succinimide motif through nitro-assisted C-H functionalization of (hetero) arenes under rhodium catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Succinimide motifs are recognized as privileged cores in anticonvulsants and antipsychotics such as phensuximide, ethosuximide, and lurasidone. These succinimides can be readily converted into pharmaceutically important pyrrolidines and γ-lactam scaffolds, making them highly promising compounds in drug discovery. Nitroarenes are also important chemical feedstocks and have attracted increased attention owing to their versatile applications in pharmaceuticals, functional materials, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors and early recurrence patterns following curative-intent resection of distal cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ER after curative-intent resection has outcomes comparable to non-curative disease, supporting risk-adapted staging and evaluation of neoadjuvant strategies for high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles from mesenchymal stromal cells: an emerging therapy for intractable neonatal disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neonatal disorders affecting different organs are highly multifactorial and involve a complex interplay among prematurity, inflammation, oxidative stress, tissue injury, immune dysregulation, and impaired regeneration. Conditions such as hypoxic-ischemic encephalopathy, intraventricular hemorrhage, neonatal stroke, bronchopulmonary dysplasia, and necrotizing enterocolitis often result from or cause multi-organ dysfunction. This multifaceted nature presents a substantial therapeutic challenge, as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes in Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease Patients with Disease Stability: Data from the KOCOSS Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) is a heterogeneous disease with progressive airflow limitation. Despite therapeutic advances, current treatments poorly halt COPD progression. Disease stability (DS) is a proposed treatment goal, but its clinical significance remains uncertain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International consensuses and guidelines on managing ocular Behçet's disease by the Academy of Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO), the Asia-Pacific Vitreo-retina Society (APVRS), the Asia-Pacific Society of Ocular Inflammation and Infection (APSOII), and the Academia Retina Internationalis (ARI)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Behçet's disease remains a complex and challenging form of uveitis, marked by a high rate of relapse, significant inflammation, and a long-term risk of visual acuity loss. The introduction of biologics, especially anti-tumour necrosis factor (TNF) agents, has revolutionized treatment, significantly reducing sight-threatening complications and minimizing the adverse effects of steroid therapy. However, several challenges persist, including variable clinical presentations, a high incidence of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence of Respiratory Infections after the COVID-19 Pandemic (2023-2024) and Its Association of Vaccination Among Entire Populations in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives We aimed to investigate nationwide trends in respiratory infections during and after the COVID-19 pandemic and to evaluate the risk according to the COVID-19 vaccine dose. Methods Using the database, which integrates the insurance claims and vaccination records for the entire Korean population (N=51,645,564), trends were assessed using SARIMAX models. We assessed associations between the doses that have been received until June 1, 2023, and the onset of respiratory infections, using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time trends in mortality from heart failure and atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease in people with and without diabetes: a multi-national population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Contemporary trends in cardiovascular disease (CVD) cause-specific mortality by diabetes status are inadequately described. We examined trends by diabetes status in coronary heart disease (CHD), cerebrovascular disease, and heart failure mortality, and mortality rate ratios (people with diabetes versus those without diabetes) across nine high-income jurisdictions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is the triptorelin stimulation test comparable to the gonadorelin stimulation test in diagnosing central precocious puberty in boys?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of continuous glucose monitoring in improving glycemic control in adolescents with type 1 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CGM use in Korean children and adolescents with T1DM significantly improves HbA1c levels over 12 months compared to SMBG. The implementation of CGM may provide valuable benefits in glycemic control and potentially reduce the risk of diabetes-related complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of high-normal thyroid-stimulating hormone levels with metabolic syndrome and abdominal obesity in euthyroid adolescents: insights from the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In euthyroid adolescents, a significant trend was observed between TSH quartile and MetS. Specifically, high-normal TSH levels showed a significant association with abdominal obesity, a key component of MetS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ChatGPT: how to use it and the pitfalls/cautions in academia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of large language models (LLMs) in academic research has transformed traditional research methodologies. This review investigates the current state, applications, and limitations of LLMs, particularly ChatGPT, in medical and scientific research. I performed a systematic review of recent literature and LLM development reports in artificial intelligence-assisted research tools, including commercial LLM services (GPT-4o, Claude 3, Gemini Pro) and specialized research platforms...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Physical Activity and the Risk of Dementia Among Patients With Depression: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Consistent engagement in PA, particularly after the onset of depression, is associated with a reduced risk of dementia. These findings underscore the importance of PA as a potential intervention for mitigating cognitive decline in depressed individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Relationship Between Depression and Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder Symptoms in Children Using Brain Activity Monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that alpha and theta activity might serve as a reliable neurophysiological marker of ADHD symptom severity, while delta activity might function as a reliable biological marker of depression severity in children with ADHD. However, further research is needed to generalize the results of this study.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[All-Cause Mortality and Bleeding Risks Associated With Serotonin Reuptake Inhibitors in Patients With End-Stage Kidney Disease and Depression: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with ESKD and depression, the use of strong SRIs was associated with a reduced risk of all-cause death and major bleeding hospitalization compared to the use of weak or intermediate SRIs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of AI-related patents, energy transition, environmental policy stringency, income, and energy consumption sub-types on the environmental sustainability: Evidence from China by KRLS approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Due to the increasing negative effects on humanity, searching for potential solutions to combat environmental problems has been developing. Accordingly, the study examines the effect of a set of critical factors on environmental sustainability (ES) proxied by ecological footprint (EFP) and load capacity factor (LCF) in China. In this context, the study considers AI-related patents, energy transition, environmental policy stringency (EPS), income, and energy consumption (EC) sub-types and applies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ocular motor dysfunction in patients with multiple system atrophy and Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MSA exhibits significantly more pronounced VOR cancellation deficits, horizontal GEN, CPN, saccadic hypermetria, and prolonged saccade latency than PD. These findings suggest a link to the more widespread neurodegeneration characteristic of MSA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differentiating suicide attempters from suicidal ideators: Differences between major depressive and bipolar disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study revealed different factors distinguishing between SIs and SAs in those with MDD versus BD, suggesting the importance of considering diagnostic differences within the ideation-to-action framework. Future research should prospectively evaluate the predictive validity of these differentiating factors in assessing suicide risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of robotic assisted gait training on physical activity, motor function, and quality of life in children with spastic cerebral palsy: Exploratory pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Wearable robot-assisted gait training appears to enhance physical activity and mobility in children with spastic CP and may be considered a promising therapeutic intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhaled microcystin-LR may induce acute liver failure through hepatic congestion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As cyanobacteria growth increases due to climate change, health issues resulting from exposure to microcystin-leucine-arginine (MC-LR), a toxin produced by cyanobacteria, are becoming a pressing public health concern. In this study, we found that the diameter of water droplets containing MC-LR was about 5 μm, indicating they are inhalable. When instilled intranasally to male mice at doses of 30, 150, and 300 μg/kg, death occurred in the groups exposed to 150 and 300 μg/kg (on Day 8 and Day 2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between changes in social isolation status and frailty among older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The transition to an isolated state was associated with frailty among older adults. These findings emphasize the need for early identification and active interventions to address social isolation to prevent frailty among older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic sonocatalytic degradation of carbamazepine and 17α-ethinylestradiol in the presence of carbon nanotube yarn]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmaceuticals such as carbamazepine and endocrine disruptors such as 17α-ethinylestradiol are persistently present in aquatic environments and pose serious ecological and human health concerns due to their chemical stability and limited removal efficiency by conventional wastewater treatment methods. In this study, a carbon nanotube yarn catalyzed high-frequency ultrasonic system was developed to synergistically enhance the degradation of carbamazepine and 17α-ethinylestradiol. carbon nanotube...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint inhibitors for recurrent ovarian clear cell carcinoma: Real-world outcomes from a Korean multicenter study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although ICIs were well tolerated, their antitumor activity in recurrent OCCC was limited. Further studies are warranted to clarify the therapeutic role of ICIs in this setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Multiple-trait Polygenic Risk Score with Obesity and Cardiometabolic Diseases in Korean Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We conducted a comprehensive genetic investigation of obesity in a cohort of 93,673 Korean individuals, categorized by body mass index and waist circumference using Korean-specific and international criteria. To explore the genetic architecture of obesity and its related comorbidities, we performed genome-wide association studies and constructed polygenic risk scores (PRSs) using both conventional single-trait and advanced multiple-trait models, including the PRSsum approach. Our analyses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarcopenia in Atrial Fibrillation: A Risk Factor for Adverse Outcomes in a UK Biobank Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Even after PS-weighting analysis, some residual confounders may remain; however, sarcopenia was independently associated with adverse clinical outcomes, particularly mortality and bleeding risk. Screening for sarcopenia may enhance risk stratification and management, particularly in patients receiving anticoagulation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Utility of Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning to Automate and Accelerate Follicle Counts in Human Ovarian Tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our AI-driven approach enhances follicle quantitation accuracy and reproducibility, representing a promising tool to support research and clinical decision-making in fertility preservation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioaugmentation to improve anaerobic digestion of fish waste: Feed-to-microbes ratio, augmentation dosage and kinetic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated bioaugmentation using fish waste (FW) adapted microbial consortia to overcome the limitations of inhibitory metabolites during anaerobic mono-digestion of FW. An enriched consortium developed through sequential batches improved COD removal from 62.4 % to 80.7 % and CH(4) yield from 369.7 to 434.9 mL/gVS(added). Protein-degrading bacteria (Fastidiosipila, Proteiniphilum, and Sedimentibacter) increased to 70.2 % of total abundance, while Methanosarcinaceae became dominant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A computational model of radial scaffolds in the human fetal brain based on MRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The organization of the human cerebral cortex during fetal development is regulated by multiple processes, including neurogenesis and neuronal migration, which are essential for cortical expansion and folding patterns. According to the radial unit hypothesis, neurons originate in the germinal zone and migrate radially along the radial glial scaffolds to reach the cortical plate. However, the spatial distributions of these scaffolds and their roles in cortical folding remain unclear....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peptide Hormones and Bile Acids Shaping Immune Tolerance of the Liver: Implications and Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postprandially reabsorbed bile acids, along with various peptide hormones released following a meal, orchestrate complex events associated with digestion and prepare the body for the disposal of incoming nutrients by regulating metabolism. Interestingly, these factors have also been shown to modulate immune function. For example, recent interest in weight-loss agents such as semaglutide has demonstrated their ability to attenuate inflammation and provide benefits in diverse clinical contexts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of cooling rate on the microstructural and mechanical properties of speed-sintered monolithic zirconia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: To evaluate the effect of different speed-sintering cooling rates on the phase composition, microstructure, optical and mechanical properties of monolithic zirconia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The hitchhiker's guide to cross-species DNA delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial hitchhikers are rewriting the rules of horizontal gene transfer. He, Patkowski, et al. reveal how phage satellites assemble chimeric infective particles that deliver DNA across species boundaries through 'tail piracy'. This discovery reframes microbial innovation and provides a blueprint for next-generation biotechnologies, achieving what phage engineering has long pursued.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additives as external plasticisers in starch-based bioplastics - towards improving the properties of food packaging: A review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The environmental burden of petroleum-based plastics, especially in single-use packaging, has driven the search for sustainable, bio-based alternatives. Starch-based materials are promising due to their abundance, low cost, and biodegradability. However, native starch lacks the mechanical and barrier properties required for packaging applications, necessitating the use of plasticisers and additives. This review critically evaluates starch as the primary biopolymer and its interactions with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of the dynamic nature of upper gastrointestinal pH: A pooled analysis using the fluid aspiration technique]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This manuscript compiles a set of temporal pH profiles of the upper gastrointestinal (GI) tract under varying physiological and pharmacological conditions, including water and food intake as well as proton pump inhibitor (PPI) co-medication. A pooled analysis was conducted using data from 19 clinical studies previously performed in our laboratory, all of which employed standardised protocols and measurement techniques. Intraluminal pH was recorded in aspirated samples from the gastric antrum,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosome 15q15 Deletion Drives Brain Metastasis in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 15q15 deletion promotes BM development through aberrant MYC signaling and the subsequent reprogramming of carbohydrate metabolism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence-Based CBCT Segmentation in the Presence of Metallic Artefacts for 3D Virtual Orofacial Patient Generation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI-based CBCT segmentation for generating 3D virtual patients is feasible, even in cases complicated by metallic artefacts. Zirconia crowns had minimal impact on segmentation accuracy for mandibular teeth and the mandible, though zirconia crown segmentation was more affected. Expert clinical supervision remains essential to ensure the reliability and accuracy of these virtual models.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Habitual consumption of fermented milk products containing Lacticaseibacillus paracasei strain Shirota and risk of anaemia in the elderly]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anaemia in the elderly increases the risk of cardiovascular disease, cognitive decline, and death. Probiotics have recently been shown to be potentially effective in preventing the onset or improving the condition of anaemia. Here, we retrospectively investigated the relationship between fermented milk intake over the prior 10 years and the risk of developing anaemia during the same period. The participants were community-dwelling Japanese aged 65-94 years who had not developed anaemia in the 10...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preconception, gestation, and childhood exposure to air pollution and risk of polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) in a US girls cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Exposure to ambient air pollution (AP) during sensitive developmental periods could dysregulate the reproductive system, resulting in later in life menstrual disorders, including polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS). Minimal research exists examining the relationship between AP exposure and PCOS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Magnetoneurography as a novel functional imaging technique for cervical myelopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MNG was able to visualise the spatiotemporal course of neural currents, which is difficult to record in conventional electrophysiological examinations. Because the lesional level of the spinal cord in MRI is not always consistent with the neurological findings, MNG might be able to detect the electrophysiological change in the spinal cord at a level below the compression site.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regional variation in age-related decline of acetylcholine-induced sweating in the forearm and lower limb: an exploratory study in males]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[It remains unclear how progressive aging alters regional differences in cholinergic sweat gland function across forearm and lower limb sites. We assessed acetylcholine-induced sweating in 52 healthy males aged 19-69 years, grouped by decade: 20s (n = 19, 21 ± 1 years), 40s (n = 12, 43 ± 3 years), 50s (n = 10, 53 ± 1 years), and 60s (n = 11, 66 ± 3 years). Sweat rate, activated sweat gland density, and sweat gland output were measured via transdermal iontophoresis at the volar forearm, anterior...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of comprehensive genomic profiling test for Ewing sarcoma in pediatric patients and adults using the nationwide clinical and genomic database in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared to previous reports, Japanese ES cases showed lower STAG2 and higher TP53 mutation frequencies. CDKN2A and CDKN2B deletions may serve as prognostic biomarkers indicating unfavorable outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clonal Hematopoiesis and Incident Heart Failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Results of this cohort study suggest that CHIP, especially non-DNMT3A CHIP, was associated with incident HF. Other CHIP-associated comorbidities explained only a minority of the association between non-DNMT3A CHIP and HF. These findings suggest that CHIP is an HF risk factor and potential therapeutic target.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The use of alcohol-free and low-alcohol drinks in pregnancy in the UK]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alcohol-free drinks [beers, ciders, wines, and spirits containing <0.05% alcohol by volume (ABV)], and low-alcohol drinks (between 0.05% and 1.2% ABV) are increasingly available and may be used as a harm reduction measure. However, it is not known what pregnant women think and feel about these drinks and how regularly they are consumed before and during pregnancy. A cross-sectional online survey was developed and piloted. Women ≥18 years in the UK who were pregnant, or recently pregnant, were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-standardized mortality-to-incidence ratio for prostate cancer in the world]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel serum autoantibodies against alpha thalassemia/mental retardation syndrome X-linked, a component of promyelocytic leukaemia nuclear bodies, in dermatomyositis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Impact of Regurgitant Volume to Left Atrial Volume Ratio on Ventricular Functional Mitral Regurgitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The RVol/LAV ratio might serve as a valuable metric for improving risk stratification in patients with VFMR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Kidneys, Old Risks: Cardiovascular Challenges After Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kidney transplantation markedly improves survival and quality of life in patients with kidney failure, yet cardiovascular disease remains the leading cause of morbidity and mortality in kidney transplant recipients (KTRs). This review outlines the complex interplay of traditional, transplant-specific, and recipient- and donor-related risk factors that sustain a high cardiovascular burden post-transplantation. While kidney function restoration reduces uremic toxins and improves cardiometabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Girinimbine produced in Bergera koenigii callus cultures with antiproliferative activity against glioblastoma stem-like cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Callus cultures derived from medicinal plants offer useful platforms for producing valuable secondary metabolites. We established a callus culture system from Bergera koenigii leaves and examined the effects of phytohormone composition on callus growth and carbazole alkaloid accumulation. To the best of our knowledge, this is the first report of girinimbine (1), a carbazole alkaloid, isolated from leaf-derived callus, and we further synthesized 1. Compound 1 displayed potent antiproliferative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41206560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When Life Hangs on a Breath: A Narrative Inquiry Into Nursing Presence and Hope]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accelerated Biological Aging and Midlife Frailty among U.S. Military Veterans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Injuries characterizing recent military service, such as traumatic brain injury and posttraumatic stress disorder, are linked to accelerated biological aging. If recent veterans have accelerated aging, they might also show early onset of aging-related phenotypes, such as frailty. In this study, we examined the prevalence of frailty and associations with biological aging using data from 1,654 post-9/11 veterans, who were followed for an average of 12.6 years. Biological aging was assessed using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined supplementation of essential oils, Saccharomyces cerevisiae and isomaltooligosaccharides improves intestinal absorption and immune functions in weaned piglets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the synergistic effects of essential oils (EOs), Saccharomyces cerevisiae (SC), and isomaltooligosaccharides (IMO) on intestinal health and systemic immunity in weaned piglets using a randomized block design across two commercial farms. Within each farm, 108 piglets weaned at 24 d of age were randomly divided into 3 groups (3 pens per group, 12 piglets per pen). The piglets were fed a basal diet (CON) and a basal diet supplemented with antibiotics (0.5 kg/t colistin sulfate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208033/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bayesian Adaptive Randomized Trial of Blended Cognitive Behavioral Therapy for Severe Fatigue in Stable Diffuse Glioma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: bCBT significantly reduces fatigue and improves anxiety and HRQoL in patients with diffuse glioma. These findings enable evidence-based supportive care strategies for reducing fatigue and enhancing HRQoL in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antimicrobial drug-resistant Neisseria gonorrhoeae (GC) infections in men using doxycycline postexposure prophylaxis. A substudy of the ANRS 174 DOXYVAC trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DoxyPEP use was associated with a significant increase in high-level tetracycline resistance and decreased susceptibility to cefixime in GC. AMR should therefore be closely monitored when using this strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expansion of Myeloid-Derived Suppressor Cells and Lymphocyte Apoptosis Beyond B-Cell Deficiency in X-Linked Agammaglobulinemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[X-linked agammaglobulinemia (XLA) is caused by Bruton tyrosine kinase gene mutations, leading to B-cell deficiency. This study aimed to investigate myeloid-derived suppressor cells (MDSCs) frequency, lymphocyte apoptosis and clinical significance in patients with XLA. The study comprised 46 paediatric (mean age: 9.9 ± 4.8 years) and 21 adult patients (24.6 ± 5.9 years). Total MDSCs (HLA-DR^(-)CD33^(+)CD11b^(+)) were subdivided into CD15^(+) polymorphonuclear (PMN-MDSCs) and CD14^(+) monocytic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Repositioning Triazoles as Phosphodiesterase-4 Inhibitors to Suppress COVID-19 Cytokine Storms and Fungal Co-Infections via Docking and Simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe COVID-19 cases are often characterised by a hyperinflammatory cytokine storm, which leads to immune dysregulation and increased mortality. Simultaneously, opportunistic fungal infections such as mucormycosis have been increasingly reported, especially in immunocompromised individuals. Triazole antifungals are widely used to treat such infections, but their potential immunomodulatory effects remain underexplored. This study aimed to investigate the off-target potential of commonly used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Supervised Noise Adaptive MRI Denoising via Repetition to Repetition (Rep2Rep) Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Rep2Rep learning offers an effective self-supervised denoising for low-field MRI by leveraging routinely acquired multi-repetition data. Its noise-adaptivity enables generalization to different SNR regimes without clean reference images. This makes Rep2Rep learning a promising tool for improving image quality and scan efficiency in low-field MRI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208014/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-branching eukaryotes and early events in protist evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The first eukaryotes evolved from their archaean ancestors in the early Proterozoic, likely ca. 2000-1800 million years ago (Mya). Their macroscopic multicellular descendants, such as plants, heterokont algae, animals and fungi, appeared hundreds of million years later. During this intermediate period of eukaryote evolution, dozens of important protist lineages emerged, either unicellular or with only simple forms of multicellularity. Recent discoveries and phylogenetic analyses point to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Circuit with Top-Down Inhibitory Feedback Outperforms Optimal Bayesian Integration in Multisensory Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bayesian integration is posited as a fundamental computational mechanism underlying multisensory integration, and feedforward neural networks have been proposed to instantiate optimal Bayesian integration (OBI). However, empirical and theoretical research highlights the prevalence of neural feedback projections, raising questions about how recurrent neural networks might contribute to multisensory OBI. We simulated a two-layer neural circuit computational model with reciprocal projections...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41208000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variations of Corticotropin-Releasing Factor Receptor 1α Contribute to the Blunted HPA Axis Responses to Hypoxia in Plateau Mammals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Corticotropin-releasing factor (CRF) and its receptor (CRFR1) are critical components of the hypothalamic-pituitary-adrenocortical (HPA) axis. Ochotona curzoniae (O. curzoniae), Myospalax baileyi (M. baileyi), and Microtus oeconomus (M. oeconomus) have diversely evolved adaptive strategies to the extreme environment at high altitude. Here, we found blunted HPA axis responsiveness in native Tibetan mammals. CRF was 100% conserved, three amino-acid variations were in M. oeconomus-urocortin (UCN),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of energy metabolism pathways in promoting phytoremediation of cadmium contamination by Bacillus amyloliquefaciens Bam1]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Remediation plants combined with plant growth promoting rhizobacteria (PGPR) is one of the most promising means of remediation of Cd-contaminated soils at present. One of the PGPR, named Bacillus amyloliquefaciens Bam1, possessed high Cd resistance. Herein, comparative transcriptome analysis of B. amyloliquefaciens Bam1 revealed that its main energy metabolism pathway was significantly down-regulated under Cd stress. The pivotal genes involved in the energy production pathway, such as TCA cycle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the implementation of nurses' advanced competencies in emergency departments: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emergency department (ED) overcrowding is a critical issue that compromises patient safety, prolongs waiting times, and increases staff workload. Contributing factors include insufficient primary-community care integration, staffing shortages, operational inefficiencies, and an ageing population with complex chronic conditions. These pressures are further exacerbated during disasters and are expected to worsen with the rising frequency of climate-related crises. Task shifting and the expansion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physician Perceptions and Intentions in Response to Unsupportive Data for Off-label Uses: An Experimental Study with Primary Care Providers and Oncologists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Disclosures about unsupportive data for off-label uses are important and useful for prescribing decisions. Physicians who prescribe drugs for off-label uses more frequently or have prescribed the drug previously may discount the importance of the information. Tailoring the specificity of the disclosure to the needs of the audience may increase its effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Reversible posterior leukoencephalopathy syndrome (RPLS) in a patient with chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) treated with Acalabrutinib, a Bruton's tyrosine kinase (BTK) inhibitor: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tongxinluo Adjunctive Therapy and 12-Month Cardiovascular Outcomes after ST-Segment Elevation Myocardial Infarction: A Real-World Multicenter Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Adjunctive Tongxinluo therapy demonstrated significant improvement in 12-month cardiovascular outcomes with favorable safety profile, suggesting potential benefits of integrating traditional Chinese medicine with evidence-based STEMI management. (Registration No. ChiCTR100054466).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone Marrow Mesenchymal Stromal Cell Osteogenesis is driven by Paracrine signals from Regulatory T Cell]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bone regeneration is a dynamic process regulated by the interplay between the immune and skeletal systems. Regulatory T cells (Treg), a specialized subset of CD4^(+) T cells, play a crucial role in immunomodulation and bone regeneration by regulating the immune response and interacting with progenitor cells. However, the specific mechanisms through which Treg influence the osteogenic differentiation of bone marrow stromal cells (BMSC) remain unexplored. Treg were isolated from six healthy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MRI-based pedicle bone quality score predicts cage subsidence following oblique lumbar interbody fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated MRI-based PBQ scores are significantly associated with an increased risk of cage subsidence following single-level OLIF. The PBQ score may serve as a reliable preoperative imaging parameter for guiding surgical planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207968/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of Dabrafenib in Erdheim-Chester disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates the efficacy and safety of dabrafenib in BRAF^(V600E) mutant Erdheim-Chester disease (ECD). This retrospective study reviewed patients who received dabrafenib treatment for at least one month at Peking Union Medical College Hospital and the Cancer Hospital of the Chinese Academy of Medical Sciences from December 2021 to February 2025. All patients received dabrafenib 75 ~ 150 mg twice daily. Treatment response was assessed through radiological examinations, and the objective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing the use of melflufen (melphalan flufenamide) in relapsed or refractory multiple myeloma: recommendations for clinical practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this report, a panel of multiple myeloma experts assesses the role of melflufen (melphalan flufenamide) in the treatment of patients with relapsed or refractory multiple myeloma (RRMM). Based on available data, recommendations for administration of melflufen, management of adverse events and optimal patient selection are given. Melflufen, a first-in-class peptide-drug conjugate, is approved in the European Union and the United Kingdom in combination with dexamethasone for the treatment of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Descendants of hypertrophic chondrocytes promote angiogenesis by secreting THBS4 during bone growth and injury repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hypertrophic chondrocytes (HCs) could transform into osteoblastic lineage cells while the pathophysiological implications of HC transformation remain largely unknown. Here, we generated a mouse line utilizing Col10a1-Cre to induce DTA expression to genetically ablate HCs and their descendants. Col10a1-Cre; R26^(DTA/+) mice displayed dwarf phenotype, abnormal spongy bone, and significantly delayed drill-hole injuries healing, suggesting an indispensable role of HC lineage extension in bone growth...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207902/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating antidiabetic drug targets as potential therapeutic modulators for schizophrenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Antidiabetic drugs may possess therapeutic potential in schizophrenia by modulating specific drug-related pathways.These findings provide new theoretical support for the selection of ADs in patients with schizophrenia comorbid with diabetes, and also offer new insights for the future development of APs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risky decision-making in the balloon analogue risk task - the role of noradrenaline and cortisol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underscore the complexity of stress effects on decision-making and suggest that pharmacological activation of stress systems may not straightforwardly mimic psychosocial stress. Methodological factors such as timing, dosage, receptor specificity, and task familiarity likely play critical roles in modulating these effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Reciprocal deregulation of NKX3.1 and AURKA axis in castration-resistant prostate cancer and NEPC models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Novel compound heterozygous ABCA2 variants cause IDPOGSA, a variable phenotypic syndrome with intellectual disability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of the Effectiveness of Allergic Rhinitis Medications Using a Target Trial Emulation Approach Based on Mobile Health Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ex Vivo Modulation of the BNST by Parabrachial CGRP Projections Is Decreased After a History of Stress-Induced Anxiety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Activity in the parabrachial calcitonin gene-related peptide to bed nucleus of the stria terminalis (PBN[CGRP] → BNST) circuit associates with anxiety-like behavior. To test whether previous stress-induced anxiety is associated with neuronal adaptations in the PBN (CGRP) → BNST circuit, C57 mice were exposed to 4 days of daily forced swim stress (FSS). The novelty-suppressed feeding test (NSFT) demonstrated repeated FSS increased anxiety-like behavior. To assess if repeated FSS potentiates...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data Stitching for Dynamic Field Monitoring With NMR Probes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our proposed stitching method provides an effective means to characterize challenging imaging gradients using commercially available hardware and without assuming a linear gradient system, thereby having utility for many applications especially those aiming for ultrahigh-resolution MRI at ultrahigh field.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207863/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eleven-year trends in walnut-induced anaphylaxis in children in Japan: A multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Since the late 2010s, the incidence of walnut-induced anaphylaxis has rapidly increased in Japan, particularly among young children with first-episode reactions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TBCK syndrome pathogenesis: the TBCK-PPP1R21-C12orf4 complex regulating RAB5-dependent endo-lysosomal homeostasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of blood biomarkers in internal jugular vein for Alzheimer's disease pathologies: the Delta Method study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Systemic factors confound blood tests for the diagnosis of Alzheimer's disease (AD). The Delta Method study explored whether blood biomarkers from the vein proximal to the brain perform better in detecting cerebral Alzheimer's pathologies using PET or cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) biomarkers as reference standards in two independent cohorts (n = 463). Blood was collected from the internal jugular vein (IJV) and median cubital vein (MCV), and AD biomarkers were measured with Lumipulse G and Simoa...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Serum proteomics identifies biomarkers for predicting non-survivors in elderly COVID-19 patients" [Journal of Proteomics, volume 311 (2025) 105356]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virus-mediated gene fusion: igniting and sustaining oncogenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human papillomavirus (HPV) integration is known to cause host genome instability and subsequent structural variants. Recently, Khan and colleagues thoroughly characterized a recurrent FGFR3-TACC3 fusion caused by HPV integration in oropharyngeal squamous cell carcinoma (OPSCC) identifying synergistic interplay with HPV E6/E7 required for transformation. These findings reveal another mechanism in which virus integration can ignite tumorigenesis and a promising avenue for future investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Interaction of N-terminal peptide analogues of the Na+,K+-ATPase with membranes" [BBA Biomembr. 1860 (6) (2018) 1282-1291]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gastric lavage for neonates with coffee-ground hematemesis in early postnatal period: Randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GL did not significantly reduce the incidence of FI in neonates with coffee-ground hematemesis and thus it cannot be considered superior based on current results. However, it was well tolerated, and the study may have been underpowered. Exploratory analyses suggested potential benefits, particularly among formula-fed neonates, warranting further investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Etiological identification of Rickettsia typhi and Coxiella burnetii by metagenomic next-generation sequencing among adults with acute febrile illness in southern Taiwan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The validation of histological criteria from the IAIH-PG to distinguish AIH from drug-induced liver injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The new histological criteria exhibit good diagnostic efficacy in distinguishing AIH from DILI in China, with high AUROC. Key discriminators include low aminotransferase, ANA ≥1:160, lobular lymphoplasmacytic infiltrate and more than mild inflammation, which may further improve diagnostic accuracy for AIH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital twin-based bronchoscopy simulator improves training performance and skill retention of novices: a randomised controlled study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Training with diverse anatomical models significantly enhanced bronchoscopy performance compared with repetitive practice on a single standardised model with partially maintained learning gains at 3 months.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Climate Change and Dermatology: A Review and Update for 2026 and Beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Climate Change and its Influence on the Cutaneous Health of Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children's health is disproportionately impacted by the burning of fossil fuels and the subsequent production of greenhouse gases and air pollution. This is due to their developing physiology, unique behavior patterns, greater body surface area to volume ratio, and reliance on adults for their essential needs. Importantly, increases in air pollution and global warming negatively influence the skin health of children, including increasing the risk of inflammatory dermatoses, climate-sensitive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydroxyurea for Children with Sickle Cell Disease: A Practical Guide for Pediatric Clinicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydroxyurea is the cornerstone therapy for children with sickle cell disease (SCD). Children with sickle cell anemia (SCA; ∼64% of children with SCD) should be started on hydroxyurea as infants and continue treatment throughout childhood. Hydroxyurea reduces acute complications and chronic organ injury in children with SCA. Hydroxyurea may reduce acute complications in children with HbSC and HbSß^(+) with frequent complications, but the evidence is limited. We recommend a close partnership...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207740/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone Health and Energy Availability in Adaptive Athletes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adaptive athletes are a high performing yet medically complex group, facing unique challenges related to bone health and energy availability. Bone health is fundamental to athletic performance, injury prevention, and long-term physical function. However, many adaptive athletes are predisposed to compromised bone integrity due to factors such as impaired mobility, reduced mechanical loading, hormonal dysregulation, and comorbid conditions. The purpose of this article is to synthesize current...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One image is not enough: AI fuses vision to predict remission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome virus infection induces thymic atrophy in IFNAR<sup>-/-</sup> mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe fever with thrombocytopenia syndrome virus (SFTSV) causes severe disease in humans, yet the pathogenesis remains poorly understood. A hallmark of fatal SFTS cases is the marked depletion of T cells. Previous studies on T cell depletion have predominantly focused on alterations in blood and peripheral lymphoid organs, while the thymus, a critical site for T cell development, has remained largely overlooked. In this study, we employed a lethal murine infection model to investigate the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient and provider perspectives on the implementation of DPYD testing in oncology care clinics in an academic health system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients, caregivers, and providers were in favor of clinical DPYD testing to prevent fluoropyrimidine TRAEs but identified key barriers that can guide efforts towards scaling and maintenance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient and Caregiver Perspectives on the Use of Elemental Formula in Eosinophilic Gastrointestinal Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DOT1L promotes phenotypic transition of vascular smooth muscle cells following vascular injury in diabetes through activation of the FGFR4/PI3K/AKT/Jag/Notch signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vascular smooth muscle cell (VSMC) phenotypic transition contributes to restenosis, impacting the long-term efficacy of percutaneous coronary intervention in diabetic patients. While DOT1L is known to regulate atherosclerosis, its role in diabetic VSMC phenotypic modulation remains unclear. Using insulin-stimulated rat thoracic aorta VSMCs and a diabetic rat carotid artery balloon injury model, we investigated VSMC proliferation, migration, and collagen synthesis. Histological and molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilization of the All of Us Research Program in study of genetics in Yao syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This large case-control study of population genetics provides valuable insights into the genetic mechanisms of YAOS, and has significant implications for ordering genetic tests, interpretation of results, genomic diagnosis and counselling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding IgE-mediated autoimmunity and autoallergy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic inflammatory diseases affect millions of people and are associated with considerable clinical, humanistic and economic burden. Available treatments have limitations, e.g. they are toxic and/or prevent disease symptoms without affecting pathogenic drivers and disease course. Recent progress in the understanding of chronic inflammation can facilitate the development of targeted and disease-modifying therapy. In particular, IgE autoantibodies against self-antigens are thought to be linked...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omics insights into retinoic acid-mediated regulation of eosinophils in severe asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight ATRA's role in maintaining eosinophil homeostasis and counter-regulating IL-5-driven activation, offering insights into potential therapeutic strategies for severe asthma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term impact of nirsevimab on prevention of respiratory syncytial virus infection using a real-word global database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study indicated that the preventive effect of nirsevimab against RSV infection was maintained for up to 12 months following administration, whereas a preventive effect beyond 12 months was not observed. The results of this study need to be interpreted with caution owing to some important limitations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Model validation confirms variable relative biological effectiveness and elevated periventricular sensitivity after proton therapy of brain tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study validates recently proposed voxel-wise and patient-wise predictive models for localization and occurrence of late radiation-induced contrast enhancements after proton therapy for brain tumors. Using an independent patient cohort, we confirmed the models' accuracy and reliability, emphasizing an increased radiosensitivity in periventricular regions and a linear-energy-transfer-dependent relative biological effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing Observed with Self-Reported Hand Hygiene Adherence Among Bedside Nurses and Physicians at Two Hospitals in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found a disconnect between actual and perceived adherence to hand hygiene recommendations among bedside nurses and physicians in inpatient general medicine wards. This disconnect may be due to social desirability, self-serving, or overestimation biases, or time pressures. Awareness of such a disconnect may help policymakers increase hand hygiene rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GLP-1RAs and tirzepatide may reduce heart failure risk in obese but not in non-obese patients with cardiovascular or renal disease: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with cardiovascular or renal disease, GLP-1RAs and tirzepatide provide consistent cardiovascular and renal protection, with a possible benefit in reducing hospitalization for heart failure among individuals with obesity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical biosensors for detection of exosomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exosomes, nanoscale extracellular vesicles secreted by various cell types, have emerged as critical mediators of intercellular communication and valuable indicators of physiological and pathological states. Their stable presence in biofluids and ability to carry disease-specific molecular cargo make them ideal candidates for non-invasive diagnostics. Traditional exosome isolation and detection techniques, while foundational, often exhibit limitations in sensitivity, specificity, and scalability....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Passive to Active: Next-Generation Mechanically Active Dressings for Wound Healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditional passive dressings significantly slow down the wound healing process due to their lack of mechanical adaptability that matches human tissues. In contrast, mechanically active dressings (MADs), as a form of active intervention, can accelerate wound closure through their own mechanical deformation and are considered a key direction for next-generation wound care. Despite the continuous emergence of high-performance MADs in recent years, the relationship between their structural design...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular cloning and functional characterization of NQO1 in Nile tilapia (Oreochromis niloticus): a quinone oxidoreductase mitigating ammonia-induced oxidative stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NAD(P)H dehydrogenase [quinone] 1 (NQO1) is a mammalian quinone oxidoreductase, which can react with cell antioxidants and nucleophiles and reduce cell damage. Although NQO1 has been widely studied in mammals, its research in aquatic animals is relatively limited, especially in Nile tilapia (Oreochromis niloticus). In this study, we successfully cloned NQO1 (OnNQO1) of O. niloticus and studied its role in oxidative stress induced by ammonia exposure. The results showed that the open reading...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent progress in developing ATR inhibitors as anticancer agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA damage response (DDR) pathways are crucial for ensuring the stability of the genome.The ataxia telangiectasia mutated and Rad3-related (ATR) kinase plays a central role in orchestrating the DDR, responding to DNA damage and replication stress (RS), and facilitating G2/M and S checkpoint arrest, which initiates DNA repair processes. ATR has gained attention as a potential target for cancer treatment, with numerous ATR inhibitors has been the subject of clinical research at present. ATR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic-guided dose reduction of emicizumab in congenital hemophilia A: Interim Analysis of the DosEmi Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These interim-results suggest that bleeding control on PK-guided reduced dosing of emicizumab (target Ctrough 30±5 μg/mL) is similar to conventional dosing. All pre-specified criteria for study continuation and inclusion of participants <16 years were met.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rare and Underexplored Lobane- and Prenyleudesmane-Type Diterpenes Primarily from Corals with Additional Plant Sources-Biosynthesis and Pharmacological Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lobane- and prenyleudesmane-type diterpenoids represent structurally unique and biologically diverse natural products, predominantly isolated from soft corals in the genera Lobophytum and Sinularia. This review comprehensively covers the literature from 1978 to 2025, isolation methods, structural elucidation, biological evaluations, and proposed biosynthetic pathways. Based on their reported bioactivities, the compounds were systematically classified, and their potential biosynthetic pathways...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication and characterization of enteric microneedle patches for oral delivery of small and macromolecule compounds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Needle patches are commonly used for administration of therapeutics via several routes such as transdermal and buccal delivery. Researchers have further used this strategy for oral delivery of poorly permeable therapeutics by direct injections in the gastrointestinal epithelium, which raises safety concerns about the long-term adverse effects. This study aims to investigate the use of microneedles for oral delivery of compounds with a wide range of molecular weights. For this purpose, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular hydrogen mitigates acetaminophen-induced liver injury and enhances the effects of N-acetylcysteine in diabetic mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acetaminophen (APAP) overdose induces severe liver injury, especially in diabetic patients. N-acetylcysteine (NAC) is commonly used as an approved antidote for APAP toxicity; however, its narrow therapeutic window limits its clinical utility. This study investigated the protective effects of molecular hydrogen (H₂) against APAP-induced hepatotoxicity in diabetic mice. Diabetic db/db mice were provided with hydrogen-dissolved water (H₂-water) for two weeks prior to APAP administration....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteomics in interstitial lung disease: new insights into pathogenesis, diagnosis and treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Interstitial lung disease (ILD), representing a heterogeneous group of diffuse parenchymal lung disorders, is characterized by inflammation and/or fibrosis within the alveolar interstitium of the lung. The overlapping clinical manifestations and progressive patterns of ILD subtypes pose substantial challenges for accurate diagnosis and effective disease management. In recent years, application of diverse omics approaches in clinical research has yielded promising insights into complex disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the impact of NPC1 single nucleotide polymorphisms on entry efficiency of filoviruses in vitro: Agent-based model approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ebola and Marburg viruses are highly pathogenic filoviruses that cause severe hemorrhagic fever in humans, with case fatality rates reaching approximately 50 %. These viruses pose significant public health challenges owing to their potential for large-scale outbreaks. A key step in their infection process is the interaction between the Niemann-Pick C1 (NPC1) protein on host cells and the viral glycoprotein (GP), which is responsible for viral entry into cells. Genetic variations in NPC1 caused...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-oncologic orphan drug approvals across the world: Types of evidence required and time to approval]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large time gaps are frequently observed between approvals of orphan products by different jurisdictions. A retrospective review of publicly accessible information for new orphan medicines approvals between 2021 and 2022 was performed to quantify the types of evidence required and timeframes for initial and subsequent approvals in six different regions. We identified 53 orphan products: 91% were approved in two or more regions, and 69% relied upon the same/highly similar types of evidence for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Core Streptavidin-Bridging Amplified ELISA Based on p54 Epitope for High-Sensitivity Detection of African Swine Fever Virus Antibodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infection with the African swine fever virus (ASFV) causes a highly acute and lethal disease in pigs, emphasizing the urgent need for early detection to manage outbreaks effectively. While indirect enzyme-linked immunosorbent assays (ELISAs) based on antigenic epitopes provide high sensitivity, conventional adsorption of epitopes onto ELISA plates can hinder antibody recognition. In this study, we developed an indirect ELISA for ASFV antibody detection by integrating the identified p54 antigenic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography angiogropahy changes in patients with diabetic retinopathy treated with panretinal photocoagulation: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We evaluated retinal microvascular changes in patients with diabetic retinopathy (DR) treated with panretinal photocoagulation (PRP), using optical coherence tomography angiography (OCTA). Nineteen studies were included to assess changes in vessel density (VD) within the superficial capillary plexus (SCP), the deep capillary plexus (DCP), and the foveal avascular zone (FAZ) area. PRP was associated with a significant increase in VD in the SCP, particularly in the foveal region, with greater...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alveolar macrophage-derived TGF-β promotes acute lung injury recovery by regulating inflammatory monocyte-derived macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AMs critically regulate the inflammatory and proliferative activities of MDMs through TGF-β secretion, which acts via the Wnt signaling pathway. This AM-MDM regulatory axis is essential for timely lung repair and represents a potential therapeutic target for acute lung injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of deficient mismatch repair colorectal cancer and precursors after kidney transplantation: a nationwide study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colorectal cancer (CRC) incidence rises post-transplant, though the mechanism remains unclear. We hypothesize that impaired immunosurveillance of kidney transplant recipients (KTRs) allows progression along the serrated pathway, increasing only immunogenic deficient mismatch repair (dMMR) CRC incidence and not proficient mismatch repair (pMMR) CRC. The nationwide transplant, pathology, and cancer registries were linked by probabilistic matching to retrieve data of all KTRs in the Netherlands....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for the Kisoboka Mukwano pilot randomized controlled trial in Uganda: A couples-based intervention to reduce intimate partner violence and alcohol use among adolescent girls and young women living with HIV and their male partners]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: If feasible, safe, and acceptable, Kisoboka Mukwano can improve HIV care engagement among Ugandan AGYWLHIV by reducing IPV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-Translational modifications and proteomic mechanisms underlying substance use disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Substance Use Disorder (SUD) is a chronic, relapsing condition driven by complex neurobiological changes, many of which are mediated by post-translational modifications (PTMs). These chemical alterations regulate receptor activity, intracellular signaling, and chromatin structure, shaping the neuroadaptations associated with SUD and relapse. This review emphasizes the central role of PTMs in modulating protein stability and function, contributing to drug-induced changes in key brain regions such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining the ability of artificial intelligence-driven occlusal contact adjustment to improve virtual occlusal record trueness for implant restorations: An in vitro study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The effect of AI-OCA on VOR trueness varied according to the scanner type and the span of edentulism. Results from both scanners for single posterior molar defects were more accurate when AI-OCA was not used. TR5 performed better in assessing VOR trueness for implant-supported restorations in free-end scenarios.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging characteristics correlated with outcomes of cranial MRgFUS - a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While research on imaging correlates of magnetic resonance guided focused ultrasound (MRgFUS) outcomes accumulates, a comprehensive synthesis across different disease populations remains absent. This systematic review aims to identify, technique-specific imaging biomarkers linked to treatment outcomes across distinct clinical conditions, including essential tremor (53 studies), Parkinson's disease (8 studies), and psychiatric disorders (2 studies). Key findings demonstrate that in ET, larger...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altered cortical alpha modulations and connectivity in complex regional pain syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic pain alters resting-state cerebral alpha rhythms (8-12 Hz), including whole-brain slowing of peak alpha frequency (PAF). Nevertheless, how the power of brain activity at PAF (PAF power) or across the entire alpha frequency range (alpha power) is decreased or increased compared to healthy controls (HC) varies greatly across pain phenotypes. The brain regions exhibiting such alterations and their association with the pain severity experienced by patients are also unclear. The study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cortico-midbrain-spinal Mechanisms Underlying Placebo Analgesia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Past research has demonstrated that pain experience can be manipulated through non-specific effects. Placebo analgesia (PA) is known to be sensitive to an individual's expectations of pain relief. This study aimed to investigate the relationship between the spinal cord, midbrain, and cortical regions commonly associated with expectancy-induced PA. Fifty healthy participants underwent separate brain and spinal fMRI scans involving application of painful heat in four conditions: baseline, placebo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Endogenous Circadian Rhythm of Mechanical Pain Sensitivity in Healthy Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Numerous studies have demonstrated diurnal rhythms of pain sensitivity in humans, yet only one has shown an endogenous circadian heat pain rhythmicity using a constant routine procedure, a well-validated chronobiological technique. Establishing the circadian rhythm of pain sensitivity is an important first step for optimizing pain assessment and personalizing pain management strategies. The present study extended this work by employing a 26-hour ultrashort sleep-wake protocol, another validated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-nuclei RNA Sequencing Reveals Distinct Transcriptomic Signatures of Rat Dorsal Root Ganglia in a Chronic Discogenic Low Back Pain Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic low back pain (LBP), often correlated with intervertebral disc degeneration, is a leading source of disability worldwide, yet remains poorly understood. Current treatments often fail to provide sustained relief, highlighting the need to better understand the mechanisms driving discogenic LBP. During disc degeneration, the extracellular matrix degrades, allowing nociceptive nerve fibers to innervate previously aneural disc regions. Persistent mechanical and inflammatory stimulation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A smart ROS-responsive hydrogel for on-demand antibacterial and platelet-rich plasma (PRP) activation in diabetic wound healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diabetic infected wounds present a significant clinical challenge due to persistent infection, chronic inflammation, and impaired angiogenesis. To address this, we developed a novel photo-crosslinked double-network hydrogel (HTC/MCP) by integrating phenylboronic acid-modified hyaluronic acid, a calcium tannate network, methacrylated carboxymethyl chitosan, and platelet-rich plasma (PRP). This smart hydrogel features reactive oxygen species (ROS)-responsiveness. Under high ROS conditions, it...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International consensuses and guidelines on management of proliferative diabetic retinopathy (PDR) by the Asia-Pacific Vitreo-retina Society (APVRS), the Academy of Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO) and the Academia Retina Internationalis (ARI)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The management of proliferative diabetic retinopathy (PDR) presents both established consensus and ongoing controversies, particularly regarding emerging therapies (anti-vascular endothelial growth factor agents [VEGF], subthreshold laser and intravitreal steroids) versus conventional approaches (laser photocoagulation and vitrectomy). The Asia-Pacific Vitreo-retina Society (APVRS), the Academy of Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO) and the Academia Retina Internationalis (ARI) saw...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards better and more effective clinical trials for Chronic Graft-versus-Host Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While the incidence of chronic Graft-versus-Host Disease (chronic GVHD) is declining due to advances in prophylaxis and survival is improving due to better supportive care, first-line treatment of chronic GVHD continues to be based on corticosteroids. Numerous attempts to establish more effective or less toxic treatment alternatives have largely failed, likely due to the biological heterogeneity of chronic GVHD and uncontrolled use of systemic corticosteroids, indicating the need for new...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Echinocandin-resistant Candida albicans: A Case Report from Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Echinocandin-resistant Candida albicans (C. albicans) is a rare but increasing global concern. In Japan, at least three cases had been confirmed by the end of 2015. Mutations in FKS cause echinocandin resistance in Candida species, which is primarily driven by previous echinocandin antifungal use. C. albicans resistance to echinocandins is raising clinicians' concerns globally and could pose a threat to Japan in the near future. The fungus is also an antimicrobial-resistant pathogen, raising...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Resistance Trends in Mycobacterium kansasii Pulmonary Isolates and identification of risk factors for drug resistance in Taiwan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study reveals increasing resistance to the first- and second-line agents in M. kansasii isolates across Taiwan. Resistance epidemiology differed between regions. Fibrocavitary lung lesion was significantly associated with drug resistance. These findings underscore the importance of region-specific surveillance to undergo individualized treatment strategies for M. kansasii pulmonary disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Characteristics of Extrapulmonary Nontuberculous Mycobacterial Diseases in Japanese Adult Patients without HIV: A Multicenter Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Most extrapulmonary NTM cases respond to antimicrobial therapy and source control. RGM infections involving prosthetic devices without source control remain challenging, warranting further research into optimized management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Screening Period Pain Inconsistency on Placebo Response in Intra-Articular Knee Osteoarthritis Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings extend earlier observations by revealing that not only the magnitude, but also the direction of screening pain fluctuation (worsening pain before randomization) predicts PR. These results highlight SPPI as a potential adjustment variable to enhance assay sensitivity and mitigate PR in intra-articular knee OA trials, supporting the development of more effective therapies for chronic pain conditions like OA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tribological impact of synovial fluid alterations in osteoarthritis: correlation analyses between cartilage friction and synovial fluid properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The impact of SF alterations on AC friction depends on the tissue's degeneration severity. These findings might provide valuable information when selecting appropriate patient populations and timing of treatment options, particularly tribosupplementation approaches, which address the knee joint's tribology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ghrelin restores D1 receptor-mediated dopamine neurotransmission and enhances attentive behaviour in Mecp2 KO mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rett syndrome is an X-linked neurodevelopmental disorder characterised by cognitive, attentional, and communicative impairments along with sensory and motor deficits. Optimal activation of dopamine D1 receptor signalling in the prefrontal cortex (PFC) is essential for cognition and object-based attention. Ghrelin has been observed to modulate dopaminergic neurotransmission and improve cognitive function and attention impairments in various animal models. Herein, we investigated the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety assessment and sub-group analysis (gender-based and age-based) of Rocuronium: A real-world pharmacovigilance study from the FAERS database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings advise medical professionals to exercise more caution when using rocuronium, especially in elderly people. This study provide guidance for early identification of rocuronium-related adverse reactions, and valuable references for more in-depth future studies and safety regulatory work.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scutellarin alleviates ferroptosis in cigarette smoke-induced chronic obstructive pulmonary disease via activation of the PI3K/AKT/Nrf2 signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrates that Scu alleviates CS-induced COPD by inhibiting ferroptosis, primarily through activation of the PI3K/AKT/Nrf2 pathway, providing a comprehensive pharmacological basis for Scu as a promising therapeutic candidate for COPD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetics, tissue distribution, in vivo metabolism and liver microsomal metabolism of GK-A, GK-2 and Eucomic acid in rats were studied by liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry and mass spectrometry imaging of Ginkgo Semen extract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GK-A, GK-2 and Eucomic acid were all rapidly absorbed by plasma and widely distributed in tissues after oral administration of GSE. There was no accumulation of GK-A, GK-2 and Eucomic acid in the tissues, and the content in the small intestine, kidney, stomach and liver was higher. And Eucomic acid was able to cross the blood-brain barrier, and CYP450 enzyme in the liver was not the main metabolizing enzyme of the extract. GK-A, GK-2 and Eucomic acid were excreted in the feces and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International Classification of Diseases-10-Based Risk Stratification and Implant Selection for Knee Arthroplasty Among Patients Who Have Psychiatric and Neurologic Comorbidities: A Registry-Based Analysis of 549,234 Cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Psychiatric and neurologic comorbidities are heterogeneous, independent predictors of failure after TKA/UKA; implant design modifies risk. An ICD-10-GM-based, code plus-name approach may guide implant selection, discourage use of constrained or unicompartmental devices in patients who are vulnerable, and inform perioperative care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuro-Multimodal Monitoring in Neonatal Brain Injury: Current Applications, Challenges, and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in neuromultimodal monitoring (MMM) have significantly enhanced early detection and prognostic evaluation of brain injury in neonatal intensive care. This review summarizes the application and integration of multimodal monitoring technologies for brain injury assessment in newborns. Compared to single-modality approaches, MMM-based combined monitoring strategies demonstrate superior accuracy in both injury identification and prediction of neurodevelopmental outcomes. Meanwhile,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A paradigm shift in corticosteroid therapy for sarcoidosis: a World Association of Sarcoidosis and Other Granulomatous Disorders Position Paper, endorsed by the Americas Association of Sarcoidosis and Other Granulomatous Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For over seven decades, oral corticosteroids have been the cornerstone of sarcoidosis management. Oral corticosteroids suppress sarcoidosis inflammation rapidly, but long-term oral corticosteroids result in toxicity and some patients are unable to taper oral corticosteroids without experiencing disease flare ups. The routine use of oral corticosteroids as first-line therapy, as recommended in sarcoidosis guidelines, could have unintentionally promoted the long-term use of oral corticosteroids....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pirfenidone for grade 2 and grade 3 radiation-induced lung injury: a multicentre, open-label, randomised, phase 2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Radiation-induced lung injury is a major dose-limiting toxicity in thoracic radiotherapy. Pirfenidone, an oral antifibrotic drug that is often used to treat idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis, could offer therapeutic benefits for patients with radiation-induced lung injury. We evaluated the efficacy and safety of pirfenidone in patients with grade 2 or grade 3 radiation-induced lung injury.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207313/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Northward expansion of Aedes albopictus-associated arbovirus transmission risk in Europe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Efficacy of Virtual Reality-Based Stabilization for Individuals With Posttraumatic Stress Symptoms: A Machine Learning Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that VRS is effective in addressing PTSS and related conditions, and incorporating clinical and demographic data can enhance prediction models, enabling more personalized intervention strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alcohol Drinking and the Associations Between Age and Posttraumatic Stress Disorder: A 2-Year Longitudinal Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A significant alcohol-dependent association between age and PTSD highlights the need for targeted prevention strategies considering both alcohol use and age in physically injured individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Congenital hyperinsulinism due to NEUROD1 gene mutation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploration of Stress-Coping Behaviors in Patients With Mood Disorders Using Cluster Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study showed four types of stress-coping behaviors, such as Balanced, Withdrawn, Impulsive, and Active types, reflecting different clinical characteristics. Future research needs to be conducted to determine whether each type of stress-coping behavior is related to clinical prognosis in prospective studies and whether modification of coping behavior can improve prognosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comparative study between cinnamon extract and cinnamon nanoparticles on growth performance, blood metabolites and gut microbiota of broiler chickens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the effects of dietary supplementation with bark powder extract of cinnamon and cinnamon nanoparticles on growth performance, antioxidant status, hematological parameters, and cecal microbiota in broiler chickens. A total of 500 one-day-old male Ross 308 chicks were randomly assigned to five treatment groups with five replicates of 20 birds each. The experimental treatments included a control (no additive), 200 and 400 mg/kg cinnamon extract (CIN-200 and CIN-400), and 200...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41207169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251110023747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>