<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:23:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antithrombotic Medications and Intraocular Hemorrhage Risk in Exudative Age-Related Macular Degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this nationwide cohort study of patients with exudative AMD, antithrombotic medications were associated with a higher risk of intraocular hemorrhage requiring vitrectomy. These results suggest the need for proactive communication and tailored monitoring strategies to help minimize such sight-threatening complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Chain Elongation Mechanism for n-Caproate Biosynthesis by Megasphaera Hexanoica]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The microbial production of medium-chain carboxylates has attracted considerable interest owing to their potential applications in biofuels and specialty chemicals; however, the underlying biosynthetic mechanisms remain incompletely understood. The present study evaluates the medium-chain carboxylate-producing microbe Megaspahera hexanoica using genomic analysis, transcriptome analysis, and metabolic engineering. Additionally, the n-caproate synthesis pathway of M. hexanoica is characterized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CD8<sup>+</sup> T-Cell Deletion Suppressed the Development of Injury-Induced Experimental Neointimal Hyperplasia in Mice With or Without Chronic Stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic stress exacerbates cardiovascular injury and remodeling. Given the pivotal roles that cytotoxic CD8^(+) T cells play in pathobiology, we investigated potential role(s) of CD8^(+) T cells in stress-related vascular remodeling in a mouse carotid injury model. Eight-week-old male wild-type (CD8a^(+/+)) and CD8a knockout (CD8a^(-/-)) mice underwent carotid artery ligation plus cuff placement (L + C) with or without being subjected to chronic stress. At surgery conducted 2 weeks later, L + C...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expanding the diversity of Celavirus, the most divergent genus in the family Potyviridae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Celavirus is a genus within the family Potyviridae, currently comprising a single recognized species, Celavirus apii, represented by celery latent virus (CeLV), and one additional potential member, Striga-associated poty-like virus 2 (SaPlV2). The Celavirus genome is highly divergent from those of other potyvirids, and its polyprotein architecture remains incompletely resolved. In this study, we conducted systematic mining of publicly available transcriptome datasets and identified eight novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid turn-on voltage engineering of a-IGZO TFTs using xenon flash lamp annealing for logic-compatible oxide electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amorphous indium gallium zinc oxide (a-IGZO) thin-film transistors (TFTs) are widely used in flexible and stretchable electronic devices due to their excellent electrical properties and low-temperature process compatibility. As display technologies advance toward higher integration and flexibility, the demand for logic circuits within display panels is growing, necessitating more versatile and stable oxide TFT performance. To this end, a-IGZO TFTs are treated using xenon flash lamp annealing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932468/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Halogen-confining host materials for high-performance zinc-halogen batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zinc-halogen batteries hold great promise for grid-scale energy storage owing to their multi-electron transfer capability, abundant halogen resources, low cost and high theoretical voltage and capacity. However, they are still constrained by the sluggish redox kinetics of halogen species and the uncontrollable shuttling of polyhalide intermediates, which compromise energy efficiency and cycling stability. In this regard, the rational design of halogen-confining host materials has emerged as a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to Comment by Capuano et al]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introduction to the soft wearable sensors themed collection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft wearable sensors offer promising potential for advanced diagnostics, therapeutics, and human-machine interfaces. Unlike conventional devices that are bulky and rigid, often compromising skin integrity, comfort, and user compliance, soft wearable sensors are flexible, conformable, and better suited to the dynamic skin surface. This improved mechanical integration enhances signal fidelity and device performance, while also enabling safer, more comfortable, and continuous physiological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eplet mismatch analysis in kidney transplantation: from concept to clinical practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eplet mismatch analysis offers a refined approach to assessing donor-recipient compatibility in kidney transplantation, surpassing conventional antigen-level human leukocyte antigen (HLA) matching in predicting immunologic outcomes. By identifying polymorphic amino acid residues on HLA molecules recognized by B cell receptors, this method quantifies immunologic risk. Clinical studies demonstrate that high eplet mismatch loads, particularly at HLA-DQ, are strongly associated with de novo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic Pathogenesis of Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm and the Role of PCSK9 (Proprotein Convertase Subtilisin/Kexin Type 9)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) is defined as a localized dilation of the abdominal aorta measuring at least 1.5 times its normal diameter. If left untreated, AAA can progress to a life-threatening condition. In the field of AAA, treatment strategies have evolved significantly, with endovascular aneurysm repair serving as a representative example. However, despite developments in surgical techniques, postoperative morbidity and mortality rates remain significant. Extensive research is being...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic values and clinical significance of POU2F3 expression in neuroendocrine carcinomas: a meta-analysis with a focus on small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: POU2F3 expression is associated with improved survival and correlates with younger age and male sex in SCLC, highlighting distinct clinical and biological characteristics of this tuft cell-originated subtype. Data on extrapulmonary NECs were limited, precluding definitive conclusions for this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Entropy, Assessed by Homeostatic Dysregulation on Electrocardiograms Predicts Fracture and Mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Entropy, characterized by increased disorder throughout biological systems, can be quantified by homeostatic dysregulation (HD). One potential measure of HD is the dispersion of points from a normal value, approximated at the individual level by Mahalanobis distance (D(M)). We hypothesized that greater HD in electrocardiogram (ECG) would also reflect greater HD in the musculoskeletal system which, in turn, would be associated with age and manifest as an increased risk of fracture independently...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Immediate defibrillation and Outcomes in Shockable Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest: A Propensity Score Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Defibrillation within 2 min of starting CPR was associated with 1-month survival, emphasizing the importance of immediate defibrillation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aldol Condensation of Bis(pentafluorophenyl)boron Enolates for the Synthesis of α-Pentafluorophenyl-Substituted α,β-Unsaturated Carbonyl Compounds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[α-Pentafluorophenyl-substituted α,β-unsaturated carbonyl compounds are valuable for synthesizing perfluoroarenes. Aldol condensation with pentafluorophenyl-substituted enolates is a highly effective method for their synthesis. This study demonstrates that bis(pentafluorophenyl)boron enolates, featuring a pentafluorophenyl group, readily undergo aldol additions with aldehydes. Subsequent elimination of borinic acid yields α-pentafluorophenyl-substituted α,β-unsaturated carbonyl compounds....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why combating climate change is so challenging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the obstacles to implementing climate change policies, emphasizing the interplay of economic, social, and political factors. Important barriers are the non-enforceability of international agreements and politicians motivated by a short-run goal of retaining office. A stable national legal framework is required that integrates clear principles, enforceable regulations, proactive judicial oversight, and inclusive public participation to bridge the gap between ambitious goals...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Severe aspirin-induced enteritis in a patient with post-renal transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present the case of a 42-year-old woman with a history of renal transplantation who developed severe enteritis while taking enteric-coated low-dose aspirin. Despite signs of localized peritonitis, conservative management-including aspirin discontinuation, fasting, and antibiotics-was effective, and surgical intervention was avoided. Endoscopic and histologic findings were consistent with drug-induced enteritis, and no infectious etiology was identified. This case highlights the potential for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932637/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential contributions of approximate number system, number line estimation, and working memory to mathematical skills in preschool and primary school]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early mathematical skills predict later mathematical skills and general school achievement. The approximate number system (ANS), number line estimation, and working memory (WM) were found to be important predictors of the development of mathematical skills. However, studies specifying contributions of ANS, number line estimation, and WM at developmental levels are scarce. Therefore, the current study aimed to evaluate differential contributions of ANS, number line estimation, and WM to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elucidating some common biases in randomized controlled trials using directed acyclic graphs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the ideal randomized clinical trial is the gold standard for causal inference, real randomized trials often suffer from imperfections that may hamper causal effect estimation. Stating the estimand of interest can help reduce confusion about what is being estimated, but it is often difficult to determine what is and is not identifiable given a trial's specific imperfections. We demonstrate how directed acyclic graphs can be used to elucidate the consequences of common imperfections, such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of preserving the bronchial artery and the azygos arch in McKeown esophagectomy: a systematic review and meta‑analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In patients with esophageal cancer, pulmonary complications such as pneumonia and pleural effusion after esophagectomy are a major concern in terms of the short- and long-term prognosis. The relationship between these postoperative complications and preservation of the bronchial artery and the azygos arch in McKeown esophagectomy is unclear. This meta-analysis was performed to compare short-term outcomes between the preservation group (PG) and the dissection group (DG) of each vessel in McKeown...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Marine constraints as philosophical opportunities: the Krogh principle and the benefits of philosophical engagement with the sea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spontaneous dichorionic diamniotic twin pregnancy simultaneously implanted in a cesarean scar]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic significance of right ventricular-pulmonary artery coupling assessed by TAPSE/PASP ratio in patients with HFmrEF]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Right ventricular-pulmonary artery (RV-PA) coupling is an indicator of the degree to which the right ventricle can adapt to afterload. The ratio of tricuspid annular plane systolic excursion (TAPSE) to pulmonary artery systolic pressure (PASP) (TAPSE/PASP ratio) has been proposed as a non-invasive measure of RV-PA coupling. RV-PA coupling is a key prognostic predictor of heart failure (HF); however, HF with mildly reduced left ventricular ejection fraction (HFmrEF) is difficult to predict. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Azapeptide-Based SARS-CoV-2 Main Protease Inhibitors: Design, Synthesis, Enzyme Inhibition, Structural Determination, and Antiviral Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[M^(pro) of SARS-CoV-2 plays a vital role in the replication and pathogenesis of virus. Additionally, its high conservation within the Coronaviridae family makes it an attractive therapeutic target for developing broad-spectrum agents. This study describes the design, synthesis, and structure-activity relationships of azapeptide-based SARS-CoV-2 M^(pro) inhibitors, leading to several compounds with nanomolar IC(50) values. Examples include 14r (IC(50) = 13.3 nM), 14s (IC(50) = 30.6 nM), 20a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leukocyte Esterase-Activated Nanoconjugates Enables Precise Local Therapy of Ulcerative Colitis via Inflamed Tissue-Selective Drug Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leukocyte esterase (LE), markedly upregulated in inflamed colonic tissues, offers a unique enzymatic trigger for selective drug activation in ulcerative colitis (UC). To exploit this pathological hallmark, we developed LE-activated nanoconjugates that enable inflamed tissue-selective drug delivery as a strategy to achieve precise local therapy for UC. Dexamethasone (DEX) was covalently conjugated to poly(lactide-co-glycolide) (PLGA) via ester bonds to form nanoconjugates (DPNCs) with suppressed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AntiviralDB: an expert-curated database of antiviral agents against human infectious diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Viral infectious diseases have caused millions of deaths worldwide. Antiviral agents are critical for controlling these infections; however, an open-access database dedicated specifically to antiviral agents remains unavailable. Here, we present AntiviralDB (https://www.antiviraldb.com/), an expert-curated resource that compiles both approved and experimental antiviral agents with laboratory-confirmed in vitro activity against a broad spectrum of human viruses. These include the human...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identity and Body in Emerging Adults With Congenital Heart Disease: A Qualitative Exploration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights the unique challenges emerging adults with congenital heart disease can encounter regarding their identity and body experiences.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931894/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzyme-Click Postsynthetic Modification of Covalent Organic Frameworks for Photocatalytic H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub> Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postsynthetic modification (PSM) is a powerful strategy for tailoring the structure and functionality of covalent organic frameworks (COFs). In this work, we present a novel enzymatic PSM strategy for functional group engineering within COFs. By taking advantage of enzymatic catalysis, 2-hydroxyethylthio (-S-EtOH) and ethylthio (-S-Et) groups were covalently implanted within the COF pore channels with high grafting efficiency under ambient aqueous conditions, highlighting the mild, efficient,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identity and Psychosis Risk in Sexual Minority Youth: Temporal Dynamics of Identity and Suspiciousness Through Experience Sampling Methodology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Identity difficulties are closely linked to suspiciousness in adolescents, particularly among sexual minority youth. The bidirectional relationship suggests a reinforcing cycle that may increase vulnerability to psychotic experiences. These findings stress the need for preventive interventions that address identity integration during adolescence, especially for sexual minority adolescents navigating identity development in a heteronormative context.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931591/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cross-scale analysis for the determinants of bonding dynamics on the distributions of rolling velocities of cells in microvessels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The interplay between subcellular adhesion dynamics and cellular-scale deformations under shear flow drives key physiological and pathological processes. While both bond kinetics and fluid-cell interactions have been extensively studied in rolling adhesion, how bond characteristics quantitatively determine cellular velocity distributions remains unclear. In this study, we systematically investigate how force-free bond kinetics and intrinsic mechanical properties govern rolling adhesion dynamics,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning stochastic processes with intrinsic noise from cross-sectional biological data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inferring dynamical models from data continues to be a significant challenge in computational biology, especially given the stochastic nature of many biological processes. We explore a common scenario in omics, where statistically independent cross-sectional samples are available at a few time points, and the goal is to infer the underlying diffusion process that generated the data. Existing inference approaches often simplify or ignore noise intrinsic to the system, compromising accuracy for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ApoD mediates age-associated increase in vulnerability to influenza virus infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Influenza A virus (IAV) infection causes significantly greater morbidity and mortality in the elderly population, but the molecular mechanisms in the aging process responsible for severe infection remain unclear. In this study, we found that increased severity in IAV infection and reduced innate immune response correlated with extensive mitophagy in senescent human cells and in the lung of aged mice. Apolipoprotein D (ApoD) was identified as strongly elevated in the lungs and sera of aged human...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chelation-induced anti-Ostwald ripening: Ultrafine bismuth nanocrystals for ultrastable aqueous sodium storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aqueous sodium-ion batteries (ASIBs) are gaining attention for their inherent safety and the use of abundant sodium resources. Bismuth (Bi) anode, with its high theoretical capacity and low cost, enhances the performance and competitiveness of ASIBs in energy storage applications. However, as a conversion-type material, Bi inevitably undergoes dramatic volume changes during cycling, limiting the structural stability and calendar life of the electrode. Herein, we present a Bi-carbon composite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and Preliminary Outcomes of a Simulated Prehospital Pediatric Ventilation Scenario Using a Ventilation Feedback Device]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Enrolling EMS clinicians and capturing real-time VFD output were feasible during shifts. Using a VFD improved ventilation in a simulated pediatric respiratory arrest scenario. Our methodology offers a model for incorporating pediatric in-situ training. Use of a HMC is a potential novel skill performance assessment tool. Larger, multi-center studies and real-world application of a VFD to evaluate patient-centered outcomes are necessary.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A formative evaluation to adapt a brief mindfulness program to increase participant engagement, participant impact, and feasibility of delivery among veterans with PTSD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brief mindfulness training can help veterans with posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD) learn essential skills to manage distressing emotions and thoughts. This study sought to (a) refine the content of Primary Care Brief Mindfulness Training (PCBMT) to address PTSD symptoms and recovery, (b) improve the feasibility of training Veterans Health Administration staff to facilitate mindfulness classes, and (c) increase veteran attendance in the mindfulness classes by incorporating veteran peer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of Long-Term Use of Atropine for Myopia in Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-Centered Approach to Assessing Voice Impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION AND RELEVANCE: This psychometric study identified a shorter version of the VHI-10 that may be more patient-centered and clinically sufficient for assessing patients with voice impairments. These findings may form the foundation for additional assessments that are more patient-centered, efficient, and nuanced.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergency Hernia Repair Outcomes for Patients With and Without Established Hernia Care With a Surgeon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral Lachnoanaerobaculum Levels and Survival in Patients With Head and Neck Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This prognostic study found that higher salivary Lachnoanaerobaculum spp abundance was associated with improved tumor control and survival in patients with HNSCC undergoing (chemo)radiotherapy. These findings support further investigation into microbiome-targeted interventions to improve HNSCC treatment effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<sup>68</sup>Ga-DOTATATE PET/CT versus MRI in neuroendocrine liver metastases: a comprehensive per-lesion analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MRI outperforms ^(68)Ga-DOTATATE PET/CT in detecting individual neuroendocrine liver metastases, particularly for subcentimeter lesions. While diagnostic CT improves PET performance, the combination of MRI with ^(68)Ga-DOTATATE PET/CT provides the most comprehensive assessment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of Synthetic Probiotic Bacteria for In Situ Delivery of Anti-SARS-CoV-2 Nanobodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2 viral infection can be inhibited by blocking the interaction between the viral spike protein and the human receptor angiotensin-converting enzyme 2 (hACE2). The development of specific spike inhibitors using nanobodies, the antigen-binding region of llamas' antibodies, arose as a promising therapeutic method against SARS-CoV-2. However, one limitation of nanobodies is that they cannot be used directly in the human body due to their susceptibility to degradation. Bacteria-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potassium-chloride cotransporter 2 activity dampens induced ictal-like activity in neocortical slices containing the seizure propagation zone of temporal lobe epilepsy patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: The K^(+)/Cl^(-) cotransporter (KCC2), which acts as the main Cl^(-) extruder in the adult brain, coregulates the driving force and therewith indirectly the amount and polarity of γ-aminobutyric acidergic (GABAergic) currents. Whether the net effect of active KCC2 is inhibitory via such Cl^(-) extrusion or excitatory due to the concomitant increase of K^(+) in the extracellular space is context-dependent and difficult to predict. Consecutively, in rodent models, antiseizure- as well...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facile construction of chitosan-ternary metal selenide biopolymer-based composite for photocatalytic degradation of petroleum derive sunset yellow and acid black azo-dyes using response surface methodology RSM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The presence of organic pollutants especially dyes in industrial wastewater is a significant threat to both human health and aquatic life. As a result, it is required to degrade toxic organic dye pollutants to ensure the safety of the environment and the public. To solve this problem, a co-precipitation technique was used to prepare chitosan-based-ternary metal selenide nanocomposites (FeMnSeCs-NPs). Chitosan was used to encapsulate the nanocomposites to stop leaching and make the catalyst...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autoimmune disease risk gene ANKRD55 promotes TH17 effector function through metabolic modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genome-wide association studies (GWAS) have linked the locus encoding ankyrin repeat domain 55 (ANKRD55) with numerous autoimmune diseases; however, its biological function and role in inflammation are unclear. Here, we demonstrate that Ankrd55-deficient mice are protected from T cell-mediated colitis but are more susceptible to Citrobacter rodentium infection. Mechanistically, Ankrd55 deletion impairs CD4+ T cell proliferation and reduces effector cytokine production in T helper 17 (TH17) cells...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Translation and Validation of the Persian ICIQ Nocturia and Nocturia Quality of Life]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Persian ICIQ Nocturia and Nocturia Quality of Life were valid and efficiently adapted for use in various settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nidulin stimulates glucose uptake in myotubes through the IRS-AKT pathway and alters redox balance and intracellular calcium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nidulin is a secondary metabolite of the depsidone family produced by Aspergillus spp., and has shown promises in pharmacological applications. This study aimed to investigate the effect of nidulin on glucose metabolism in skeletal muscle, the primary site of physiological glucose disposal, and its underlying mechanisms. Using a 2-[³H]-deoxy-glucose (2-DG) uptake assay, nidulin stimulated 2-DG in L6 myotubes in a dose- and time-dependent manner. This effect of nidulin was additive to insulin and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing interpretability of AI with radiomics-based deep neural network: proof of concept in the classification of Parkinsonian syndromes with <sup>18</sup>F-FDG PET imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The RDDNN framework provides a clinically interpretable and reproducible DNN solution for classifying Parkinsonian disorders. By integrating radiomics and attention-based modeling, it enhances lesion localization, supports clinical decision-making, and offers performance comparable to human specialists-while substantially improving diagnostic efficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of 18F-FDG PET/CT metabolic parameters for early prediction of pathological response in NSCLC treated with neoadjuvant immuno(chemo)therapy: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The study support ΔSUVmax as a reliable indicator of MPR, although its specificity for pCR remains limited. PERCIST's high sensitivity aids in excluding non-responders. However, limited study numbers for parameters like ΔSULpeak, SULpeak-Post, and ΔSULmax reduce generalizability, necessitating larger validation studies to confirm their diagnostic utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise and Cognition in Multiple Sclerosis in 2025: Forward Momentum or Going Nowhere Fast?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: There is increasing interest in the study of exercise training as an approach to treat the cognitive consequences of multiple sclerosis (MS). The current paper reviews recent research on exercise training effects on cognition in MS, and provides several future directions for guiding, and perhaps optimizing, research in this area.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Long-Acting Injectable Versus Oral Antipsychotic Treatment on All-Cause Discontinuation Risk in People with Early Phase Schizophrenia and Comorbid Substance Use Disorder: A Secondary Analysis of the EULAST Randomized Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LAI antipsychotics significantly delayed treatment discontinuation compared with oral antipsychotics in participants with early phase schizophrenia and comorbid SUD but not in those without SUD. While these findings provide robust evidence supporting the use of LAIs in people with schizophrenia and comorbid SUD, future studies are needed to more precisely quantify the potential clinical benefits and tolerability of LAIs in this high-risk population. EULAST was registered at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932600/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Appropriateness of antibiotic use in nursing homes for suspected urinary tract infections: comparison across five European countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the efficacy of local thermotherapy versus Glucantime® in the treatment of anthroponotic cutaneous leishmaniasis: a pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This pilot study is the first in Iran that evaluates the effectiveness of thermotherapy compared to intralesional Glucantime® in the treatment of cutaneous leishmaniasis caused by Leishmania tropica. Forty patients with cutaneous leishmaniasis were separated into two groups, each consisting of 20 patients. The control group received intralesional Glucantime® weekly for 8 weeks, while the other group received a single session of thermotherapy for each lesion using ThermoMedTM model 1.8. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of a Whole-School Prevention Program Targeting Mental Health and Nonsuicidal Self-Injury in Swedish Adolescents: A Cluster-Randomized Experimental Study with Longitudinal Follow-Up]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rising rates of mental health problems and nonsuicidal self-injury (NSSI) among adolescents highlight the need for preventive interventions and the lack of evidence regarding such measures. To date, few studies have investigated school-based prevention programs targeting NSSI. In this study, a whole-school preventive intervention was carried out at Swedish lower secondary schools and evaluated in a cluster-randomized controlled trial. The whole-school intervention included classroom-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of hearing ability on inflammation and glymphatic function affecting cognition in older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mechanisms linking hearing ability, inflammation, glymphatic system function, and cognitive impairment in older adults are largely unknown. To investigate this issues, magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) was used to test for dysfunctions in the glymphatic system of older adults with hearing loss and to determine the relationship of glymphatic dysfunction, inflammation and cognitive deficits. This cross-sectional observational study included participants with ARHL and healthy controls (HCs)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medication Non-adherence in Older Adults: Underlying Factors, Potential Interventions and Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polypharmacy is very common among older adults and is associated with poor health outcomes. This scoping review aimed to understand the underlying factors for poor medication taking by older patients and potential solutions to mitigate these risks. The ability to take medications and adherence are affected by various factors related to patients, treatments, health conditions and socio-demographics, healthcare providers and the healthcare systems. Educational and behavioural interventions are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare Costs Associated with Adverse Events in Pediatric Patients with Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD): A Claims-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AEs were common during ADHD treatment episodes in pediatric patients and were associated with significant healthcare costs. ADHD treatments with a favorable safety profile could help alleviate the economic burden of AEs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Evaluation of the Pathways Community HUB Approach To Improving Birth Outcomes: A Retrospective Study Using Propensity Score Matching in Richland, Ohio]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among high-risk pregnant women, the PCHI^(®) Model can significantly improve prenatal care utilization and reduce the incidence of LBW infants. In addition, pregnant women participating in the Pathways Community HUB program appeared to benefit more if they entered the program in their first trimester rather than later in their pregnancy, suggesting that longer durations of program participation are associated with better birth outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Trifactor Model Approach to Understand School-Aged Children's Psychosocial Adjustment: Integrating Father, Mother, and Teacher Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined factors contributing to shared and unique perspectives among fathers', mothers', and teachers' ratings of school-aged children's psychosocial adjustment among military families. Utilizing baseline data from three randomized controlled trials of a preventive parenting program (N = 870, 51.7% girls; M(age) = 8.13; 12.7% fathers and 12.8% mothers identified as people of color), we first described the pattern of informant (dis)agreement on children's psychosocial adjustment rated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncloggable ventriculoperitoneal shunt system for hydrocephalus via an integrated soft robotic device: CLEARS device]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ventriculoperitoneal (VP) shunt obstruction, often caused by protein and fat accumulation at the ventricular catheter ports, impedes cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) outflow, increases intracranial pressure (ICP), and leads to hydrocephalus. Current treatments require invasive shunt removal, reimplantation, or retrograde flush cleansing. We present a next-generation VP shunt system that actively removes blockages via external actuation. Our system, called CLogging Elimination ActuatoR Silicone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and synthesis of novel Osimertinib analogs for dual EGFR and P-glycoprotein 1 inhibition targeting multidrug resistance in non-small cell lung cancer: In vitro and in vivo evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overcoming multidrug resistance (MDR) remains a critical challenge in non-small-cell lung cancer (NSCLC) therapy, particularly in cases driven by EGFR mutations and P-gp1 overexpression. This study aimed to design and synthesize Osimertinib (OSB) analogs (14a-14m) as dual inhibitors of EGFR and P-gp1, and optimize their activity, selectivity, and pharmacokinetics. Among these, compounds 14g and 14l emerged as potent candidates, demonstrating superior cytotoxicity against EGFR-mutant and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Comparative evaluation of live attenuated and killed tachyzoites as vaccine candidates for toxoplasmosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Migraine patients treated with CGRP(R) antibodies : Are they different from patients treated with nonspecific oral prophylaxis? Analysis from the DMKG headache registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CGRP(R) antibodies are prescribed for to patients affected by exceedingly severe migraine. Insurance coverage has a significant effect on use of medicines for migraine prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corneal biomechanical changes in patients with anterior chamber inflammation: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with ACI exhibit significant reductions in corneal biomechanical properties (CH and CRF), with CRF consistently lower across all age groups. CCT significantly impacts corneal biomechanics, potentially making biomechanics alterations more evident during remission states.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary cardiac lymphoma initially suspected as device-associated thrombus: a multimodal imaging diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicenter, real-world observational study of AVA therapy following ELT/HET switching in Chinese children with persistent/chronic primary ITP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Avatrombopag (AVA), a second-generation thrombopoietin receptor agonist (TPO-RA), has demonstrated efficacy in pediatric persistent/chronic immune thrombocytopenia (ITP). However, critical evidence gaps persist regarding treatment-switching strategies between TPO-RAs, particularly when transitioning from eltrombopag (ELT) or hetrombopag (HET) to AVA. This multicenter cohort study evaluated 55 pediatric ITP patients unresponsive to or relapsing after ELT (n = 46) or HET (n = 9) who underwent AVA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revaccination Response and Lack of Hepatitis B Reactivation After HCT for Sickle Cell Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Results indicate that HBV immunity can decline post-HCT, but most patients remain immune, and revaccination is effective. However, some non-responders-especially those treated with IVIG, rituximab, or prolonged immunosuppression-need further study. Prospective research is needed to optimize revaccination timing and immune monitoring in this high-risk group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932460/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromatic and achromatic contrast sensitivity in the far periphery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The contrast sensitivity function (CSF) has been studied extensively; however, most studies have focused on the central region of the visual field. The current study aims to address two gaps in previous measurements: first, it provides a detailed measurement of the CSF for both achromatic and, importantly, chromatic stimuli in the far periphery, up to 90 dva of visual angle. Second, we describe visual sensitivity around the monocular/binocular boundary that is naturally present in the periphery....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Cognitive Impairment and Spinal Pain in the Older Adult Population in the United States: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There was a significant association between cognitive impairment and spinal pain in the older adult population in the United States. Within this population, there were vulnerable subgroups for which spinal pain and cognitive impairment had a greater impact, namely people who are older, female, and those with less education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Aficamten Compared With Metoprolol on Echocardiographic Measures in Symptomatic Obstructive Hypertrophic Cardiomyopathy: MAPLE-HCM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In addition to lowering Valsalva LVOT-G and left atrial volume index, treatment with aficamten compared with metoprolol over 24 weeks led to improvement in measures of LV diastolic function, mitral valve systolic anterior motion, and mitral regurgitation. Aficamten therapy resulted in modest reduction in LVEF compared with metoprolol. These exploratory findings further support the overall superiority of therapy with aficamten over metoprolol demonstrated in MAPLE-HCM with evidence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["I Feel Like there's a Politician in the Room": Provider Perceptions of the Impacts of State Abortion Bans on Physician-Patient Relationships]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[State-level abortion bans enacted after Dobbs v. Jackson may have a deleterious impact on the health of women and may increase maternal morbidity and mortality. In obstetrics-gynecology, strong patient-physician relationships, which are built via patient-centered care strategies, are associated with better pregnancy-related outcomes. Abortion bans may limit physicians' ability to utilize these strategies by restricting care that can legally be provided. Further, all members of the care team,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable Nafion-Cellulose Composite Membrane: Role of Biomass-Derived Cellulose Loading in Suppression of Polysulfide Shuttling for Redox Flow Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The cross-shuttling of polysulfide ions in bromine/polysulfide-based redox flow batteries (RFBs) is one of the major challenges that hinder their overall performance. Herein, we utilized cellulose extracted from waste date palm trees (DPT) and Nafion to fabricate an in-house membrane that contributes to mitigating this problem. A series of Nafion membranes with cellulose ratios of 5, 10, 20, and 30 wt% were fabricated and labeled CNF5, CNF10, CNF20, and CNF30, respectively. The CNF20 displayed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete genome sequence of a <em>Desulfovibrio legallii</em> clinical isolate, GTC18478, from Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the complete genome sequence of a clinical isolate of Desulfovibrio legallii obtained from a human patient in Japan. The genome consists of a 2,750,737-bp circular chromosome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Glucose-Rethinking Prediabetes for Precision Prevention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prediabetes affects more than one-third of U.S. adults, yet represents a biologically heterogeneous state that is only partly captured by traditional glycemic categories (impaired fasting glucose, impaired glucose tolerance, or borderline elevated HbA1c). Leveraging unsupervised clustering in comprehensively phenotyped cohorts has identified six reproducible prediabetes subtypes integrating insulin sensitivity, insulin secretion, visceral and hepatic fat, and genetic risk. Three high-risk...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphological analysis of hostile neck anatomy in abdominal aortic aneurysm with consecutive 6-months computed tomography angiography - a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The neck deteriorates over time as AAA progresses in size, with development of neck hostility even before the maximum aortic diameter reaches the current threshold for repair of 50 mm/55 mm (women/men). The progressive nature of neck anatomy should be carefully considered when surveilling AAA patients and selecting them for future endovascular or open repair.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Navigating the Transition From Adolescence to Adulthood Among Young People With Severe Haemophilia: The Qualitative Phase of the TRANSHEMO Project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Based on the enlightened determinants, supportive strategies and patient education programs should focus on the development of autonomy, personal factors such as acquisition and application of health literacy in haemophilia care, and family factors such as support from family.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beta-blockers in patients with heart failure with reduced ejection fraction and concomitant chronic obstructive pulmonary disease: Cardiovascular and respiratory outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with HFrEF and COPD, beta-blocker use was associated with lower risk of cardiovascular death/total HHF, without evidence of safety concerns for COPD exacerbations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraosseous Venous Malformation of the Zygoma: Computer-Assisted Surgical Planning and Navigation-Guided Resection of Intraosseous Lesion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraosseous venous malformation (IVM) of the zygoma is an extremely rare benign vascular lesion. The authors present a case of IVMZ treated with meticulous preoperative analysis and computer-assisted surgical planning, followed by navigation-guided resection and contouring. At 6 months follow-up, the aesthetic result was satisfactory and the functional recovery was excellent. To the authors' knowledge, this is the first reported case of navigation-guided resection for intrazygomatic venous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myocardial ischemia from giant aneurysm of the sinus of valsalva: a distinct etiology of chest pain in young adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[β-Cell Neogenesis From the Pancreatic Ductal Epithelium Revealed Dynamically by Long-term Intravital Imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The adult pancreas' capacity to regenerate endocrine cells through ductal neogenesis has been disputed based on some pulse-chase lineage-tracing designs; however, no model described thus far has enabled the real-time study of regeneration in vivo. To facilitate long-term intravital imaging of pancreatic remodeling, we designed a novel system where pancreatic slices are transplanted into the anterior chamber of the eye of recipient mice. Using a transgenic mouse strain that enables the tracing of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Logic of Cellular Life: The 2025 Lasker~Koshland Special Achievement Award in Medical Science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum Metabolomics Reveals Potential Differences in Gut Microbiota-Associated Metabolites in Twins Discordant for Type 1 Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We believed this cohort of twins discordant for type 1 diabetes (T1D) would allow for control over genetic variability to examine environmental factors. We aimed to identify differences in microbial and microbiota-associated metabolites in twins discordant for T1D to examine the effect of the gut microbiome on T1D. Thirteen metabolites were identified as significantly different. Our results show dysregulation of several microbial metabolites in twin pairs, suggesting the role of the gut...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconfigurable Room-Temperature Exchange Bias through Néel Order Switching in van der Waals Heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exchange bias (EB) effects play a crucial role in modern magnetic memory technology. Recently, the van der Waals heterostructures have shown potential for investigating mechanisms of the EB effect owing to their tunable physical properties and flexibility in fabrication. However, due to low magnetic ordering temperatures for most van der Waals magnets, establishing EB in van der Waals antiferromagnet/ferromagnet heterostructures at room temperature is challenging. In this study, we fabricate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acetyl-CoA synthetase mutations affect the susceptibility of <em>Plasmodium falciparum</em> to antimalarial drugs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plasmodium falciparum acetyl-CoA synthetase (PfAcAS) is an important source of acetyl-CoA. We detected mutations S868G and V950I in PfAcAS by whole-genome sequencing analysis in certain recrudescent parasites after treatment with artesunate and dihydroartemisinin-piperaquine. Using CRISPR/Cas9 technology, we engineered parasite lines to carry the PfAcAS S868G and V950I mutations in two genetic backgrounds and evaluated their susceptibilities to antimalarial drugs in vitro. The results...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Picornavirus 3D polymerase inhibits antiviral innate immunity by blocking the activation of JAK-STAT signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Picornaviruses are known for their rapid replication rate, which is a key characteristic that allows them to quickly infect host cells and produce progeny viruses. The interactions with host cells established by the virus to bypass host defense are essential for their rapid replication. The 3D protein, identified as the RNA-dependent RNA polymerase (RdRp) of picornaviruses, is central to viral replication. In this study, we delineated a conserved strategy employed by picornavirus 3D proteins to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating gains in student self-efficacy in scientific literacy associated with a brief curricular intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Undergraduate research experiences (UREs) are high-impact practices that enhance retention, motivation, and self-efficacy in science, particularly for students with limited prior exposure to scientific environments. However, many students-especially those from underrepresented or marginalized backgrounds-enter these experiences with low research self-efficacy, stemming from limited familiarity with academic language, scientific literature, and research communication. The Research Induction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of EvenBluerMoon: a bacteriophage of <em>Arthrobacter globiformis</em> from Lubbock, Texas, topsoil]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the genome sequence analysis of an environmental bacteriophage discovered from topsoil in Lubbock, Texas, USA, as part of the SEA-PHAGES program. The bacteriophage, EvenBluerMoon, infects Arthrobacter globiformis and is a member of the FO cluster. EvenBluerMoon has an icosahedral head with a long non-contractile tail.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry analysis reveals the distinct reaction pathways of d(Cp<sup>ox</sup>G) with a photoactivatable Pt(IV) anticancer prodrug]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The interactions between d(Cp^(ox)G) (^(ox)G = 8-oxo-guanine), a major form of the oxidatively damaged CpG island motif, and a photoactivatable anticancer Pt(IV) prodrug, trans,trans,trans-[Pt(N(3))(2)(OH)(2)(pyridine)(2)] (1), were investigated using electrospray ionization mass spectrometry (ESI-MS). Surprisingly, the primary MS analysis showed that the major photooxidative products were the platinum-free dinucleotides d(CpGh) (2a)/d(CpIa) (2b) (possibly a mixture of the two isomers) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932237/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expeditious Synthesis of Chiral Imidazolidines and 1,2-Diamines via Photocatalytic [3 + 2] Cycloaddition of Chiral Sulfinamides with Azomethine Ylides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study introduces the first example of a photocatalytic [3 + 2] cycloaddition reaction to efficiently generate novel chiral imidazolidines using a chiral sulfinamide. A broad range of substrates, including different (S)-N-tert-butanesulfinyl imines and dipole precursors, were found to be compatible, delivering chiral imidazolidines in good yields with high diastereoselectivity (up to 93% yield, up to >25:1 dr). The reaction mechanism was investigated through radical trapping experiments....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steering Amide Synthesis from Acetonitrile by Electrochemically Derived Active Superoxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amides with unique carbonyl-nitrogen linkage are fundamental functional groups that are active and essential for a wide range of natural and synthetic products, pharmaceuticals, agrochemicals, and key intermediates. Amide bond formation is one of the most fundamental reactions in chemistry. Conventional amide synthesis faces challenges of poor atom economy and reliance on hazardous reagents. Herein, we present a tandem electro-thermal catalytic pathway for the synthesis of acetamide from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating socio-behavioral, ethics, community, and translational science considerations in HIV cure research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: HIV cure research efforts are expanding globally, yet several critical areas in the socio-behavioral, ethics, community engagement, and translational aspects remain underexplored. This article critically reviews the relevant literature from the past 5 years (2021-2025), highlights key gaps, and offers recommendations for future research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dextromethorphan/quinidine (DMQ) for reducing bulbar symptoms in amyotrophic lateral sclerosis - assessment of treatment experience in a multicenter study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: In amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), dextromethorphan/quinidine (DMQ) has been reported to reduce bulbar symptoms, including dysarthria and dysphagia. However, data on patients' perceptions of DMQ treatment are limited.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[<sup>68</sup>Ga]Ga-HM or [<sup>68</sup>Ga]Ga-PM: Which Is Superior for PET/CT Imaging of HMGB1-Positive Tumors?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High mobility group box 1 (HMGB1) is highly expressed in various malignancies and has been considered as a promising molecular target for cancer diagnosis and therapy. In this study, two novel peptide-based radiotracers targeting HMGB1 were synthesized, each achieving high radiochemical purity (>95%). Of these tracers, [^(68)Ga]Ga-HM possessed superior characteristics with a high binding affinity for the PC3 cell line (K(d) = 46.11 ± 0.97 nM). Micro-PET imaging and biodistribution investigation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strengthening Intermediate Adsorption on a Cobalt Phthalocyanine Assembly by Polymeric Modification for Electrochemical Carbon Dioxide Reduction into Methanol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical carbon dioxide reduction (CO(2)R) to generate value added methanol (MeOH) in water has been considered as a potential strategy to realize efficient carbon cycle and reutilization. Cobalt phthalocyanine (CoPc) represents as a classical molecular catalyst carrying precisely tunable active sites, which has been widely explored for the CO(2)-to-MeOH conversion, but optimization of performance is suffering from relatively easiness in desorption of *CO intermediate. To this end, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Yield on Reinterpretation of Genetic Variants in Pediatric Cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: One in 5 patients with cardiomyopathy had a clinically relevant change in variant pathogenicity on systematic reevaluation that would require modifying family clinical screening and cascade genetic testing. These findings underscore the clinical importance of regular variant reinterpretation on follow-up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ovotransferrin Fibrils Formed by Peptides Self-Assembly Improve the Stability and Antioxidation of Quercetin and Their Application in Quercetin Fortified Soybean Milk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quercetin (Que) is a natural flavonoid compound with multiple biological functions. However, it is easily dissociated by external conditions and difficult to apply in the food industry, so it needs to be encapsulated with food-derived nanocarriers to improve its stability. Here, ovotransferrin (OVT) is hydrolyzed into peptides by subtilisin A, and then the peptides self-assemble into hollow nanofibrils under Ca^(2+) ion induction at 50°C and pH 7.5 for 1 h. The increase in Thioflavin T (ThT)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the American Heart Association Predicting Risk of Cardiovascular Disease Events Equations in Diverse Socioeconomic Groups: The All of Us Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The PREVENT equations showed strong discrimination across all strata in this national cohort. Overprediction of CVD events likely reflects baseline differences in comorbidity burden between the PREVENT development cohort and this All of Us cohort, particularly due to the exclusion of individuals missing estimated glomerular filtration rate, a variable not routinely collected and likely missing, not at random. Strong discrimination supports potential clinical utility, though further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VEGFC/VEGFR3 Signaling-Dependent Lymphatic Remodeling Modulates Cardiac Response to Pressure Overload]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings highlight that targeting cardiac lymphangiogenesis via VEGFC/VEGFR3 signaling through genetic approaches represents a promising therapeutic strategy for heart failure. Moreover, VEGFC administration may offer a novel, noninvasive decongestive approach by modulating the lymphatic system in heart failure management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Right Strap: The Role of Tether Position and Length in Acene Distortion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report how the tether position affects the conformation, rigidity, and (chiro)optical properties in anthracene derivatives. While 1,5- and 1,10-tethers (long and short diagonal tethering, respectively) induce comparable twisting, short diagonal tethered derivatives display greater conformational flexibility, significantly impacting fluorescence and chiroptical behavior. Notably, short and long diagonal octyl-tethered anthracenes exhibit inverse temperature-dependent CD responses attributed to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Altering the Biotransformation Fate of Mercury by Coordinating Respiratory, Electron Flow, and Trapping Module]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dissimilatory metal-reducing bacteria (DMRB) have the talent to convert mercury ions (Hg^(2+)) into elemental mercury (Hg⁰). Here, we shed light on the directed biomineralization of Hg^(2+) into mercury selenide (HgSe), which is a promising environmental sink for Hg with minimal ecological risk. This process displays a controlled subcellular localization, improved efficiency, and redistribution of Hg species through the coordination of three modules, including reinforced respiratory,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noise Annoyance Among College Students: A Qualitative Analysis of Complaint Emails in a Chinese University]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that campus noise affects students' sleep quality, study efficiency, and mental health. It is recommended that universities strengthen campus noise control and ensure that on-campus construction activities do not interfere with students' study and rest.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of Five-Element Music Therapy Combined with Family-Participatory Psychological Care During the In Vitro Fertilization-Embryo Transfer Treatment Period for Infertile Patients with Polycystic Ovary Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Integrating Five-Element Music Therapy with Family-Participatory Psychological Care during IVF-ET treatment for patients with PCOS-related infertility alleviates negative emotional states, enhances family function and quality of life, reduces perceived disease burden, and improves nursing satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunosenescence phenotypes and prognostic significance of CD8 + CD28- T cells in AIDS-related non-Hodgkin lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AR-NHL patients warrant standard full-dose cancer therapy to improve prognosis despite immunocompromised and immunosenescence phenotypes. CD8 + CD28- T cells serve as an independent prognostic biomarker for AR-NHL, potentially associated with chronic immune activation and viral exposure. Our data suggest that characterizing T-cell subsets may enhance understanding of immune dynamics in AR-NHL, providing a foundation for exploring personalized approaches to infection prophylaxis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sodium butyrate regulates the sulfur respiration of rhizosphere soil to produce hydrogen sulfide modulating histone acetylation dynamics to enhance drought tolerance in rice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen sulfide (H(2)S), a well-established gaseous signaling molecule, can effectively enhance plant tolerance to various environmental stresses. However, there is still a lack of suitable methods to release H(2)S in agricultural production, and the mechanism by which H(2)S improves stress resistance remains poorly understood. Here, we show the novel role of sodium butyrate (NaB) in producing H(2)S consistently in rice rhizosphere soil and the epigenetic mechanism of H(2)S to enhance rice...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The levels of circulating tumor DNA and inflammatory proteins depict the clinical response in a patient with metastatic undifferentiated pleomorphic sarcoma, a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Superaerophobic 3D Array Electrode Promotes Gas Bubble Management in Alkaline Water Splitting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient gas bubble management is critical for enhancing the efficiency of alkaline water electrolysis, where adherent bubbles cause large overpotentials and unstable current densities. While optimizing the electrode structure has proven effective in promoting bubble detachment and improving reaction kinetics, achieving an ordered structure with a clear structure-performance relationship still remains challenging. Herein, a superaerophobic ordered 3D honeycomb Ni micromesh (3D HNM) integrated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Moisture on Enhanced Coalbed Methane Recovery by Microwave Irradiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microwave irradiation enhances coalbed methane (CBM) recovery under dry conditions, but moisture always exists in coal seams. It is still unknown how moisture affects this technique. This work analyzed the adsorption and desorption patterns of methane (CH(4)), the main component of CBM, in moist versus dry coals induced by microwave irradiation. These patterns were further interpreted with critical physicochemical properties of the coals. Results indicated that although moisture intensifies the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Benzodiazaborine Derivatives as Potent Antifungal Agents Targeting Leucyl-tRNA Synthase: Synthesis, Bioactivity, and <em>In Silico</em> Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The search for novel antifungal drugs is driven by the rise of drug-resistant fungal infections. This study aimed to develop benzodiazaborine derivatives targeting leucyl-tRNA synthase and evaluate their antifungal activity. A total of 35 derivatives were designed, synthesized, and tested against six common phytopathogenic fungi. The in vitro tests identified several potent compounds, especially compounds 1, 2, and 3, with compound 3 (EC(50) = 0.3837 μg/mL) outperforming boscalid (EC(50) =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postpartum hemorrhage: Findings of a global survey by the World Association of Trainees in Obstetrics and Gynecology (WATOG)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postpartum hemorrhage (PPH) remains the leading cause of maternal mortality globally. This global survey was conducted to identify any disparities in the causes, prevalence, treatment, and mortality burden of PPH, with the aim of proposing relevant recommendations to bridge these disparities and ultimately reduce the global maternal mortality and morbidity burden of PPH. A cross-sectional survey of maternity care providers worldwide was conducted by the World Association of Trainees in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating the Effects of Continuous Albuterol Dosage on Clinical Outcomes for Pediatric Critical Asthma Exacerbation: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings suggest that starting continuous albuterol at 10 mg/h provides clinical outcomes comparable to 15 mg/h in managing pediatric critical asthma exacerbations. A lower starting dose may optimize resource use and reduce treatment-related adverse effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental Resonance-Like Features in the Barrierless Reaction of O(<sup>1</sup>D) + D<sub>2</sub> at Collision Energies from 20 to 168 cm<sup>-1</sup>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reaction resonances have been extensively studied in barrier reactions, whereas the observation of reaction resonances is rarely reported in barrierless reactions. In this work, a high-resolution crossed molecular beam experiment using the D atom Rydberg tagging technique was systematically carried out to investigate the barrierless reaction of O(¹D) + D(2) → OD + D over a collision energy range of 20-168 cm^(-1). Four experimental observations were found, including the dramatic changes of OD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of drug retention rates between TNF inhibitors and tocilizumab for Takayasu arteritis: a multicenter retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tocilizumab has a higher continuation rate than TNFi, suggesting that tocilizumab may have better benefit-risk balance for TAK patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vivo Cervical Precancer Classification Through Multifractal Analysis of Spectral Fluctuations in Intrinsic Fluorescence Spectra]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spectral fluctuations in fluorescence spectroscopy, often ignored as noise, contain significant information about the fluorophore microenvironments. We present a discrete wavelet transform (DWT)-based technique to extract spectral fluctuations from the intrinsic fluorescence signals and utilize them to classify normal and precancerous patients. The fluctuations are extracted by applying the inverse DWT after zeroing the approximation and noisy detail coefficients. Multifractal detrended...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determinants of geographic variation in the incidence of adult nonmalignant meningioma in the United States, 2010-2019]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although general health and environmental factors cannot be ruled out in explaining the geographic variation in NMM incidence rates, results suggest that socioeconomic factors, certain demographic characteristics, and cancer diagnosis and registry practices may all play a significant role in driving such variation. These results may have implications for other tumor types diagnosed primarily radiographically or outside hospital settings, where variation in detection and reporting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nano-Raman Spectroscopy Figure of Merit and Chemical Analysis of Contaminations in Single-Layer MoSe<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Contaminations in the formation of two-dimensional heterostructures can hinder or generate the desired properties. Recent advancements have highlighted the potential of tip-enhanced Raman spectroscopy (TERS) for studying materials in the 2D semiconductor class. In this work, we investigate the influence of 50-200 nm sized nanoprotuberances within a monolayer of MoSe(2) using nano-Raman spectroscopy, establishing correlations between the presence of localized contaminations and the observed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of follow-up outcomes in patients with cervical histologic low-grade squamous intraepithelial lesion preceded by serious cytology and repeated diagnosis for at least 2 years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cervical histologic LSIL had a high natural regression rate and a low progression rate. Multiple gravidities, high-risk HPV positivity, HPV 16 positivity, and cytological examination ⩾ASC-H were risk factors for histologic LSIL progression. For patients with histologic LSIL preceded by cytologic ASC-H, stratified management based on the number of gravidities might be an option.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subnanometric Control of Coupling between WS<sub>2</sub> Monolayers with a Molecular Spacer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stacking monolayer semiconductors into heterostructures allows for control of their optical and electronic properties, offering advantages for nanoscale electronics, optoelectronics, and photonics. Specifically, adding a thin spacer between monolayers can yield bulk materials that retain interesting monolayer properties, such as a direct bandgap and a high emission quantum efficiency. The interaction mechanisms between monolayers, including interlayer coupling, charge transfer, and energy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supraparticle Assembly of La<sub>0.8</sub>Sr<sub>0.2</sub>CoO<sub>3</sub> Nanoparticles for Enhanced Lattice Oxygen Oxidation in Alkaline Electrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing effective non-noble metal electrocatalysts for the oxygen evolution reaction (OER) remains challenging due to limited active sites, poor electronic conductivity, and high overpotentials associated with the conventional adsorbate evolution mechanism (AEM). To address these limitations, a one-step spray drying method is employed to assemble high-surface-area La(0.8)Sr(0.2)CoO(3) nanoparticles (LSCO-NP) into hierarchical supraparticles with ≈65% porosity and interconnected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing Health Disparities Associated with the HIV PrEP Initiation Cascade, Baltimore City Health Department Sexual Health Clinics, 2016-2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Expansion of access to PrEP and usage of 'priority patient' criteria for PrEP initiation, along with direct feedback to clinicians, was associated with decreased disparities in 1) PrEP discussions overall and 2) prescriptions among MSM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Research progress on isopentenyl compounds and their derivatives from marine sources]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There exists a wealth of biological resources within the marine environment, where compounds containing isopentenyl and their derivatives exhibit remarkable biological activities alongside unique chemical structures. This article presents a thorough and systematic review of the provenance, structural characteristics, biological activities, as well as the biosynthetic pathways of isopentenyl-incorporated compounds and their derivatives originating from the marine realm, thereby offering...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to Letter to the editor A&amp;R: "Negative" finding supports two-hit model, by Ronald van Vollenhoven]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931885/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct <em>S</em>-Azidomethylation of Thiols with <em>N</em>-Azidomethyldisulfonimides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A direct azidomethylation reaction at the sulfur atoms of thiols with N-azidomethyldisulfonimides is presented, providing a facile and efficient approach for the synthesis of azidomethylated compounds with broad substrate scope and mild reaction conditions. Under optimized conditions using N-azidomethyl-bis(4-trifluoromethylbenzene)sulfonimide as the azidomethyl source, various aliphatic and aromatic thiols furnish the corresponding S-azidomethyl compounds in moderate to high yields. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Guishen-erxian Decoction can improve ovarian function in rats with premature ovarian failure by inhibiting oxidative stress and granulosa cell DNA fragmentation mediated by the PI3K/Akt/FOXO3a pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Inhibition of oxidative stress damage and excessive DNA fragmentation of granulosa cells is a key pathway for GSEXD to promote follicle growth and development and alleviate ovarian function decline, which may be related to the inhibition of the PI3K/AKT/FOXO3a pathway by GSEXD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct interleukin-6 production in IPL and TAFRO subtypes of idiopathic multicentric Castleman disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Idiopathic multicentric Castleman disease (iMCD) is a rare lymphoproliferative disorder characterized by systemic inflammation and lymphadenopathy. Two major clinical subtypes, idiopathic plasmacytic lymphadenopathy (iMCD-IPL) and iMCD with thrombocytopenia, anasarca, fever, renal dysfunction/reticulin fibrosis, and organomegaly (iMCD-TAFRO), exhibit distinct pathophysiologic mechanisms. While interleukin-6 (IL-6) is known to be elevated in iMCD, the differences in IL-6 production sources...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to Comment on: a case series of patients with β- thalassemia trait and iron overload: from multifactorial hepcidin suppression to treatment with mini-phlebotomies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Not available.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IGLV3-21<sup>R110</sup>-directed bispecific antibodies activate T cells and promote killing in a high-risk subset of chronic lymphocytic leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We previously used a disease-specific B cell receptor (BCR) point mutation (IGLV3-21R110) for selective targeting of a high-risk subset of chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL) with chimeric antigen receptor (CAR) T cells. Since CLL is a disease of the elderly and a significant fraction of patients is not able to physically tolerate CAR T cell treatment, we explored bispecific antibodies as an alternative for precision targeting of this tumor mutation. Heterodimeric IgG1-based antibodies consisting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early cytokine and chemokine signals shape the anti-AML activity of bispecific engager-secreting T cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunotherapies, including cell therapies, are effective anti-cancer agents. However, cellular product persistence can be limiting with short functional duration of activity contributing to disease relapse. A variety of manufacturing protocols are used to generate therapeutic engineered T-cells; these differ in techniques used for T-cell isolation, activation, genetic modification, and other methodology. We sought to determine how preselection affected the phenotype of T cells engineered to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of demographic factors on clinical outcomes of patients with acute myeloid leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Not available.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931864/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Splenic erythrophagocytosis is regulated by ALX/FPR2 signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maintaining a healthy pool of circulating red blood cells (RBCs) is essential for adequate perfusion, as even minor changes in the population can impair oxygen delivery, resulting in serious health complications including tissue ischemia and organ dysfunction. This responsibility largely falls to specialized macrophages in the spleen, known as red pulp macrophages, which efficiently take up and recycle damaged RBCs. However, questions remain regarding how these macrophages are acutely activated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Plasmonic Cavities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20250911152328&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene-based photonic structures have emerged as fertile ground for the controlled manipulation of surface plasmon polaritons (SPPs), providing a two-dimensional platform with low optoelectronic losses. In principle, nanostructuring graphene can enable further confinement of nanolight─enhancing light-matter interactions in the form of SPP cavity modes. In this study, we engineer nanoscale plasmonic cavities composed of self-assembled C(60) arrays on graphene. Using scattering-type scanning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20250911152328&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing risk prediction in intracranial aneurysm clipping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20250911152328&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20250911152328&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Li-Well ZnO Memtransistors: High Reliability for Neuromorphic Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memtransistors are active analog memory devices utilizing ionic memristive materials as channel layers. Since their introduction, the term "memtransistor" has widely been adopted for transistors exhibiting nonvolatile memory characteristics. Currently, memtransistor devices possessing both transistor on/off functionality and nonvolatile memory characteristics include ferroelectric field-effect transistors (FeFETs) and charge-trap flash (floating gate), yet ionic memtransistors have not matched...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Torsional Malalignment Syndrome: The Hidden Role of Medial Tibial Slope in Knee Varus and the Potential of PETS Treatment for Correction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A steeper posterior slope of the medial tibial plateau likely contributes to knee varus in TMS subjects when feet are neutral. Although PETS doesn't address the underlying rotational deformity, it improved coronal alignment and appearance in selected patients without functional compromise, offering a simple and cosmetically effective treatment alternative.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40932220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abbreviated liver magnetic resonance imaging with a second-shot arterial phase image to assess the viability of treated hepatocellular carcinoma after non-radiation locoregional therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The abbreviated LR-TR score in AMRI with SSAP showed non-inferior diagnostic performance to FP-MRI in terms of evaluating the viability for the treated HCC, which may be helpful in clinical practice alongside a decreased scan time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Astrocytic monoamine oxidase B (MAOB)-gamma-aminobutyric acid (GABA) axis as a molecular brake on repair following spinal cord injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroregeneration and remyelination rarely occur in the adult mammalian brain and spinal cord following central nervous system (CNS) injury. The glial scar has been proposed as a major contributor to this failure in the regenerative process. However, its underlying molecular and cellular mechanisms remain unclear. Here, we report that monoamine oxidase B (MAOB)-dependent excessive γ-aminobutyric acid (GABA) release from reactive astrocytes suppresses the CNS repair system by reducing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, POSTECH, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The WHO pandemic agreement: why countries will not use compulsory licensing - and how to fix it]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma Exosomes from Viral Hemorrhagic Septicemia Virus-Infected Olive Flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus): Proteomic Insights and Wound Healing Effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) or their sub types, such as exosomes are valuable nano-biomolecules for immunotherapeutic, drug delivery, and diagnostic purposes. Freshwater and marine fish, including olive flounder (Paralichthys olivaceus), are highly susceptible to the contagious Viral hemorrhagic septicemia virus (VHSV). In this study, we aimed to determine how infection alters the biological responses by analyzing the proteomic profiles of plasma-derived exosomes from phosphate buffered saline...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Threshold-based analysis of eutrophication dynamics in a semi-enclosed bay: The dominant role of dissolved inorganic nitrogen in Masan Bay, South Korea (2010-2015)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eutrophication in semi-enclosed coastal systems remains a persistent concern due to restricted water circulation and continuous nutrient inputs. To better characterize nutrient-driven water quality degradation, we applied a threshold-based analysis to seasonal monitoring data collected from Masan Bay, South Korea, between 2010 and 2015. Eutrophication status was assessed using a composite Eutrophication Index (EI) integrating chemical oxygen demand (COD), dissolved inorganic nitrogen (DIN), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Construction of Co/Co<sub>2</sub>N<sub>0.67</sub> nanoparticles embedded S and N-doped carbon from a cobalt-complex as a bifunctional Electrocatalyst for ORR and OER]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advancing impactful, economical, and durable Co-based bifunctional electrocatalysts for the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) and oxygen evolution reaction (OER) has been crucial in developing sustainable energy technologies. In this work, Co and Co(2)N(0.67) nanoparticles (NPs)-incorporated S, N-doped carbon catalysts (Co/Co(2)N(0.67)/SNC) were prepared via direct pyrolysis of the CoDATT complex, exhibiting high bifunctional electrocatalytic performance for ORR and OER. The complex precursor,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strong Magnon-Phonon Coupling in the Kagome Antiferromagnets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Magnon-phonon hybridization in ordered materials is a crucial phenomenon with significant implications for spintronics, magnonics, and quantum materials research. We present direct experimental evidence and theoretical insights into magnon-phonon coupling in Mn_{3}Ge, a kagome antiferromagnet with noncollinear spin order. Using inelastic x-ray scattering and ab initio modeling, we uncover strong hybridization between planar spin fluctuations and transverse optical phonons, resulting in a large...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioadaptive liquid-infused multifunctional fibers for long-term neural recording via BDNF stabilization and enhanced neural interaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brain-computer interfaces (BCIs) enable direct communication between the brain and computers. However, their long-term functionality remains limited due to signal degradation caused by acute insertion trauma, chronic foreign body reaction (FBR), and biofouling at the device-tissue interface. To address these challenges, we introduce a multifunctional surface modification strategy called targeting-specific interaction and blocking nonspecific adhesion (TAB) coating for flexible fiber, achieving a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40929275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Evaluations of a Mixed Extract of <em>Salvia Miltiorrhiza Bunge</em> and <em>Paeonia Lactiflora</em> Pall. (USCP-GVH-014): A 12 Weeks Clinical Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salvia miltiorrhiza Bunge and Paeonia lactiflora Pall. are traditionally used to manage cardiovascular health. However, clinical evidence evaluating standardized extracts for specific cardiovascular benefits is still evolving. This study aimed to evaluate its efficacy and safety of a mixed extract of S. miltiorrhiza Bunge and P. lactiflora Pall. (USCP-GVH-014) for improving cardiovascular function in adults with early-stage vascular health decline. This 12-week, single-center, single-arm,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Replication stress-induced nuclear hypertrophy alters chromatin topology and impacts cancer cell fitness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microscopic examination of biopsy tissues remains essential for cancer diagnosis, despite advancements in sequencing technologies. Alterations in nuclear size or the nuclear-to-cytoplasmic ratio are hallmark features of cancer cells and often correlate with disease progression. However, the mechanisms underlying nuclear size abnormalities and their impact on tumor progression remain unclear. In this study, we demonstrate that nuclear hypertrophy occurs in response to enhanced DNA replication...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40928878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wafer-scale integration of monolayer MoS<sub>2</sub><em>via</em> residue-free support layer etching and angular strain suppression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A crack-free and residue-free transfer technique for large-area, atomically-thin 2D transition metal dichalcogenides (TMDCs) such as MoS(2) and WS(2) is critical for their integration into next-generation electronic devices, either as channel materials replacing silicon or as back-end-of-line (BEOL) components in 3D-integrated nano-systems on CMOS platforms. However, cracks are frequently observed during the debonding of TMDCs from their growth substrates, and polymer or metal residues are often...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of <em>Streptococcus mitis</em> subsp. <em>carlssonii</em> isolated from human vagina: prevalence, phenotypic, and genomic insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The genus Streptococcus is a heterogenous group of commensal and pathogenic bacteria. Members of this genus are classified into two major groups, the pyogenic group and the viridans group streptococci (VGS). VGS are frequently found as normal members of the human microbiome and are regarded as commensals. In this work, we characterized a VGS strain isolated from the vaginal swab sample of a Korean patient diagnosed with endometrial cancer. Phylogenetic, phenotypic, and genome-based analyses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40927450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polystyrene particles induces asthma-like Th2-mediated lung injury through IL-33 secretion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastics, particularly polystyrene (PS), are extensively used worldwide, especially in disposable packaging, which contributes to environmental pollution by generating microplastic particles. Herein, we investigated the pulmonary toxic effects of PS microplastics, focusing on airway inflammation and immune response. PS microplastic (50 nm to 1 μm) exposure was more likely to cause a severe pulmonary inflammatory response, particularly with smaller particle sizes. PS microplastic nose-only...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Characteristics of Individuals with COPD, Pre-COPD, Smokers with Normal Lung Function in Korea: Updated Analysis of the KOCOSS Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This analysis of the KOCOSS cohort highlights the distinct clinical characteristics of individuals with COPD, pre-COPD, and smokers with normal lung function. Notably, individuals without spirometric COPD still showed substantial symptom burden and inhaler use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40926396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-Learning System for Automatic Measurement of the Femorotibial Rotational Angle on Lower-Extremity Computed Tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To develop and validate a deep-learning-based algorithm for automatic identification of anatomical landmarks and calculating femoral and tibial version angles (FTT angles) on lower-extremity CT scans. In this IRB-approved, retrospective study, lower-extremity CT scans from 270 adult patients (median age, 69 years; female to male ratio, 235:35) were analyzed. CT data were preprocessed using contrast-limited adaptive histogram equalization and RGB superposition to enhance tissue boundary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Late fluid flow in a primitive asteroid revealed by Lu-Hf isotopes in Ryugu]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbonaceous asteroids are the source of the most primitive meteorites¹ and represent leftover planetesimals that formed from ice and dust in the outer Solar System and may have delivered volatiles to the terrestrial planets^(2-5). Understanding the aqueous activity of asteroids is key to deciphering their thermal, chemical and orbital evolution, with implications for the origin of water on the terrestrial planets. Analyses of the objects, in particular pristine samples returned from asteroid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triplet-harvesting materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40931059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of glaucoma surgery on recurrence rate in cytomegalovirus anterior uveitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GS significantly reduced recurrence rate by 77.4% in patients with CMV-AU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social support and subjective care burden among the family caregivers of terminally ill cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Properly addressing the multiple dimensions of social support alleviates the subjective care burden of the FCs of terminal cancer patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40930953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250911152327&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>