<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 07:37:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiomics-enhanced modelling approach for predicting the need for ECMO in ARDS patients: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decisions regarding veno-venous extracorporeal membrane oxygenation (vv-ECMO) in patients with acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS) are often based solely on clinical and physiological parameters, which may insufficiently reflect severity and heterogeneity of lung injury. This study aimed to develop a predictive model integrating machine learning-derived quantitative features from admission chest computed tomography (CT) with selected clinical variables to support early individualized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The relationship between retinal vascular tortuosity and retinal vasculitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hippocampal-cortical interactions in the consolidation of social memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Episodic memories are initially encoded in the hippocampus and subsequently undergo systems consolidation into the neocortex. The nature of memories stored in the hippocampus and neocortex differs, with the cortex encoding memories in more generalized forms. Although several brain regions encode social information, the specific cortical regions and circuits involved in the consolidation of social memories and the nature of the information encoded in the cortex remain unclear. Using in vivo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027906/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Boron and Nitrogen Bridged Mn Single-Atom Catalyst for Highly Efficient Nitrogen Electroreduction to Ammonia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ammonia (NH(3)) is a globally important commodity for energy storage, carbon-free energy carrier, and fertilizer production, but its synthesis through the Haber-Bosch process is energy-intensive and emits significant amounts of CO(2). Electrochemical reduction of N(2) under ambient conditions is a green and potentially promising approach for NH(3) synthesis, but is limited by a high energy barrier of the first *N(2) protonation step, competitive hydrogen evolution reaction, and lack of efficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electric Field Tunable Interlayer Sliding Ferroelectricity in 2H-Stacked Multilayer WSe<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroelectricity in two-dimensional (2D) materials has strong potential for the development of ultrathin, low-power memory devices. However, most 2D ferroelectric systems reported to date rely on moiré superlattices or structural asymmetry, such as rhombohedral stacking, limiting their scalability and fabrication yield. Here, we report emergent ferroelectric switching in hexagonal (2H)-stacked multilayer Tungsten diselenide (WSe(2)) heterostructures. In devices composed of 2L or thicker WSe(2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of trivalent Sb<sup>3+</sup>-ion doping on charge carrier recombination dynamics of cesium lead bromide perovskite quantum dots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-ion doping of perovskites has proven to enhance their photoluminescence (PL) properties and stability; however, the underlying charge carrier dynamics remain unclear. We synthesized a cesium lead bromide (CsPbBr(3)) perovskite quantum dot (PQD) incorporating a heterovalent Sb^(3+) ion dopant and its pristine counterpart and performed time-resolved single-particle PL spectroscopy. The PL intensity and lifetime of the Sb-CsPbBr(3) PQD were remarkably enhanced compared to those of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catastrophic Degradation in Solid Oxide Fuel Cells Caused by Air Supply Interruption in Real-World Operations: Fundamental Mechanisms and Mitigation Strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid market expansion of solid oxide fuel cells (SOFCs), real-world operational incidents have unveiled various critical challenges. Malfunction of the gas supply system is among the most frequent and critical issues, severely damaging cells and stacks. However, the actual cause of this degradation remains completely unknown; existing explanations have been mostly speculative, and simple engineering-based solutions have proven ineffective. The study reveals that air supply interruption...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anticooperative self-assembly of perylene diimide dyes in water unveiled by advanced molecular dynamics simulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The self-assembly mechanism and the dynamics in water of π-stacked columnar aggregates of N,N-bis(2-(trimethylammonium)ethylene)perylene-3,4,9,10-tetracarboxylic acid bis-imide (PDI) have been investigated using classical molecular dynamics (MD) simulations based on an accurate quantum mechanically derived force field. Nano-scale aggregates composed of up to twelve monomers were studied through a combination of bottom-up and top-down approaches, complemented by enhanced sampling MD techniques....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fully Aqueous and Printable Photonic Inks with Tunable Pitch and Optical Memory via Hydrogen-Bonded HPC-PVA Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rewritable and structurally colored biopolymer coatings demand fully aqueous processing, optical tunability, and dry-state color retention, yet these requirements remain difficult to reconcile without chemical crosslinking. Competitive hydrogen bonding between hydroxypropyl cellulose (HPC) and poly(vinyl alcohol) (PVA) is leveraged to achieve dynamic pitch modulation and kinetic trapping of cholesteric order, thereby overcoming the intrinsic limitations of HPC-based inks. In this study, a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving the Performance of Vacuum-Deposited Perovskite Light-Emitting Diodes via a Tailored Sequential Deposition Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vacuum-deposited perovskite light-emitting diodes (PeLEDs) are attracting increased attention owing to their precise thickness control and absence of solvent-orthogonality constraints, offering significant potential for optimizing device performance. Here, we systematically compare how varying the deposition sequence of a single additive, triphenylphosphine oxide (TPPO)─known for its effective defect passivation─critically affects the crystallization dynamics, film morphology, and optoelectronic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LC-MS-Guided Isolation of Triterpene Glycosides from <em>Holothuria atra</em>: Structural Features Governing TRPA1 Inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The LC-MS-guided separation of the extract from the sea cucumber Holothuria atra led to the isolation of 16 triterpene glycosides (1-16), including seven previously unreported derivatives consisting of three sulfated (1, 3, 5) and four nonsulfated congeners (12, 13, 15, and 16). Notably, compounds 15 and 16 feature a new aglycone structure bearing an 8(9),11(12)-diene scaffold. All isolates were evaluated for their inhibitory activity toward transient receptor potential ankyrin 1 (TRPA1). In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Position statement: Evidence-Based Exercise Guidelines for Sarcopenia in Older Adults: Insights from the Korean Working Group on Sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first Korean evidence-based exercise guideline developed within the KWGS algorithm, offering clinical and community practitioners specific, actionable strategies for preventing and managing sarcopenia. It supports tailored interventions using FITT principles aligned with individual goals and sarcopenia classification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol for efficient recovery of high-quality DNA from microbiome of marine invertebrates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Marine organisms often form symbiotic relationships with various microorganisms to adapt and thrive in harsh environments. These symbiotic microbes contribute to host survival by providing nutrition, modulating the hosts' immune system, and supporting overall physiological stability. Advances in high-throughput sequencing technologies have enabled a deeper understanding of the structure and function of symbiotic microbial communities, as well as host-microbe interactions. Notably, symbiotic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the biosynthetic potential of Korean Actinobacteria for antibacterial metabolite discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Actinobacteria, a phylum of Gram-positive bacteria, are renowned for their remarkable ability to produce antibacterial natural products. The National Institute of Biological Resources (NIBR) of Korea maintains a collection of Korean native actinobacteria. In this study, we explored the phylogenetic and biosynthetic diversity of the NIBR actinobacteria collection to assess its potential as a source of new antibacterial natural products. A 16S rDNA-based phylogenetic analysis revealed a high level...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving the Conductivity and Stability of Silver Nanowires Through Spontaneous Ligand Exchange for Joule Heating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silver nanowires (AgNWs) are promising materials for optoelectronic devices, owing to their high transparency and conductivity. However, their performance is limited by polyvinylpyrrolidone (PVP) as an insulating capping agent that is essential for the synthesis of AgNWs but increases their intrinsic resistance. Herein, we introduce a facile spin-coating ligand exchange strategy that considers the physicochemical properties of ligands, including PVP solubility, viscosity, volatility, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and immunogenicity of adenoviral Fc-fused FMDV virus-like particle vaccine in swine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Foot-and-mouth disease (FMD) remains a major threat to global livestock health, and current inactivated vaccines face limitations in biosafety and cross-protection. Virus-like particle (VLP) -based vaccines offer a safer alternative, however, their production is often hindered by the cytotoxicity of the viral 3C protease. In this study, we developed a modified 3C protease with reduced cytotoxicity, enabling efficient expression of FMDV VLPs via an internal ribosome entry site (IRES)-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lactose-functionalized photosensitizer nanoparticles derived from thiophene-fused BODIPY for NIR-imaging-guided photodynamic treatment of hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Four near-infrared (NIR) photosensitizers (PSs) (PHTB, PBrTB, THTB, and TBrTB) based on thiophene-fused, BODIPY-conjugated, and liver-tumor-targeting lactose were synthesized and characterized. Brominating the BODIPY core of PHTB and the terminal thiophene rings of THTB yielded PBrTB and TBrTB, respectively. All derivatives exhibited strong NIR absorption (λ(ab) = 640-674 nm) as well as moderate fluorescence quantum yields (Φ(F) = 0.21-0.35) and self-assembled into stable, uniform nanoparticles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of preoperative immunonutrition in malnourished patients undergoing colorectal cancer surgery: a study protocol for a multicenter randomized clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Malnutrition is a significant risk factor for postoperative complications in patients undergoing colorectal cancer surgery. Although current guidelines recommend preoperative immunonutrition for malnourished patients, its clinical benefit remains controversial. Our previous randomized clinical trial assessing immunonutrition in unselected colon cancer patients showed no reduction in infectious complications. This study aims to evaluate the efficacy of preoperative immunonutrition in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proteome mining of Yersinia Enterocolitica for drug targets and computational inhibitor identification with ADMET, anti-inflammation potential and formulation characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Yersinia enterocolitica infection can manifest as self-limiting gastroenteritis and may lead to more severe conditions, such as mesenteric lymphadenitis, reactive arthritis, or rare systemic infections. Fluoroquinolones and third-generation cephalosporins are the most effective treatment options but tetracyclines and co-trimoxazole effectiveness may vary based on resistance patterns. To explore new therapeutic options in case of antibiotic resistance, we initially mined drug targets from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Author Reflections: OPSCC Survivorship-Patient Determinants and Treatment‑Specific Quality‑of‑Life Trade‑offs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: Psilocybin's lasting action requires pyramidal cell types and 5-HT2A receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Selenium-alloyed tellurium oxide for amorphous p-channel transistors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wind speed interannual variability with measured data validations and its impact on energy yield in the Southwest Sea of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Republic of Korea (ROK) has set an ambitious goal of 40.7 GW of onshore and offshore wind farms by 2038, as outlined in the "11th Basic Plan for Electricity Supply and Demand" in May 2024. To achieve this target, both wind farm developers and the government are crafting policies for "Project Site Planning" and "Offshore Wind Farm Clusters". A major concern for stakeholders is the variability in annual wind resources driven by climate phenomena and climate change, which can lead to increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251001033719&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Regenerating the uterus: translational advances in endometrial bioengineering and immunotherapeutics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Uterine disorders, such as thin endometrium and intrauterine adhesions, remain significant challenges in reproductive medicine, often leading to infertility and poor pregnancy outcomes. Recent advances in regenerative medicine and tissue engineering have led to the development of innovative therapeutic strategies aimed at restoring endometrial structure and function. Biomaterials play a central role in these advancements, serving not only as structural scaffolds and delivery vehicles for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing retinal images based carotid atherosclerosis prediction with explainable foundation models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carotid atherosclerosis is a key predictor of cardiovascular disease (CVD), necessitating early detection. While foundation models (FMs) show promise in medical imaging, their optimal selection and fine-tuning strategies for classifying carotid atherosclerosis from retinal images remain unclear. Using data from 39,620 individuals, we evaluated four vision FMs with three fine-tuning methods. Performance was evaluated by predictive performance, clinical utility by survival analysis for future CVD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multicenter validation of a scalable, interpretable, multitask prediction model for multiple clinical outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Predicting multiple postoperative complications remains challenging in perioperative care. Current approaches often address complications individually, limiting the potential for integrated risk assessment. We developed and externally validated a scalable, interpretable, tree-based multitask learning model to predict three critical postoperative outcomes-acute kidney injury (AKI), postoperative respiratory failure (PRF), and in-hospital mortality-using 16 preoperative features generally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028168/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Field outbreak investigation and immunoinformatic analysis suggest potential immune evasion by Newcastle disease virus Sub-Genotype XIV.2 in Nigeria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Poultry production is one of the fastest-growing agricultural sub-sectors in Nigeria. However, it faces numerous challenges, mainly from frequent Newcastle disease (ND) outbreaks even in vaccinated flocks, causing huge economic losses. The recurring outbreaks raise concerns about the efficacy of ND vaccine and the need to understand the immunomodulatory mechanism of the ND virus (NDV). This study investigated a recent outbreak of NDV that resulted in 95% mortality in a vaccinated broiler parent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic profiles of squamous cell lung carcinoma and diagnostic model construction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer cells exhibit metabolic reprogramming to fulfill their increased demands for abnormal growth and proliferation. We studied metabolic profiles of squamous cell lung carcinoma (LUSC).Elevated arginine levels and reduced acylcarnitine C18:2, along with decreased phosphatidylcholine (PC) with acyl-alkyl residues C38:0 were associated with the diagnosis and prognosis of LUSC. Most of the PCs demonstrated a decrease, while lysophosphatidylcholines (LPC) exhibited an increase in LUSC patients....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polygenic risk score for breast cancer risk prediction in Asian BRCA1 and BRCA2 pathogenic variants carriers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polygenic risk scores (PRS) have been shown to be predictive of breast cancer (BC) risk in European BRCA1 and BRCA2 pathogenic variant (PV) carriers, but their utility in Asian populations has not been evaluated. In this study, we evaluated the association of two breast cancer PRS developed for the East Asian general population and three versions of a PRS developed for the European general population in 604 BRCA1 (390 affected by breast cancer) and 785 BRCA2 (552 affected by breast cancer) PV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postsynthetic Triazolate Functionalization of Ni<sub>2</sub>Cl<sub>2</sub>BTDD: Creation of Supplementary CO<sub>2</sub> Adsorption Sites and Exceptional CO<sub>2</sub> Selectivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Postsynthetic modification (PSM) offers a versatile approach to tune metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) by introducing functional groups or exchanging bridging ligands while preserving open metal sites (OMSs). Nevertheless, generating additional adsorption sites via PSM remains challenging. Herein, we report a new PSM strategy that creates supplementary sorption sites within a robust MOF framework. We synthesized triazolate-exchanged Ni(2)(triazolates)(x)Cl(2-x)BTDD (BTDD =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027835/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Evaluation of emission factors for resuspended tire-wear particles in urban road dust using empirical model-based methods" [Sci. Total Environ., volume 975 (2025) 179322]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic modulation of claudin18.2 expression and remodeling of the tumor microenvironment in gastric cancer during chemo-immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CLDN18.2 expression is dynamically regulated during chemoimmunotherapy and is associated with a distinct immunosuppressive and fibrotic TME. These findings highlight the importance of repeated biomarker assessment and suggest potential combinatorial therapeutic strategies targeting both epithelial and stromal compartments in GC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Description of Redo Gastric Per-Oral Endoscopic Myotomy for Refractory Gastroparesis: Technical Conduct and Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction: Gastroparesis is a progressive disease that may require endoscopic or surgical intervention, such as gastric per oral endoscopic myotomy (G-POEM), when conservative measures are ineffective or not tolerated. Limited data exist on redo G-POEM safety and effectiveness. We describe outcomes of patients undergoing repeat G-POEM for refractory gastroparesis. Methods: A retrospective review of patients who underwent redo G-POEM at our center from 2008 to 2024. Data included demographics,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current state of artificial intelligence applications in assisted reproductive technology: A narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has rapidly advanced in healthcare, demonstrating significant potential in analyzing large, heterogeneous datasets using optimized algorithms for disease prediction and personalized treatment. Assisted reproductive technology (ART), particularly in vitro fertilization (IVF) and embryo transfer, generates extensive data, making it especially suitable for AI-driven analysis. AI-based applications aim to improve clinical outcomes through personalized ART strategies and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A triple-responsive nanozyme platform of AgAu-CeO<sub>2</sub> heterojunction integrated with probiotics for precision antibacterial therapy in periodontitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanozymes hold significant promise for biomedical applications; however, their clinical translation is hindered by the mismatch between physiological conditions and their optimal catalytic environments, particularly with respect to temperature and pH. To address this challenge, we developed a multifunctional composite nanozyme (AgAu C-L, formed by covalent conjugation of AgAu@CeO(2) with Lactobacillus reuteri) by anchoring an ultrasmall cerium dioxide (CeO(2)) nanozyme with peroxidase (POD)-like...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are long-term care systems aligned with person-centered integrated care? Evidence from the Western Pacific]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Western Pacific LTC systems are not yet fully aligned with effective integrated LTC. Strengthening coordinated and accountable governance, integrating financing streams and incentive, enhancing IM&E systems for performance management, and leveraging innovation are crucial to enhancing integrated LTC in the region.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distal Radial Access vs Transradial Access in Patients With ST-Segment Elevation Myocardial Infarction: The DRAMI Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In STEMI patients, DRA failed to demonstrate noninferiority to TRA in terms of puncture success. However, both access routes showed comparable procedural efficacy and safety. Further validation with a larger, adequately powered study is required to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[US and Korean children prefer equality, but Korean children are more tolerant of ingroup-favoring allocations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[It has been shown that with age, US children become more likely to prefer equal over unequal allocations and do so in an impartial way for both ingroup and outgroup members. However, it is possible that such findings are based on norms of impartiality that are more common in Western societies than in collectivistic societies which place a greater emphasis on group loyalty. For example, children from a collectivist society might endorse ingroup-favoring allocations more than equal allocations or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027077/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When seeing follows believing: The role of social likelihood in demographic estimation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates how individuals estimate the size of demographic groups and whether these estimations are guided by contextual expectations rooted in social associations. Across three experiments (N = 180), we explore the hypothesis that people employ a rational compensation strategy when estimating group prevalence, adjusting their judgments toward likely values depending on contextual cues. In Experiment 1, participants estimated the proportions of gender and political affiliation from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Appearance management's impact on identity and well-aging in late Middle-aged Korean women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examines the complex relationships between appearance management motivation, multidimensional identity, and well-aging among Korean women aged 50-69. Research with 700 participants in the Seoul metropolitan area revealed that appearance management functions as a psychosocial mechanism for identity reconstruction and well-aging beyond aesthetic practice. Key findings demonstrated that appearance management motivation serves as a core mechanism of identity formation, grounded in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phyllostachyos Caulis in Taeniam extract stimulates longitudinal bone growth via IGF-1 and JAK2/STAT5 signaling in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Longitudinal bone growth, which is regulated by endocrine and paracrine factors, is a critical determinant of linear growth during childhood. This study investigated the effects of an aqueous extract of Phyllostachyos Caulis in Taeniam (PCE) on longitudinal bone growth and its regulatory effects on circulating insulin-like growth factor-1 (IGF-1) in rats. Twenty-eight adolescent rats were randomly assigned to four groups (n = 7 per group): control, recombinant human growth hormone (rhGH) 20...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deciphering Multi-Axis Facial Rotation: The Key to Understanding Facial Asymmetry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Facial asymmetry, manifesting as visible differences between the two sides of the face, is common. These disparities can be structural (inherent in the individual's facial bone structure or soft tissues), or functional (the result of variations in muscle tone or nerve function, and apparent only during expressions like smiling or frowning). To achieve optimal aesthetic and functional outcomes in aesthetics, orthodontics, and facial reconstructive surgery, practitioners must understand and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antiaging Strategies Utilizing Multilayer Rejuvenation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is an ongoing process involving changes in the skin, muscle, bone, fat, and ligaments. This process has been extensively studied, especially by plastic surgeons who have categorized the process into four distinct facial regions that include the upper face, midface, lower face, and neck regions. Approaches to mitigate the aging process encompass surgical options such as facelifts and blepharoplasty, as well as treatments employing energy-based technologies like high-intensity focused...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sugar intake trajectories in adolescents: Evaluating behavioral change with group-based trajectory modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Intake-based tailored interventions effectively accommodate individual variability in dietary behavior change, with particularly pronounced benefits among participants with higher baseline intake. These findings underscore the importance of adaptive intervention strategies and the need to consider individual and structural factors when designing public health interventions targeting adolescent diet.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Final Results from a First-in-Human Phase 1 Study of the Dual Isocitrate Dehydrogenase (IDH) 1/2 Inhibitor, LY3410738, in Advanced Solid Tumors Harboring IDH1 or IDH2 Mutations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LY3410738 demonstrated largely cytostatic antitumor activity in IDH1- or IDH2-mutated cholangiocarcinoma and IDH1-mutated gliomas. LY3410738 plus cisplatin-gemcitabine exhibited favorable antitumor activity in patients with treatment-naïve IDH-mutated cholangiocarcinoma, warranting further exploration as a treatment strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiographic Assessment of Successful Lumbar Spinal Fusion: A Systematic Review of Fusion Criteria in Randomized Trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study TypeSystematic Scoping Review.IntroductionRadiographic assessment is crucial for diagnosing symptomatic pseudarthrosis and evaluating spinal fusion outcomes, yet no consensus exists on defining successful lumbar fusion. This scoping review presents criteria for imaging-based assessment after posterolateral and interbody lumbar fusion, aiming to guide consistent evaluation methods.MethodsFollowing PRISMA guidelines, a comprehensive search of Medline, Embase, and Scopus identified eligible...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel agents and evolving strategies for anemia management in lower-risk myelodysplastic syndromes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in the treatment of lower-risk myelodysplastic syndromes have focused on improving anemia management, which remains a major clinical challenge. Erythropoiesis-stimulating agents (ESAs) and lenalidomide are the standard therapies; however, their effectiveness is limited by resistance and patient selection criteria. Luspatercept, a transforming growth factor-beta superfamily ligand trap, has shown improved transfusion independence and is now considered a frontline option for a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Importance of Lysosomal Trapping and Plasmodium Parasite Infection on the Pharmacokinetics of Pyronaridine: A Physiologically Based Pharmacokinetic Model-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates the value of PBPK modeling in elucidating key pharmacokinetic mechanisms, revealing the critical roles of lysosomal sequestration, Hb level, and parasitemia in pyronaridine disposition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Type 2 diabetes in patients undergoing gastric cancer surgery: areas requiring disease-specific glycemic management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review provides a comprehensive analysis of phase-specific management strategies for type 2 diabetes (T2D) in patients undergoing gastric cancer (GC) surgery, encompassing the preoperative, intraoperative and postoperative phases within the context of oncodiabetology. In the preoperative phase, predicting T2D remission and evaluating antidiabetic medications while considering their adverse event profiles are important. These medications include metformin and sodium-glucose cotransporter 2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of dioxin exposure on diabetes and potential dietary modification in the Korean population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic pass bias control for temperature-resilient neural networks using vertical NAND flash memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vertical NAND (V-NAND) flash memory has emerged as a promising candidate for neuromorphic computing platforms due to its high density, scalability, and reliability. However, synaptic weights stored in V-NAND cells are highly sensitive to ambient temperature variations, resulting in significant conductance shifts that degrade the inference accuracy of neural networks. To address this challenge, we propose a dynamic pass bias (DPB) control scheme that compensates for temperature-induced weight...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letters to the Editor: rebuttal to OSIN-D-25-01417R1 "Letter to the editor concerning "Association between osteoporosis and risk of dementia: a Korean women nationwide population-based cohort study""]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Use of Late Gadolinium Enhancement and Left Ventricular Global Longitudinal Strain in Hypertrophic Cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LGE and LV-GLS provide complementary prognostic information in HCM. Patients with both increased LGE and decreased LV-GLS are at particularly high risk, highlighting the value of integrating both biomarkers for risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Using a Vision-Language Model to Generate Visual Abstracts for Radiology Journals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between exposure to VOCs mixture and impaired renal function in Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Evidence suggests that volatile organic compounds (VOCs) is linked to negative health outcomes. This study investigated the association of exposure to VOC mixtures with renal function parameters. Our study included a nationwide sample of Korean adults (n = 1758). The following nine urinary VOC metabolites were measured: SPMA, BMA, 3,4-MHA, 2-MHA, MA, 3-HPMA, BPMA, DHBMA, and PGA. Estimated glomerular filtration rate (eGFR) was calculated based on the serum creatinine levels. Urine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lace Index: Predict the High-Risk of 30-Days Readmission of Patients With Acute Myocardial Infarction: National Health Insurance Claims Data 2011-2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Study findings suggest the LACE index is a useful tool for predicting 30-day readmissions among AMI patients in Korea. Its simplicity and moderate accuracy support its application in clinical and policy-level risk stratification strategies. Future prospective studies should refine prediction models by incorporating additional clinical variables.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term Risk of Hydrocephalus Following Traumatic Brain Injury and Hemorrhagic Stroke: A Nationwide Cohort Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TBI and HS are associated with a substantially increased long-term risk of hydrocephalus, especially in the early years following diagnosis. HS confers a greater risk than TBI. These findings underscore the need for prolonged surveillance in high-risk individuals and appropriate management of hydrocephalus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing Venous Pulsatile Tinnitus Using Intraoperative Doppler Ultrasound: How I Do It]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraoperative Doppler ultrasound (IDU) can determine the exact location of sigmoid sinus dehiscence (SS-deh), diverticulum (SS-div) and large emissary vein (LEV). Furthermore, real-time measurement of the sufficiency during surgical SS-deh resurfacing procedures, periosteal flap insertion into the SS-div or LEV compression is possible with IDU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expansion Pattern of Miniscrew Assisted Rapid Maxillary Expansion (MARPE) After Midpalatal Suture Separation: Clustering-Based Classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study introduces a concrete classification system for MARPE outcomes, emphasising the role of expansion efficiency and parallelism in optimising clinical results. These four identified phenotypes provide a data-driven validation of the existing concepts of expansion patterns and their implications for treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary valve-in-valve implantation using a Pulsta valve in repaired Tetralogy of Fallot]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the first case in Vietnam of transcatheter pulmonary valve-in-valve implantation using the self-expanding Pulsta valve in a young adult with repaired Tetralogy of Fallot. This case demonstrates the feasibility, safety, and early effectiveness of self-expanding valves in complex right ventricular outflow tract anatomies and highlights the importance of multimodal imaging in procedural planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of Boolean 2.0 criteria for remission and quality of life prediction in Korean patients with rheumatoid arthritis receiving targeted therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although Boolean 2.0 improves concordance with DAS28-ESR, it does not enhance the prediction of long-term functional or QoL outcomes. Its broader definition of remission warrants cautious interpretation in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Prognostic Value of the Prognostic Nutritional Index in Patients Undergoing Coronary Artery Bypass Grafting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative PNI was significantly associated with long-term mortality after coronary artery bypass grafting, and addition of PNI improved risk discrimination beyond conventional clinical models. Further prospective studies are warranted to validate these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Assessment of Condylar Bone Changes in Osteoarthritis Patients Using Single-photon emission computed tomography/computed tomography and Magnetic resonance imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study can provide the basis that SIR can be helpful in diagnosis in patients clinically suspected of having OA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure and Cardiovascular Outcomes in Adults With Diabetes and Chronic Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among patients with diabetes and chronic kidney disease, SBP <130 mm Hg and diastolic BP <80 mm Hg were associated with reduced risk of CVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025438/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perianal Disease Modifiers Are Associated With Less Severe Luminal Disease Activity in Children With Crohn's Disease at Diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perianal fistulizing disease was more common in boys who exhibited milder disease activity, indicating the importance of recognizing perianal fistulizing disease as a clinical clue to the early diagnosis of underlying luminal CD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative Cosmetic Outcomes and Quality of Life After Thyroidectomy: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Remote-access approaches and MIVAT offer superior cosmesis over CTA. TOA and BABA generally rank highest in both cosmesis and QOL, although evidence on QOL remains limited. These approaches may be considered for patients prioritizing aesthetic and psychosocial outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of healthcare providers and patients with diabetes mellitus regarding continuous glucose monitoring use in South Korea: a multicenter, cross-sectional survey study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CGM provides significant clinical benefits but is limited by discomfort, costs, and educational burden. Sustained adoption requires device improvements, insurance support, and workforce expansion.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Injection-Based Therapies for Migraine in Older Adults: A Narrative Review of OnabotulinumtoxinA, Greater Occipital Nerve Block, and Anti-Calcitonin Gene-Related Peptide Monoclonal Antibodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As global populations age, the clinical approach to managing migraine must evolve. Migraine in older adults presents unique treatment challenges due to comorbidities, poor adherence to treatment, altered pharmacokinetics, and polypharmacy. Injection -based preventive treatments such as onabotulinumtoxinA (BoNT-A), greater occipital nerve blocks (GONB), and anti-calcitonin gene-related peptide monoclonal antibodies (CGRP mAbs) offer promising alternatives. This narrative review highlights the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drawing Guideline for <em>JKMS</em> Manuscript (07) Baseline Table and Plots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The appropriate plot effectively conveys the author's conclusions to the readers. Journal of Korean Medical Science will provide a series of special articles to show you how to make consistent and excellent results easier. In this article, we will cover baseline table and plots. The baseline table is a very popular and essential table introduced in almost all medical papers, but it takes a lot of time and effort to create it. We introduce a simple yet effective tool to make this easy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary Fibrosis in Critically Ill Patients With COVID-19: A Multi-Center Retrospective Cohort Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrated that in patients with severe COVID-19 pneumonia requiring MV, chest CT revealed fibrotic-like changes in approximately three-quarters of patients. In addition, our results suggest that higher daily doses of steroids may be associated with a reduced risk of pulmonary fibrosis. Further research is needed to determine the appropriate steroid dose that may reduce the progression of pulmonary fibrosis and improve clinical outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Cutaneous and Genital Warts in Organ and Hematopoietic Stem Cell Transplant Patients: A Nationwide Population-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that transplantation is associated with an increased risk of both cutaneous and genital warts, with variations in risk based on age. These findings highlight the need for targeted surveillance and management strategies for wart prevention in transplant recipients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Peripheral NLRP3 Inflammasome Expression in Parkinson's Disease and Multiple System Atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings challenge the prevailing hypothesis that NLRP3 inflammasome activation directly contributes to PD pathogenesis. Instead, the observed increase in ASC and caspase-1 expression suggests the potential involvement of alternative inflammasome pathways during disease progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiotherapy omission in low-risk, early-stage breast cancer: a single-center, real-world comparative analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Low-risk, early-stage breast cancer patients exhibited comparable disease recurrence and survival rates regardless of the RT status. Our study underscores the necessity for further investigation into RT omission in carefully selected patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025282/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility study of dose de-escalation in postoperative intensity-modulated radiation therapy for locally advanced thymoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Radiation dose de-escalation in locally advanced thymoma patients undergoing PORT showed comparable survival outcomes with reduced toxicity and shorter treatment duration, but requires longer follow-up to confirm efficacy and safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of radiotherapy in patients with intermediate- and high-risk meningiomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: RT with adjuvant or salvage intent showed favorable treatment outcomes in patients with intermediate- to high-risk meningioma. WHO grade 3 histology and recurrent tumors were identified as adverse prognostic factors for PFS in high-risk patients. LF was the dominant failure pattern after CFRT, accounting for 86.7% of all recurrences. These findings underscore the need for further studies on dose-escalated RT to enhance local control in patients with these adverse features.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is there a role of radiotherapy for steroid-resistant thyroid eye disease?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Community Care in Korea: Implementation and Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent progress in nickel oxide-based chemiresistive toxic-gas sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous advancements in technology and industry have resulted in the discharge of toxic and hazardous gases that pose a threat to human health and the environment. Consequently, developing gas-sensing devices with high sensitivities and selectivities toward these gases is crucial. In recent years, interest in sensors for gases based on p-type nickel oxide (NiO) materials has increased owing to their good catalytic activity, outstanding repeatability, high availability, excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum: Staphylococcus parequorum sp. nov. and Staphylococcus halotolerans sp. nov., isolated from traditional Korean soybean foods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025250/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bak and Bax are crucial for Gbp2-mediated pyroptosis during Vibrio and Salmonella infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pyroptosis a lytic form of programmed cell death, is a crucial host defense mechanism against bacterial pathogens. While caspase-mediated pathways are central to pyroptosis, the involvement of apoptotic regulators such as Bak, Bax, and MCL-1 in bacterial infection-induced pyroptosis remains unclear. Here, we investigated how these BCL-2 family proteins modulate pyroptosis induced by Vibrio vulnificus and Salmonella enterica serovar Typhimurium in murine cells. In mouse embryonic fibroblasts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PhoU interaction with the PhoR PAS domain is required for repression of the pho regulon and Salmonella virulence, but not for polyphosphate accumulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pho regulon plays a critical role in maintaining phosphate homeostasis in bacteria, with the PhoU protein functioning as a regulator that bridges the PhoB/PhoR two-component system and the PstSCAB2 phosphate transporter. While PhoU is known to suppress PhoR autophosphorylation under high phosphate conditions via interaction with its PAS domain, its broader regulatory functions remain elusive. Here, we investigated the role of the PhoU Ala147 residue in Salmonella enterica serovar Typhimurium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additive manufacturing of MXene electrodes: from rheology-tunable nanoinks to size-scalable integrated electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Additive manufacturing (AM) has emerged as a transformative strategy for translating nanoscale materials into wafer-scale functional architectures, empowering the scalable fabrication of advanced electronics and energy systems. MXenes-a class of two-dimensional transition metal carbides and nitrides-exhibit exceptional electrical conductivity, tunable surface terminations, and mechanical compliance, positioning them as ideal candidates for AM-driven printed electronics. This review uniquely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of umbilical cord-derived mesenchymal stem cell-conditioned media for preventing and treating skin aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: UCMSC-CM is effective and safe for preventing and treating skin aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcomes of endoscopic resection of 1-1.5 cm sized grade 1 rectal neuroendocrine tumor: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Endoscopic resection of 1-1.5 cm grade 1 rectal NETs yielded comparable outcomes to those < 1 cm in size, suggesting its feasibility as a treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Priority Habitats for Dung Beetle Conservation: Taxonomic and Functional Responses Across a Land-Use Disturbance Gradient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anthropogenic activities are causing a decline in dung beetles due to land-use change and overexploitation. This underscores the need for their conservation, for which identification of high-priority habitats and associated species is necessary. To achieve this, this study evaluated taxonomic and functional diversity across various land-use types and dung types. Field experiments were conducted using dung-baited pitfall traps set up in different land-use types along a disturbance gradient: built...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative evaluation of three traditional herbal formulas on gastrointestinal motility in a mouse model of cold stress-induced dyspepsia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PS more effectively alleviated CS-induced GI dysfunction than both YT and ST. These comparative findings offer valuable insights for clinical applications in the treatment of cold-related digestive disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intraoperative and postoperative suprachoroidal hemorrhage in pediatric patients undergoing penetrating keratoplasty or Ahmed valve implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The risk of intraoperative and delayed SCH should be considered in eyes with Peters anomaly, CG, and aniridia during intraocular surgeries that involve significant intraocular pressure fluctuations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024720/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A case of Birdshot Chorioretinopathy successfully treated with Adalimumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clonal Burden, Immunoglobulin Heavy Chain Variable Gene Somatic Hypermutations, and Immunoglobulin Gene Repertoire in Korean Patients with Chronic Lymphocytic Leukemia Assessed by Next-generation Sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: NGS may underestimate CLL clonal size, particularly when using the IGH leader primer set. IGHV SHMs were inversely associated with negative prognostic factors. Our data suggest ethnic differences in CLL pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Disparities in Obesity: A Comprehensive Review of Hormonal and Genetic Influences on Obesity-Related Phenotypes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Worldwide Incidence of Obesity, which tripled in 2016 from 1975, is a leading risk factor for chronic diseases. The presence of sex-dependent disparities in obesity has spurred increased interest in understanding the diverse environmental and genetic factors influencing this condition. Typically, men tend to have more visceral adipose tissue (VAT), while women generally have higher amounts of subcutaneous adipose tissue (SAT). These differences have been largely attributed to the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genesis of Bolus Pressure During Primary Peristalsis: Key to Understanding "Functional Dysphagia"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS & INFERENCES: In patients with FD, bolus pressure is partly related to the compression of the manometry catheter by the esophageal wall. The proportion of BP-positive, bolus-negative areas in the BD distinguishes FD patients and controls.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-Transplant Outcomes in Patients with Previously Treated Extrahepatic Malignancies Undergoing Living Donor Liver Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND Post-transplant outcomes were analyzed in adult patients with primary extrahepatic malignancies (EHM) who underwent living donor liver transplantation (LDLT). Few studies to date have analyzed post-transplant outcomes in adult patients with primary extrahepatic malignancies (EHM) who underwent LDLT. MATERIAL AND METHODS The study cohort included 109 patients who were treated for EHM more than 6 months before LDLT between January 2000 and December 2022. The clinicopathological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024424/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative red blood cell transfusion in gallbladder cancer surgery: Trends and determinants from nationwide data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative RBC transfusion rates in patients with GBC have declined over the past decade. Nevertheless, women, patients with lower income, and those managed at non-tertiary hospitals continue to receive transfusions at higher rates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-priming CD8<sup>+</sup> natural killer T-like cells as an efficient novel cell therapy for relapsed/refractory multiple myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TPNC represents a novel cytotoxic lymphocyte product generated through tumor-driven priming. Their dual recognition capacity, functional versatility, and favorable safety profile highlight their potential as a scalable and personalized immunotherapy platform for hematologic malignancies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of core temperature monitoring methods during cytoreductive surgery with hyperthermic intraperitoneal chemotherapy: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: All three monitoring methods correlated strongly overall, but Teso exhibited phase-dependent discrepancies, particularly after HIPEC. These findings support tailoring core temperature measurement site selection with attention to the target organ, especially in laparotomy-based HIPEC procedures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori infection is associated with an increased risk of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: H. pylori infection is associated with an increased risk of COPD and asthma. The risk of asthma was consistent across age groups and smoking statuses; in contrast, the risk of COPD varied. The findings of the present study underscore the pathophysiological interactions between chronic inflammation in the stomach and the lungs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41024079/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between prescription patterns and primary care clinic closures in South Korea: A longitudinal retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Steroid and benzodiazepine prescriptions were linked to lower clinic closure risk, while antibiotic and injectable prescriptions were not. These findings suggest that evidence-based prescribing may not compromise clinic viability and that appropriate care and sustainability can be achieved together through informed policy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploration of Likert scale in terms of continuous variable with parametric statistical methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complete genome sequence of Streptococcus hominis isolated from subgingival biofilm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Streptococcus hominis is a recently described species within the genus Streptococcus, yet its genomic characteristics remain poorly understood, particularly in the context of the oral microbiome. Previously, only two complete genomes from non-oral sources were available. To address this gap, we sequenced and analyzed S. hominis strain KHUD_010, isolated from the subgingival biofilm of a healthy Korean adult.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STALARD: Selective Target Amplification for Low-Abundance RNA Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: STALARD provides a sensitive, simple, and accessible method for isoform-level quantification of low-abundance transcripts that share a known 5'-end sequence. Its compatibility with both qPCR and long-read sequencing makes it a versatile tool for analyzing transcript variants and identifying previously uncharacterized 3'-end structures, provided that isoform-specific 5'-end sequences are known in advance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of liver stereotactic body radiotherapy plans based on free breathing and averaged CTs after trans-arterial chemoembolization using lipiodol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: For liver SBRT with lipiodol retention, 3D plans based on FB and AVG images were virtually equivalent in producing the 4D cumulative doses under the accuracy of the XVMC algorithm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of adenovirus-based oncolytic virus to induce EBV lytic reactivation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ad-TBZ demonstrates potent and selective antitumor activity against EBVaGC through hTERTp-mediated selective replication and BZLF1-induced EBV lytic reactivation. These findings support Ad-TBZ as a promising novel monotherapeutic strategy for EBVaGC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Context-Aware Prompting Techniques for Classification of Tumor Response Categories in Radiology Reports Using Large Language Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radiology reports are essential for medical decision-making, providing crucial data for diagnosing diseases, devising treatment plans, and monitoring disease progression. While large language models (LLMs) have shown promise in processing free-text reports, research on effective prompting techniques for radiologic applications remains limited. To evaluate the effectiveness of LLM-driven classification based on radiology reports in terms of tumor response category (TRC), and to optimize the model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward new clinical evaluation models for skin longevity: the need for predictive and accelerated approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Readability versus accuracy in LLM-transformed radiology reports: stakeholder preferences across reading grade levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher-grade levels were generally preferred due to better accuracy, with a range of 12-17. Further increasing grade levels reduced readability sharply, limiting preference. These findings highlight the limitations of unsupervised LLM transformations and suggest the need for hybrid approaches that maintain original reports while incorporating explanatory content to balance accuracy and readability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41023287/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251001033717&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of dietary vitamin E on growth, immune response, antioxidant capacity, intestinal histomorphology, digestibility and disease resistance of juvenile Pacific white shrimp (Penaeus vannamei)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vitamin E (tocopherols, VE) is a lipid-soluble antioxidant involved in neutralizing reactive oxygen species and maintaining immune function in animals. This study aimed to determine the optimum dietary VE requirement of juvenile Pacific white shrimp (Penaeus vannamei) for growth, feed utilization, immune responses, antioxidative capacity, diet digestibility, intestinal histomorphology and disease resistance against Vibrio parahaemolyticus. Eight experimental diets were formulated to contain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Crystal structure of heliorhodopsin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of matrix-assisted laser desorption/ionization mass spectrometry imaging (MALDI-MSI) to visualize and support interpretation of toxic effects of 4-hydroxyphenylpyruvate dioxygenase inhibitors in rat tissues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[4-Hydroxyphenylpyruvate dioxygenase inhibitors (HPPDi) are mainly used as herbicides and for therapeutic use in genetic diseases of tyrosine catabolism. Their primary mechanism of action is the inhibition of the second enzyme of tyrosine catabolism, leading to an accumulation of this amino acid in blood and tissues. In this work, rats were administered diets with 1 ppm, 2 ppm, and 10 ppm of HPPD-inhibitor BCS-CR75391 for up to 28 days, and tyrosine levels were measured in blood and in selected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital hypertension - what we need for the high-quality management of hypertension in the new era]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital technologies are playing an increasing role in hypertension management. Digital hypertension is a new field that integrates advancing technologies into hypertension management. This research area encompasses various aspects of digital transformation technologies, including the development of novel blood pressure (BP) measurement devices-whether cuffless or cuff-based sensors-the transmission of large-scale time-series BP data, cloud-based computing and analysis of BP indices,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of lower body joint kinematics during change of direction tasks estimated using a markerless and a markerbased method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Marker-based (MB) motion capture systems face challenges like marker loss, soft tissue artifacts, and manual processing. Markerless (ML) motion capture systems might be particularly advantageous for capturing dynamic, non-linear movements like change of direction (COD) movements. The agreement between MB and ML systems for lower extremity joint kinematics during COD tasks was evaluated. Nineteen athletes performed cutting movements in 5 directions at 3 intensities. Data was captured using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41028120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhibition of formyl peptide receptor-1-mediated cell death as a therapy for lethal cutaneous drug reactions in preclinical models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stevens-Johnson syndrome and toxic epidermal necrolysis are life-threatening mucocutaneous adverse drug reactions characterized by disseminated skin and mucosal detachment. Mortality rates remain high and have increased in recent years, highlighting the need for effective therapeutic strategies. Programmed cell death, specifically necroptosis, induced by the interaction between annexin A1 and formyl peptide receptor-1 on the keratinocyte membrane, plays a critical role in disease pathogenesis....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[X-chromosome upregulation operates on a gene-by-gene basis at RNA and protein levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gene dosage compensation mechanisms are crucial for mammalian development. In mice, recent findings show that cells can sense the number of X chromosomes. Loss or inactivation of one of the two X chromosomes is compensated by upregulating the remaining active X chromosome, a process termed X-chromosome upregulation (XCU). However, how cells sense X-chromosome dosage and induce XCU remains unclear. Here, we show that heterozygous X chromosome fragment deletions in mouse pluripotent stem cells...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Best practices and tools in R and Python for statistical processing and visualization of lipidomics and metabolomics data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry-based lipidomics and metabolomics generate extensive data sets that, along with metadata such as clinical parameters, require specific data exploration skills to identify and visualize statistically significant trends and biologically relevant differences. Besides tailored methods developed by individual labs, a solid core of freely accessible tools exists for exploratory data analysis and visualization, which we have compiled here, including preparation of descriptive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-destructive evaluation of defects in thermal barrier coating system using combined electromagnetic and thermographic signals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermal barrier coating system plays key role in high temperature gas turbine blades. During the manufacture and in-service processes, defects are inevitable due to the inconsistent deformation and fatigue loading. The typical defects, e.g. interfacial debonding and crack in substrate, may significantly degrade the performance, safety and service life of gas turbine. However, it is challenging to non-destructively evaluate the small defects and/or coexistent multi-defects in thermal barrier...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equivalent relative biological effectiveness for cell survival and micronuclei formation: insights from a biophysical approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The present model indicates that the analysis of MN is useful in both radiation therapy and radiation protection to quantitatively evaluate curative effects and histological damage at early stages after exposure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Analysis of the characteristics of anticipatory postural adjustments in older adults using smartphones: Association between cognitive and balance functions" [Gait Posture, 112 (2024) 115-119]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With Being Perceived as Vocally Young in Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Frequent social interactions and better mental well-being are independently associated with being perceived as vocally young. These findings suggest that psychosocial factors contribute meaningfully to perceived vocal youthfulness, supporting the development of multidimensional programs for older adults that promote mental well-being and social engagement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enrichment of soy protein-derived peptides that decrease pancreatic lipase activity using heat-treated porous silica gel and their relationship with bile acid binding activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive lipid absorption is a key factor in obesity. Lipids are solubilized in the gut via bile acid (BA) micelles, where pancreatic lipase hydrolyzes them for absorption. This study aimed to enrich pancreatic lipase inhibitory (PLI) peptides from food protein hydrolysates and clarify their inhibition mechanisms. We used heat-treated porous silica gel (HTSG) to selectively enrich basic and hydrophobic peptides through adsorption-desorption. While HTSG has previously enriched PLI peptides, the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Importance rapid initial decline in oxidation-reduction potential, followed by an increase in extracellular electron transport activities, for the rapid onset of indigo reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In most complex microbial systems, the ideal process underlying transitional microbial changes that lead to the formation of functional states is not fully elucidated. To understand the basis for the occurrence of indigo reduction, we analyzed the prerequisites causing transitional shifts in microflora that lead to the indigo-reducing state. To this end, timing of wheat bran (WB) addition, during indigo fermentation process using sukumo (composted leaves of Polygonum tinctorium L.) as the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions of physical activity for health promotion among people living with HIV in Uganda: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundPromoting health and quality of life for people living with HIV (PLHIV) in low-resource settings is vital. Understanding perceptions of physical activity (PA) and factors influencing participation can guide culturally appropriate interventions. This study explored how PLHIV in Central Uganda perceive PA, factors affecting its acceptability, and views on integrating PA into antiretroviral treatment (ART) services.MethodsA qualitative exploratory design was used. Semi-structured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of lung silica deposition with epidermal growth factor receptor-mutant lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Silica can be deposited in the lungs even without occupational exposure and is associated with EGFR-mutant lung adenocarcinoma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Motor imagery of usual walking and obstacle negotiation in early-stage Parkinson's disease: An electroencephalographic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings about α activity in PD might indicate an abnormal basal ganglia-sensorimotor interaction (high α), together with attentional and executive functions deficit (low α). Low β ERD modulation is normal in patients with PD, whereas high β ERD results may indicate top-down control impairments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-selected movement patterns during lateral locomotion with body weight support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this study was to investigate metabolic cost, muscle activity, and perceptual responses during lateral and forward locomotion at different BWS levels at individual's preferred speed. Twelve participants performed lateral and forward locomotion on a lower body positive pressure treadmill at 0 %BWS, 20 %BWS, and 50 %BWS conditions at mode-specific preferred speed. Oxygen uptake, muscle activity, stride frequency, rating of perceived exertion (RPE), and feeling scale were measured...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between maternal exposure to per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances and childhood neurodevelopment up to age 4: The Japan environment and children's study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prenatal PFAS exposure was associated with improved overall development and language-social scores at 2 and 4 years. Only one negative association was observed between PFHxS and gross motor development in KSPD at age 2.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stakeholder perspectives on injury prevention training in girls' and women's elite football: A group concept mapping study involving coaches, physical performance coaches, physical therapists, medical doctors, and club management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Stakeholders in Danish girls' and women's elite football identified interconnected factors influencing the use of injury prevention training, with "interdisciplinary cooperation" rated as most important. The findings reveal a complex interplay across structural, individual, team, and organizational levels, offering insights that can inform context-specific strategies to promote the implementation of evidence-based injury prevention training in Danish girls' and women's elite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism of IL-10 production via IL-1R in gut macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) is a chronic condition characterized by intestinal immune imbalance. Gut macrophages help maintain homeostasis by producing interleukin-10 (IL-10), which prevents excessive immune responses. However, the mechanism of IL-10 production remains unclear. This study hypothesized that an IL-1 receptor (IL-1R)-dependent pathway, independent of gut microbes, contributes to IL-10 production in gut macrophages. We compared Il10 expression in gut macrophages from germ-free...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporally increased 4-sulfated chondroitin sulfate promotes proper progression of bone morphogenetic protein 4-mediated chondrogenic differentiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chondroitin sulfate (CS) is a principal extracellular matrix component in cartilaginous tissues, well known for its role in cartilage elasticity owing to its physicochemical properties. However, its intrinsic role in chondrogenesis remains unelucidated. This study aimed to investigate the expression pattern and corresponding effects of 4-sulfated CS chains throughout the differentiation processes in chondrogenic ATDC5 cells. Herein, chondroitin 4-O-sulfotransferase-1 (C4ST-1) knockdown (KD)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Power ultrasound-driven silane-modified cement paste: Insights into microstructural evolution, hydrophobic and mechanical performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the potential adverse impact of silane on cement hydration, this study systematically investigates the effects of power ultrasound on the mechanical and hydrophobic properties, and the microstructure of silane-modified cement paste. Experimental results showed that ultrasonic treatment within the 240-720 W range significantly enhanced the compressive strength compared to the reference group. In particular, the 480 W group exhibited increases in compressive strength of 36.9 %, 10.7 %,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adherence to the Japanese Diet is Associated with Lower Risk of Geriatric Depression: A Prospective-Cohort Study Based on the New Integrated Suburban Seniority Investigation (NISSIN) Project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adherence to the Japanese diet, especially those rich in green-yellow vegetables, soybean-derived products, and fish and shellfish, may be protective against geriatric depression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triggering Photoluminescence in High-Nuclear Silver Nanoclusters via Extra Silver Atom Incorporation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoluminescence (PL) in silver (Ag) nanoclusters (NCs) is intrinsically linked to their structural architecture, yet their low quantum yield at room-temperature hinders practical applications. Although various strategies have been explored to enhance the PL efficiency of Ag NCs, their effectiveness in high-nuclear Ag NCs remains largely uncertain. Here, we demonstrate a 77-fold enhancement in room-temperature PL quantum yield by modulating both radiative and nonradiative decay pathways in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41027005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Further evidence supporting the existence and accumulation of triacylglycerol and acylplastoquinol in cyanobacteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triacylglycerol (TAG) has been frequently reported in cyanobacteria; however, unlike in plants and algae, the isolation of TAG as a pure substance and its subsequent chemical characterization have proven challenging. The slr2103 gene in Synechocystis sp. PCC 6803, which encodes a putative acyltransferase involved in TAG biosynthesis, has been considered evidence for the existence of TAG. However, the identification of acylplastoquinol (APQ) as the major component of the "TAG fraction" obtained...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Cardiotoxicity Profiling Using Field Potential Imaging with UHD-CMOS-MEA in Human iPSC-Derived Cardiomyocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate assessment of cardiotoxicity using human iPSC-derived cardiomyocytes is critical for ensuring drug safety during preclinical development. However, existing in vitro methodologies predominantly focus on QT interval prolongation and arrhythmia risk, often lacking the capacity to capture the complex interplay among multiple ion channels or to detect early manifestations of chronic cardiotoxicity-both of which are essential for evaluating long-term cardiac safety. Moreover, reliable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of exercise limitation in heart failure with preserved ejection fraction and obesity: A case of engine-chassis mismatch]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity is a major risk factor for heart failure with preserved ejection fraction (HFpEF), but its impact on limitations in peak oxygen uptake (VO(2)peak) and its Fick determinants remains unclear. We assessed these factors in obese and non-obese patients with HFpEF, and non-HFpEF controls. Patients with HFpEF were sub-grouped by body mass index (BMI ≥30 or <30 kg/m²) into HFpEF with (HFpEF(Obese), n=139) or without obesity (HFpEF(Non-Obese), n=317), and non-HFpEF controls (CON, n=270)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antigenic variation is caused by long plasmid segment conversion in a hard tick-borne relapsing fever Borrelia miyamotoi]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Borrelia miyamotoi is a hard tick-borne spirochete genetically related to relapsing fever Borrelia and the etiological agent of an emerging infectious disease in humans. Like relapsing fever Borrelia, B. miyamotoi carries clusters of gene cassettes encoding variable major proteins (Vmps) on multiple linear plasmids and shows antigenic variation in mammalian hosts by switching the expression vmp gene cassette. However, it remains unknown how the switch occurs in B. miyamotoi. Here we determined...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intensification of thermophilic anaerobic digestion of sewage sludge by thermal hydrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermal hydrolysis (THP) combined with thermophilic anaerobic digestion (TAD) offers promising pathways for enhancing sewage sludge treatment. This study is among the first to directly compare THP as both pre- and post-treatment options for TAD. Pre-treatment of waste activated sludge (THP-WAS) and post-treatment of digested sludge (THP-DS) were evaluated on their impacts on process stability, biogas production, and sludge dewaterability. Pilot-scale trials at a wastewater treatment plant (WWTP)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutrophil-enriched gene signature correlates with teplizumab therapy resistance in different stages of type 1 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Teplizumab, a humanized anti-CD3 monoclonal antibody, represents a breakthrough in autoimmune type 1 diabetes (T1D) treatment, by delaying clinical onset in stage 2 and slowing progression in early stage 3. However, therapeutic responses are heterogeneous. To better understand this variability, we applied single-cell transcriptomics to paired peripheral blood and pancreas samples from anti-mouse CD3-treated non-obese diabetic (NOD) mice and identified distinct gene signatures associated with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychophysical dissection of temporal error monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recent line of research robustly demonstrated that humans and rodents can keep track of the magnitude and direction of timing errors, composing a temporal error monitoring ability (TEM). However, the degree of dissociation between these two measures of TEM has not been investigated at the level of the underlying mental magnitude metrics. Specifically, we do not know whether the two behavioral manifestations of TEM differentially rely on subjective vs. objective time, whether the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comment on: "Anatomical distribution and prognostic heterogeneity in glioma: unique clinical features of occipital glioblastoma"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Strategy for occipital isolation by disconnecting convergent white matter fibers. A region of interest (ROI, yellow sphere) was placed in the occipital lobe, and tractography shows streamlines from the ROI. Two major bundles course along the bottom of the parietooccipital fissure (POF) and the trigone of the lateral ventricle. The anterior resection border (light-blue line) is defined by a line connecting the bottom of the POF to the trigone; the lateral resection border (green line) corresponds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postmastectomy radiation therapy for implant-based breast reconstruction: a systematic review and meta-analysis for the 2022 Japanese Breast Cancer Society Clinical Practice Guideline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This meta-analysis demonstrated that PMRT in implant-based breast reconstruction is associated with a significantly increased risk of adverse outcomes. Given these risks, treatment decisions should involve through discussions with patients to ensure that they are fully informed of the potential benefits and complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a machine learning model for early prediction of intensive care unit acquired weakness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Machine learning models, especially random forests, can be used to predict if patients are at risk of developing ICU-AW, using data available within 24 h of admission. This tool allows prognostication early in an adult general critically ill patient population, with the potential to detect high cost and high need patients who benefit from different levels of care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026286/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>In situ</em> observation of polyurea formation by rapid-scan time-resolved infrared spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyurea and its derivatives exhibit excellent physical and chemical properties originating from intermolecular hydrogen bonding. Consequently, they have been used as coating materials that are resistant to heat, water, and chemicals, and in recent years, as materials for 3D printers. Their properties depend on their formation and hydrogen bonding mechanisms; however, these processes are very fast, making them challenging to study experimentally. In this study, polyurea formation via the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026184/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transperineal Ultrasound Immediately After Birth to Predict Postpartum Anorectal Dysfunction: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The presence of levator avulsion immediately after vaginal delivery predicts postpartum AI. Ultrasound appearance of the anal sphincter, genital hiatus and rectovaginal septum was not informative.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential modulation of adipose tissue insulin resistance by modified traditional Japanese diet and SGLT-2 inhibitor canagliflozin in type 2 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This prospective observational study investigated the differential modulation of metabolic parameters by modified traditional Japanese dietary therapy for diabetes (MJDD) and SGLT-2 inhibitor canagliflozin in treatment-naïve patients with T2DM. Particular emphasis was placed on adipose tissue insulin resistance (adipo-IR). Newly diagnosed, drug-naïve T2DM patients were treated with either MJDD (n = 53) or canagliflozin (n = 55) for 3 months. Key metabolic indices-including BMI, FBG, HbA1c,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026174/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor response and thyroglobulin change in differentiated thyroid carcinoma treated with dabrafenib plus trametinib]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tg changes during dabrafenib plus trametinib treatment may not be associated with clinical response to dabrafenib plus trametinib treatment. Further study is needed to clarify the association between Tg level or inflammatory biomarkers change and clinical response to dabrafenib plus trametinib treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis and Structure-Activity Relationship Studies of Truncated Artificial Analogues of Amphidinol 3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structure-activity relationship studies of artificial analogues of amphidinol 3 (AM3) were conducted. Based on the truncated molecule corresponding to the C21-C67 section of AM3, which elicited comparable antifungal activity to the parent compound, its stereoisomers were synthesized from polyol, bis-THP, and polyene units via Suzuki-Miyaura coupling and Julia-Kocienski olefination. Variants at both polyol and polyene termini were also synthesized. Evaluation of the antifungal activity of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CRISPR/Cas9-directed disruption of wc-2 leads to absence of fruiting body development in Pleurotus ostreatus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Light, particularly blue light, is a key environmental factor that induces fruiting in certain agaricomycetes. In this study, we characterised mutant strains of Pleurotus ostreatus with disrupted wc-2, which encodes one of the white-collar proteins, Wc-2, to investigate the role of light in fruiting in P. ostreatus. We introduced two different plasmids containing expression cassettes for Cas9 and two different gRNAs targeting wc-2 separately into the dikaryotic P. ostreatus strain PC9×#64. Among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation in sperm motility and seminal protein expression is shaped by pre- and post-mating sexual selection in the mouthbrooding cichlid (Ophthalmotilapia ventralis)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sexual selection is a key driver of reproductive strategy evolution; however, its molecular mechanisms remain poorly understood. In the mouthbrooding Tanganyikan cichlid (Ophthalmotilapia ventralis), fertilization occurs in the female mouth cavity, where sperm competition and post-mating female choice arise because females collect sperm from multiple territorial males. Seminal plasma glycoprotein 120 (SPP120) is involved in sperm immobilization and aggregation, which may contribute to prolonged...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41026088/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thymic Stromal Lymphopoietin Promotes Ozone-induced Inflammation in the Airway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ozone is associated with induction of airway hyperresponsiveness (AHR) and neutrophilic airway inflammation which is the characteristic of type 2 low inflammatory phenotype. Recently, epithelial cell-derived cytokines such as thymic stromal lymphopoietin (TSLP) have been recognized as therapeutic targets for asthma with type 2 low inflammation, but the mechanisms remain unknown. In the present study, BALB/c mice and TSLP receptor-deficient mice were exposed to ozone at 2 ppm for 3 hours. AHR,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025995/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FRET-based biosensor moxCRONOS enables quantitative monitoring of macromolecular crowding in organelles and protein aggregates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macromolecular crowding is a fundamental property of the intracellular environment that influences protein folding, enzymatic activity, and phase behavior. Disruptions to the homeostasis of macromolecular crowding can drive pathological processes, such as aberrant liquid-liquid phase separation and protein aggregation, which are central features of several neurodegenerative diseases. However, tools for quantifying crowding and aggregation remain limited. Here, we describe moxCRONOS, a Förster...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of viral activators of the HSV-2 UL13 protein kinase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although previous studies reported that the herpes simplex virus 2 (HSV-2) UL13 protein kinase mediates the phosphorylation of elongation factor 1δ (EF-1δ) in infected cells, we found here that individual expression of UL13 was insufficient to induce phosphorylation of EF-1δ in mammalian cells. This led us to hypothesize that HSV-2 UL13 requires viral cofactors for full kinase activity and prompted us to identify such cofactors. Our results were as follows. (i) Co-expression of UL13 with UL55 or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41025809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251001033718&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>