<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:01:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual antiplatelet therapy after percutaneous coronary intervention according to bleeding risk (HOST-BR): an open-label, multicentre, randomised clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The optimal duration of dual antiplatelet therapy (DAPT) after coronary stenting according to bleeding risk is not well established. We aimed to evaluate the optimal duration of DAPT after coronary stenting according to bleeding risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidics-guided localized low-temperature modulation of axonal signal propagation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low-temperature stimulation is recognized as a promising approach for neuromodulation, with the potential to suppress or slow neural activity. However, its impact on the spatial and electrophysiological properties of axonal conduction remains poorly understood. Conventional methods have lacked the spatial resolution necessary to isolate axon-specific responses to localized cooling. To overcome these limitations, we developed a microfluidic platform that integrates a microelectrode array (MEA)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of adding a fourth oral antidiabetic drug versus metformin dose escalation in patients with type 2 diabetes inadequately controlled on triple oral combination therapy (EFFORT): A 24-week, randomized, open-label, multicenter trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Oral quadruple therapy achieved greater glycaemic and metabolic improvement without compromising safety, compared with metformin uptitration, supporting its role as an intensification strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[K-MIMIC: a nationwide Korean multi-institutional Multimodal intensive care dataset]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The K-MIMIC is the first large-scale, multicenter, multimodal ICU dataset in Asia to provide a robust resource for critical care research, including AI-based prediction, monitoring, and longitudinal outcome studies. The dataset demonstrates the feasibility of secure and standardized ICU data integration across diverse institutions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Two-Wave Study of Avatar Customization and Psychological Benefits in Social Virtual Reality: The Role of Identification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As social virtual reality (social VR) platforms increasingly captivate users worldwide, questions arise about how digitally mediated self-representation affects psychological health. This study investigates how avatar characteristics-specifically perceived avatar appearance similarity and perceived attractiveness-shape users' well-being in social VR, with a focus on the mediating role of avatar identification. Drawing on two-wave longitudinal data collected over a three-month period from 486...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of bictegravir/emtricitabine/tenofovir alafenamide in people with HIV in Asia: 24-Month findings from the observational BICSTaR study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BICtegravir Single Tablet Regimen is a multiregional, observational cohort study assessing the effectiveness and safety of bictegravir/emtricitabine/tenofovir alafenamide (B/F/TAF) in treatment-naïve (TN) and treatment-experienced (TE) people with HIV. We present 24-month data for the BICtegravir Single Tablet Regimen Asia cohort. Between December 2020 and March 2024, prospective and retrospective data were collected from TN and TE people with HIV receiving B/F/TAF in routine clinical care in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muscle mass in critically ill patients: analysis using ultrasound, traditional bioelectrical impedance analysis, and wearable devices: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ultrasound is a reliable method for monitoring muscle atrophy in critically ill patients, demonstrating a consistent decrease in muscle mass. The outcomes of traditional BIA and wearable devices suggest that careful consideration of their interpretations is necessary. Utilizing these tools may be valuable for assessing patient prognosis and facilitating more proactive interventions for patients experiencing muscle loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EEG-based epileptic seizure prediction with patient-tailored spectral-spatial-temporal feature learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epilepsy is a chronic brain disorder characterized by recurrent seizures resulting from abnormal brain cell activity. The unpredictability of these seizures underscores the criticality of anticipating and promptly addressing them to enhance the patient's overall quality of life. Electroencephalography (EEG) is a frequently employed technique for seizure prediction, leveraging its economic viability and high temporal resolution. However, the complexity of EEG signals has driven interest in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-Programmable IGZO Optoelectronic Memristor for Multifunctional Neuromorphic Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Next-generation neuromorphic systems require hardware platforms that seamlessly integrate sensing, memory, and computation. Here, we present a light-programmable optoelectronic memristor based on an ITO/IGZO/W structure, capable of emulating a broad spectrum of synaptic and neuronal functions under purely optical stimulation through the transparent ITO top electrode. The device exhibits short-term plasticity, including excitatory postsynaptic current (EPSC), paired-pulse facilitation (PPF), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluoxetine minimally affects hearing loss but induces gene expression changes in the cochlear nuclei after noise exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fluoxetine exerted only modest, 4 kHz‑restricted improvements in ABR thresholds and did not restore cochlear structure or normal hearing following noise‑induced hearing loss. However, it induced distinct transcriptional alterations in the VCN and modulated the extracellular environment, suggesting a potential role in neural remodeling rather than direct auditory restoration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of tumor necrosis factor inhibitors on risk of depression in patients with ankylosing spondylitis: a nationwide propensity score-matched cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TNFi exposure was associated with a lower incidence of depression in patients with AS, suggesting a potential mental health benefit of TNFi, extending beyond symptom control to prevention of new-onset depression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PGVDA: a pathway-aggregated genetic dosage framework for interpretable disease classification using machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although neuromuscular junction disorders (NMDs) and inflammatory polyneuropathies (IPNs) are biologically distinct, direct genetic comparisons between them remain limited, suggesting that additional underlying biological differences may yet be uncovered. Few studies have explored whether differences in variant patterns within shared biological pathways can be leveraged to distinguish NMDs and IPNs using machine learning (ML). We propose an interpretable ML framework based on Pathway-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diverging trajectories of Depressive Symptoms After Retirement: The Moderating Role of Social Engagement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Retirement marks a major life transition that can influence psychological well-being in later life. Although previous studies have examined the mental health consequences of retirement, less is known about how depressive symptoms evolve before and after retirement and whether these trajectories differ by levels of social engagement. This study investigates longitudinal changes in depressive symptoms surrounding retirement and examines whether social engagement moderates these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reproductive Shifts and Ovarian Cancer Risk in Women Aged 40 Years or Older]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This cohort study found that reproductive factors were associated with ovarian cancer risk, with distinct patterns across menopausal status and birth cohorts. These findings highlight the need for tailored prevention strategies in aging, low-fertility populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polluting cooking fuels and life satisfaction among middle-aged and older adults: a cross-sectional study from the Longitudinal Ageing Study in India]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polluting cooking fuels are a major source of household air pollution and may reduce life satisfaction (LS). Yet, this relationship remains unexplored in India where polluting fuel use is still widespread. We utilized cross-sectional data from the Longitudinal Aging Study in India, a nationally representative study of individuals aged 45 years and above. Cooking fuel type was classified as households using clean fuels (CF) or non-CF. Based on kitchen type, non-CF was categorized into non-CF in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632425/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[α-Crystallins and vascular endothelial growth factor in aqueous humor of patients with neovascular age-related macular degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In nAMD, AH αB-crystallin levels were elevated compared with controls. Among good responders to anti-VEGF therapy, αB-crystallin levels decreased. Moreover, αB-crystallin levels showed a positive correlation with VEGF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vulnerability of Large Language Models to Prompt Injection When Providing Medical Advice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this quality improvement study using a controlled simulation, commercial LLMs demonstrated substantial vulnerability to prompt-injection attacks that could generate clinically dangerous recommendations; even flagship models with advanced safety mechanisms showed high susceptibility. These findings underscore the need for adversarial robustness testing, system-level safeguards, and regulatory oversight before clinical deployment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Influencing Terminal Care Performance in Korean Hospitals: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the increasing demand for high-quality end-of-life care in acute settings, it has become essential to identify the factors that influence nurses' terminal care performance. This study aimed to examine the predictors of terminal care performance among 174 nurses working in hospitals in South Korea, with a focus on physical, psychological, and spiritual domains. Using a cross-sectional survey and multiple linear regression analysis, the study found that higher terminal care stress (β = .272),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Modulated Vertically Stacked Transistors With Fully Laminated Plate-Type Architecture Featuring Nanoscale Channel Length]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A transistor with fully laminated plate-type triode electrodes, source, drain and gate offers higher current density than a typical transistor design by allowing a 2D current path. Nanoscale transistors face challenges like off-state leakage, so we introduce a new design using a laminated plate-type architecture and a dual-modulation strategy to improve performance and stability. Both top and bottom gates are used as active electrodes to fully control the channel's thickness. A micro-hole...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ginger supplementation alleviates autistic behaviors by modulating AKT/GSK3β signaling in mice exposed to prenatal valproic acid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autism spectrum disorder (ASD) is a neurodevelopmental disorder characterized by deficits in social interaction and comorbid symptoms including anxiety and cognitive problems. The main pathological mechanisms underlying ASD are synaptic abnormalities and neuroinflammation. Ginger, commonly used as a spice, has been reported to enhance neurogenesis and attenuate inflammation in neurological disease; however, its effects on ASD remain unknown. This study aimed to investigate the therapeutic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Plasma Epstein-Barr Virus DNA and Clinical Outcomes to Pembrolizumab or Chemotherapy in Recurrent/Metastatic Nasopharyngeal Cancer in KEYNOTE-122]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher baseline plasma EBV DNA load was negatively associated with outcomes in participants with NPC treated with pembrolizumab or SOC. These findings provide additional support for plasma EBV DNA as a prognostic biomarker for NPC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631899/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Compact Base Editors by AlphaFold-Guided Mutation Scan and Escherichia coli-Based Tri-Selection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[APOBEC1-based cytosine base editors such as BE4max enable base conversion, but many alternative deaminases show low activity and cytotoxicity, especially when miniaturized for delivery. SsdA(tox), a DNA deaminase toxin from Pseudomonas syringae that is two-thirds the size of APOBEC1, is attractive for compact base editors but, in native form, shows low C-to-T editing efficiency and high cytotoxicity. Guided by an AlphaFold- and CASTpFold-based alanine scan, we identified K31 as a gatekeeping...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631734/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Active Surface Area and Gas Diffusion Properties of Low-Temperature Solid Oxide Fuel Cell Cathodes by Sputtering with Glancing Angle Deposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper reports an effective approach we have developed to sputter nanoporous single-phase La(0).(6)Sr(0).(4)Co(0).(2)Fe(0).(8)O(3)-(δ) (LSCF) thin-film cathodes using glancing angle deposition (GLAD), which leverages the self-shadowing effect to engineer nanocolumnar architectures with high porosity. By systematically tuning the sputtering pressure and film thickness, we achieved precise control over the cathode morphology, resulting in tunable porosity and triple-phase boundary (TPB)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multifunctional β-Defensin-3 Mimetic Peptide Modulates Host-Biofilm Interactions and Reduces Bone Loss in Periodontitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: BDMP exhibited sustained antimicrobial and anti-inflammatory activity and attenuated bone loss in a beagle periodontitis model when used alongside standard SI therapy. These findings support BDMP as a promising adjunctive therapeutic candidate for managing periodontal inflammation and biofilm-associated disease, although further studies are needed to confirm long-term safety and to define its mechanistic contributions to periodontal tissue preservation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding disease management and the patient journey in chronic myeloid leukemia: results from the CML SUN survey in South Korean patients and physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results highlight the significant impact of ATP-competitive TKIs on patients' QoL and provide useful insights into CML treatment in South Korea. The differences in patient and physician perspectives emphasize the need for shared treatment decisions that balance efficacy and tolerability to enhance QoL and to minimize unnecessary treatment switching.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-conditioned inter-patient registration using planning computed tomography for voxel-based analysis to predict radiation pneumonitis in lung cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TRACER improved registration accuracy, with better tumor volume preservation and reduced OAR dose impact. Incorporating VBA-derived dose enhanced RP prediction accuracy compared with using MLD. CRRs identified through VBA were robust to the choice of DIR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal vitiligo is associated with increased autoimmune and atopic disease in offspring: A nationwide birth cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Tuning of Doping Efficiency and Charge Transport in n-Type Thermoelectric Polymers via Rational Backbone Design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the growing interest in organic thermoelectrics, n-type polymers generally exhibit lower performance than their p-type counterparts, limiting the development of efficient thermoelectric generators. Herein, we report two new n-type polymers based on cyanothiophene-flanked diketopyrrolopyrrole (CDPP) copolymerized with either diketopyrrolopyrrole (PCDPP-DPP) or dialkoxybithiazole (PCDPP-BTzOR) to investigate the critical yet scarcely explored role of orbital interaction between counits in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Basis of Recognition of Anti-CRISPR Operon by Aca3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The CRISPR-Cas system equips bacteria with adaptive immunity by storing fragments of invading nucleic acids in CRISPR loci and deploying Cas proteins to recognize and degrade matching sequences. In turn, bacteriophages have evolved small anti-CRISPR (Acr) that neutralize diverse CRISPR-Cas types. Acr genes are often co-encoded with transcriptional regulators called anti-CRISPR-associated (Aca) proteins, which suppress acr expression. Although 13 Aca families have been identified through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood pressure thresholds for the administration of balanced crystalloids and the effect on intra-operative hypotension: A proof-of-concept causal inference analysis featuring idealised dynamic treatment regimens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Using modern causal inference methods, we demonstrated the clinical utility of idealised DTRs to study the impact of time-dependent haemodynamic management on the incidence of intra-operative hypotension in idealised settings. Future studies are required to investigate more complex DTRs mirroring clinical practice and to assess the robustness of the findings with respect to the different surgical populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen-Independent Mineralization of Acetaldehyde by a Cyclodextrin-Anchored WO<sub>3</sub> Photocatalyst under Visible Light]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photocatalytic degradation of volatile organic compounds (VOCs) using visible light has been widely investigated, but its practical implementation remains constrained by several limiting factors. Here, we prepared carboxymethyl-β-cyclodextrin (CMCD)-anchored WO(3) that enabled visible-light-driven mineralization of acetaldehyde even under O(2)-free conditions. Anchoring CMCD on WO(3) facilitated interfacial charge separation, enhancing the photocatalytic performance. Spectroscopic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of electroencephalographic changes induced by different hypnotics in elderly patients: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is associated with widespread structural and functional changes in the brain including reduced neural plasticity, slower information processing, and impaired network integration. These age-related alterations influence the brain's response to anesthetic agents, particularly electroencephalography (EEG) activity. This narrative review summarizes the characteristic EEG features induced by commonly used hypnotic agents such as propofol, inhaled anesthetics, dexmedetomidine, ketamine, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of large language models and conventional machine learning in postoperative outcome prediction: a retrospective, multi-national development and validation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings support the versatility and efficiency of LLMs for clinical decision support through on-premises compatibility, addressing data privacy. Further validation with diverse datasets is needed to ensure their reliability and applicability across different perioperative settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opioid-based versus opioid-sparing patient-controlled analgesia using ketorolac and nefopam after total knee arthroplasty: a randomized, double-blind, non-inferiority trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Opioid-sparing PCA with ketorolac and nefopam provides non-inferior analgesia to opioid-based PCA, while reducing opioid consumption and drug-related adverse effects after TKA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of Mental Health Nurses in Providing Care to Inpatients With Suicidal Behaviours in Psychiatric Care Settings: A Meta-Synthesis of Qualitative Research Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the context and challenges of psychiatric nursing care is essential for optimising patient outcomes and ensuring effective suicide prevention. While mental health nurses play a pivotal role in caring for inpatients with suicidal behaviours, research on their experiences and perspectives remains fragmented. This study aimed to synthesise qualitative studies on the experiences of mental health nurses in providing care to inpatients with suicidal behaviours. Manual searches were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brucine as a Natural Modulator of Cancer Signaling: Cellular Mechanisms, Therapeutic Potential, and Translational Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brucine (BRU), a naturally occurring indole alkaloid primarily derived from Strychnos nux-vomica, has recently gained attention for its notable anticancer potential. Preclinical studies using both in vitro and in vivo models have demonstrated that BRU and its semi-synthetic derivatives exhibit significant inhibitory effects on tumor development across various cancer types, including cervical, breast, liver, skin, colon, and prostate cancers. This review explores the phytochemical properties of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Utility of FAR1 Methylation Levels in Hepatocellular Carcinoma Patients Undergoing Liver Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND Recent research has highlighted DNA methylation as a promising diagnostic biomarker for hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC). Fatty Acyl-CoA Reductase 1 (FAR1) exhibits a high propensity for methylation in HCC. This study aimed to evaluate diagnostic and prognostic potential of FAR1 methylation in liver transplantation (LT) recipients with HCC. MATERIAL AND METHODS This analysis used droplet digital polymerase chain reaction to quantify FAR1 methylation levels in stored pretransplant blood...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Binational component-wise association between cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic syndrome and life's essential 8 in South Korea and the US: A nationally representative comparative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the American Heart Association (AHA) has emphasized the integration of cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic (CKM) syndrome and life's essential 8 (LE8) score, research on their association remains limited. To address this gap, this study analyzed the component-wise association between CKM syndrome and LE8 scores using nationally representative data from South Korea and the US. This binational study included adults aged 30 to 79 years from the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjunctive cannabidiol in intractable pediatric epilepsy: A retrospective study on tolerability, efficacy, and safety across genetic and nongenetic etiologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective cohort study evaluated the tolerability, efficacy, and safety of adjunctive cannabidiol (CBD) therapy in pediatric-onset intractable epilepsy across diverse genetic and nongenetic etiologies. Twenty-nine patients aged 6 to 24 years, treated at Korea University Hospitals between April 2019 and May 2024, were included. The median follow-up duration was 14.3 months. Confirmed genetic etiologies included SCN1A-related epilepsy (6.9%); GABRB3-, SCN2A-, KCNT1-, KIF1A-, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term effectiveness on glycemic control of insulin compared to combined oral antidiabetic drugs for initial intensive treatment in newly diagnosed type 2 diabetes: A duplicated target trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although both intensive insulin therapy (IIT) and combined oral antidiabetic drugs (COAD) can achieve initial intensive glycemic control, evidence comparing their long-term effectiveness following initial remission remains limited. Therefore, this study aims to compare long-term glycemic control and the risk of drug-free remission failure between IIT and COAD in patients who successfully achieved initial intensive glycemic control. This duplicated target trial utilized a cohort of 60,736...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and side effect of transcatheter arterial embolization using a novel embolic agent for lateral epicondylitis in a diabetic patient: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RATIONALE: Lateral epicondylitis (LE) is an overuse syndrome of the extensor carpi radialis brevis tendons of the forearm, leading to pain around the lateral epicondyle of the humerus exacerbated by several activities and a decrease in work productivity. This case study reports the efficacy and side effects of transcatheter arterial embolization (TAE) using Smartgel MIRIP, a novel quick-soluble gelatin sponge particles agent, through a LE patient with diabetes mellitus (DM).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogen-Assisted Asymmetric and Nonlinear Memristor Array for Reconfigurable Olfactory Graph Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memristor-based olfactory systems have attracted significant interest. However, a multifunctional memristor array capable of sensing, memory, and computation has not been realized. This study develops a selector-less crossbar array (CBA) composed of Pt/HfO(2) nanorods/TiN memristors, termed "chemo-memristive" devices, that exhibits asymmetric current-voltage (I-V) characteristics under a hydrogen (H(2)) atmosphere. H(2) exposure creates oxygen vacancies (V(O)) in the nanogap, corresponding to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathological Nitric Oxide-Triggered Microneedle Patch for Spatiotemporally Controlled Therapy of Acute and Chronic Inflammatory Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammation underlies the progression of both acute and chronic diseases, yet conventional therapies remain limited by systemic side effects, poor compliance, and insufficient responsiveness to dynamic pathological cues. Nitric oxide (NO), a gaseous mediator with high diffusivity and membrane permeability, is aberrantly overproduced in diverse inflammatory conditions and thus represents a promising trigger for responsive drug delivery. Here, we present a NO-responsive microneedle (NOR-MN)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive functional atlas of ALK kinase domain variants reveals resistance landscape to ALK inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides a comprehensive functional atlas of ALK tyrosine kinase domain variants under TKI selection, offering a valuable experimental framework for interpreting resistance-associated variants. Although derived from in vitro models and therefore context dependent, this resource complements existing clinical and genomic knowledge and may aid in the functional interpretation of ALK variants observed in ALK-driven cancers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of intravenous administration of high-dose selenium for preventing chemotherapy-induced peripheral neuropathy in platinum-sensitive recurrent ovarian cancer: a phase 3, double-blind, parallel group, randomized controlled pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intravenous high-dose selenium safely failed to reduce grade 1 or more CIPN, whereas it reduced grade 2 or more motor dysfunction during chemotherapy in patients with PSROC, especially those ≥ 60 years. While the primary endpoint was not met, selenium showed the potential of protective effects against motor neuropathy without safety and survival concerns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of housing instability in the association between ambient temperature and preterm birth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commissioning of the linear accelerator for the extreme ultraviolet synchrotron of the Pohang Accelerator Laboratory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pohang Accelerator Laboratory (PAL) constructed a novel extreme ultraviolet (EUV) radiation generation synchrotron facility. We call this facility the Extreme Ultraviolet Synchrotron of the Pohang Accelerator Laboratory (PAL-EUV). The PAL-EUV facility consists of a linear accelerator, a booster synchrotron, and a storage ring synchrotron. Due to spatial constraints, these devices were installed very densely. For this reason, it is important to design the transport section from the linear...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selection of metal-tellurium (M-Te) alloy as Recyclable Controlled Te Precursors for Wafer-Scale Synthesis of M<sub>x</sub>Te<sub>y</sub> Thin Films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wafer-scale synthesis of metal telluride films has been hindered by the high volatility and limited reactivity of tellurium. To overcome this, we introduce a confined tellurization strategy utilizing in situ formed metal-tellurium (M-Te) alloys as controllable Te sources. Systematic investigation on appropriate metal species through cohesive energy calculations and experiments demonstrates that the cohesive energy of the source metal and metal-to-Te atomic ratio in the source bilayer are the key...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multilevel Regulation in RNA-Protein Hybrid Incoherent Feed-Forward Loop Circuits for Tunable Pulse Dynamics in <em>Escherichia coli</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regulating gene expression with precision is essential for cellular engineering and biosensing applications, where rapid, programmable, and sensitive control is desired. Current approaches to regulatory circuit design often rely on control at a single regulatory level, primarily the transcriptional level, thereby limiting the capability of fine-tuning the regulatory dynamics in response to complex stimuli. To address this challenge, we developed four novel RNA-protein hybrid type-1 incoherent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal RSV vaccination in Japan: Beyond financial barriers toward the 2026 routine immunization transition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elevated risks of pneumonia, cognitive dysfunction, and cerebrovascular disorder in super-elderly knee arthroplasty patients: insights from a nationwide Japanese database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Super-elderly patients exhibit increased risks for certain complications, though not for mortality. When clinically appropriate, performing knee arthroplasty before the age of 85 may help reduce these risks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personal Agency Support Questionnaire in Acute Psychiatric Inpatients: Development and Instrument Validation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This PASQ is a valuable tool for assessing personal agency support in acute psychiatric wards, demonstrating promise for both clinical use in acute psychiatric wards and clinical research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Antiemetic Support in Anthracycline-Based Chemotherapy for Early Breast Cancer: Protocol for a Prospective Observational Study of Four-Drug Antiemetic Therapy Including Fosnetupitant and Olanzapine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study will provide real-world evidence on the effectiveness and safety of a four-drug antiemetic regimen, including FosNTP and OLZ, in patients receiving anthracycline-based HEC and may inform optimal OLZ dosing strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Material properties and antibacterial activity of carbonate apatite cement prepared with silver-containing vaterite powder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, silver-containing carbonate apatite (CO(3)Ap) cement was prepared by mixing silver-containing vaterite and calcium hydrogen phosphate (DCPA) powder in an aqueous phosphate solution. The material properties and antibacterial performance of the cement were evaluated. Silver ions were introduced during vaterite synthesis, resulting in a composite CO(3)Ap cement containing silver phosphate (Ag(3)PO(4)). The addition of silver nitrate did not affect key physical properties of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of tissue lymphocyte immunophenotype and clinical outcomes: A prospective study in patients with ulcerative colitis treated with vedolizumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: T cell immunophenotype may be a promising predictive biomarker of vedolizumab treatment efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial distribution and age estimation of microplastics collected from rivers, seas, and sediment in Shizuoka Prefecture, Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics (MPs) have become a major concern for the general public. Although their sources and sinks have been studied, the fate of MPs in the environment remains unclear. Understanding their fate is essential for governments to develop effective countermeasures against MP pollution. In this study, MP pollution was investigated at 22 rivers and 11 beaches in Shizuoka Prefecture, Japan. Polyethylene (PE)-, polypropylene (PP)-, and polystyrene (PS)-MP concentrations in sediments ranged from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A multicomponent intervention consisting of exercise, proteins and omega-3 supplementation to improve sarcopenia in community-dwelling older adults: Lessons learned from a 5-armed randomized controlled feasibility trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A multicomponent intervention to treat sarcopenia showed low feasibility, moderate acceptability, and high safety. Preliminary efficacy results showed that exercise with protein supplementation may improve physical function. Adding omega-3 PUFA might offer further benefits for muscle strength and mass, but should be confirmed in larger studies. The insights and the practical challenges in the ENHANce study inform future sarcopenia intervention designs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-stratified clinical outcomes and adverse events in patients with metastatic castration-sensitive prostate cancer receiving triplet therapy with darolutamide, androgen deprivation therapy, and docetaxel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this real-world cohort, triplet therapy showed substantial PSA declines and acceptable tolerability, with no significant differences in short-term efficacy or safety between patients aged <75 and ≥ 75 years. These findings suggest that chronological age alone should not preclude consideration of triplet therapy in appropriately selected patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in antisense oligonucleotide treatment for cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RNA therapeutics, including antisense oligonucleotides (ASOs), have emerged as a promising class of drugs, with several already approved for clinical use. To date, most approved ASO-based RNA therapies target non-malignant disorders such as neurodegenerative diseases, and only a single therapy in this class has been approved for cancer. Notably, nearly half of existing RNA therapeutics act by modulating RNA splicing. Given the growing evidence implicating aberrant RNA splicing in cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of long-term outcomes between proximal gastrectomy and total gastrectomy for advanced gastric cancer in the upper third of the stomach: a propensity score-matched analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The long-term survival outcomes of PG and TG for upper-third AGC patients are comparable, suggesting that PG may be an oncologically acceptable option in carefully selected patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Permeability Behavior and Catalytic Effectiveness in Zwitterionic Polymer Hydrogel-Enzyme Hybrid Nanocarrier]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enzyme-encapsulated nanogels serve as promising platforms for constructing enzyme nanoreactors in which mass transport plays a crucial role in the enzymatic performance. However, it remains a challenge to investigate the relationship between the permeability of nanoreactors and their catalytic efficiency owing to their small dimensions. The molecular permeability behavior and enzyme activity of two types of nanogels with different hydrophobicities are compared using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Possible role of ribosome biogenesis in the recovery from transient hepatic damage caused by ethylene glycol in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings reveal a pathway underlying EG-induced transient liver damage and suggest a possible mechanism of recovery, thereby providing new insights into EG poisoning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Successful transition from long-term peritoneal dialysis to intermittent hemodialysis in a patient with Fontan circulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soft, Flexible, and Stretchable Platforms for Tissue-Interfaced Bioelectronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seamless integration of electronic systems with living tissues requires not only biocompatibility but also careful matching of mechanical properties across heterogeneous organs. This review clarifies the often-conflated notions of "soft," "flexible," and "stretchable" electronics, and links these definitions to a tissue-mechanics framework spanning brain, nerve, skin, myocardium, and visceral organs. Based on this framework, we outline general mechanical design principles-ultrathin structures,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute kidney injury requiring temporary hemodialysis due to HELLP syndrome: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[HELLP syndrome (hemolysis, elevated liver enzymes, and low platelets) is a severe form of hypertensive disorder of pregnancy, causing multiorgan injury via thrombotic microangiopathy (TMA). Acute kidney injury (AKI) is a serious complication, but cases requiring dialysis are relatively uncommon. A 40-year-old, previously healthy primigravida developed acute hypertension, hemolysis, elevated liver enzymes, and thrombocytopenia on postpartum day 0, leading to a diagnosis of HELLP syndrome....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attenuated Li-Fraumeni syndrome with TP53 p.R181H in a Japanese patient with metastatic rectal adenocarcinoma: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Li-Fraumeni syndrome (LFS) is a hereditary cancer-predisposing disorder caused by germline pathogenic variants in the TP53 gene. Attenuated LFS represents a clinically milder form characterized by lower penetrance and later tumor onset, evading standard diagnostic criteria. We report a case of a 36-year-old Japanese woman who presented with hematochezia and was diagnosed with metastatic rectal adenocarcinoma. After failure of the first- to third-line chemotherapies, plasma-based comprehensive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psoriasiform eruption in Kawasaki disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Validation of a Prediction Model for Intracranial Aneurysm Rupture Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this prognostic study, the MLM consistently identified features of UIAs as significantly associated with rupture across different cohorts. These results support the MLM's potential to assist physicians and patients in UIA treatment decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Towards Personalised Assessment of Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm Structural Integrity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) is a life-threatening condition characterized by the progressive dilation of the aorta, which can lead to rupture if undetected or untreated. Stress-based rupture risk estimation using computational biomechanics has been widely studied; however, it requires wall strength data that cannot be measured in humans in vivo. To overcome this limitation, the goal of this study is to present a new method for biomechanical assessment of AAA via simultaneous consideration of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632035/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a large volume injection technique for a portable gas chromatograph with a ball surface acoustic wave sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Most portable gas chromatographs (GCs) were designed exclusively for gas samples. If they can handle liquid samples too, the range of application is expected to expand substantially. However, in general, the injection volume of liquid samples in GCs is limited to about 1 μl or less to prevent the loss of analytical precision and instrument contamination. Therefore, it is difficult to achieve sufficient sensitivity with the limited resources of the portable GCs. In this study, we developed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvent-Dependent Bioactive Composition and Antifungal Potential of Neem (Azadirachta indica) Seed Extracts Against Mycotoxigenic Aspergillus Species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the bioactive composition and antifungal efficacy of neem seed extracts (NSE) prepared using acetone, ethyl acetate, chloroform, methanol, and ethanol against Aspergillus parasiticus and Aspergillus flavus. Gas chromatography-mass spectrometry (GC-MS) analysis revealed solvent-specific compounds profiles: ethanol extract contained 35 bioactive compounds (mainly esters and fatty acids), dominated by n-hexadecanoic acid (28.65%); methanol extract had 29 diketopiperazines,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Synthesis to Efficacy: Synthesis, Structural Analysis, and Antiviral Activity of 5-(Trifluoromethoxy)-1H-indole-2,3-dione 3-Thiosemicarbazones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Viral infections are a global cause of serious morbidity and mortality. The recent COVID-19 pandemic further testifies to the continued need to develop novel classes of antiviral agents with broad activity and high selectivity. In this work, 5-(trifluoromethoxy)-1H-indole-2,3-dione 3-(4-phenylthiosemicarbazones) bearing a methyl or ethyl group at position 1- of the indole ring were synthesized. Along with previously synthesized compounds 5a-j, 5l, 6b-d, 6g, 6i, and 6k-n, the novel compounds 5k,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal remodelling of the cloacal region determines the position of the anal opening in mouse embryos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional embryological models propose that the urorectal septum (URS) fuses with the cloacal membrane (CM) to form separate exits for the hindgut and urogenital sinus (UGS). However, previous studies have been re-evaluating this assumption, and the precise morphogenetic mechanisms determining the position of the anal opening remain unclear. To elucidate the spatial and temporal dynamics of cloacal development, we analysed mouse embryos from embryonic day (E)11.5 to E13.5 using serial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chem-Bio Hybrid Synthesis Enables Reengineering of Natural Product-Based Methionine Aminopeptidase 2 Inhibitors for Treating Amebiasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Natural products remain a vital source of therapeutic innovation, but their structural complexity often limits the systematic optimization and clinical translation. This challenge is exemplified by the fungal metabolite fumagillin, a covalent inhibitor of methionine aminopeptidase 2 (MetAP2), which advanced toward clinical development but whose semisynthetic derivatives were discontinued in trials for cancer and obesity because of adverse effects. To overcome these barriers, we reengineered the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvation structures of potassium bis(trifluoromethylsulfonyl)imide-glyme highly concentrated electrolytes and cycling on organic cathodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The physicochemical properties of highly concentrated electrolytes consisting of potassium bis(trifluoromethylsulfonyl)imide in oligo(ethyleneglycol) dimethyl ethers (glymes) are reported. The solvation structures were analyzed by Raman spectroscopy, single crystal X-ray diffraction, and theoretical calculations revealing significant ion-pairing at high concentrations especially for the shorter glymes, leading to them being classified as poor solvate ionic liquids with the general formula...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of unsymmetrical boron complexes bearing (iso)quinolylphenol ligands and their halogenated derivatives; crystal polymorphism for white-light-emitting properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Boron complexes bearing (iso)quinolylphenol ligands and their halogenated derivatives were synthesized to investigate their optical properties. The structural effects of the (iso)quinoline rings and halogenated positions on the photoabsorption and fluorescence emission properties of the complexes were observed in both solution and the solid state. In particular, chlorination at the C5 position of the phenol moiety induced crystal polymorphism. This resulted in unique dual emission bands in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directed evolution of phage Romulus in biofilm-embedded <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em>: mutations in baseplate proteins enhanced its antibiofilm activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ability of Staphylococcus aureus to form biofilm and the emergence of multidrug-resistant strains make staphylococcal infections often chronic and difficult to treat. To face these challenges, alternative or adjunct strategies to antibiotics are urgently required. In this context, phage therapy gained renewed interest as promising approach to target multidrug-resistant bacteria. To enhance their efficacy as natural phages, they can undergo directed evolution via serial host passages. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EBUS-TBNA for lung cancer in the apical segment of the right upper lobe using a new EBUS scope]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The applicability of ultrasound-guided transbronchial needle aspiration (EBUS-TBNA) for diagnosing central parenchymal tumors has been well established; however, lesions requiring puncturing under extreme angulation, especially the apical segment of the right upper lobe lesions, are often inaccessible with EBUS scopes. We report two cases of centrally located lung cancer in the apical segment of the right upper lobe. Case1. A 77-year-old man presented to the outpatient clinic with right chest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of human induced pluripotent stem cells cultured on soft substrates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the impact of culture surface rigidity on the proliferation and maintenance of undifferentiated human induced pluripotent stem cells (hiPSCs), which are crucial in regenerative medicine and stem cell-based organ therapy. Given the need for a substantial number of cells per patient, there is a pressing demand for methods that ensure homogeneous and efficient large-scale cultivation of hiPSCs. Mechanotransduction, the process by which cells, including hiPSCs, respond to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colloidal state and emulsifying properties of protein isolates from kilned and non-kilned oats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a strong need for basic insights into the colloidal state of oat proteins as function of environmental conditions, and the relationship with functional properties. Relevant in this regard is the commonly applied industrial oat groat heat treatment ('kilning') which is here hypothesized to affect the colloidal and functional properties of oat protein isolates (OPIs). Here, we prepared OPIs from non-heat-treated (NHT) and industrially heat-treated (IHT, kilned) oats and investigated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of APOE testing for reducing ARIA under probabilistic stopping rates to treat with anti-amyloid therapy for ε4-homozygote patients: A simulation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The direct safety impact of APOE testing for ARIA mitigation is limited, even under universal discontinuation policies. Its primary value lies in supporting shared decision-making and operational planning rather than as a standalone safety lever.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of one-year cognitive decline via self-perceived memory in older adults during the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Subjective memory complaints (SMC) are associated with increased risk of cognitive decline and dementia. SMCs are also influenced by mood and anxiety symptoms, which increased among older adults during the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional connectivity of youth in family-like residential care in Japan: Impact of reactive attachment disorder and disinhibited social engagement disorder symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adverse childhood experiences are a risk factor for attachment disorders. While several neuroimaging studies have shown changes in functional networks in children who have experienced institutional care, the results are inconsistent. Furthermore, no research has been conducted on how structured residential care, such as Japan's small-group family-style care, influences attachment-related symptoms and functional connectivity. This study compared attachment-related symptoms (reactive attachment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability and validity of Japanese version of Neonatal Pain, Agitation, and Sedation Scale for acute pain in infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The N-PASS-J is a dependable and valid instrument for assessing acute pain in infants with illness treated in the NICU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of drift-reducing spray configurations on spray deposition and coverage in winter wheat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Spray configuration had a negligible effect on the relative spray deposition at the different collector positions in winter wheat, except at the spike and at the ground level. The results indicate that spray applications in winter wheat require optimizations tailored to the specific target location within the canopy, rather than a uniform approach. Air support combined with a fine spray quality nozzle appears particularly promising in improving deposition without compromising drift...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of AI systems in the clinical laboratory: insights from an expert survey and recommendations for best practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although many challenges remain, clinical laboratories demonstrate strong enthusiasm for AI, particularly with the growing prevalence of commercial AI products. The timely expert insights from our survey and C-AILM recommendations for both AI system providers and clinical laboratories on essential information, verification requirements, and monitoring strategies will inform standardized guideline development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiologic and clinicopathologic features of 19,352 jaw cysts: a single-center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This large retrospective study provides a detailed epidemiological profile of jaw cysts. The findings revealed distinct patterns according to cyst type, age, sex, and anatomical site, providing a valuable reference for diagnostic refinement and future comparative studies of oral and maxillofacial pathology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of proton pump inhibitor use on immune-related adverse events in patients with non-small cell lung cancer: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PPI use was potentially associated with a lower incidence of non-CIP irAEs, whereas no significant effect was observed for CIP. In contrast, PPI use was not an independent prognostic factor, suggesting that irAE occurrence is influenced by multiple factors beyond PPI use. This study highlights the importance of investigating the interplay between PPI exposure, irAE occurrence, and gut microbiome alterations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[USP18 orchestrates malignant progression in nasopharyngeal carcinoma through UBR5-driven attenuation of p53 signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study unveils a previously unrecognized oncogenic mechanism wherein USP18 promotes malignant progression of nasopharyngeal carcinoma via UBR5-dependent suppression of the p53 signaling pathway. These findings highlight USP18 as a promising candidate biomarker and potential therapeutic target in NPC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of ECOG performance status 2 participants on outcomes of pivotal cancer clinical trials: a meta-analysis and meta-regression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although PS 2 participants showed a greater propensity to serious toxicity, no significant differences in efficacy outcomes were observed compared with those with PS ≤1. Our results support the inclusion of PS 2 participants in clinical trials, as their exclusion limits the generalizability of results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential effects of orexin system activation on dizocilpine-induced schizophrenia-like behaviors in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Schizophrenia encompasses positive, negative, and cognitive symptoms, and accumulating evidence suggests that the orexin system may modulate circuits relevant to these domains. Here, we investigated whether orexin-related interventions influence schizophrenia-like behaviors induced by the NMDA receptor antagonist dizocilpine in female and male mice. Two distinct approaches were used: nasal orexin A administration and chemogenetic activation of orexin neurons via DREADDs. Behavioral assessments...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633010/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The morphology of male accessory glands in the Glenea cantor (Fabricius, 1787) (Coleoptera: Cerambycidae: Lamiinae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Male accessory glands of insects serve as secretory organs, exhibiting the ability to produce secretions that regulate reproductive processes. Their histology and ultrastructure are generally regarded as being diverse within insect groups, however, as one of the largest groups of insects, the ultrastructure of male accessory glands in Cerambycidae has never received sufficient attention. The longhorn beetle Glenea cantor (Fabricius, 1787) (Coleoptera: Cerambycidae: Lamiinae) is a wood-boring...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41633006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating human exposome data into next-generation risk assessment: a systematic framework to infer real-life exposure levels and prioritize chemical compounds for testing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exposome research and next-generation risk assessment (NGRA) share the goal of improving the human relevance of chemical safety evaluations, yet practical integration remains limited. We developed a flexible framework that combines human biomonitoring (HBM) data, exposome datasets, and exposure modeling results with chemical property, toxicity, and bioactivity information to support NGRA and chemical prioritization. The framework comprises three modules: a curated human exposome database,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Lightweight Depthwise Separable Convolution and Channel Attention Based GRU Network for Multichannel EEG Seizure Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epilepsy is the fourth most common neurological disorder, and seizures significantly impact quality of life of affected individuals. Electroencephalography (EEG) based seizure detection has emerged as a critical research area to improve the diagnosis and management of epilepsy. However, existing methods often suffer from poor generalisability and high computational complexity, emphasizing the need for rapid, accurate, and non-invasive detection frameworks. This study proposes a lightweight end...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonlinear transport fingerprints of tunable Fermi-arc connectivity in magnetic Weyl semimetal Co<sub>3</sub>Sn<sub>2</sub>S<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fermi arcs in Weyl semimetals provide a unique platform for surface-state engineering, yet directly tracking of their evolution under surface tuning remains experimentally challenging. Here we theoretically propose that nonreciprocal charge transport can serve as a direct probe of Fermi arc Lifshitz transitions (FALT). We show that different surface terminations in Co3Sn2S2 can produce finite and highly tunable second-order nonreciprocal signals, which can be further modulated by adjusting the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632976/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing the Associations of Internet Addiction and Internet Gaming Disorder With Psychopathological Symptoms: Cross-Sectional Study of Three Independent Adolescent Samples]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides additional evidence that IGD and IA are distinct yet interrelated constructs, and further demonstrates that IA consistently exhibits stronger associations with the severity of psychopathological symptoms than IGD. These findings underscore the importance of recognizing and addressing compulsive and problematic online behaviors that extend beyond gaming, highlighting the need to refine diagnostic frameworks and prioritize targeted clinical interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanofluidic Confined DNA Aptamers for Neuromorphic Multiplex Discrimination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bioinspired nanofluidic systems that utilize ions as signal carriers hold great promise for emulating neural processing in biochemical sensing and neuromorphic computing. However, achieving parallel, brain-like processing of multiple biochemical signals remains a significant challenge. Herein, we present a nanofluidic artificial postsynaptic membrane (APM) functionalized with confined DNA aptamers to construct a neuromorphic signal processing platform. Target-induced conformational switching of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632967/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrated Prediction System for Individualized Ovarian Stimulation and Ovarian Hyperstimulation Syndrome Prevention: Algorithm Development and Validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study introduces an integrated framework for predicting NOR and early-onset moderate-to-severe OHSS risk across different FSH doses. Future prospective evaluation is needed before clinical implementation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chronic Facial Abscess Mimicking Cervicofacial Actinomyces From Dermal Filler Migration: Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dermal fillers are commonly used for facial augmentation, but delayed complications such as granulomatous inflammation and filler migration can mimic chronic bacterial infections, such as cervicofacial actinomycosis, and lead to diagnostic misdirection. We present the case of a woman aged 56 years with a chronic, draining abscess on the right cheek that persisted for 3 years and was initially suspected to represent cervicofacial actinomycosis. Tissue cultures were negative, and histopathologic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma Proteomic Signatures of Accelerometer-Measured Sedentary Behavior Are Associated with Future Disease Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have shown the link between sedentary behavior and health outcomes. However, self-reported sedentary behavior is less accurate than accelerometer-measured sedentary behavior. Additionally, the proteomic signatures associated with sedentary behavior and their potential impact on biological pathways remain unknown. In this study, we identified proteomic signatures of sedentary behavior using whole-proteome association analysis and LASSO regression based on data from 2921 plasma...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632939/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Happening in the Prostate Tumor Microenvironment: Ion Channels and Extrachromosomal DNA Driving Phenotypic Plasticity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ion channels and ecDNA are central to the disease progression and treatment resistance of PCa through regulation of EMT, CSC phenotype, and tumor microenvironment (TME) interactions. Targeting the drivers-through ion channel modulators, ferroptosis induction, and ecDNA-targeting interventions (BET/HDAC inhibitors, CRISPR-based methods) offers a promising way to overcome resistance. Integration of multi-omics, and combination treatments will be key to construct precision medicine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adoption and Regional Variation of Prostate-Specific Membrane Antigen Positron Emission Tomography in the United States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PSMA-PET was rapidly incorporated into clinical practice among commercial insurance beneficiaries with prostate cancer with higher adoption in geographic regions with higher income and education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling the Tailored Exfoliation Mechanism and Electrochemical Behavior of α-NiCo Hydroxide Nanoplates for Water-Splitting Catalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The chemical exfoliation of layered metal hydroxides (LMHs) is a cutting-edge technology to obtain unilaminar and few-layer LMH nanosheets with positive charges and an ultrathin thickness, which widely serve as building blocks for functional composites in emerging fields. However, the preparation of high-quality monolayers with a large lateral dimension and regular morphology and the investigation of the exfoliation mechanism remain formidable challenges. Herein, uniform hexagonal NiCo LMH...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632922/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-Activity Relationship and Crystallographic Study of New Monobactams]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monobactams, a subclass of β-lactam antibiotics with a monocyclic scaffold, are uniquely resistant to hydrolysis by metallo-β-lactamases, providing a distinct therapeutic advantage. Here, we report an in silico-based structure-activity relationship (SAR) investigation of aztreonam-related monobactams. A focused library of monobactam derivatives was synthesized and evaluated for inhibition of penicillin-binding proteins (PBPs) and antibacterial activity. Ten compounds, including aztreonam, were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Didychaudianin A: a new tirucallane triterpenoid from the stem bark of Indonesian <em>Didymocheton gaudichaudianus</em> (Meliaceae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new tirucallane-type triterpenoid, didychaudianin A (1), along with two known tirucallane analogs (2 and 3), was isolated from the stem bark of D. gaudichaudianus (Meliaceae) growing in West Java, Indonesia. Their structures, including absolute configurations, were elucidated using HRESIMS, extensive 1D and 2D NMR spectroscopic analysis, ECD spectroscopy, and quantum chemical calculations based on density functional theory (DFT), supported by DP4+ statistical analysis. Cytotoxic evaluation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipid nanoparticle-delivered ornithine transcarbamylase mRNA alleviates liver fibrosis in preclinical models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Collectively, our study provides the first direct preclinical evidence supporting OTC mRNA therapeutics for treating liver fibrosis and establishes proof-of-concept for mRNA therapy as a novel strategy to reverse liver fibrosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomanufacturing Biobased Organic Amines from Biomass-Derived Aldehydes Through the Amination with Transaminase 3FCR-3M]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lignocellulose, as the most abundant renewable biomass, offers a sustainable source of valuable chemicals. This study explores the biosynthesis of vanillylamine, a versatile lignin derivative used in producing furans, food additives, and pharmaceuticals, from biobased aldehydes under mild conditions. A transaminase (3FCR-3M) from Ruegeria sp. TM1040 was expressed in E. coli and applied in ethylene glycol-water medium (ethylene glycol, 20 vol%). Under optimized conditions (35 °C, pH 7.5), using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NPM1 Mediates mRNA Sorting into Extracellular Vesicles via Specific RNA Motif Binding and Phase Separation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) deliver genetic material to recipient cells, thereby influencing immunity, development, and various diseases. However, the precise mechanism by which specific mRNAs are selected for packaging into EVs remains poorly understood. This study identifies Nucleophosmin 1 (NPM1) as a key protein responsible for sorting mRNAs into EVs. NPM1 achieves this by binding to specific RNA motifs, including those within mRNAs such as the epidermal growth factor receptor (EGFR),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personal Health Goals in Homeless-experienced Veterans: Rates, Patterns, and Associations With Health-related Needs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings highlight the high value that many high-need homeless-experienced patients place on their social well-being and the potential benefits to measuring both deficiency and growth needs in this population. Clinical implications and future directions for research are discussed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coupled anatexis and extreme differentiation are the keys for producing giant lithium-rich pegmatites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the economic importance of lithium, there is considerable disagreement over the processes that concentrate it and other rare metals in pegmatite-type lithium deposits. Two main processes have been invoked, namely extreme differentiation of a peraluminous granitic magma and direct anatexis of a sedimentary protolith. We use geochemical modeling to quantify lithium enrichment via these two processes from a study of the Jiajika lithium pegmatite field, one of the largest of its type in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A framework for assessing the trustworthiness of scientific research findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vigorous debate has erupted over the trustworthiness of scientific research findings in a number of domains. The question "what makes research findings trustworthy?" elicits different answers depending on whether the emphasis is on research integrity and ethics, research methods, transparency, inclusion, assessment and peer review, or scholarly communication. Each provides partial insight. We offer a systems approach that focuses on whether the research is accountable, evaluable,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular tuning of DNA framework-programmed silicification by cationic silica cluster attachment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The organizational complexity of biominerals has long fascinated scientists seeking to understand biological programming and implement new developments in biomimetic materials chemistry. Nonclassical crystallization pathways have been observed and analyzed in typical crystalline biominerals, such as calcium phosphate, calcium carbonate, and ferric oxide, involving the controlled attachment and reconfiguration of nanoparticles and clusters on organic templates. However, the understanding of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modelling chemotaxis of branched cells in complex environments provides insights into immune cell navigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell migration in vivo is often guided by chemical signaling, i.e., chemotaxis. For immune cells performing chemotaxis in the organism, this process is influenced by the complex geometry of the tissue environment. In this study, we use a theoretical model of branched cell migration on a network to explore the cellular response to chemical gradients. The model predicts the response of a branched cell to a chemical gradient: how the cell reorients its internal polarity and how it navigates through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632822/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QO-BRA: A Quantum Operator-Based Autoencoder for De Novo Molecular Design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We introduce a variational quantum autoencoder tailored for de novo molecular design, named QO-BRA (Quantum Operator-Based Real Amplitude autoencoder). QO-BRA leverages quantum circuits for real-amplitude encoding and the SWAP test to estimate reconstruction and latent-space regularization errors during back-propagation. Adjoint encoder and decoder operators enable unitary transformations and a generative process that ensures accurate reconstruction, as well as the novelty, uniqueness, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632821/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic formation and regional disparities of Kra-Dai and Hmong-Mien speakers inferred from ancient genomes of cave burial populations in southwest China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cave burial is a funerary practice believed to be associated with modern Kra-Dai (KD) and Hmong-Mien (HM) speakers for thousands of years. However, the extent to which these ancient cave burial practitioners contributed to the formation of modern ethnic minority groups remains poorly understood due to the limited ancient genomic data. We generated 14 newly sequenced ancient human genomes from cave burial sites in Guangxi. The findings reveal continuous gene flow from northern lineages into...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and spatial distribution characteristics of human brucellosis in Ningxia from 2010 to 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings reveal a substantial burden of human brucellosis in Ningxia. The disease exhibits distinct seasonality, peaking in summer and autumn. Priority interventions should include: (1) Enhanced health education and targeted behavioral interventions for middle-aged and elderly males to improve personal awareness and competency in prevention and control; and (2) Timely identification of key risk factors and implementation of tailored prevention strategies in regions experiencing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soil environment effects on the occurrence of black sesame spot and clubroot disease in Chinese Cabbage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chinese cabbage is a popular leafy vegetable widely consumed in Asian cuisine, particularly in China. However, it is susceptible to various diseases, including clubroot and black sesame spot, which can significantly impact yield and quality. The soil environment plays a crucial role in developing these two diseases. In our experiment, we measured eight soil indicators-soil pH, organic matter, alkali-hydrolyzable nitrogen, available phosphorus, rapidly available potassium, total salinity, total...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The influence of stigma on PrEP uptake among adolescent girls and young women in Johannesburg, South Africa and Mwanza, Tanzania: Qualitative findings from the EMPOWER study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest that anticipated stigma is a common yet surmountable concern of AGYW initiating PrEP in eastern and southern Africa. Future PrEP implementation should be paired with multi-level activities to reduce stigma including empowerment activities for adolescents, strategies to reduce negative attitudes among health care providers and community-wide education to raise awareness and position PrEP as a responsible choice for young people to protect their health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring phonological complexity in statistical learning of artificial words]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Findings suggest that passive exposure to complex patterns does not enhance generalization within a statistical learning paradigm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of fermented Rosa roxburghii Tratt pomace on growth performance, lipid metabolism, antioxidant activity, and amino and fatty acid profile in goats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rosa roxburghii Tratt pomace, is a juice extraction rich in polyphenols with strong antioxidant activity. The objective of this study was to evaluate the effect of fermented Rosa roxburghii Tratt pomace (FRRT) on growth performance, plasma biochemistry and antioxidant status, and longissimus dorsi muscle amino- and fatty-acid profiles in meat goats. Twenty-four goats with similar body weights (30.7 ± 4.71 kg) were allotted in a completely randomized design to either basal diet (CON) or the same...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Death to Onchocerciasis and Lymphatic Filariasis (DOLF) project: Accomplishments and ongoing research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Death to Onchocerciasis and Lymphatic Filariasis (DOLF) project conducts clinical and translational research to accelerate the global elimination of lymphatic filariasis (LF) and onchocerciasis (river blindness). Research needs were identified during several meetings of experts and helped study design. Over the last 15 years the project has conducted mass drug administration (MDA) studies and clinical trials with outstanding research teams in 11 countries that have led to many important...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of African swine fever emergency on the mental health of first responders in the Dominican Republic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[African swine fever (ASF) has become a global pandemic, affecting nearly 2 million pigs since 2022 alone and causing significant disruption to food security and trade. The Dominican Republic (DR) has been affected by ASF since 2021. Veterinarians are key first responders in animal health emergencies and at risk for negative impacts from prolonged emergency response. We used mixed methods and network analysis to characterize the mental and social impacts of ASF on 29 DR swine veterinarians. All...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resource landscape shapes the composition and stability of the human vaginal microbiota]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The vaginal microbiota is associated with the health of women and newborns alike. Despite its comparatively simple composition relative to other human microbiota systems, the mechanisms underpinning the dynamics and stability of vaginal microbial communities remain elusive. A crucial, yet so far underexplored, aspect of vaginal microbiota ecology is the role played by nutritional resources. Glycogen and its derivatives, produced by vaginal epithelia, are accessible to all bacterial constituents...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzymatic Production of Prebiotic Xylooligosaccharides Using a <em>Bacillus pumilus</em> GH30_8 Glucuronoxylanase: Structural Basis of Glucuronoxylan Recognition and Hydrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transformation of agro-industrial products into value-added products, such as prebiotic oligosaccharides, is a key element of the emerging bioeconomy. Here, we characterized a new GH30_8 glucuronoxylanase from Bacillus pumilus (BpXyn30_8A) for its potential in producing xylooligosaccharides (XOS). BpXyn30_8A showed tolerance to ethanol and NaCl and released both linear and branched XOS containing MeGlcA at the penultimate nonreducing end residue. Its X-ray structure, determined at 2.16 Å...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic learning mechanisms for flexible human locomotion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Movement flexibility and automaticity are necessary to successfully navigate different environments. When encountering difficult terrains such as a muddy trail, we can change how we step almost immediately so that we can continue walking. This flexibility comes at a cost since we initially must pay deliberate attention to how we are moving. Gradually, after a few minutes on the trail, stepping becomes automatic so that we do not need to think about our movements. Canonical theory indicates that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Older Patients with NPM1-Mutated or KMT2A-Rearranged AML Before Menin Inhibitors: A Beat AML Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and Efficacy of CT-Guided Lung Biopsy in Elderly Patients age 75 Years and Older: A Single-Centre Retrospective Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[IntroductionCT-guided biopsy has good diagnostic accuracy, but adverse events such as pneumothorax are common. There are few reports on the safety and efficacy of CT-guided biopsy in the elderly.MethodsThis was a retrospective single-centre cohort study. Patients who underwent CT-guided lung biopsy between February 2017 and August 2024 were included. Patient background, disease background, examination status, and adverse events were ascertained. Elderly were defined as those aged 75 years and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metacognition in Decision-Making Across Domains and Modalities: Evidence from Three Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metacognition involves second-order judgments about first-order judgments. It remains unclear whether an individual's confidence in being correct is generated by the same system across tasks (domain generality) or whether it is computed independently in the context of each task (domain specificity). Previous studies have focused on correlations across several tasks, yet the evidence is mixed, and more complex models of domain generality were not taken into account. Analyzing data from 10 tasks...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the U.S. Food and Drug Administration's Method for Detection of Per- and Polyfluoroalkyl Substances Analytes in Food and Feed: First Action 2025.06]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The FDA's method for detection of 30 PFAS in food and feed compares favorably with the requirements of AOAC SMPR 2023.003 and should be adopted as a First Action AOAC Official Method.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Gap-free Petunia Genome Assemblies Reveal the Evolutionary Dynamics of the S-locus Supergene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Petunia hybrida is a key genetic model for investigating self-incompatibility (SI), a reproductive barrier governed by the multi-allelic S-locus, which encodes a pistil-specific S-RNase and multiple S-locus F-box (SLF) genes. Due to high heterozygosity and abundant repetitive sequences, previous S-locus assemblies in reference genomes have been fragmented and collapsed. Here, we present the telomere-to-telomere (T2T), haplotype-resolved genomes of two homozygous SI lines (P. hybrida S3LS3L and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[mRNA Mediated Expression of Novel Fusion Phage Tail Protein with Antimicrobial Peptides inside Macrophages for Targeted Clearance of Intracellular <em>Mycobacterium tuberculosis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current anti-tuberculosis treatments primarily target extracellular Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb), but exhibit limited efficacy against intracellular Mtb, leading to incomplete clearance of pathogens and an increased risk of recurrence. Antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) possess broad-spectrum antimicrobial activity and low potential for resistance development. Here we developed an in vitro mRNA expression platform which not only facilitates intracellular AMPs expression within macrophages, but...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of A Risk Assessment Model for Venous Thromboembolism among Patients with Cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Venous thromboembolism (VTE) has a high incidence among patients with cholangiocarcinoma (CCA). However, appropriate risk assessment models (RAMs) for CCA are limited. This study aimed to develop a RAM for predicting VTE in patients with CCA. We conducted a retrospective study at a single university-based hospital in Thailand. We included consecutive patients who were newly diagnosed with CCA between January 2018 and December 2022. A total of 694 CCA patients were included in the study. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of Idiosyncratic Gaze-Fingerprint Signatures in Humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Do individuals possess a "gaze fingerprint" that reveals how they uniquely look at the world? We tested this question by examining intra- and intersubject gaze similarity across 700 static pictures of complex natural scenes. Independent discovery (n = 105) and replication data sets (n = 46) of adults aged 18 to 50 years (sampled from Italy and Germany) revealed that gaze fingerprinting is possible at relatively high rates (e.g., 52%-63%) compared with chance (e.g., 1%-2%). We also identify...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[18F-FDG PET/CT Findings in a Case of Primary Leptomeningeal Melanomatosis With Diastematomyelia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Primary leptomeningeal melanomatosis is a rare and aggressive variant of primary central nervous system melanoma. Diagnosis is often challenging due to nonspecific radiologic features. We hereby report the 18F-FDG PET/CT and MRI findings in a case of primary leptomeningeal melanomatosis in a 47-year-old woman with a previously unidentified diastematomyelia. Spinal MRI showed diffuse abnormal signal. 18F-FDG PET/CT showed hypermetabolism most notably in the lumbar and caudal portion of the spinal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2 fusion-peptide-directed antibodies are elicited by natural infection and can mediate broad sarbecovirus neutralization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Studies have demonstrated that repeated mRNA vaccination enhances the breadth of neutralization against diverse severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2 (SARS-CoV-2) variants. However, the development of antibodies capable of neutralizing across the Coronavirinae subfamily is poorly understood. In this study, we analyze serum samples to determine their neutralization breadth and potency and identify their antigenic targets. Using a cohort of older individuals and healthcare workers, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limited sex-based differences in viral outcomes of ART-treated SIV/SHIV infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lentiviral infection of rhesus macaques represents a robust model for HIV persistence and a key system to evaluate HIV cure-directed interventions. How sex impacts viral reservoirs in macaques is unknown. We sought to uncover potential sex differences in viral measurements during antiretroviral therapy (ART) using data from 19 studies conducted at Emory Primate Center. Sex differences in total and intact SIV/SHIV-DNA levels in blood and lymph node CD4+ T-cells were not observed, although...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrated Tripodal Polydentate Terpyridine Cobalt Complex-Based Metal-Organic Gel as a Bifunctional OER/ORR Electrocatalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the pursuit of a technological breakthrough in zinc-air batteries, it is critical to find economical, durable, and high-performance catalysts for the oxygen evolution reaction (OER) and oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) to accelerate the slow reaction kinetics. Herein, a one-pot method was employed to synthesize the polymer within a mixed solvent of CHCl(3) and CH(3)OH (v/v = 2:1). The resulting polymer can be well-dispersed in deionized water to form an aqueous metal-organic gel (MOG). Testing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gastric cancer surgery centralization under scrutiny]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunotherapy targeting drug-tolerant Mycobacterium tuberculosis persisters accelerates tuberculosis cure in preclinical models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb) remains a global health crisis, ranking among the deadliest infectious diseases worldwide. In response to the World Health Organization's call for therapeutic vaccines to complement antibiotic regimens and reduce tuberculosis (TB) treatment duration, we developed an intranasal DNA vaccine fusing the Mtb stringent response gene relMtb with the gene encoding the dendritic cell-targeting chemokine Mip3a/CCL20. Administered alongside the first-line regimen, this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced glycoprotein hormone β-5 links male aging and testosterone decline to increased adiposity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging commonly causes decline of testosterone or estrogen, leading to overaccumulation of fatness in males or females, respectively. Although such phenomenon can be readily explained by estrogen's direct action on adipocytes in females, accumulative evidence does not support the direct action of testosterone in adipocyte lipid metabolism, suggesting that there is a missing intermediary link. Herein, we propose that glycoprotein hormone β5 (GPHB5) is the intermediary linkage between testosterone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacial Hopping Integral as a Predictive Descriptor for Electron Transport: Saturated Alkane Junctions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electron transport across interfaces governs a broad range of fundamental phenomena. Although orbital overlap is recognized as a key determinant, its experimental quantification remains elusive. Here, we establish the interfacial hopping integral (t(eld-mol)), quantifying orbital overlap between contacting atoms, as a predictive descriptor of single-molecule conductance in a benchmark domain of saturated α,ω-functionalized alkane junctions. Using scanning tunneling microscopy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Culturally Tailored Diabetes Self-Management Education Program With Mobile Health Integration for Chinese Americans With Type 2 Diabetes: Development and Pilot Evaluation Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our pilot study demonstrated the feasibility of implementing the CASCADe program among CAs to improve diabetes self-management skills and yielded promising results, warranting further evaluation in a larger randomized trial.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Repression of PRMT activities sensitize human homologous recombination-proficient ovarian and breast cancer cells to PARP inhibitor treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic epigenetic modulation is currently being evaluated in the clinic to sensitize homologous recombination (HR)-proficient tumors to PARP inhibitors. To broaden its clinical applicability and identify more effective combination strategies, we conducted a drug screen combining PARP inhibitors with 74 well-characterized epigenetic modulators targeting five major classes of epigenetic enzymes. Notably, both type I PRMT inhibitors and PRMT5 inhibitors scored highly in combination efficacy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When the System Is the Treatment: Rethinking Nonpharmacologic Breakthroughs in Oncology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Underwater hearing sensitivity of the Kemp's ridley sea turtle (Lepidochelys kempii)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anthropogenic noise may pose a threat to Kemp's ridley sea turtles in nearshore and offshore waters of the western North Atlantic and Gulf of America, where shipping and energy industries are widespread. Understanding hearing sensitivity is necessary for the development of effective noise impact mitigation strategies. However, data gaps currently exist. Therefore, in this study, we measured auditory evoked potentials (AEP) to determine the underwater hearing sensitivities of 13 juvenile Kemp's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Transcription Factor TCF21 is Necessary for Adoption of Cell Fates by Foxd1+ Stromal Progenitors during Kidney Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The stromal compartment of the developing kidney arises from Foxd1-expressing progenitors and gives rise to diverse cell types essential for nephrogenesis, including the renal stroma, capsule, mesangial cells, renin cells, pericytes, and vascular smooth muscle cells (VSMCs). However, the molecular mechanisms guiding their fate specification remain incompletely defined. Here, we identify the basic helix-loop-helix transcription factor Tcf21 as a critical determinant of stromal cell identity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Hearing Loss on Annual Incident Age-Associated Dementia Cases and Quality of Life in the US]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Model-projected estimates support that hearing loss prevention could substantially reduce new dementia cases and should be a priority.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bolstering the Pathway to Promote Scientific Workforce Diversity: The UCSF Mid-Career Development Program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PROBLEM: Academic medical institutions face longstanding challenges in recruiting and retaining historically excluded, midcareer research faculty. Although progress in recruiting has been documented, retention has focused on individuals rather than a system-level approach.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Travel Time to Opioid Treatment Programs in Connecticut-Still Waiting for Methadone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimated Effectiveness of 2024-2025 COVID-19 Vaccination Against Severe COVID-19]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this multicenter, case-control analysis of VE, 2024-2025 COVID-19 vaccines may have provided protection against hospitalizations and severe in-hospital outcomes as multiple JN.1 descendant lineages circulated. Monitoring COVID-19 VE, including stratifying by SARS-CoV-2 lineage and spike protein mutations, remains important to guide COVID-19 vaccine composition and recommendations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41632473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260204030056&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>