<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 07:37:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Riemannian denoising model for molecular structure optimization with chemical accuracy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce a framework for molecular structure optimization using a denoising model on a physics-informed Riemannian manifold (R-DM). Unlike conventional approaches operating in Euclidean space, our method leverages a Riemannian metric that better aligns with molecular energy change, enabling more robust modeling of potential energy surfaces. By incorporating internal coordinates reflective of energetic properties, R-DM achieves chemical accuracy with an energy error below 1 kcal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interplay of Silver-Mean Quasiperiodicity and Weyl Semimetal Phase in WTe_{2}]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the intercalation of epoxy resin into a Weyl semimetal, WTe_{2}, by using a scanning tunneling microscopy. We show that intercalant molecules have self-similar height variations with the silver-mean quasiperiodicity and also that they create phason and soliton defects to yield a mean coherence length of 15 sequential order. In addition, we unravel that weak quasiperiodic potentials imposed by the intercalation layer drive a WTe_{2} surface to have an enhanced conductance near the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal Exposure to Polypropylene Nanoplastics Disrupts Sex- and Region-Specific Lipid Metabolism in the Brains of C57BL/6N Mouse Offspring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polypropylene nanoplastics (PPNPs), produced through the degradation of widely used plastic products, are increasingly recognized as emerging environmental contaminants with potential neurodevelopmental toxicity. However, the long-term biochemical consequences of prenatal PPNP exposure on brain development remain poorly understood. In this study, we performed a region- and sex-specific targeted lipidomic analysis to examine how maternal oral exposure to PPNPs during pregnancy and lactation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The health effects of diaphragmatic breathing: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DB is a promising complementary therapy for specific conditions, including GERD, but the evidence base is constrained by methodologically weak and heterogeneous primary studies. Future research requires rigorous, standardized trial designs to establish its clinical value. Despite these limitations, DB is a low-cost, accessible, and apparently safe intervention for select conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Localized vitamin D delivery via 3D-printed nanofiber sheets combined with systemic supplementation enhances tendon-to-bone healing in a rabbit rotator cuff tear model: A preclinical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this preclinical rabbit model, dual delivery of vitamin D using localized nanofiber sheets and systemic supplementation enhanced tendon-to-bone healing and muscle regeneration compared to single interventions. These findings provide a foundation for future studies aimed at optimizing delivery methods and evaluating safety and efficacy in clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morning sleep inertia and its associated factors: Findings from a nationwide study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sleep inertia was associated with sleep duration, chronotype, sleep-related symptoms, and anxiety. These findings underscore the need for targeted interventions to alleviate the adverse impact of sleep inertia on daily functioning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The traffic controller: GARLH4 dictates neuroligin synapse-type preference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuroligin isoforms are commonly thought to intrinsically specify synapse identity. In this issue, Yamasaki et al. (https://doi.org/10.1083/jcb.202507190) show that the auxiliary protein GARLH4 (LHFPL4) instead dictates neuroligin preference via competitive hierarchy, enabling dynamic reassignment between excitatory and inhibitory postsynaptic domains.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological Justification Criteria of Pediatric Computed Tomography in Kenya]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Computed tomography is acknowledged as the most widely used imaging technique in both adults and children. Although computed tomography offers valuable diagnostic information, it contributes to a high radiation dose and poses relatively high risks of stochastic effects to patients. Stochastic risks are of special concern in pediatric imaging since children are more vulnerable to effects of ionizing radiation than adults. Therefore, the justification of pediatric computed tomography examinations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidic Solid-State pH Sensor for Dynamic Monitoring of Extracellular pH in Live Cell Cultures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate, real-time monitoring of the extracellular acidification is crucial for understanding the dynamics of cellular metabolism. Here, we present a microfluidic device with a solid-state potentiometric pH sensor for monitoring the extracellular acidification rate (ECAR) in live cell culture. The sensor employs a two-electrode configuration made up of Ag/AgCl and RuO(2) electrodes. The sensor showed excellent analytical capabilities, a consistent Nernst response with high sensitivity (-93...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Timing of Initiation and Efficacy of Dual Antiplatelet Therapy in Minor Stroke or High-Risk TIA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Early initiation of DAPT was associated with the greatest clinical benefit, consistent with current guideline recommendations. The therapeutic effect appeared to decline progressively beyond this period, with an estimated threshold around 42 hours.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoexcited Nitroarene-Mediated Oxidation Enables the Total Synthesis of (-)-Securingine G]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In general, dehydrogenation of piperideine and piperidine to pyridine requires precious transition-metal catalysts or harsh oxidative conditions. In this study, we show that photoexcited triplet-state nitroarenes act as effective dehydrogenation agents for a one-step anaerobic aromatization of these cyclic amines. The utility of this transformation is demonstrated in the second-generation total synthesis of securingine G.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal changes in subcortical functional connectivity during Alzheimer's disease progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human cognition and behavior rely on the integration of large-scale neural networks that connect the cerebral cortex and subcortical structures. Emerging evidence suggests that alterations in the functional connectivity (FC) between the cortical and subcortical regions in Alzheimer's disease (AD) may influence the onset and progression of both cognitive and noncognitive symptoms at the group level. However, an individualized and longitudinal framework to capture deviations in subcortico-cortical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Universal Electric Medical Clamp for Rotational Intraperitoneal Aerosol Chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A universal electric medical clamp was successfully developed for RIPAC, providing stable rotational motion and improved drug distribution potential compared with PIPAC. This innovation lays the groundwork for clinical translation of RIPAC as a promising strategy to enhance intraperitoneal chemotherapy efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Protective Effect of Decellularized Extracellular Matrix in Osteoarthritis: An <em>In Vitro</em> and <em>In Vivo</em> Study in Rat Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Meni-dECM hydrogels demonstrated protective effects against OA progression by modulating inflammation and preserving cartilage architecture. These findings support Meni-dECM hydrogel as a promising injectable biomaterial for OA management in both veterinary and translational medicine. Further studies are warranted to confirm long-term stability, elucidate molecular mechanisms, and evaluate clinical feasibility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA Damage-induced Post-transcriptional Regulation of SIRT4 by the miR-15/16 Family Modulates Chemosensitivity in Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The miR-15/16-SIRT4 axis represents a novel mechanism of post-transcriptional regulation in the DNA damage response and may serve as a therapeutic target to improve the efficacy of chemotherapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Implications of Exosomal miRNA Networks Regulating TGFβ1-induced Epithelial-Mesenchymal Transition Signature in Oral Squamous Cell Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EMT-related gene networks regulated by exosomal miRNAs carry clinically meaningful information about tumor aggressiveness in OSCC. The derived Exo-miR EMT signature offers biologically grounded risk stratification that complements conventional clinicopathological factors and supports further development of exosome-based liquid biopsies for prognostic assessment in OSCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Liquid Biopsy: Spike-In Panel Approach for ctDNA Copy Number Variation Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Incorporation of a spike-in panel into the Avenio ctDNA assay enabled reliable detection of high-level MYC/MYCN amplifications and fulfilled practical requirements for local reimbursement. The estimated CNV limit of detection in this setting is ≈3 copies. Further replicate testing and validation with clinical specimens are warranted to refine sensitivity and interlaboratory robustness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of the Egg Glue Protein from Two Belostomatidae Family Aquatic Water Bugs, Appasus japonicus and Lethocerus indicus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Egg glue proteins are essential for the survival of aquatic insects, as they provide the means for securely attaching eggs to substrates and preventing them from being dislodged by water. In this study, we aimed to identify and characterize the egg glue proteins from two species of Belostomatidae family aquatic insects, Appasus japonicus and Lethocerus indicus, which are both commonly known as "toe biters" or "(giant) water bugs". Both species exhibit unique adhesive strategies to secure their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glucose-responsive cascade nanozyme for controlled ROS release and bacterial carbon metabolic reprogramming in infected diabetic wounds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic bacterial infections in diabetic wounds remain a major clinical challenge due to persistent inflammation, biofilm formation, and antibiotic resistance. Herein, we report a glucose-responsive cascade nanozyme system (PPCG) that functions as a microenvironment-adaptive reactive oxygen species (ROS) delivery platform for localized treatment of infected diabetic wounds. The PPCG integrates glucose oxidase (GOx) with a PdPtCu nanozyme core, enabling a triggered and self-sustaining catalytic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Intensity Ultrasound-facilitated exosome delivery promotes hippocampal neurogenesis in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intranasal hADSC-Exos combined with LIUS is safe, enhances brain delivery, and synergistically improves cognition and neurogenesis in AD mice. The Fos-Kcnj13 axis may mediate these effects, suggesting a promising noninvasive therapeutic strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does Temporomandibular Joint Disc Displacement Influence Joint Space Dimensions, and Does Sex Play a Role?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: DD is associated with smaller condyles and enlarged fossa, contributing to increased anterior joint space dimensions. These findings may aid diagnosis and treatment planning in patients with TMJ DD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Effects of Mobile-Based Metamemory Cognitive Training in Older Adults With Mild Cognitive Impairment: 15-Month Prospective Single-Arm Longitudinal Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study showed that long-term use of a mobile-based metamemory cognitive training app was associated with cognitive improvements over 15 months. Although limited by the small sample size and the absence of a control group, these findings suggest potential for mobile cognitive training as a sustainable intervention that warrants validation in larger trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abbreviated gadoxetic acid-enhanced MRI versus ultrasonography for HCC surveillance in high-risk patients: A randomized trial protocol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Although ultrasonography (US) is widely recommended for HCC surveillance, its limited sensitivity for early-stage HCC remains a concern. Gadoxetic acid-enhanced abbreviated MRI (HBP-AMRI) has demonstrated high diagnostic performance; however, its role in routine surveillance settings remains uncertain due to limited prospective comparative evidence. The AMRIUS study (Abbreviated MRI using gadoxetic acid versus Ultrasonography for Surveillance of early-stage HCC in high-risk patients)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posterior Tibial Slope Is Associated With the Chondral Wear Pattern of the Medial Tibial Plateau]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Posterior tibial slope is associated with the chondral wear pattern of the medial tibial plateau. The anteromedial OA, centromedial OA, and posteromedial OA groups each exhibit distinct characteristics, including differences in mHKA angle and medial meniscus radial tears. Among these factors, observed chondral wear patterns shifted posteriorly as posterior tibial slope increased, suggesting an association between greater slope and the development of posterior wear patterns. These...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stereoselective Construction of <em>C</em><sub>2</sub>-Symmetric Adjacent Bis-α,α'-<em>cis</em>-Disubstituted THF Skeleton via Double Intramolecular Amide Enolate Alkylation: Total Syntheses of (+)-Membranacin and (+)-Squamocin-N]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Described herein is the highly stereoselective and concise first asymmetric total synthesis of (+)-squamocin-N (1b) bearing a C15-C24 adjacent bis-tetrahydrofuran (THF) backbone with threo/cis/threo/cis/threo stereochemistry. This approach features construction of C(2)-symmetric adjacent cis/threo/cis bis-THF core 5 via a novel double intramolecular amide enolate alkylation (IAEA) protocol, reductive desymmetrization of C(2)-symmetric bis-THF 5, and chelation-controlled nucleophilic addition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Software for dataset-wide XAI: From local explanations to global insights with Zennit, CoRelAy, and ViRelAy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The predictive capabilities of Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) are well-established, yet the underlying mechanisms driving these predictions often remain opaque. The advent of Explainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) has introduced novel methodologies to explore the reasoning behind complex model predictions of complex models. Among post-hoc attribution methods, Layer-wise Relevance Propagation (LRP) has demonstrated notable adaptability and performance for explaining individual predictions -...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The influence of garden spatial configuration on tourist behavior: A systematic review based on Space Syntax]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As composite spaces that integrate nature and culture, gardens are no longer regarded as merely static objects of visual appreciation in the context of urbanization, but have become essential venues for public cultural tourism and leisure. Consequently, the behavioral characteristics of tourists in gardens have attracted increasing academic attention. Space syntax, as a tool for analyzing the influence of spatial organization on human behavior, quantifies spatial configuration characteristics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geographic variation in lack of food group consumption among children in India: An analysis of change across 720 districts, 2016-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adequate dietary intake in early childhood is essential for growth and development. However, evidence on geographic disparities and recent trends in food group consumption among young children in India remains limited. This study investigated district-level changes in the consumption of specific food groups among children aged 6-23 months in India. Data from two National Family Health Surveys conducted in 2016 and 2021 of India were used, and a harmonized 720-district geometry was applied to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Susceptible host dynamics explain pathogen resilience to perturbations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Interventions to slow the spread of SARS-CoV-2 significantly disrupted the transmission of other pathogens. As interventions lifted, whether and when human pathogens would eventually return to their prepandemic dynamics remains to be answered. Here, we present a framework for estimating pathogen resilience based on how fast epidemic patterns return to their prepandemic dynamics. By analyzing time series data from Hong Kong, Canada, Korea, and the United States, we quantify the resilience of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of acute kidney injury stages with in-hospital and long-term mortality in older adults with hip fractures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher AKI stages are associated with increased in-hospital and long-term mortality in older adults with hip fractures. Preventing AKI development and progression is essential to improve prognosis in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A unified model: chromatin-bound multi-component onco-condensates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In cells, highly coordinated multivalent interactions give rise to discrete functional assemblies-commonly referred to as biomolecular condensates-that compartmentalize the molecular components required for specific biological reactions. These condensates are increasingly recognized as organizational entities with central roles in normal cellular regulation and in the pathogenesis of human cancers. In a recent issue of Cell, Datar and colleagues investigated the condensation of NPM1c, a common...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data Resource Profile: Climate and Enteric Diseases Research Project (ClimED)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: "Comparison of microscopic dynamics and continuum theory for Poiseuille and diffusioosmotic flows in a microchannel" [J. Chem. Phys. 163, 134902 (2025)]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tuning Electronic Skeleton Properties of Porphyrin Covalent Organic Frameworks (COFs) for High-Performance Selective Gas Chemiresistive Sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Covalent organic frameworks (COFs) have emerged as promising platforms for chemiresistive gas sensing due to their intrinsic porosity and tunable electronic structures. However, achieving high sensitivity, low detection limits, and long-term stability simultaneously remains challenging. Herein, we report a skeleton engineering strategy applied to three isostructural porphyrin-based metal free COFs, synthesized with skeleton linkers bearing methyl, hydrogen, or fluorine substituents, enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Polynucleotide-Based Therapy in Atopic Dermatitis Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This exploratory case series provides preliminary observations suggesting that PN-based injectable therapies may offer benefits for patients with AD, particularly in improving skin hydration, barrier function, and symptomatic relief. While positive outcomes were documented in all four cases, the absence of validated scoring systems, objective biophysical measures, long-term follow-up, and a control group limits the strength and generalizability of these findings. PN injections in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of glucagon-like peptide-1 receptor agonists on gastric mucosal visibility during upper endoscopy in Asian patients with diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: GLP-1RA use was associated with a higher risk of inadequate gastric mucosal visibility and aborted and repeat procedures during upper gastrointestinal endoscopy in Korean patients with T2DM while pulmonary aspiration was not observed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fixation stability and stress redistribution following metal block use in opening-wedge high tibial osteotomy: a finite element analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Metal block augmentation improved the biomechanical stability in OWHTO constructs, with greater grains in uniplanar osteotomies and LHF models. This enhancement was accompanied by altered stress distribution, characterized by increased stress on the plate and reduced stress in the proximal tibia, suggesting a potential stress-shielding effect. By quantifying these effects under various conditions, this study provides biomechanical evidence for the selective application of metal block...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical significance of citrullinated glial fibrillary acidic protein in predicting outcomes in hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Following curative resection in patients with HCC, high cit-GFAP expression may serve as a potential prognostic biomarker, although further validation through independent cohort studies is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health diplomacy training, pedagogical approaches, and skills assessment: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Health diplomacy education is key in strengthening the practice of public health diplomacy by equipping learners with essential skills in negotiation, leadership, cultural competency, and communication skills. However, current training initiatives remain fragmented, inequitable, and under-evaluated.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480065/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between smoking behavior and sleep health among South Korean adolescents: A cross-sectional study 2020-2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Poly tobacco use is significantly associated with poor sleep health among South Korean adolescents. Future longitudinal studies are needed to establish causal pathways and provide sufficient evidence to guide effective interventions and policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal brain connectivity changes associated with successful smoking cessation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Taken together, the reduction of initially elevated pre-quit FC in SN-ECN and SN-DMN circuits may reflect an adaptive neural process that supports successful withdrawal management and attentional reallocation during cessation. The identification of these neural substrates not only enhances our mechanistic understanding of smoking cessation over time but also underscores the need for targeted interventions that focus on these neural circuits to enhance quit outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multifocal transcranial electrical stimulation to enhance cognitive functions: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although multifocal tES is a promising modality, clearly determining its efficacy is currently limited by heterogeneous study designs, small sample sizes, and conflicting findings. Future research should prioritize multi-arm trials, incorporate neurophysiological biomarkers, and develop personalized stimulation protocols to optimize the effectiveness of this technique.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative effectiveness and safety of herbal medicine therapy for low back pain and radiculopathy caused by lumbar intervertebral disc herniation: a study protocol for a pragmatic randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This pragmatic randomized controlled trial aims to provide robust clinical evidence on the effectiveness, safety, and cost-effectiveness of herbal medicine therapy for lumbar intervertebral disc herniation, particularly in comparison to other traditional Korean medicine interventions. The findings are expected to contribute significantly to developing evidence-based guidelines and optimizing treatment strategies for this prevalent condition, addressing an urgent healthcare need and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of aerobic exercise interventions on cognitive function, sleep quality, and quality of life in older adults with mild cognitive impairment: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings of this study demonstrate that aerobic exercise may significantly improve cognitive function and quality of life in older adults with MCI, with enhanced effects observed when intervention parameters are optimized.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-center evaluation of Neurophet AQUA for brain MRI segmentation: T1 compared with FreeSurfer and T2-FLAIR compared with ground truth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Neurophet AQUA demonstrated high segmentation accuracy and excellent repeatability in rescanned measurements, as well as exploratory evidence of inter-scanner reproducibility on T1-weighted MRI, showing comparable performance to established tools such as FreeSurfer. It also showed consistent WMH segmentation across FLAIR types. Neurophet AQUA is highly suitable for clinical applications that require accurate analysis, high repeatability and reproducibility, and rapid brain MRI...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted-Immunomodulatory Nanomedicines for the Treatment of Autoimmune Diseases via Multiple Administration Routes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence and prevalence of autoimmune diseases are rising globally, presenting a significant health challenge. Current treatments focus on symptom management and immunosuppression, often resulting in side-effects such as increased infection risk and broad immunosuppression. Targeted immune modulation strategies, particularly through nanomedicines, offer promising advancements by enabling precise drug delivery and reducing systemic toxicity, risks, and pharmacokinetic issues. Nanocarriers,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allometric equations for orchard and vineyard trees: enhancing AFOLU-based climate change mitigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Perennial orchard systems are emerging as important yet underrepresented carbon sinks within the AFOLU sector, which contributes 20-24% of global GHG emissions. Many countries still rely on Tier 1 default values that fail to capture the structural and management characteristics of orchard species. Accurate biomass and carbon estimation, particularly through species-specific allometric equations, is essential for improving Tier 2-3 GHG reporting and recognizing orchards as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Albumin-bilirubin score as a practical tool for prognostication in metabolic-associated steatotic liver disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) has become the leading cause of chronic liver disease worldwide, yet reliable tools for prognostication remain limited. Fibrosis-based indices such as the fibrosis-4 and nonalcoholic fatty liver disease fibrosis score are widely used but primarily reflect structural damage rather than functional decline. The albumin-bilirubin (ALBI) score, originally established to assess hepatic reserve in patients with hepatocellular carcinoma, provides a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Ultrasound Image-and-Intervention Paradigm for a Neglected Lumbar Transverse Process Fracture: A Case Report of Diagnosis and Hydrodissection Treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lumbar transverse process (TP) fractures are often overlooked, leading to chronic pain that is frequently refractory to standard treatments. This case report describes the diagnostic use of musculoskeletal ultrasound (MSK-US) and a novel therapeutic application of ultrasound-guided hydrodissection for a case of neglected TP stress fracture. A 41-year-old male presented with an 18-month history of chronic right groin and thoracolumbar pain, unresponsive to extensive prior treatments, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progress of lateral flow assays for the detection of molecular and microbial species: from basic formats to microfluids, CRISPR and artificial intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lateral flow assays (LFAs) have garnered much interest in the biomedical and agricultural sciences because of their user-friendly design, quick turnaround times, minimal interference, affordability, and ease of use by individuals. To date, many researchers have reported the use of LFAs for microbial and molecular species identification in the area of clinical and environmental fields, respectively. In this review, we describe the progress in the design of LFA techniques from basic formats to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Genetic Significance of Chromosomal Microarray Screening of Asymptomatic Newborns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although a high rate of clinically significant CNVs was detected through LR-CMA screening, only a minority of asymptomatic newborns exhibited developmental concerns within the observed follow-up period. These findings suggest that while LR-CMA may identify genetic alterations of interest, its routine use in asymptomatic newborns warrants careful consideration of clinical relevance and potential psychosocial impact.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LC‑MS/MS for Thyroglobulin: A Complementary Approach to Immunoassay Limitations for Thyroid Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consensus on the Diagnosis of Cushing's Disease: A Collaborative Statement from the Korean Endocrine Society and Japan Endocrine Society]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cushing's disease (CD) is a rare but serious endocrine disorder caused by excessive cortisol secretion due to adrenocorticotropic hormone-secreting pituitary tumors. Despite recent developments in diagnostic criteria and treatment options, CD remains associated with substantial comorbidities and mortality. Early and accurate diagnosis is thus essential. Both the Korean Endocrine Society (KES) and Japan Endocrine Society (JES) guidelines are intended to standardize diagnostic approaches to CD,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating Density Functional Theory with Deep Neural Networks for Accurate Voltage Prediction in Alkali-Metal-Ion Battery Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate prediction of the voltage of battery materials plays a pivotal role in the advancement of energy storage technologies and the rational design of high-performance cathode materials. In this work, we present a fully connected deep neural network (FCDNN) model, built using PyTorch, to estimate the average voltage of cathode materials across Li-ion, Na-ion, and other alkali-metal-ion batteries. The model is trained on an extensive dataset from the Materials Project, incorporating a wide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bidirectional Ultrafast Control of Charge Density Waves via Phase Competition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The intricate competition between coexisting charge density waves (CDWs) can lead to rich phenomena, offering unique opportunities for phase manipulation through electromagnetic stimuli. Leveraging time-resolved x-ray diffraction, we demonstrate ultrafast control of a CDW in EuTe_{4} upon optical excitation. At low excitation intensities, the amplitude of one of the coexisting CDW orders increases at the expense of the competing CDW, whereas at high intensities, it exhibits a nonmonotonic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ligand Counting and Size Determination of Quantum Dots Using Electronegative Matrix-Assisted Laser Desorption Ionization Mass Spectrometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface-capping ligands on quantum dots (QDs) modify the physical and chemical properties of QDs to enable diverse applications. Accurate qualitative and quantitative analyses of these ligands are therefore essential for the advancement of QD research; however, conventional methods (e.g., UV-vis, TEM) seldom provide direct stoichiometric insight. MS can offer a solution, but traditional MALDI induces an excessive ligand loss. Here, we employed a highly electronegative, fluorinated porphyrin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Randomised trial on the economic impact of proficiency-based progression vs conventional robotic surgical training]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We conclude that PBP training is significantly more effective and becomes increasingly cost-efficient as the number of trainees increases. These findings support its integration into high-volume national training programmes, offering a scalable and economically sustainable alternative to apprenticeship-based surgical education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RUNX2 Represses the EWS-FLI1-mediated Transcription in Ewing's Sarcoma Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EWS-FLI1 suppresses RUNX2 gene expression in Ewing's sarcoma cells, and re-expressing RUNX2 inhibits cell growth. These findings suggest that RUNX2 has a negative impact on the oncogenic process in Ewing's sarcoma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Combinational Measurements of the Electron Density and Electric Field in Secondary Streamer Discharge under Atmospheric-Pressure Air]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electron density and electric field govern physical and chemical reactions in a secondary streamer discharge under atmospheric-pressure air. We present direct combinational measurements of these essential quantities and demonstrate their consistency by solving the continuity equation for electrons. The measurements enabled validity examination of previous computational studies and clarified contradictions; the prominence was a near-cathode phenomenon measured during primary-to-secondary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directional Searching for Light Dark Matter with Quantum Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The presence of dark matter (DM) stands as one of the most compelling indications of new physics in particle physics. Typically, the detection of wavelike DM involves quantum sensors, such as qubits or cavities. The phase of the sensors is usually discarded as the value of the phase itself is not physically meaningful. However, the difference of the phase between the sensors contains the information of the velocity and direction of the DM wind. We propose a measurement protocol to extract this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine Learning-Based Clustering of Right Ventricular Free-Wall Strain Features for Cardiovascular Risk Prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482253/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The 2025 ESC Guidelines for Myocarditis and Pericarditis and the Evolving Role of Cardiovascular Magnetic Resonance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The plastidial phosphorylase Pho1 co-localizes in situ with Photosystem1-associated PsaC as assessed by double labeling immunocytochemistry - transmission electron microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The plastidial phosphorylase Pho1 is essential for normal starch biosynthesis in cereal grains. Biochemical studies, however, have shown that this starch biosynthetic enzyme interacts with PsaC, the terminal electron acceptor-donor protein of Photosystem I (PSI). This association with PsaC associated with PS1 is supported by the localization of Pho1 to thylakoid membranes enriched in PSI complexes. To obtain direct in situ evidence for this protein-protein interaction within thylakoid membranes,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of nutrition impact symptoms with dietary intake among patients with advanced cancer referred to palliative care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lack of appetite, early satiety, nausea, vomiting, abnormal taste, and fatigue were significantly associated with dietary intake independently of the influence of other symptoms and other confounders. Furthermore, lack of appetite, early satiety, and nausea were good predictors for reduced dietary intake.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Mapping of PUFA Incorporation into Phospholipids with bisallylic deuteration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mass spectrometry (MS) imaging using stable isotope-labeled fatty acids provides a groundbreaking approach to precisely localizing exogenous fatty acids and their metabolites in vivo. However, challenges persist, particularly with fatty acids labeled with fixed isotopic numbers, which can lead to spectral interferences and limit the number of metabolites that can be detected. In this study, we employed a bisallylic deuteration method to synthesize dihomo-γ-linolenic acid (DGLA) isotopes with m/z...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trigeminal Nerve Direct Current Stimulation Modulates Raphe-Hippocampal Network Synchrony in Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TN-DCS dynamically modulates raphe-hippocampal firing and theta synchrony via predominantly amplitude-dependent mechanisms that require intact trigeminal input and serotonergic signaling, supporting its potential as a targeted neuromodulation approach for subcortical circuits involved in cognition and mood.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between the rate of force development of quadriceps and physical performance in older patients undergoing cardiovascular surgery: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Rate of force development and physical performance were significantly correlated after cardiovascular surgery, especially in those with low muscle mass.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-term perfluoro-n-octane tamponade for combined penetrating keratoplasty and pars plana vitrectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Short-term PFO tamponade for combined PKP and PPV may be useful surgical approach for cases involving corneal pathology and PVR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tracing 2500 years of human betaherpesvirus 6A and 6B diversity through ancient DNA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human betaherpesviruses 6A and 6B (HHV-6A/6B) are DNA viruses, which integrate into the human genome, and are best known to cause "sixth disease." Despite their recent discovery (1980s), they were speculated to have a much longer history within the human population than modern data suggest. We present the first 11 ancient genomes of HHV-6A and HHV-6B, dating as far back as the 8th to 6th century BCE. We demonstrate that large fractions of current HHV-6 diversity were already established by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of Supra-Bivalent GSK3β Inhibitory Peptides Containing an ATP-Mimetic Amino Acid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[De novo discovery of highly selective inhibitors of protein kinases (PKs) remains a significant challenge in drug discovery. Although ATP-site-directed bivalent inhibitors targeting a distinct binding site are an emerging alternative, their rational design is impeded by limited knowledge about allosteric binding sites unique to the target kinase and the complexity of the linker design. Here, we report a strategy that overcomes the above-mentioned issue using a macrocyclic peptide library...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzyme cascade reactions encapsulated in a liposome compartment with size-limited molecular transport]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We designed a liposome-coated DNA origami compartment to encapsulate a defined number of cascade enzymes with retained cofactors. Confinement enhanced cascade reaction efficiency particularly at low cofactor levels. Efficiency gains plateaued at higher NADH concentrations, indicating that intermediate diffusion and enzyme spatial organization influence cascade performance in confined environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultralight and mechanically robust carbon monoliths with aligned microchannels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While macroporous carbon materials have attracted considerable attention due to their tunable porosity, chemical and thermal stability, and electrical conductivity, they still face critical limitations in achieving a balance of ultralow density, high mechanical toughness, and efficient fluid transport through a cost-effective and environmentally friendly approach. To address these issues, an ice-templating approach is employed to fabricate ultralight yet mechanically robust carbon monoliths with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting bifurcation of mechanical systems using reservoir computing: Case studies on legged locomotion and pneumatic soft actuator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding and predicting how mechanical systems respond to environmental variability is essential for advancing next-generation robotic systems with physical intelligence. In this study, we investigated the use of echo state networks (ESNs), a representative class of reservoir computing (RC) models, to predict the bifurcation structures of real-world mechanical systems from limited observations. We examined two representative cases: a simulated passive dynamic walking (PDW) robot with hybrid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41481262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3-Acetyl-11-Keto-Beta-Boswellic Acid Inhibits Adipogenesis by Suppressing Autophagy and Inducing AMPK Phosphorylation in 3T3-L1 Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AKBA suppresses adipogenesis by inhibiting adipogenic transcription factors, autophagy, and activating AMPK, supporting its potential as an anti-obesity therapeutic candidate.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary cobalt suppresses starch-induced succinate accumulation via colonic synthesis of vitamin B<sub>12</sub> and its analogues in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-amylose maize starch (HAMS) can lead to succinate accumulation in the rat colon depending on the colonic microbiota. Since succinate is primarily produced via the vitamin B(12) (VB(12))-dependent succinate pathway, limited VB(12) availability in the colon may impair fermentation. While a portion of dietary VB(12) may reach the colon, most of it is absorbed in the upper gastrointestinal tract, potentially resulting in an insufficient supply for colonic bacteria. This study aimed to determine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human adenosine deaminase type 2 deficiency enhances NK cell activation but impairs maturation and function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[NK cells, or natural killer cells, might be interesting players to investigate further in the disease process of patients with deficiency of ADA2, a rare, recently discovered inborn error of immunity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of continuous glucose monitoring systems (CGMs) during commercial flights in T1DM: A within-subject comparative pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: G7 and Libre3 showed consistently higher accuracy and clinical reliability across various phases of flight and ground conditions. Simplera and i3 exhibited greater variability in accuracy. These findings suggest that while modern CGMs could support diabetes management in aviation, individual system performance may differ under specific operational conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differences in the efficacies of commonly used asthma questionnaires for predicting asthma-related outcomes among elderly and non-elderly patients in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Commonly used asthma questionnaires may not be suitable for predicting outcomes in patients with EA. However, specific questions addressing factors such as wheezing, nocturnal symptoms, nasal issues, and activity limitations may serve as reliable indicators of asthma-related outcomes in these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transdisciplinary training to address challenges in genomic epidemiology of infectious diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During the COVID-19 pandemic, the emergence and detection of SARS-CoV-2 variants of concern highlighted the pivotal role of genomic epidemiology in public health decision and policy making. The pandemic also revealed a need for genomic epidemiologists to effectively engage with a broader audience, including policymakers and the public. To address this need, we introduced a new transdisciplinary training workshop, "From Trees to Public Health Policy," at the Virus Evolution and Molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41480072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distant mothering, grandparenting, intergenerational coparenting relationship, and child adjustment: evidence from Chinese families with young left-behind children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: In China, it is a common practice for rural-to-urban migrant parents, due to working conditions, to leave their children with grandparents in their rural hometowns, and to raise their child from a distance (e.g., via mobile phone). Little is known about the association between (co-)parenting processes and child adjustment in these families. This cross-sectional study examined, in households with left-behind children (LBC), how positive grandparenting and distant mothering are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and safety of endoscopic ultrasound-guided liver biopsy to diagnose parenchymal liver disease: A multi-centre retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EUS-LB is an effective and safe method for obtaining liver biopsy in patients with suspected parenchymal liver disease. EUS-LB demonstrated a favorable safety profile in our cohort, although larger prospective studies are required to validate bleeding risk. The use of 19-gauge FNB needles, wet-heparin suction technique, and performing ≤ 2 passes is associated with improved quality of the specimen obtained without increasing the risk of adverse events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cochlear Implantation in Patients with CHARGE Syndrome: A 10-Year Institutional Experience and Literature Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It is not the bottle, it is the gas: why recycling desflurane bottles misses the point]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41479311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With Opioid-Involved Overdose: Descriptive Data From a Randomized Controlled Trial Evaluating Extended-Release Buprenorphine for Perinatal Opioid Use Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underscore the critical need to address substance use, co-occurring mental health, and socioeconomic challenges that are associated with previous opioid overdose. Identifying and targeting key modifiable overdose risk factors can inform the development of tailored interventions to improve outcomes for this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insecticidal activity of manuka essential oil triketones against two major lepidopteran pests]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate that manuka essential oil and its components are promising biopesticides, but improved delivery systems are needed to reduce phytotoxicity. Published 2026. This article is a U.S. Government work and is in the public domain in the USA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring Structure-Function Relationship of Lignin Derivatives to Enhance Its Biostimulant Potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lignin is a promising biostimulant for enhancing plant growth and stress tolerance. In this study, bamboo kraft lignin (BKL) and its oxygen-alkali-modified derivative (OBKL) were applied to maize seedlings to elucidate the structure-function relationship. The increased hydrophilic groups of OBKL improved its capacity to enhance water and nutrient uptake, resulting in a 50% increase in root elongation, 65% enhancement in photosynthesis, and a 106% rise in transpiration. Low-molecular-weight OBKL...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dissolution Behavior of Lithium-Ion Battery Cathode Materials in Aquatic Systems: Key Drivers and Molecular Mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid expansion of lithium-ion battery (LIBs) deployment has generated increasing volumes of spent batteries that are often improperly discarded, raising concerns about their environmental impact. Lithium nickel cobalt manganese oxides (NCM), the predominant cathode materials in modern LIBs, are of particular concern because of their high content of redox-active transition metals (TMs). Nevertheless, their dissolution behavior and underlying molecular mechanisms under environmentally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[LTB4 Activates the MAP Kinase Pathway in Endothelial Cells to Cause Long-Lasting Neutrophil Tethering, MCP-1 and NO Releases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leukotriene B(4) (LTB(4)), a potent chemotactic and immune-modulating eicosanoid, signals via two receptors (BLT(1) and BLT(2)), leading to rapid but transient migratory, adhesive and secretory responses in phagocytes. Previously, we reported that BLT(1) is the predominating BLT in human umbilical vein endothelial cells (HUVEC). However, little is known about how ligation of these receptors affects adhesive and secretory endothelial responses over time. Here, we demonstrate that in HUVEC, LTB(4)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anchored random reverse primer sequencing for quantitative detection of novel gene fusions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Identifying novel gene fusions is critical for cancer diagnosis and drug development. While a few advanced methods have shown the capability to detect gene fusions involving unknown partners, comprehensive detection of gene fusions, especially of those with low copy numbers, remains a challenge. Indeed, most current panel-based sequencing methods fall short in reliability and cost efficiency. Here we present a method for detecting potentially novel gene fusions using anchored random reverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TGFβ signaling mediates microglial resilience to spatiotemporally restricted myelin degeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microglia survey and regulate central nervous system myelination during embryonic development and adult homeostasis. However, whether microglia-myelin interactions are spatiotemporally regulated remains unexplored. Here, by examining spinal cord white matter tracts in mice, we determined that myelin degeneration was particularly prominent in the dorsal column (DC) during normal aging. This was accompanied by molecular and functional changes in DC microglia as well as an upregulation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482590/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A generative spike prediction model using behavioral reinforcement for re-establishing neural functional connectivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prediction models that generate neuronal spikes from upstream neural activities offer a promising way to re-establish neural functional connectivity. Traditional methods train these models by supervised learning, which requires downstream recordings as ground truth. However, functional downstream activity cannot be recorded when neurological disorders exist. Here we introduce a reinforcement learning (RL)-based point process framework to generate spike trains that directly maximize...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482588/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into type-I and type-II Lamassu antiphage systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacteria have developed a variety of immune systems to combat phage infections. The Lamassu system is a prokaryotic immune system with a core conserved structural maintenance of chromosomes (SMC) superfamily protein LmuB and diverse effectors named LmuA, whose mechanism remains unclear. Here we present a series of cryo-electron microscopy structures of the type-I Lamassu complex from Bacillus cellulasensis and the type-II Lamassu complex from Vibrio cholerae, both in apo and dsDNA-bound states,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stable foliar colonization of nanocoated nitrogen-fixing bacteria enhances crop nitrogen supply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Biological nitrogen fixation through foliar application of nitrogen-fixing bacteria presents a promising route to reduce reliance on synthetic fertilizers but remains limited by challenges in bacterial adhesion and survival in the phyllosphere. We developed a nanocoated inoculant encapsulating Klebsiella variicola W12 using metal-phenolic networks and sodium alginate for enhanced nitrogen fixation under nitrogen-depleted conditions. The nanocoating improved bacterial resistance to UV radiation,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence-driven approaches for materials design and discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Materials design is an important component of modern science and technology, yet traditional approaches rely heavily on trial and error and can be inefficient. Computational techniques, enhanced by modern artificial intelligence, have reshaped the landscape of designing new materials. Among these approaches, inverse design has shown great promise in designing materials that meet specific property requirements. In this Review, we present key computational advances in materials design over the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell perturbations decipher ribosomal stress-surveillance regulators in type 2 diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Systemic characterization of genes and pathways underlying the genetic architecture of type 2 diabetes (T2D) requires scalable functional genomics approaches. Molecular readouts from CRISPR perturbations can effectively uncover the mechanistic effects of underexplored genes. Here we performed single-cell RNA sequencing on pooled CRISPR screens (Perturb-seq) of 61 T2D-associated genes and 40 ribosome-associated quality control (RQC) genes in human pancreatic β cells (EndoC-βH1) for investigations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI-based low-dose digital subtraction angiography for intra-operative radiation dose reduction: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital subtraction angiography (DSA) devices guide procedures across numerous diseases, performed on more than 100,000 patients daily worldwide. However, these procedures expose patients and healthcare providers to radiation, increasing the risk of health issues. Despite many low-dose DSA imaging methods proposed, none have been prospectively clinically validated. In this study, 46,829 patients (over 5 million DSA images) from 70 centers were used to iterate our previously developed generative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autologous multiantigen-targeted T cell therapy for pancreatic cancer: a phase 1/2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[T cell therapy has proven challenging for pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC), partly due to heterogeneous expression of tumor-associated antigens (TAAs). To address tumor heterogeneity and mitigate immune evasion, an ex vivo expanded, polyclonal, T helper 1 cell-polarized T cell product targeting five TAAs-PRAME, SSX2, MAGEA4, Survivin and NY-ESO-1-was developed. These antigens were chosen based on their tumor specificity, oncogenicity, immunogenicity and level of expression. In a phase 1/2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multi-omic definition of metabolic obesity through adipose tissue-microbiome interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity's metabolic heterogeneity is not fully captured by body mass index (BMI). Here we show that deep multi-omics phenotyping of 1,408 individuals defines a metabolome-informed obesity metric (metBMI) that captures adipose tissue-related dysfunction across organ systems. In an external cohort (n = 466), metBMI explained 52% of BMI variance and more accurately reflected adiposity than other omics models. Individuals with higher-than-expected metBMI had 2-5-fold higher odds of fatty liver...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A One Health trial design to accelerate Lassa fever vaccines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lessons in public trust]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lymphotoxin-dependent elevated meningeal CXCL13:BAFF ratios drive gray matter injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In multiple sclerosis (MS), B cell-rich tertiary lymphoid tissues (TLTs) in the brain leptomeninges associate with cortical gray matter injury. Using a model of Th17 cell-driven experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis in mice, we found that inhibitors of Bruton's tyrosine kinase (BTKi) prevented TLT formation and cortical pathology in a B cell activating factor (BAFF)-dependent manner. BTKi reduced expression of lymphotoxin ligands, and cotreatment with a lymphotoxin-β receptor agonist...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-presentation of dead cell-associated antigens shapes the neoantigenic landscape of tumor immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Type 1 conventional dendritic cells (cDC1s) acquire and cross-present tumor antigens to prime CD8⁺ T cells. Whether this selects for specific neoantigens is unclear. DNGR-1 (CLEC9A), a cDC1 receptor for F-actin exposed on dead cells, promotes cross-presentation of cell-associated antigens. Here we show that DNGR-1-deficient mice develop chemically induced tumors more rapidly and at higher incidence, and these are more frequently rejected on transplantation into wild-type recipients. Whole-exome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skin-derived myeloid precursors and joint-resident fibroblasts spread psoriatic disease from skin to joints]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psoriatic disease initially affects the skin and later extends to the joints. Here, we show a two-step process that orchestrates the spread of inflammation from the skin to the joints. Induction of psoriatic skin disease in photoconvertible mice, followed by sequencing and computational characterization of skin-derived cells in the joints, was used to identify a population of CD2^(+)MHC-II^(+)CCR2^(+) myeloid precursors that builds a skin-derived myeloid cell compartment in the joints....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting small molecule-RNA interactions without RNA tertiary structures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Small molecules can bind RNAs to regulate their fate and functions, providing promising opportunities for treating human diseases. However, current tools for predicting small molecule-RNA interactions (SRIs) require prior knowledge of RNA tertiary structures. Here we present SMRTnet, a deep learning method that uses multimodal data fusion to integrate two large language models with convolutional and graph attention networks to predict SRIs on the basis of RNA secondary structure. SMRTnet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective combinatorial antifungal therapy using a host defense peptide mimic that self-assembles into delivery micelles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The synergistic combination of two antimicrobial drugs is a promising therapeutic modality for many infectious diseases. However, systemic fungal infections still have a high mortality rate because of distinct in vivo distributions of the two drugs. Here we address this challenge by designing an antifungal polymer that forms micelles suitable for delivering a second antifungal agent to achieve temporal and spatial consistency of delivery. We show that the polymer, which mimics host defense...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-strand deaminase-assisted editing for functional RNA manipulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rewriting RNA information to alter function requires controllable tools to edit RNA sequences within a user-defined region. Here we report a single-strand deaminase-assisted platform for adjustable RNA information manipulation (AIM). AIM is composed of a loop-forming guide RNA bound to an RNA-targeting Cas protein and an evolved TadA. AIM induces a loop, flanked by paired regions, in the target RNA; the loop size can be adjusted to allow conversions of single and multiple bases. We evolve TadA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor ecosystem and microbiome features associated with efficacy and resistance to avelumab plus chemoradiotherapy in head and neck cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune checkpoint blockade-based multimodal therapy is widely used across oncology; yet drivers of resistance in most cancer types are not well understood. Here, we comprehensively characterized the tumor genome, microenvironment and microbiome in a phase 3 international randomized trial ( NCT02952586 ) to identify factors that shape outcomes to anti-PD-L1 avelumab plus standard-of-care chemoradiotherapy versus placebo/chemoradiotherapy in individuals with locally advanced head and neck cancer....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intratumoral bacteria are immunosuppressive and promote immunotherapy resistance in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the promise of immune checkpoint blockade (ICB) in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma (HNSCC), mediators of response are poorly understood. To address this, here we analyzed oropharyngeal HNSCCs treated with neoadjuvant durvalumab (anti-PDL1) alone or in combination with tremelimumab (anti-CTLA4) from the CIAO clinical trial ( NCT03144778 ). We found that only the total abundance of intratumoral bacteria predicted ICB response, which was validated in multiple independent cohorts. High...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel cis-element enabled bacterial uptake by plant cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The root nodule symbiosis of plants with nitrogen-fixing bacteria is phylogenetically restricted to a single clade of flowering plants, which calls for as yet unidentified trait acquisitions and genetic changes in the last common ancestor. Here we discovered-within the promoter of the transcription factor gene Nodule Inception (NIN)-a cis-regulatory element (PACE), exclusively present in members of this clade. PACE was essential for restoring infection threads in nin mutants of the legume Lotus...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shear stress governs hematopoietic stem cell fate to promote inflammation-induced aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hematopoietic stem cells (HSCs) reside in the bone marrow in a quiescent state, but can be mobilized into the blood in response to inflammation, cytokine stimulation, nervous activity or hypoxia. Chronic inflammation, a hallmark of aging, accelerates HSC aging by promoting myeloid-biased differentiation and reducing self-renewal capacity, yet the role of mechanical stimulation in regulating these processes remains poorly understood. Here, we found that PIEZO1 senses shear stress in blood flow to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface/Interface Engineering for High-Resolution Micro-/Nano-Photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photodetectors can convert light energy into electrical signals, so are widely used in photovoltaics, photon counting, monitoring, and imaging. Photodetectors are easy to prepare high-resolution photochips because of their small size unit integration. However, these photodetector units often exhibit poor photoelectric performance due to material defects and inadequate structures, which greatly limit the functions of devices. Designing modification strategies and micro-/nanostructures can...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Analysis and Inhibitor Modeling of Bacterioferritin From Brucella abortus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Iron homeostasis in various pathogenic bacteria is regulated by bacterioferritins (Bfr) which function to store Fe^(3+) and release Fe^(2+) as needed for metabolic processes. The Bfr structure consists of 18 kDa subunits in which dimer pairs bind a heme molecule and are assembled into a highly symmetrical 24-meric spherical structure with an internal core diameter of approximately 80 Å. Release of iron is facilitated by the binding of a 7 kDa [2Fe-2S] ferredoxin (Bfd) to specific sites on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution of coronary artery calcium volume and density by age, sex, and race using AI-based quantification algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This analysis provides percentile distributions of directly measured CAC volume and average mean density across age, sex, and race. The data may better contextualize CAC interpretation and risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Organ-specific low-dose assessment in pediatric radiotherapy using nanodot OSL and NTCP modeling: Application to medulloblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By systematically quantifying and integrating imaging doses with therapeutic irradiation, this study underscores the often underestimated role of imaging in cumulative exposure during pediatric craniospinal irradiation. The results provide a solid foundation for tailoring radioprotection strategies and emphasize the need to reconsider planning and follow-up protocols to deliver safer and more targeted treatments for children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complex 2D Square Nanopatterns via Intrinsic Anisotropic Confinement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Square patterns are integral to industry-standard rectilinear coordinate systems, yet fabricating complex two-dimensional (2D) square patterns remains a formidable challenge. Herein, we report the emergence of complex 2D nanopatterned morphologies with p4mm and p4gm plane group symmetries and ultrasmall feature sizes (∼3 nm) in three-component bolaform giant surfactants which consist of a central polystyrene chain flanked by a perfluoroalkyl-functionalized polyhedral oligomeric silsesquioxane...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myth and medicine: a historical perspective on caesarean section in Ferdowsi's <em>Shahnameh</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferdowsi's Shahnameh, composed around 1000 CE, contains a remarkable narrative of the birth of the Persian hero Rostam, which describes a procedure resembling a caesarean section, termed 'Rostam-zad' or 'Rostamina'. This account, predating Roman associations with the procedure, offers insights into ancient Persian medical practices, including surgical techniques, anaesthetic methods and postoperative care. The story details a lateral incision, the use of a cannabis and camphor concoction for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with all-cause mortality and morbidity of motorcycle crash-related neurological and musculoskeletal injuries in Uganda: the MOTOR cluster randomised trial ancillary study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The key determinants of mortality and adverse neurological and musculoskeletal injury outcomes observed in this study are essential for establishing core outcome sets in future research and predictive models.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Streptococcus anginosus</em>-derived methionine promotes gastric cancer progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results elucidate the role of S. anginosus-derived methionine in GC progression, shedding light on intricate metabolic interplay between S. anginosus and host.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When the vascular lining loosens, dysfunctional macrophages permit pathological bacterial translocation in cirrhosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane Lipid Remodeling Modulated Maize Response to Environmentally Relevant Atmospheric Nanoplastics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atmospheric nanoplastics are emergingly found to deposit on leaves of terrestrial plants and adversely affect plant growth. Lipid remodeling has been verified as one of the important strategies for plants to respond to abiotic stress; however, its molecular response to atmospheric nanoplastics in crop leaves remains unclear. In this study, maize leaves were exposed to 50 nm polystyrene nanoplastics (PSNPs) with pristine (nPS), carboxy (nPS-COOH), and amino groups (nPS-NH(2)) at environmentally...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intravital imaging of the formation and resolution of MHC class II-positive T-cell activation niches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intravital imaging has revealed many of the cellular interactions that regulate immune responses, but is limited by the number of cells that can be simultaneously identified and often restricted to analysis of a single time point. We have developed two new fluorescent reporter strains, IEbeta-mAmetrine and CD8beta-LSSmOrange, that faithfully label cells expressing MHC class II and CD8-positive conventional T cells, respectively. These fluorescent proteins are spectrally distinct from commonly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482451/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of transfusion-dependent β-thalassaemia in the era of novel therapies: a prioritisation-based matrix for settings with limited resources]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[β-thalassaemia is an inherited haemoglobinopathy characterised by ineffective erythropoiesis and chronic anaemia of varying severity, which is predominant in the region extending from the Mediterranean basin and Middle East towards southeast Asia. Patients with severe phenotypes require lifelong transfusions, iron overload monitoring, and chelation. Suboptimal management due to access challenges continues to be directly linked to increased morbidity and mortality in many regions. In the past few...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intravenous iron for non-anaemic iron deficiency in pregnancy: a multicentre, two-arm, randomised controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: In non-anaemic iron deficiency during pregnancy, it remains unclear whether the administration of intravenous iron improves maternal and infant outcomes, compared with prophylactic oral iron that is currently recommended for antenatal care. This study evaluated whether the addition of intravenous iron to routine oral prophylaxis had an effect on maternal haemoglobin concentration before delivery in non-anaemic iron deficient pregnant women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Immune Profiling of T Cell Exhaustion During IL-17A Blockade in a Patient With HLA-B27-negative Spondyloarthritis and Sjögren's Syndrome: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case shows phased immune rebalancing under long-term IL-17A blockade. Serial monitoring revealed dynamic exhaustion marker changes and partial regulatory recovery linked to clinical improvement, underscoring the value of longitudinal immune profiling for personalized management of complex autoimmune syndromes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a Step-down FSH Superovulation Protocol in Microminipigs for Zygote Collection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The step-down FSH protocol effectively enhanced ovarian response and embryo yield in microminipigs, marking a foundational step toward the efficient reproductive engineering for this animal model that may contribute to the advancement of translational research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rhupus Syndrome With Multiple Drug Intolerances Managed by Reduced-dose Rituximab and Adjunctive Molecular Hydrogen Therapy: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case suggests molecular hydrogen therapy as a potential adjuvant for refractory Rhupus with multiple drug intolerances, showing immune modulation, reduced inflammation, steroid withdrawal, and sustained control with low-dose rituximab. Further studies are needed to confirm its efficacy and standardize its use.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulating <em>ACVRL1</em> Expression in HMEC1 Cells as a Simplified <em>In Vitro</em> Model for Hereditary Hemorrhagic Telangiectasia (HHT) Type 2 Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Knockdown of ACVRL1 in HMEC-1 endothelial cells leads to pathological angiogenesis with enhanced tube formation capacity, which is similar to the angiogenesis in vivo in patients with HHT2. The presented HMEC-1 cell-based system therefore has the potential to be deployed as an in vitro model for HHT2 studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482373/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Transcriptomic Analysis Identifies Predictive Biomarkers of Pathological Complete Response in Triple-negative Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We identified and validated a 15 gene signature associated with pCR in TNBC across independent cohorts. These findings offer a promising basis for improving patient stratification, guiding treatment decisions, and developing targeted therapies for NAC-resistant TNBC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482355/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augmenter of Liver Regeneration Enhances Hepatocellular Carcinoma Cell Growth Through COX-2-associated Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings connect ALR to the dysregulation of multiple oncogenic signaling pathways in HCC. Additionally, ALR may promote the proliferation of HCC by modulating the downstream pro-inflammatory factor COX-2, suggesting that ALR could serve as a potential therapeutic target for HCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering β-Galactosidase with Enhanced Catalytic and Transglycosylation Activity for GOS Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lactases are important glycoside hydrolases that have widespread applications in the food and pharmaceutical industries. However, the application of lactase is limited by its poor stability and transglycosylation activity. In this study, a Kluyveromyces lactis-derived lactase was engineered to improve its hydrolytic activity and transglycosylation. L764T and M2-3(L764T/V842G) had increased catalytic performance (k(cat)/K(M)) compared to Kl-β-Gal (2.9 and 4.8-fold increases, respectively) by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of disorders of consciousness based on source-level microstate characteristics under deep brain stimulation neuromodulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: High-frequency brain stimulation elicits a pronounced transition in spatiotemporal dynamics of microstates and induces global brain dynamic alterations centred on right temporal nodes, underscoring the pivotal role of the default mode network in consciousness circuits during the DBS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Theory of Magnetoroton Bands in Moiré Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The recent realization of Hofstadter spectra and fractional Chern insulators in moiré materials has introduced a new ingredient, a periodic lattice potential, to the study of quantum Hall phases. While the fractionalized states in moiré systems are expected to be in the same universality class as their counterparts in Landau levels, the periodic potential can have qualitative and quantitative effects on physical observables. Here, we examine how the magnetoroton collective modes of fractional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergent Gauge Field in Composite-Fermion Metals: A Large-Scale Microscopic Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Field theories of the composite-fermion (CF) metal model it as a Fermi sea of composite fermions coupled to an emergent gauge field. Within a random phase approximation, these theories predict that the Landau damping of the gauge field resulting from its coupling to the low-energy, long-wavelength CF particle-hole excitations modifies the electrons' density-density correlation function related to the static structure factor S(q) at wave vector q. This produces a nonanalytic correction ∝q^{3}lnq...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Source of Heralded Atom-Photon Entanglement for Quantum Networking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Communication in quantum networks suffers notoriously from photon loss. Resulting errors can be mitigated with a suitable measurement herald at the receiving node. However, waiting for a herald and communicating the measurement result back to the sender in a repeat-until-success strategy makes the protocol slow and prone to errors from false heralds such as detector dark counts. Here, we implement an entanglement herald at the sending node by employing a cascaded two-photon emission of a single...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Kardar-Parisi-Zhang Scaling to Soliton Proliferation in Josephson Junction Arrays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We propose Josephson junction arrays as realistic platforms for observing nonequilibrium scaling laws characterizing the Kardar-Parisi-Zhang (KPZ) universality class, and space-time soliton proliferation. Focusing on a two-chain ladder geometry, we perform numerical simulations for the roughness function. Together with analytical arguments, our results predict KPZ scaling at intermediate time scales, extending over sufficiently long timescales to be observable, followed by a crossover to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two-Dimensional Superconducting Diode Effect in Topological Insulator/Superconductor Heterostructure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The superconducting diode effect (SDE) is characterized by the nonreciprocity of Cooper-pair motion with respect to current direction. In three-dimensional (3D) materials, SDE results in a critical current that varies with direction, making the effect distinctly observable: the material exhibits superconductivity in one direction while behaving as a resistive metal in the opposite direction. However, in genuinely two-dimensional (2D) materials, the critical current density is theoretically zero,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Double Spacelike Collinear Limits from Multi-Regge Kinematics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We study scattering amplitudes and form factors in planar N=4 super Yang-Mills theory in the limit where two pairs of gluons become collinear. We find that, when the virtualities of both collinear pairs are spacelike, the collinear factorization of the amplitude involves a generalized splitting amplitude that correlates the two collinear directions, confirming a recent proposal in the literature. Remarkably, we find that our generalized splitting amplitude agrees with the Bern-Dixon-Smirnov...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482331/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Energy Spectrum of Ultrahigh-Energy Cosmic Rays across Declinations -90° to +44.8° as Measured at the Pierre Auger Observatory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The energy spectrum of cosmic rays above 2.5 EeV has been measured across the declination range -90°≤δ≤+44.8° using ∼310 000 events accrued at the Pierre Auger Observatory from an exposure of (104 900±3 100) km^{2} sr yr. No significant variations of energy spectra with declination are observed, after allowing or not for nonuniformities across the sky arising from the well-established dipolar anisotropies in the arrival directions of ultrahigh-energy cosmic rays. The instep feature in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical Injection and Detection of Long-Lived Interlayer Excitons in van der Waals Heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Interlayer excitons in semiconducting bilayers separated by insulating hexagonal boron nitride (h-BN) layers constitute a promising platform for investigation of strongly correlated bosonic phases. Here, we report an optical method for the generation and characterization of long-lived interlayer excitons. We confirm the presence of tightly bound interlayer excitons by measuring 1s and 2s intralayer excitons in each layer concurrently. Using a pump-probe technique, we find interlayer exciton...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uniting Quantum Processing Nodes of Cavity-Coupled Ions with Rare-Earth Quantum Repeaters Using Single-Photon Pulse Shaping Based on Atomic Frequency Comb]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present an architecture for remotely connecting cavity-coupled trapped ions via a quantum repeater based on rare-earth-doped crystals. The main challenge for its realization lies in interfacing these two physical platforms, which produce photons with a typical temporal mismatch of one or two orders of magnitude. To address this, we propose an efficient protocol that enables custom temporal reshaping of single-photon pulses while preserving purity. Our approach is to modify a commonly used...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gyrotropic Magnetic Effect in Metallic Chiral Magnets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We study the gyrotropic magnetic effect (GME), the low-frequency limit of optical gyrotropy, in metals and semimetals coupled to chiral spin textures. In these systems, the chiral spin texture which lacks inversion symmetry can imprint itself upon the electronic structure through Hund's coupling, leading to novel low-frequency optical activity. Using perturbation theory and numerical diagonalization of both relativistic and nonrelativistic models of conduction electrons coupled to spin textures,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Active Quantum Flocks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flocks of animals represent a prominent archetype of collective behavior in the macroscopic classical world, where the constituents, such as birds, concertedly perform motions and actions as if being one single entity. Here, we address the so far open question of whether flocks can also form in the microscopic world at the quantum level. For that purpose, we introduce the concept of active quantum matter by formulating a class of models of active quantum particles on a one-dimensional lattice....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Euler Buckling on Curved Surfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Euler buckling epitomizes mechanical instabilities: an inextensible straight elastic line in the plane buckles under compression when the compressive force F reaches a critical value F_{*}>0. But how does an elastic line buckle within a general curved surface? Here, we reveal that the classical instability changes fundamentally: by weakly nonlinear analysis of the buckling of an asymptotically short elastic line, we show that the critical force for the lowest buckling mode is F_{*}=0 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482318/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoscale Detection of Many-Body Entanglement via Multidimensional Correlation Imprinting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the nonequilibrium dynamics of isolated quantum many-body systems is a central goal of modern physics. Measuring genuine many-body correlations in quantum systems is central to this aim, while it remains a fundamental challenge for systems lacking individual addressability. We introduce a multidimensional correlation imprinting technique that encodes the structure of a many-body state into the temporal fluctuation spectrum of a local quantum probe. This allows direct measurement of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Universal Equilibration Condition for Heavy Quarks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kinetic equilibration at late times is physically required for heavy particles in a finite temperature medium. In Fokker-Planck dynamics, it is ensured by the Einstein relation between the drag and longitudinal momentum diffusion coefficients. However, in certain gauge field theories, this relation is violated at any nonzero heavy quark velocity. Recent work in strongly coupled N=4 SYM gauge theory shows that the Kolmogorov equation for the heavy quark phase space distribution (that reduces to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultimate Quantum Precision Limit at Colliders: Conditions and Case Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate whether collider experiments can reach the quantum limit of precision, defined by the quantum Fisher information (QFI), using only classical observables such as particle momenta. As a case study, we focus on the τ^{+}τ^{-} system and the decay channel τ→πν, which offers maximal spin-analyzing power and renders the decay a projective measurement. We develop a general framework to determine when collider measurements can, in principle, saturate the QFI in an entangled biparticle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Supercooled Goldstone Bosons at the QCD Chiral Phase Transition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We discuss a universal nonequilibrium enhancement of long-wavelength Goldstone bosons induced by quenches to the broken phase in Model G-the dynamical universality class of an O(4) antiferromagnet and the chiral phase transition in QCD. Scaling arguments for the coarsening dynamics describing the formation of the chiral condensate predict a parametric enhancement in the infrared spectra of Goldstone bosons, a prediction confirmed by stochastic simulations of the transition. The details of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482309/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sample-Half-Inserted Quantum Interferometer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum technologies have been widely recognized as unprecedented opportunities for ultrahigh precision metrology. As a celebrated example in modern quantum optics, the Hong-Ou-Mandel (HOM) interferometer is well known for enabling temporal resolutions on the attosecond scale. However, the relatively low Fisher information per trial in ordinary HOM measurements typically necessitates tens of thousands of repetitions to achieve such precision. Here, we propose and demonstrate a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First Evidence of Solar Neutrino Interactions on ^{13}C]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The SNO+ Collaboration reports the first evidence of ^{8}B solar neutrinos interacting on ^{13}C nuclei. The charged current interaction proceeds through ^{13}C+ν_{e}→^{13}N+e^{-} which is followed, with a 10 minute half life, by ^{13}N→^{13}C+e^{+}+ν_{e}. The detection strategy is based on the delayed coincidence between the electron and the positron. Evidence for the charged current signal is presented with a significance of 4.2σ. Using the natural abundance of ^{13}C present in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482298/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of Entanglement in a Cold Atom Analog of Cosmological Preheating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We observe entanglement between collective excitations of a Bose-Einstein condensate in a configuration analogous to particle production during the preheating phase of the early Universe. In our setup, the oscillation of the inflaton field is mimicked by the transverse breathing mode of a cigar-shaped condensate, which parametrically excites longitudinal quasiparticles with opposite momenta. After a short modulation period, we observe entanglement of these pairs that reveals the role played by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41482285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260103023736&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>