<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:23:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Aquamicrobium lusatiense NLF 2-7 as a Biocontrol Agent in Manure Composting: Effects on Odorous Compounds and Microbial Community Under Mesophilic Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial inoculation is a commonly applied approach in composting to enhance organic matter biodegradation and reduce odor emissions. However, the different characteristics of bacteria in terms of temperature can be considered to optimize their effect during different phases of composting. A mesophilic bacterium, namely Aquamicrobium lusatiense NLF 2-7, was evaluated to mitigate odor emissions and enhance the bacterial community under mesophilic composting. Two different treatments were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quinoidal Nitrogen-Bridged Terthiophene Acceptors Enabling Broadband Spectral Response Reaching 1.4 µm in SWIR Organic Photodetectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic photodetectors (OPDs) capable of detecting short-wavelength infrared (SWIR) radiation beyond the silicon cutoff (≈1.1 µm) have attracted significant attention due to their potential applications, such as machine vision, remote sensing, medical imaging, artificial intelligence, etc. However, designing organic materials with high sensitivity in the SWIR range remains challenging. Here, a new series of ultra-narrow bandgap small molecular acceptors, 5MTT-F, 5MCN-F, and 5MCN-Cl, based on a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spontaneous Wrinkle Collapse in Anisotropic Condensed Matter Predicted by Deep Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A deep learning framework is presented for predicting equilibrium nematic liquid crystal configurations, trained on datasets generated by a finite element Landau-de Gennes solver. The model, a 3D U-Net, accurately captures both global orientational order and local defect structures, providing predictions in milliseconds compared to conventional simulations. Reliability is validated by comparing simulated director fields with experimental observations on photoaligned wrinkle substrates fabricated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Mobility IZO Thin-Film Transistors Enabled by Precise Hydrogen Control Using a SiO<sub>2</sub>-Al<sub>2</sub>O<sub>3</sub> Supercycle via Plasma-Enhanced Atomic Layer Deposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A precise strategy to control hydrogen incorporation is essential for achieving high-performance oxide thin-film transistors (TFTs) as hydrogen plays a key role in tuning carrier concentration and passivating defect states. In this study, we report a top-gate oxide thin-film transistor structure that utilizes a plasma-enhanced atomic layer deposition (PEALD) supercycled SiO(2)-Al(2)O(3) gate insulator (GI), enabling precise hydrogen control through a tunable layering sequence. Hydrogen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288151/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refining Western Dementia-Risk Paradigms: Evidence From a Decade of the Korean Longitudinal Study on Cognitive Aging and Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the most rapidly aging nation, Korea offers a unique lens into the future of dementia, one of the most pressing global health challenges of the 21st century. The Korean Longitudinal Study on Cognitive Aging and Dementia (KLOSCAD), launched amid the country's rapid demographic transition, exemplifies how population-specific research can guide national policy and challenge universal assumptions in dementia science. More than a cohort study, KLOSCAD provides a methodological blueprint for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidic Chip-Based <em>In Vitro</em> Screening System of Synthetic Signal Peptides for Enhanced Monoclonal Antibody Production in Chinese Hamster Ovary Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Establishing an in vitro screening system for synthetic signal peptides in Chinese hamster ovary (CHO) cells is crucial, as selecting an appropriate signal peptide ensures efficient secretion and enhances therapeutic protein production. However, expanding library sizes to increase peptide diversity and improving screening efficiency by minimizing false positives remain significant challenges. In this study, we optimized a synthetic-biology-driven in vitro screening system by incorporating the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First genetic characterization and phylogenetic analysis of Okutama tick virus in a tick collected from a raccoon dog (Nyctereutes procyonoides) in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Okutama tick virus (OKTV) is a novel tick-borne RNA virus that has been reported in Japan and China. In the present study, an OKTV was detected in Haemaphysalis flava that had bitten a raccoon dog in South Korea by reverse transcription polymerase chain reaction using viral family-specific primers. Whole-genome sequencing revealed that the South Korean OKTV strain contains L and S segments with lengths of 6,529 and 1,890 nucleotides, respectively. Phylogenetic analyses revealed that OKTV strains...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computed tomography-based unsupervised clustering identifies clusters associated with progression free survival in clear cell renal cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Radiologic clustering using CT features enables non-invasive prognostic stratification of ccRCC. The C1 score derived from this approach may serve as a practical tool to guide surveillance and treatment decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A viral codon usage strategy enhances antigen production and protection in SFTSV mRNA vaccination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe Fever with Thrombocytopenia Syndrome Virus (SFTSV) is an emerging tick-borne pathogen with a high case-fatality rate and no approved vaccine, posing a global health threat. Human codon-optimized viral antigens can enhance mRNA vaccine efficacy by improving antigen expression but often requires high mRNA doses, increasing the risk of side effects. In this study, we introduce a codon optimization strategy using Herpes Simplex Virus 1 glycoprotein B (HSVgB) codon usage to develop an mRNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reversible Spin Splitting Effect in Altermagnetic RuO<sub>2</sub> Thin Films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spin-dependent anisotropic Fermi surfaces in altermagnets can give rise to nonrelativistic spin-charge conversion, known as the altermagnetic spin splitting effect (ASSE). While several studies have reported the inverse ASSE (IASSE) in altermagnetic RuO(2) thin films, its magnitude and sign relative to the spin Hall effect (SHE) remain controversial. Here, we demonstrate reversible IASSE in RuO(2) thin films by controlling the Néel vector orientation and accounting for the anisotropic transport...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288998/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptome Transformer: improving patient survival prediction via multitask learning of transcriptomic and clinical features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurate survival prediction is essential in healthcare as it guides treatment strategies and improves patient outcomes. While clinical features provide valuable prognostic information, they often fail to represent the molecular complexity of diseases. Transcriptomic data, which reflects gene expression patterns of tumors, present a complementary perspective to address this limitation. We introduce Transcriptome Transformer (TxT), a multitask learning framework that uses a transcriptome-centric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of 1H-pyrazol-1-yl benzenesulfonamide derivatives in alleviating inflammatory bowel disease via PI3K/Akt/mTOR signaling pathway in zebrafish models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence of inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) is increasing in developed nations, leading to a significant increase in healthcare expenses. It is characterized by chronic intestinal inflammation driven by excessive oxidative stress and dysregulated immune responses, leading to epithelial injury and impaired mucosal healing. Existing treatments have adverse effects, patient noncompliance issues, and high costs, emphasizing the need for new treatments. Pyrazole derivatives are promising...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Value of Precontrast Low Attenuation as a LI-RADS CT Ancillary Feature for Hepatocellular Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Current CT ancillary features (AFs) have limitations, as several AFs are more evident at MRI. Precontrast low attenuation may serve as a potential AF in the Liver Imaging Reporting and Data System (LI-RADS). Purpose To evaluate the diagnostic value of precontrast low attenuation at CT as an additional AF for diagnosing hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) and to assess its impact on LI-RADS diagnostic performance. Materials and Methods This retrospective study included adults at risk of HCC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Underweight and cardiovascular risk in Type 2 diabetes: a Korean nationwide study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Underweight status in T2DM patients is significantly associated with increased risk of CVDs, particularly in those severely underweight, exceeding the risks observed with obesity. These findings emphasize the need for dedicated guidelines for managing underweight T2DM patients to mitigate cardiovascular risks.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Level 2 Screening for Autism Spectrum Disorder in Young Children: Cross-Cultural Adaptation and Validation of the Behaviour Development Screening for Toddlers (BeDevel) in China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Chinese version of the BeDevel has demonstrated high reliability and effectiveness in screening for autism. Therefore, we recommend this validated C-BeDevel for Level 2 ASD screening in both clinical and maternal and child health settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[White Matter Hyperintensities in Relation to Cognition and Amyloid Burden in a South Korean Cohort With Subjective Cognitive Decline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that WMH and amyloid burden independently influence cognitive function in SCD patients. Notably, a significant association was observed between amyloid burden and regional WMH volumes. These findings underscore the distinct roles of WMH and amyloid burden in cognitive decline among individuals with SCD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288278/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Room-Temperature Electrical Coupling of PbS Colloidal Quantum Dots for High-Performance N-Type Thin-Film Thermoelectrics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Colloidal quantum dot (QD) films inherently exhibit a high Seebeck coefficient (α) and low thermal conductivity (κ), making them attractive for thermoelectric (TE) applications. However, achieving high electrical conductivity (σ) while preserving these advantages remains challenging due to limited interdot coupling and high-temperature treatments that compromise interdependent TE parameters. Herein, room-temperature inter-dot bridging of individual PbS QDs is demonstrated, leading to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Formation and Decay of Aqueous Fe(IV) during Fe(II) Ozonation under Acidic Conditions: Kinetics and Mechanistic Insights into pH-Dependent Behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aqueous Fe(IV) is a crucial oxidant in iron-mediated oxidation processes relevant to water purification and atmospheric aqueous systems; yet, its chemical behavior under environmentally relevant pH conditions remains poorly understood. This study elucidated the pH-dependent kinetics and mechanisms of Fe(IV) formation, self-decay, and secondary reactions during Fe(II) ozonation at pH 1.0-5.0. The Fe(II)-O(3) reaction involved Fe^(II)(H(2)O)(6)^(2+) and (H(2)O)(5)Fe^(II)(OH)^(+), generating Fe(IV)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital Twin-Driven Mechanical Degradation Diagnostics: Unraveling Microstructure Evolution of Silicon-based Lithium-Ion Battery Anodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Silicon is a promising anode material due to its high theoretical capacity, but its extreme volume change (>300%) during cycling leads to contact loss, electrode delamination, and crack propagation, ultimately compromising mechanical integrity. While operando imaging captures morphological evolution, it remains insufficient to resolve the coupled electrochemical, mechanical, and microstructural dynamics that govern degradation. Here, a microstructure-resolved digital twin model of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288140/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Choosing the One Who Sees You: Emotional Responsiveness as a Cue in Children's Help-Seeking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prior research has explored children's help-seeking tendencies in relation to the characteristics of help providers with a primary focus on the helper's competencies. In the current study, we propose that acknowledging a child's emotions without judgment, referred to as emotional validation, is another cue that guides children's help-seeking behavior. In Study 1, we surveyed mothers of children aged 3-6 years (N = 200) and found that their tendency to validate their children's emotions was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrugated-Surface Goethite Nanoparticles with Reduced Magnetization and Increased Surface Area for Enhanced <em>T</em><sub>1</sub> MRI Contrast Effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gadolinium (Gd)-based MRI contrast agents are commonly used for T(1) imaging but raise safety concerns, including nephrogenic systemic fibrosis and tissue buildup. Conventional iron oxide nanoparticles (IONPs), seen as safer options, often have residual magnetization, causing T(2) effects and negative contrast, complicating interpretation. These limitations highlight the need for safer, positive-contrast agents with optimized relaxivity profiles. Here, we report the development of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discrete Cation Exchange in Ag-Au-S Quantum Dots Using Reactivity Engineered Cation Precursors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tailoring precursor reactivity in colloidal nanocrystals (NCs) is a powerful strategy to achieve the uniformity. The gold precursor reactivity was engineered in multistep cation exchange reactions of Ag-Au-S quantum dots (QDs) through ligand coordination, metal-metal bonding, and steric effects, resulting in a series of discrete exchange pathways. With the conventional precursor HAuCl(4), Ag(2)S QDs undergo complete conversion to Au(2)S QDs via Ag(3)AuS(2) and AgAuS alloy QD intermediates;...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288095/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overcoming the energy-durability trade-off in aluminum foil anodes <em>via</em> hierarchical laminated grain boundaries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aluminum foil anodes offer a lightweight and scalable design by integrating the active material and current collector, but their practical deployment has been limited by rapid mechanical degradation from ∼100% volume expansion during lithiation. Previous strategies to stabilize Al foils have primarily relied on grain refinement, alloying, or prelithiation, which improve either mechanical robustness or electrochemical reversibility, but rarely both. Here, we introduce a fundamentally different...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal exposure to benzodiazepines, Z-drugs and long-term risk of neurodevelopmental disorders in offspring: nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prenatal BZRA exposure was associated with increased long-term risks of LNDDs in offspring, with evidence of dose-response and class-specific effects, and persistence in sibling analyses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of Multimodal Generative AI Models in Addressing Complex Dental Inquiries With Text, Images, and Analytical Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multimodal LLMs show potential in answering multimodal dental inquiries, though performance varies across models, with challenges in interpreting clinical scenarios, visual data, and terminology ambiguity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287924/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of a government-led employment program on the onset of depressive symptoms and suicidal ideation in older adults: A nationwide longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Structured government-supported employment may mitigate the risk of depressive symptoms and suicidal ideation in later life. These findings support the potential of senior employment programs as effective mental health promotion and suicide prevention strategies for aging populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polysaccharide Adjuvants as Innate Immune Trainers: Bridging Pattern Recognition Receptor (PRR) Activation and Metabolic Reprogramming for Synthetic Vaccine Design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The concept of trained immunity has redefined the understanding of innate immune memory and opened new opportunities for vaccine design. Polysaccharides, as naturally occurring pathogen-associated molecular patterns (PAMPs), can activate pattern recognition receptors (PRRs) and induce durable immunomodulatory effects. This review examines the historical context of microbial immunotherapy, beginning with Coley's toxin, and traces its evolution toward the rational use of polysaccharides as vaccine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Subcostal single-port versus intercostal multi-port robotic lobectomy for non-small cell lung cancer: a retrospective propensity score-matched cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Robotic lobectomy using the SP system showed favorable perioperative outcomes and mid-term results comparable to those of the MP group. However, further large-scale studies are required to validate our findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Advances in Nanoparticle-Based Antiretroviral Drug Delivery Systems for HIV Treatment and Prevention: A Comprehensive Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Though nanotechnology offers many advantages over the conventional system of medications, it also gives rise to many side effects and challenges that need to be rectified for its better application. This review discusses the status and limits of conventional drug treatment and the recent advancements and updated strategies in nano-therapeutics for HIV treatment and cures, along with the possible mechanism of action of nano-mediated drugs, clinical translational challenges, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of an Advanced Clinical Practice Nurse-Led Discharge Management and Education Program on Patient Outcomes in an Acute Medical Care Unit (ADIEU)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ADIEU program effectively reduced 30-day readmissions and increased satisfaction among healthcare providers and patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of probiotics on testosterone synthesis in the TM3 cell line]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings suggest that probiotic supplementation can modulate testosterone synthesis and improve mitochondrial functionality in Leydig cells. These results underscore the potential of probiotics as modulators of male reproductive health, with possible therapeutic applications in conditions such as male hypogonadism.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroimaging correlates and biomarker performance of a fully automated plasma p-tau217/Aβ42 ratio assay in a clinical cohort with Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Blood-based biomarkers offer scalable, non-invasive tools for Alzheimer's disease (AD) detection. We investigated the performance of plasma biomarkers associated with AD on the automated Beckman Coulter Access DxI 9000 analyzer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Outcomes of Long-Course Chemoradiotherapy vs. Short-Course Radiotherapy Followed by Consolidation Chemotherapy in Rectal Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SCRT with CCT demonstrated long-term oncologic outcomes and surgical safety comparable to those of LCRT, supporting its role as a viable alternative, particularly in resource-constrained healthcare settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in Health Expenditures for Chronic Disease Management: Hypertension, Diabetes Mellitus, and Dyslipidemia from 2013 to 2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The economic burden of managing chronic diseases is substantial, particularly for patients with multiple conditions or complications. Strengthening preventive care and integrated management strategies, alongside sustained financial support, is crucial for improving cost-efficiency in chronic disease care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Triple-Cuff versus Conventional Double-Cuff Double-Lumen Endobronchial Tube in Patients with Risk Factors for Tube Misdirection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Triple-cuff DLT was superior to conventional DLT in reducing DLT misdirection in short, obese females with narrow airways. Furthermore, it facilitated a faster intubation process and reduced airway complications, thereby enhancing patient safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287499/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes of Photodynamic Therapy for Choroidal Nevus with Subfoveal Fluid]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PDT demonstrated noticeable efficacy in reducing subfoveal fluid associated with choroidal nevus within 1 month of treatment. However, in some cases, the effect may be limited in long-term maintenance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mid-Term Outcomes of Acetabular Reconstruction Using a Rapid Prototyping Pelvic Model in Complex Total Hip Arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative planning using 3D prototyping pelvic models resulted in accurate cup positioning and stable outcomes in complex THA cases. Further studies with larger cohorts and longer follow-up are necessary to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial Circulating CD138 Predicts End-Stage Kidney Disease in Patients with Microscopic Polyangiitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that circulating CD138 measured at diagnosis has clinical utility as a biomarker for predicting future progression to ESKD in patients with MPA, and incorporating CD138 measurement at diagnosis may assist in identifying high-risk patients and guiding early therapeutic interventions in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Chest Imaging Alone Adequate for Diagnosing Interstitial Lung Disease in Microscopic Polyangiitis Based on the 2022 Criteria?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lung biopsy should be considered in highly selected patients who are MPO-positive without involvement of other organs. The decision to determine the need for lung biopsy should be made by a multidisciplinary team.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-Utility Analysis of Universal Lynch Syndrome Screening among Colorectal Cancer Patients in a Low-Middle-Income Country]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: All LS screening strategies for CRC patients are cost-effective within the Vietnamese health system, with germline testing being the most favorable. These findings support the inclusion of LS screening in health policies, even in resource-limited settings such as Vietnam.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drug-Coated Balloon-Based Intervention for De Novo Acute Myocardial Infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with de novo AMI, DCB-based PCI showed more favorable clinical outcomes after 2 years of follow-up compared to conventional DES-only PCI. DCB-based PCI may serve as a safe and effective alternative to DES-only PCI in carefully selected patients with satisfactory pre-dilation results (Impact of Drug-Coated Balloon Treatment in De Novo Coronary Lesion; NCT04619277).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: Correction of Funding in the Article "Growing Threat of Macrolide-Resistant <em>Mycoplasma pneumoniae</em> Among Children: What We Know and What We Need"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This corrects the article on p. e317 in vol. 40, PMID: 41218593.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal Satisfaction With Universal Postnatal Nurse Home Visiting Services and Its Covariates: A Cross-Sectional Survey of 22,040 Mothers With Young Children in Seoul, Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Mothers with young children who received universal postnatal nurse home visits reported high satisfaction. Increasing visit frequency and expanding mothers' group program opportunities could further improve satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Pelvic Insufficiency Fractures in Cervical Cancer Survivors: Using the National Claim Database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The incidence of PIFs in cervical cancer survivors was 1.0% in this national claim database study and it demonstrated that RT and older age were significantly associated with an increased risk of PIF. Our findings suggest that clinicians should be aware of the risk of PIF, especially in older patients who underwent RT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Trends in Hearing Aid Utilization in Korean Adults: A KNHANES-Based Study (2010-2022)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: HA adoption rates have nearly doubled over the past decade, with the greatest increases observed among financially supported individuals and those in their 70s. Expanding financial support eligibility may further enhance HA adoption, particularly among those with disabling but unsupported HL, ensuring broader access to hearing rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of Allplex™ MG &amp; AziR Assay for Detecting Macrolide-Resistant <em>Mycoplasma genitalium</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results show that the AziR assay can identify specific mutants in a single reaction and demonstrates high sensitivity and specificity for detecting macrolide resistant M. genitalium. Therefore, the AziR assay can be reliably used for MRT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Health Insurance Type and Survival Outcomes: Insight Into the Impact of Socioeconomic Disparities in the Postoperative Outcomes of Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients undergoing EVAR for AAA, insurance type was independently associated with postoperative AAA-related mortality, with Medical Aid patients experiencing worse outcomes. In contrast, no significant difference in AAA-related mortality was observed between insurance types among patients undergoing OAR. These findings highlight the need to improve postoperative care and address outcome disparities in vulnerable populations undergoing EVAR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systemic Lupus Erythematosus Presenting With Ascites: A Historical Cohort of Clinical Outcomes and Recurrence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SLE-related ascites is characterized by marked hypoalbuminemia. Low serum albumin and elevated CRP levels are predictors of recurrence, highlighting the need for close monitoring and tailored management in high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silver Nanowire-Based Stretchable Transparent Electrodes for Precise Biosignal Sensing from Small Skin Areas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large-area stretchable transparent electrodes (STEs) are essential in wearable biosignal sensors to achieve high signal-to-noise ratios (SNRs), primarily due to the low electrical conductivity of traditional stretchable materials. Silver nanowires (AgNWs) offer excellent conductivity and transparency; however, their poor mechanical compliance restricts their use in stretchable electronics. To overcome this challenge, we developed an STE by creating a grid-like AgNW network using a bar-coating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aspirin and HCC risk in MASLD: Nationwide cohort study with genetic risk analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Findings from both population-based and genetic analyses suggest a possible protective association between aspirin use and HCC in patients with MASLD, which warrants further validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287437/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Up-to-date concepts and procedures in shoulder instability: a comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shoulder instability, particularly anterior instability, remains a significant clinical and socioeconomic burden, especially in young, active populations. Recent advancements have refined our understanding of critical and subcritical bone loss, bipolar lesions, and dynamic stabilization concepts. This review synthesizes current evidence by analyzing recent clinical studies, biomechanical research, and technological developments related to the management of anterior shoulder instability. While...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-assisted measurement of humeral version: a radiation-sparing alternative to whole-humerus computed tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that ultrasound-assisted measurement combined with proximal humerus CT is a reliable and accurate alternative to whole-humerus CT, reducing radiation exposure and cost. Level of evidence: III.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterogeneously Catalyzed Depolymerization of Polyurethane for the Efficient Recovery of Polyol and Dianiline]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyurethane (PU) recycling remains a significant challenge owing to its inherent stability and crosslinked nature. Conventional chemical recycling methods, including solvolysis and catalytic hydrogenation, often rely on homogeneous catalysts with limited product recoveries. Herein, we report a novel approach incorporating heterogeneous catalysis with alcoholysis, utilizing commercially available zinc oxide and tert-butyl alcohol (TBA) for the efficient depolymerization of both model and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence of Chronic Kidney Disease According to Steatotic Liver Disease and Its Subclassifications: A Longitudinal Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SLD was linked to a higher incidence of CKD, with the CKD risk increasing sequentially from cryptogenic SLD to MASLD and MetALD. Advanced fibrosis in each SLD subclassification further increases the risk of CKD. Stratifying SLD according to metabolic dysfunction, significant alcohol intake, and fibrosis severity may help identify and monitor individuals at high risk of developing CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vertical Self-Rectifying Memristive Arrays for Page-Wise Parallel Logic and Arithmetic Processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Logic-in-memory (LIM) architectures are explored to address the data transfer bottleneck of conventional von Neumann architectures by integrating computation directly within memory arrays. Among various candidates, memristor-based LIM systems have gained significant attention due to their non-volatile switching behavior and compatibility with dense integration. In this work, a page-wise LIM architecture is implemented using a 3D vertical resistive random-access memory array composed of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Trends in Cytomegalovirus IgG Seropositivity in the Adult Population of Korea: a Cross-Sectional Study and Literature Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings provide the most up-to-date estimate of CMV IgG seropositivity in the Korean adult population. Because of lower seropositivity in younger adults, continued monitoring and further education are essential for CMV control and prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of patients repeatedly presenting to the emergency department for self-harm injuries: a 6-year retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with repetitive self-harm were more likely to be female, to use cutting or stabbing as methods, and to have psychiatric issues, and they showed a lower in-hospital mortality rate than those without prior episodes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287027/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative feasibility of reasoning and non-reasoning large language models for gynecologic cancer emergency care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both GPT-4o and o3-mini-high are feasible tools for emergency care of patients with gynecologic cancer. GPT-4o may provide advantages, reflecting the pattern-based structure of emergency care in this domain. LLM selection should be based on the domain-specific medical knowledge required rather than on the reasoning status or model version. Further prospective multicenter studies are warranted to confirm our findings as well as clinical effectiveness of LLMs in gynecologic cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical usability and functional outcomes of a lightweight robotic orthosis (HKAFO) in chronic stroke patients with hemiplegic gait: a pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286918/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domain generalization for voice-based cognitive impairment detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The adapted DDAIG framework effectively reduced center-specific learning, enhancing the model's ability to generalize cognitive impairment classifications across different centers. These findings suggest the role of domain generalization in developing reliable AI diagnostic tools for cognitive disorder detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric properties of the heart failure caregiver burden questionnaire among Korean family caregivers: a methodological study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of an app for self-efficacy of patients with cancer through tailored information delivery and coaching: protocol for a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Though numerous mobile apps have been developed to support patients with cancer, there is no comprehensive app that integrates evidence-based medical information, schedule management, lifestyle modification tools, psychological support, and access to appropriate community resources, to address the needs of patients with cancer. This paper presents a protocol for a randomized controlled trial to evaluate the efficacy of a newly developed app designed specifically for patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of intracranial hemorrhage using ultralow-dose brain computed tomography with deep learning reconstruction versus conventional-dose computed tomography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ultralow-dose CT with DLR is not inferior to conventional-dose CT in terms of image quality and diagnostic performance for the detection of intracranial hemorrhage, while achieving an approximate 87.7% reduction in radiation dose.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurodevelopmental delays in children born after medically assisted reproduction: a national population cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Children conceived via IUI or IVF demonstrated a modest but significant increase in screen-positive neurodevelopmental delay compared with those conceived spontaneously. These findings highlight the need for neurodevelopmental monitoring in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral Health Associated With Sleep Quality Among Korean Adults: A Nationwide Cross-Sectional Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasonic-driven grain uniformity of commercially pure nickel in continuous heat input directed energy deposition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-enabled inverse design of bioinspired layered composite structures with maximum auxetic performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Layered composite structures inspired by biological tissues can exhibit out-of-plane negative Poisson's ratio, but identifying layups that maximize auxetic performance is challenging in high-dimensional designs. Here, we introduce an inverse design framework that searches for laminate layups with minimum Poisson's ratio. The approach combines multi-start resampling with machine learning-guided clustering to map layup families across layer numbers. Analytical relations from laminate mechanics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286364/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling the metastatic tumor microenvironment: a co-culture platform of lung cancer and blood vessel organoids for drug evaluation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor cell-vasculature interactions play a crucial role in lung cancer progression and metastasis; however, traditional cell culture models rarely capture these complex dynamics. We developed a vascularized lung cancer organoid (VLCO) model by coculturing lung cancer organoids (LCOs) with blood vessel organoids (BVOs) to recreate the tumor-vasculature niche in a three-dimensional in vitro system. During coculture, LCOs migrated along BVO-formed vascular networks and invaded vessel-like...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a machine learning model to diagnose pediatric lower respiratory tract infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective cohort study aimed to develop and validate a two-step machine learning (ML) approach for diagnosing pediatric community-acquired lower respiratory tract infections (CA-LRTIs) and distinguishing bacterial from viral pathogens to aid decision-making regarding antibiotic use. We employed five ML algorithms for model development and two testing sets for model evaluation. Patients < 19 years presenting with symptoms suggestive of CA-LRTIs between January 2005 and November 2023 were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of age and place of fall on the risk of hip fracture in older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hip fractures in older adults are a significant health issue, linked to high mortality, disability, and socioeconomic costs. This study examined the effects of age and place of injury on hip fractures from falls in older adults using data from the Emergency Department-based Injury In-Depth Surveillance (EDIIS) database in South Korea. Patients aged 65 years or older who visited 23 emergency departments from 2011 to 2020 were included. Among 170,095 older adults who visited the ED after a fall,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling the nexus of natural radioactivity and radio-ecotoxicological effects in Bengal Basin: recent findings and way forwards]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Elevated levels of naturally occurring radionuclides (^(238)U, ^(226)Ra, ^(232)Th, and ^(40)K) present significant global environmental and public health challenges due to their increasing radio-ecotoxicological effects. Numerous localized studies have examined natural radioactivity within the Bengal Basin (BB), but comprehensive regional-scale assessments remain limited. This review synthesizes thirty years of research to provide a thorough understanding of radionuclide contamination levels,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286223/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing IIoT security through blockchain-enabled workload analysis in fog computing environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robots and software are utilized in industrial automation to run machinery and processes in a variety of sectors. Numerous applications incorporate machine learning, the Internet of Things (IoT), and other methods to offer clever features that enhance user experience. Businesses and individuals can successfully accomplish both commercial and noncommercial requirements with the help of such technologies. Due to high risk as well as inefficiency of traditional procedures, organisations are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286215/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Studying rare variant polygenic risk scores using whole exome sequencing and imputed genotype data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rare variant polygenic scores (rvPRS) are developed to improve phenotype prediction, yet a standardized construction protocol remains unavailable. We aim to establish an optimal rvPRS protocol using whole exome sequencing (WES) and imputed genotype (IMP) data from 502,369 UK Biobank participants and to evaluate its predictive performance compared to common variant PRS (cvPRS). rvPRS models are constructed for 13 binary and 5 quantitative traits using gene-burden and single-SNP associations and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stage-related changes of bone density and volume in treatment of medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective study evaluated changes in lesion bone density and volume in medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw (MRONJ) using cone-beam computed tomography (CBCT) at different disease stages following conservative and surgical treatment. Additionally, the study analyzed the correlations between these changes and influencing factors. A total of 54 patients (mean [SD] age, 75.43 [7.44] years) diagnosed with stage 0, 1, 2, or 3 MRONJ, according to the American Association of Oral and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based personalized training models for optimizing marathon performance through pyramidal and polarized training intensity distributions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Training intensity distribution significantly influences marathon performance, yet individual variability in training responses remains poorly understood. This study compared pyramidal and polarized training methodologies using machine learning to identify optimal personalization strategies. A total of 120 recreational marathon runners were randomly assigned to 16-week pyramidal (n = 60) or polarized (n = 60) training interventions. Machine learning models analyzed individual responses using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286008/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shifts in emergency physicians' attitudes toward large language model-based documentation: a pre- and post-implementation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) can assist physicians in writing medical notes more efficiently. This study evaluates whether using an LLM assistant for writing emergency department discharge notes can reduce doctors' workload and addresses concerns regarding the incorporation of AI in medical practice. Eight emergency doctors with an average experience of 12 years participated in our study. We surveyed them prior to, post 3 days, and post 5 weeks of their LLM usage. The results showed that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[School-level variation in physical fitness outcomes among children and adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Physical fitness is one of the key indicators of overall health in youth and plays an important role in decreasing the risk of a number of chronic conditions. There has been limited research on the relationship between school-level factors and young people's physical fitness, with no studies examining school-level variation in physical fitness outcomes for children and adolescents in Croatian schools. The primary aim of this article is to examine school-level variation in a number of health and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving retinal vessel assessment precision by integrating deep learning with interactive editing and graphical modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present the SEoul Retinal Vessel Assessment Library (SERVAL), a novel software platform for precise quantitative measurement of vascular structures in fundus images. SERVAL integrates deep learning-based automatic artery and vein mask initialization, subpixel vessel centerline and boundary refinement, and interactive editing tools within a user-friendly graphical interface. From the refined artery and vein delineations, it enables accurate computation of a wide range of vessel assessment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of toothbrushing on aesthetic and mechanical properties of hydrophilic antibacterial coating materials for orthodontic clear retainers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to analyze the aesthetic, mechanical, and antibacterial properties of clear retainer materials with an antibacterial coating. Specifically, it evaluates whether the coating can retain its effectiveness after repeated toothbrushing by assessing material integrity, surface roughness, and bacterial adhesion in vitro. Four types of 1.0-mm thermoplastic sheets widely used in orthodontic clear retainers were tested: PUL (Magicfoil R, Osstem, Korea), PUC (Magicfoil R with a hydrophilic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285891/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural and functional insights into internal domain replacement in SpCas9 for protein engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The CRISPR-Cas9 system has emerged as a powerful tool for precise genome editing, with ongoing research focused on enhancing its reliability and expanding its versatility. One effective strategy involves the integration of foreign functional domains into Cas9 to confer new capabilities. However, successful integration requires identification of insertion sites that preserve the protein's structural integrity and function. In this study, we identified a C-terminal region of Streptococcus pyogenes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41285890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Total Synthesis of Trigocherrins A and C]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Trigocherrins A (1) and C (2), isolated from an endangered tropical plant in New Caledonia, belong to a rare class of daphnane diterpenoid orthoesters with an unusual conjugated dichloroalkene moiety. Compound 1 displays antiviral activity against the chikungunya and dengue viruses. The fused 5/7/6-membered rings (ABC-rings) of 1 and 2 possess dichloromethylene, hydroxymethyl, and isopropenyl groups as the branched carbon chains, and epoxy, hydroxy, alkanoate, and C9,12,14-orthobenzoate groups...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of endoscopic response evaluation after induction chemotherapy for determining treatment strategies in esophageal cancer: a post hoc analysis of the CROC trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: High interobserver concordance supports standardizing endoscopic evaluation criteria. Furthermore, an uncertain response may indicate the suitability of dCRT because of favorable outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular adverse events associated with denosumab versus zoledronic acid in patients with breast cancer: a propensity score overlap weighted analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with breast cancer bone metastases, denosumab was associated with lower risks of cardiovascular events, fractures, and mortality than those with zoledronic acid.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288760/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroptosis and cancer: when iron turns against tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Ferroptosis is an iron-dependent form of regulated necrosis driven by unchecked lipid peroxidation. Its relevance to cancer biology has become increasingly evident. Our long-standing ferric nitrilotriacetate (Fe-NTA) rat model exemplifies how chronic Fenton chemistry induces DNA damage, genomic instability, and selection of ferroptosis-resistant malignant clones, underscoring the central role of iron in carcinogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explainable AI in nuclear medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We conclude that explanations are likely required when a black box AI tool undertakes tasks that users cannot perform or validate themselves. If the user can verify outputs manually, documented reliability and accuracy may suffice, but explainability can still add value when outputs are uncertain or errors occur. More generally, close collaboration among physicians, AI developers, and other stakeholders is crucial to ensure that AI tools are trustworthy and useful in clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catheter Ablation Outcomes and Life Expectancy in Very Elderly Atrial Fibrillation Patients: The REHEALTH AF Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The REHEALTH AF Study (Registry for Evaluating Healthy Life Expectancy and Long-Term Outcomes After Catheter Ablation of Atrial Fibrillation in the Very Elderly) study is the first prospective comparison of ablation vs nonablation in patients aged ≥80 years with AF. Although ablation improved functional and structural outcomes, its prognostic benefit was limited without adjustment but emerged after multivariable correction. Ablation may offer meaningful advantages in well-selected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288543/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of Titin-Associated Electrocardiography Features in Dilated Cardiomyopathy Using Conventional and Deep Neural Network Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Conventional ECG and DNN analyses demonstrated similar good predictive performance in distinguishing TTNtv from gene-elusive DCM patients, emphasizing their potential as clinical tools to guide targeted genetic testing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gate-Tunable Ionothermoelectric Cooling in a Solid-State Nanopore]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient heat dissipation at the nanoscale remains a major challenge for high-performance microelectronics. Here, we demonstrate a proof-of-concept approach for ionothermoelectric cooling, the ionic analogue of the Peltier effect, using gate-tunable solid-state nanopores integrated with nanoscale thermocouples. By integrating a nanoscale thermocouple directly adjacent to a gate-tunable solid-state nanopore, we quantitatively map local thermal responses driven by voltage-induced ion transport....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288501/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the power of microbes: the mud-battery project for high school students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microorganisms are expected to play vital roles in the development of sustainable societies, but this idea is still poorly understood by the general public. In addition, it would also be important for the future development of microbiology that young students understand this idea and become interested in microorganisms. To this end, we have initiated a citizen-science project known as "the mud-battery project," in which junior high and high school students examine the ability of bacteria in mud...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dielectric behavior of propylene carbonate solutions with LiPF6, LiClO4, and LiBF4. II. Molecular dynamics simulation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Propylene carbonate (PC) solutions with three different lithium salts (LiPF6, LiClO4, and LiBF4) were investigated by combining experimental dielectric relaxation spectroscopy (DRS) and molecular dynamics (MD) simulations. Although DRS spectra include rich information regarding microscopic structure and local dynamics in solution systems, the interpretation of spectra is not straightforward and needs complementary analysis. In this work, we applied MD simulations to the PC solutions and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288345/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dielectric behavior of propylene carbonate solutions with LiPF6, LiClO4, and LiBF4. I. Dielectric relaxation and Raman spectroscopic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dielectric relaxation spectroscopy (DRS) is an evolving technique for extracting molecular-level information on orientational polarization and dielectric relaxation in liquids. It reveals fundamental properties, such as permittivity and dipole moments, essential for characterizing electrolyte solutions. However, the use of DRS for electrolyte analysis often faces challenges, such as low-frequency measurement limits, and difficulties in interpreting and assigning complex overlapping relaxation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A systems immunology analysis of Alzheimer's disease reveals an age- and environmental exposure-independent disturbance in B cell maturation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Alzheimer's disease is a severe neurodegenerative disorder, with multifactorial mechanisms of disease development and progression. Evidence from genetic association studies, animal models, and clinical investigation suggests a neuroimmunological component to disease, with links to the peripheral immune system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287979/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lifting the veil: probing altered visual perception in derealization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[During an acute episode of depersonalization/derealization (DP/DR), people report a complex and idiosyncratic change in their perceptual experience. Specifically, derealisation describes the experience of detachment from the external world and altered visual perception in which the surroundings look faded, foggy, or dream-like. Whilst some have argued that there may not be genuine perceptual changes in derealization, this proposal is yet to be tested empirically. Thus, we set out to investigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287817/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Near real-time data on the human neutralizing antibody landscape to influenza virus to inform vaccine-strain selection in September 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The hemagglutinin of human influenza virus evolves rapidly to erode neutralizing antibody immunity. Twice per year, new vaccine strains are selected with the goal of providing maximum protection against the viruses that will be circulating when the vaccine is administered ~8-12 months in the future. To help inform this selection, here we quantify how the antibodies in recently collected human sera neutralize viruses with hemagglutinins from contemporary influenza strains. Specifically, we use a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287634/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microphase water control utilizing highly hydrophilic anion-exchange ionomers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In anion-exchange membrane water electrolysis (AEMWE), the dry-cathode condition can simplify balance-of-plant systems and improve hydrogen purity, but it is prone to cathode drying, which leads to polarization loss. By optimizing the hydrophilicity of ionomers, the water uptake and retention capacity of the catalyst layer can be enhanced. Here, a three-dimensional (3D) ionomer, Pip(BPF-BPN)/Trip-x is developed, for AEMWE, a promising green hydrogen technology. The ionomer integrates triptycene...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pentoxifylline dose finding trial in preterm neonates with suspected late onset sepsis (PTX-trial)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In this dose-finding trial for PTX in preterm neonates, our findings reveal no discernible clinical advantage associated with either increasing or decreasing the PTX dosage. The relatively high variability in sepsis severity and patients' post-natal ages increase the uncertainty of our findings, but the standardly used dosage of 30 mg/kg/day (5 mg/kg/h for 6 h) has consistently demonstrated safe tolerability without any reported severe adverse events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of Quinoxalinyl Radical Produced by Muonium Addition to 1,2-Diisocyanobenzene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Radical isocyanide (isonitrile) insertion reactions have advanced considerably, yet the nature of the underlying paramagnetic intermediates remains poorly understood. We previously studied the isocyanide insertion of muonium (Mu), a light isotope of hydrogen, into 2-isocyano-1,1'-biphenyls by transverse field muon spin rotation (TF-µSR) spectroscopy and characterized the resulting radical, which was identified as an imidoyl radical. The cyclized product was not observed on the microsecond...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gold Quantum Needles Synthesized by Thermal-Induced, One-Dimensional Oligomerization of Au<sub>24</sub>(SC<sub>2</sub>H<sub>4</sub>Ph)<sub>20</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gold quantum needles (AuQNs), which have double-pointed cores Au(1)-(Au(3))(2+4n)-Au(1) (n = 1, 2, 3, etc.) protected by 2-phenylethanethiolate (PET) ligands, have attracted significant attention due to their unique NIR-responsive properties. Herein we demonstrate that these AuQNs can be synthesized through the long-term heating of a highly concentrated solution of Au(24)(PET)(20) without the use of directing templates. Additionally, we obtained two unprecedented series of AuQNs that exhibit...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in national-level school feeding policy objectives worldwide: Japan and multiple countries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Public policy denotes a government's formal intent to address specific issues in pursuit of defined objectives. The vision and mission of school feeding have progressively expanded. This study examined school feeding policy objectives across multiple countries, drawing on data from the Global Survey of School Meal Programs, and identified 23 relevant policies. The objectives were classified into five domains: health and nutrition, education, social protection, agriculture, and other areas. Japan...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between the frequency of treating foreign patients and the cultural competency of Japanese healthcare professionals: a mixed-method study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Treating foreign patients is associated with high motivation and skill but low attitude scores among J-HCPs, due to systemic challenges. Providing reliable interpretation services, offering practical cultural competence training, and strengthening institutional support may help reduce these challenges.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Training communication skills in a multiuser medical virtual reality simulation: a qualitative, observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multiuser VR simulation shows certain possibilities for CST in medical undergraduate simulations. Recommendations on the contextual design of VR simulations, however, need to be taken into account to safeguard the focus of attention and flow of CST.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An enhanced nutrition support system is associated with greater adequacy of enteral nutrition in long-term ICU patients: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Implementation of an enhanced nutrition support system was associated with higher EN adequacy, higher day-14 EN and oral intake rates, and lower CVC use in long-term ICU patients, without increasing gastrointestinal intolerance. These findings support the adoption of multidisciplinary, protocol-based nutrition support as a standard approach for ICU patients at high nutritional risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41287024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medial plica is associated with progression of medial meniscus extrusion in middle-aged persons with Kellgren-Lawrence grade 0: data from the osteoarthritis initiative]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In middle-aged persons with K/L grade 0, the presence of medial plica-particularly higher-grade lesions-was associated with progression of MME and cartilage loss, and grade ≥ 2 lesions were additionally associated with radiographic progression of knee OA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survey of perioperative treatment in muscle-invasive bladder cancer using Japanese hospital-based claims database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of clinical practices during the transitional and young adult phases between patients with oligoarticular/polyarticular juvenile idiopathic arthritis and those with rheumatoid arthritis in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite an overlap in age, patients with JIA and RA exhibit distinct disease characteristics and therapeutic patterns. These differences underscore the need to expand approved treatment options for JIA, promote equitable access to biologics, and strengthen transitional care frameworks. Further research is warranted to explore long-term outcomes, reproductive health considerations, and socioeconomic barriers that influence treatment continuity in young adults with childhood-onset...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impaired sensitivity to thyroid hormones is associated with frailty in older patients with cardiometabolic disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A noninvasive test for human prion disease using hair roots and scalp]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invasive tests like cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) examination are highly effective for diagnosing human prion disease (HPD). Real-time quaking-induced conversion (RT-QuIC) CSF assay demonstrates 80-90% sensitivity for HPD diagnosis. To establish a minimally invasive diagnostic approach, we evaluated RT-QuIC testing on hair root and scalp samples. We collected scalp samples from 22 HPD and 5 non-HPD patients during pathological examinations and analyzed them using RT-QuIC assay and neuropathological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the public dissemination and open sourcing of ultrasound resources, datasets and deep learning models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound data is relatively under-utilized in machine learning applied to medical imaging research when compared to other imaging modalities. Towards rectifying this, this paper (and the associated webpage) catalogs and assesses the usability of publicly available ultrasound datasets and models. Datasets were categorized and ranked using an original dataset quality score, SonoDQS. The models were scored using our model quality score, SonoMQS. We identified 72 public ultrasound datasets...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to the Letter to the Editor: Cardiac computed tomography imaging in atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Alzheimer's therapeutic Lecanemab attenuates Aβ pathology by inducing an amyloid-clearing program in microglia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Controversies over anti-amyloid immunotherapies underscore the need to elucidate their mechanisms of action. Here we demonstrate that Lecanemab, a leading anti-β-amyloid (Aβ) antibody, mediates amyloid clearance by activating microglial effector functions. Using a human microglia xenograft mouse model, we show that Lecanemab significantly reduces Aβ pathology and associated neuritic damage, while neither fragment crystallizable (Fc)-silenced Lecanemab nor microglia deficiency elicits this effect...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A direct comparison of simultaneously recorded scalp, around-ear and in-ear EEG for neural selective auditory attention decoding to speech]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current assistive hearing devices, such as hearing aids and cochlear implants, lack the ability to adapt to the listener's focus of auditory attention, limiting their effectiveness in complex acoustic environments like cocktail party scenarios where multiple conversations occur simultaneously. Neuro-steered hearing devices aim to overcome this limitation by decoding the listener's auditory attention from neural signals, such as electroencephalography (EEG). While many auditory attention decoding...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Dependent Gut Microbiota Dynamics and Their Association with Male Life-History Traits in Drosophila melanogaster]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Growing evidence suggests that the gut microbiota is closely intertwined with life-history evolution in a wide range of species, including well-studied model organisms like Drosophila melanogaster. Although recent studies have explored the relationship between gut microbiota and female life-history, the link between gut microbiota and male life-history remains relatively unexplored. In this study, we investigated how gut microbiota changes with male age as well as the associations between gut...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inherent surface heterogeneity of carbon black by one-shot structure analysis using hybrid reverse molecular dynamics simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Analyses of the surface properties of carbon materials have been limited despite their importance for adsorption, catalysis, and electrochemical reactions. In this study, the bulk and surface structures of carbon black were comprehensively evaluated by one-shot structure analysis using the hybrid reverse molecular dynamics (HRMD) simulations, in which X-ray or electron diffraction was evaluated by the simulations. The one-shot structure analysis agreed with observations obtained by other...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SINE compounds activate exportin 1 degradation through an allosteric mechanism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overexpression of exportin 1 (XPO1/CRM1) in cancer cells mislocalizes numerous cancer-related nuclear export cargoes. Covalent selective inhibitors of nuclear export (SINEs), including the cancer drug selinexor, restore proper nuclear localization by blocking XPO1-cargo interaction. These inhibitors also induce XPO1 degradation through the Cullin-RING E3 ligase (CRL) substrate receptor ASB8. Here we present cryo-electron microscopy structures revealing ASB8 binding to a cryptic XPO1 site that is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive study of cognitive control in healthy aging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings show that changes in cognitive control subcomponents follow different onsets and trajectories, highlighting the importance of including them in cognitive aging research. While some cognitive control functions decline, others seem to be preserved or even improve with age. Longitudinal follow-up studies can help uncover inter- and intra-individual changes in subcomponents with aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hepatic vein-derived factors may affect pulmonary arteriovenous malformations after single ventricle palliation by modulating vascular cell behavior]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary and asymmetric tapered bent mid-infrared waveguide arrays for subwavelength-pitch integration and crosstalk minimization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper delivers the first report of a mid-infrared (MIR) waveguide array design that employs complementary and asymmetric tapered Euler-shaped bends. These provide greater fabrication flexibility to achieve subwavelength-pitch integration while reducing crosstalk to below 30 dB across the 3.1 [Formula: see text]m to 3.6 [Formula: see text]m wavelength range. Unlike previous designs, which maintained constant waveguide widths, the Euler waveguide bends are characterized by asymmetric and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mannitol versus furosemide for prevention of cisplatin-induced nephrotoxicity in a multicenter retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cisplatin (cis-diamminedichloroplatinum [CDDP]) is a widely used anticancer drug with a significant risk of nephrotoxicity. This study aimed to compare the nephroprotective effects of mannitol and furosemide as forced diuretics in patients receiving CDDP-based chemotherapy. This multicenter retrospective study analyzed 472 patients with cancer receiving CDDP (≥ 60 mg/m²) with either mannitol or furosemide as forced diuretics. Patient characteristics were balanced using inverse probability...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes and prognostic significance of endoscopic laryngo-pharyngeal surgery for head and neck squamous cell carcinoma: a retrospective analysis of 111 cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ELPS provides favorable mid- to long-term outcomes and can be safely applied to selected patients, including those with prior CRT. Tumor size and lymphatic invasion are key prognostic factors. These findings support ELPS as a minimally invasive, function-preserving treatment option for superficial HNSCC with careful patient selection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41286019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The design of a novel Pd-nanoparticle-encapsulating covalent organic framework-based catalyst for solvent-free CO<sub>2</sub> conversion at ambient pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41289004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The conversion of CO(2) into value-added products offers an economically viable approach to CO(2) capture, contributing to cost reduction in the overall process while aiding in the mitigation of global warming. However, this transformation requires highly effective catalysts due to the thermodynamic and kinetic stability of CO(2). In this study, we explore a new class of covalent organic framework (COF) as a potential catalytic material, leveraging its unique framework chemistry to enhance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41289004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceived Vulnerability and Parents' Views on Intimate Relationships: Adults With Intellectual Disabilities Versus Their Siblings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41289001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Findings highlight the nuanced challenges parents face due to societal norms, communication barriers and their adult child's cognitive and adaptive functioning-all of which contribute to heightened perceptions of vulnerability. These perceptions, in turn, shape the level and nature of parental involvement in their adult child's romantic and intimate relationships. This study emphasises the need for parental support, resources and programming to facilitate safe and fulfilling romantic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41289001/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Near-infrared imaging of intraperitoneal ovarian cancer enhanced by BrCy112 in a dual mode (MR and NIR), dual-Gd nanoparticle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41289000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual-Mode-Dual-Gd (DMDG) nanoparticles incorporating BrCy112, a brominated carbocyanine dye, were investigated for their potential in magnetic resonance (MR) and optical imaging of intraperitoneal ovarian tumors in an animal model two days post-intravenous injection. DMDG nanoparticles were synthesized using either BrCy112 or indocyanine green (ICG) as the near-infrared (NIR) fluorophore, combined with positive contrast MR imaging agents. The optical properties of these fluorophores were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41289000/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extreme Heat, Social Factors, and Mortality Among California Veterans With Cardiometabolic Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study of California veterans with common cardiometabolic diseases, EHEs were significantly associated with mortality. These results suggest that the VA should develop EHE risk-mitigating interventions to protect veterans, particularly those at greatest risk, from heat-related mortality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proton Pump Inhibitor Use and Survival in Patients With Newly Diagnosed Glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this meta-analysis of patients with newly diagnosed glioblastoma, PPI use was associated with inferior survival outcomes. These findings suggest that PA-PPI use should be discouraged in patients with glioblastoma, since alternative agents are available and a detrimental effect cannot be excluded. Translational research studies should explore whether PPI-induced activity of ALDH mediates the potential adverse effects of PPI in glioblastoma. .]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in trans-scale RNA regulation and imaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Use of Ruxolitinib Cream Results in Economic Benefits Compared with Dupilumab in Treatment of Patients with Atopic Dermatitis Meeting Severity Thresholds for Systemic Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This model demonstrates that 1.5% ruxolitinib cream reduces treatment costs by over 80% compared to dupilumab in patients with moderate AD eligible for systemic therapy. Combined with comparable efficacy, these savings position ruxolitinib cream as a cost-effective treatment option.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workplace health promotion for healthy aging: a randomized controlled trial within the Semmelweis-EUniWell Workplace Health Promotion Model Program comparing email-based and face-to-face motivational interviewing to increase step count]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the aging population in Europe, particularly Hungary, unhealthy aging is emerging as a growing public health challenge. Physical inactivity is a modifiable risk factor for age-related diseases and remains highly prevalent. Increasing daily physical activity is a key strategy for extending health span. Step-count-based interventions, including motivational interviewing and email-based feedback, have been shown to promote physical activity, but direct comparisons of these approaches in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kindergarten predictors of dyslexia pathways in Hebrew: a 5-year longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While dyslexia is often considered a uniformly persistent condition, research has identified two additional developmental pathways: resolving and late-emerging dyslexia. Yet, most studies have focused on Western languages, and only a few have examined kindergarten predictors of these pathways, with morphological awareness largely overlooked. This five-year longitudinal study examined dyslexia pathways and their kindergarten predictors, including morphological awareness, in Hebrew-a Semitic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel oleanolic acid derivatives containing piperazine pyrimidine moieties: design, synthesis, and antimicrobial activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Natural products are main sources of new chemical entities for pesticide discovery and also important modification substrates for activity enhancement. In this study, a series of novel oleanolic acid derivatives containing piperazine pyrimidine structures were designed and synthesized. Multi NMR and high resolution-mass spectrometry technologies were utilized to characterize the synthesized compounds' structures. Antimicrobial potential of the title compounds was assessed against several...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Efficacy and Safety between Anterior Cisterna and High Cervical Intrathecal Drug Delivery for Craniofacial Cancer Pain: A Multicenter Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both AC and HC catheterization provide comparable pain control for refractory craniofacial cancer pain. The AC approach offers superior initial delivery efficiency but requires advanced technical skill, while the HC approach provides comparable long-term outcomes with a more familiar technique. Selection should be guided by institutional expertise and patient-specific risk profiles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroptotic resistance involved in PTEN-loss prostate cancer progression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ferroptosis, a newly recognized form of regulated cell death characterized by iron accumulation and lipid peroxidation, plays a pivotal role in cancer development. Herein, we investigated the mechanisms of ferroptotic resistance mediated by Phosphatase and tensin homolog deleted on chromosome 10 (PTEN) loss in prostate cancer cells. The ferroptosis inducer Erastin was used to evaluate the effects on cell viability, colony formation, and Reactive Oxygen Species (ROS) level in three prostate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: B-mode ultrasound and contrast-enhanced ultrasound-based radiomics interpretable analysis for the prediction of macrotrabecular-massive subtype of hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288867/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Small Molecule Compound Eupalinolide B Alleviates Neuropathic Pain by Regulating the USP7/Keap1/Nrf2 Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropathic pain is a chronic pain condition characterized by complex pathogenesis and poor prognosis. EB (Eupalinolide B), a highly bioactive sesquiterpene lactone derived from Eupatorium lindleyanum DC, has been demonstrated to possess multiple pharmacological activities, including antihistamine, antibacterial, and antioxidant effects. USP7 (ubiquitin-specific protease 7) is a crucial deubiquitinating enzyme in eukaryotes, while the Keap1, Nrf2, and HO-1 signaling pathways play pivotal roles...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288853/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scutellarin triggers ferroptosis in ovarian cancer cells via inhibiting AKT/mTOR and JAK2/STAT3 pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ovarian cancer (OC) ranks as the second most prevalent gynecologic malignancy worldwide, largely attributed to the difficulties in detecting early stages, frequent disease reappearance, and unresponsiveness to existing therapies. Contemporary treatment selections for individuals with OC remain limited. Scutellarin (Scu), an active compound, demonstrates suppressive properties against multiplication, invasion, and survival of certain cancer cell types. Nevertheless, the exact anti-cancer...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A homolog of methionine γ-lyase is required for biofilm development in the cyanobacterium Synechococcus elongatus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacterial type IV pilus assembly systems are involved in diverse functions including motility, adhesion and DNA uptake. Studies of the cyanobacterium Synechococcus elongatus sp. PCC7942 revealed that this machinery is also involved in suppression of biofilm formation: inactivation of components of this complex results in robust biofilm development. EbsA, a unique component of cyanobacterial type IV pilus assembly complexes, immunoprecipitates with a homolog of methionine γ-lyase (MGL). Here we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of ITGA2 as a methylation-regulated oncogene through a CeRNA network in papillary thyroid carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study established a ceRNA regulatory network in PTC and identified ITGA2 as a potential therapeutic target. Its dysregulated expression is closely associated with epigenetic alterations, offering new insights into the molecular mechanisms of PTC progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond mTOR: Unraveling the Complex Pathophysiology and Signaling Pathways in Focal Cortical Dysplasia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Focal cortical dysplasia (FCD) is a common cause of drug-resistant epilepsy, characterized by abnormal cortical development and disrupted neuronal connectivity. The pathogenesis of FCD involves complex molecular mechanisms, among which the mTOR (mechanistic target of rapamycin) pathway has been extensively studied. Despite its well-established role in cellular growth and neurodevelopment, mTOR signaling does not fully explain the diverse clinical manifestations of FCD. This is evident in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mesothelin-expressing triple-negative breast cancer: a highly invasive and immunosuppressive subtype]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study provides novel insights into the role of MSLN in TNBC and lays the foundation for future therapeutic strategies targeting MSLN in this aggressive breast cancer subtype.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dueling diagnosis of cancer and cognitive impairment: exploring the association of cognitive impairment with survival using the Women's Health Initiative (WHI) Life and Longevity After Cancer (LILAC) study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The association between CI and overall survival was not significant when adjusted for covariates. The sample size was small and included mostly white females with breast cancer. A larger sample with additional sub analysis will be important to examine overall survival in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revision arthroplasty versus open reduction and internal fixation in Vancouver type B2 and B3 periprosthetic femoral fractures: results from a matched pairs analysis of the registry for geriatric trauma of the DGU<sup>®</sup>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results of the present study support the estimate that ORIF represents a valid treatment alternative for Vancouver type B2 and B3 PFFs, as comparable midterm outcomes were demonstrated for each patient group. However, individualized decisions should always be made, especially for multimorbid geriatric patients, to reduce complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient health engagement as a predictor of symptom outcomes in patients receiving chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PHE, particularly psychological readiness, was associated with better overall, emotional, and functional symptom outcomes. Identifying patients with low engagement may enable more timely, tailored supportive care. Future research should validate these findings in larger and more diverse groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Letter to the Editor: "Outcome of femoral fractures treated with cerclages and intramedullary Nailing"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288764/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Lung ultrasound for predicting surfactant administration in ventilated and non-ventilated infants with respiratory distress syndrome: a multicenter prospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The O-GlcNAcylation of β-actin Ser199 controls nuclear speckle localization and is dysregulated in diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Actin is a pivotal cytoskeletal protein that also regulates chromatin remodeling, transcription, and RNA processing within the nucleus. These nuclear functions are regulated by post-translational modifications (PTMs), but the roles of specific PTMs of nuclear actin remain poorly understood. Of these, the O-GlcNAcylation of Ser199 (gS199) is of particular interest, because this residue can also be phosphorylated (pS199) and is adjacent to the Thr201-203 cluster, a known promoter of filament...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author Correction: Quantification of Pesticides and In Vitro Effects of Water-Soluble Fractions of Agricultural Soils in South Africa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracellular IL-24 ameliorates lipid metabolic disorders in metabolic dysfunction-associated steatohepatitis by restoring the autophagy-lysosome pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: IL-24 preferentially utilizes the IL-22R1/IL-20R2 receptor complex to modulate the AMPK/mTOR/TFEB axis, thereby inducing autophagic-lysosomal activation, regulating glucose and lipid metabolism, and ameliorating hepatic lipid accumulation in MASH. These findings highlight IL-24 as a novel therapeutic target for MASH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Delineating white matter phenotypes of sensori-/psychomotor functioning in large-scale cohorts of healthy individuals and patients with mental disorders across the lifespan (whiteSPAN): rationale and methods of an interdisciplinary bicentric project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aberrant sensori-/psychomotor functioning-including muscular hand weakness, sedentary behavior, psychomotor agitation, slowing, agitation, apathy, and anxiety-is increasingly recognized as a transdiagnostic feature across mental and neurodegenerative disorders. Objectively measured sensori-/psychomotor abnormalities serve as rapid, noninvasive indicators of cognitive and affective dysfunction, yet large-scale neuroimaging studies examining their white matter (WM) correlates remain limited. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating the causal associations between neuroticism, schizophrenia, and cardiovascular diseases using Mendelian randomization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our preliminary genetic evidence suggests that neuroticism may increase the risk of SVS and MI, while schizophrenia may elevate the risk of HF. These findings could inform the identification of patient populations that would benefit from CVD prevention strategies that emphasize mental health improvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutritional nanotherapy with quercetin-loaded chitosan nanoparticles ameliorates imidacloprid-induced liver toxicity through antioxidant, anti-Inflammatory, and genoprotective mechanisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This experiment aimed to determine whether quercetin encapsulated in chitosan nanoparticles (QU-CHNPs) offers greater hepatoprotection than free quercetin (QU) against Imidacloprid (IMD)-induced toxicity. Docking analyses demonstrated a strong binding affinity of QU to key proteins involved in antioxidant regulation, apoptotic pathways, and inflammatory signaling. Based on Docking prediction, sixty adult rats were evenly divided into six groups: control, QU (100 mg/kg BW), QU-CHNPs (100 mg/kg...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of drug-coated balloon vs. second-generation drug-eluting stent for coronary in-stent restenosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DCBs were associated with lower rates of the primary end point all-cause death or myocardial infarction, as well as secondary end points all-cause death and bleeding compared with second-generation DES. These findings suggest that DCBs may represent a safe and effective alternative to DES in selected patient populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41288667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251125142327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>