<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:39:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[X-ray Crystallographic Visualization of a Nucleation and Anisotropic Growth in Thiolate-Protected Gold Clusters: Toward Targeted Synthesis of Gold Quantum Needles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding and controlling the nucleation and growth processes of gold clusters are crucial for advancing the nucleation theory and targeted cluster synthesis. While in situ mass spectrometry has revealed the intermediate species formed during the growth process, the overall structural evolution remains unclear due to a lack of crystallographic information. In this study, we examined a new synthetic method for thiolate-protected gold clusters in their embryonic stage. In this method, only...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908517/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circulating proteins and bone mineral density: A Proteome-Wide Mendelian Randomization Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This large-scale Proteome-Wide MR study introduced novel targets for BMD and osteoporosis at transcriptional and translational levels, presenting new prospects for drug repurposing and development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Publisher Correction: Evaluation of familial phenotype deviation to measure the impact of de novo mutations in autism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Clinical Impact of Intravascular Imaging-Guided Percutaneous Coronary Intervention in Acute Myocardial Infarction Patients with High Thrombus Burden]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the established clinical efficacy following intravascular imaging (IVI)-guided percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI) than angiography-guided PCI, evidence regarding prognostic benefits of IVI-guided PCI in acute myocardial infarction (AMI) patients with high thrombus burden remains limited. Using the nationwide registries of KAMIR-NIH and KAMIR-V, we evaluated the prognostic impact of IVI-guided PCI in AMI patients with high thrombus burden. A total of 4,074 patients with AMI and TIMI...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality Matters: Effect of High-Quality Early Palliative Care in Advanced Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The quality of EPC services significantly impacts depression, patient survival, aspects of QoL, and self-management capabilities. These findings emphasize the importance of high-quality EPC beyond mere provision.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recommendation for use of a long-acting monoclonal antibody to prevent respiratory syncytial virus infection in infants and young children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) is a leading cause of acute lower respiratory tract infections (LRTIs) in infants and young children. In April 2024, the Korea Ministry of Food and Drug Safety approved nirsevimab (Beyfortus), a long-acting monoclonal antibody, as a passive immunization to prevent RSV-associated LRTI among infants and young children. Nirsevimab was launched in Korea in February 2025. This report summarizes the recommendations of the Committee on Infectious Diseases of the Korean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Environmental impact analysis for manufacturing 200 kW SOFC and PAFC systems via life cycle assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fuel cells of the future for sustainable development are solid oxide fuel cell (SOFCs) and phosphoric acid fuel cell (PAFCs), and they will have to coexist as future energy sources. This requires a proper understanding of the properties of the materials used in both fuel cell systems and the ability to identify and mitigate the challenges associated with materials that have a high environmental impact. In this study, all materials and processes involved in the manufacturing of 200 kW SOFC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triazine-Functionalized Covalent Organic Framework Ultrathin Films for Enhancing Local CO<sub>2</sub> Concentrations in Electrochemical CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical CO(2) reduction (CO(2)R) with transition-metal catalysts often suffers from low selectivity for value-added products. Organic layers have been explored to enhance selectivity by modifying local environments and adjusting the CO(2) and CO adsorption, but their role remains unclear due to structural and mechanical instability. Here, we designed a well-defined organic layer model consisting of ∼4 nm-thick covalent organic framework (COF) films with ∼3 nm pores and a cm²-scale area....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D Multilayered BNMR/Epoxy Composites with Enhanced Neutron Shielding Performance for Protection of Space Electronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advancement of space technologies, ensuring the reliable performance of electronic systems in extreme space environments has become increasingly critical. However, conventional polymeric materials used in electronic device packaging suffer from insufficient neutron shielding capability and poor thermal stability, requiring improved effectiveness in protecting sensitive components from high-energy radiation and drastic temperature fluctuations. In this study, we report a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuropeptide-mediated synaptic plasticity regulates context-dependent mating behaviors in Drosophila]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropeptides play crucial roles in regulating context-dependent behaviors, but the underlying mechanisms remain elusive. We investigate the role of the neuropeptide SIFa and its receptor SIFaR in regulating two distinct mating duration behaviors in male Drosophila: Longer-Mating-Duration (LMD) and Shorter-Mating-Duration (SMD). We found that SIFaR expression in specific neurons is required for both LMD and SMD behaviors. Social context and sexual experience lead to synaptic reorganization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SIFa peptidergic neurons orchestrate the internal states and energy balance of male Drosophila melanogaster]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropeptide SIFamide (SIFa) neurons in Drosophila melanogaster have been characterized by their exceptionally elaborate arborization patterns, which extend from the brain into the ventral nerve cord (VNC). SIFa neurons are equipped to receive signals that integrate both internal physiological cues and external environmental stimuli. These signals enable the neurons to regulate energy balance, sleep patterns, metabolic status, and circadian timing. These peptidergic neurons are instrumental in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fe-N<sub>4</sub>@Graphene Single-Atom Catalyst-Based Nanozyme against Influenza A Virus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent COVID-19 pandemic has raised an urgent need for effective strategies to combat viruses that can pose serious health threats to the entire human race. Incorporating antipathogenic functions into everyday objects and personal protective equipment has become increasingly important, motivating the development of general-purpose antiviral materials. Single-atom catalysts, known for superior catalytic performance and maximized atomic utilization, have been explored in various research fields,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Return to Duty After Arthroscopic Bankart Repair in the South Korean Military Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Arthroscopic Bankart repair provides excellent short-term outcomes and facilitates a high return-to-duty rate in South Korean military personnel. With appropriate patient selection and structured rehabilitation, this procedure remains a reliable first-line treatment option for anterior shoulder instability in active duty soldiers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Induction of Nephron-Ductal Dual Lineages via Early Retinoic Acid Signaling Establishes a Platform for Fully Patterned Kidney Organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kidney organoids are powerful tools for renal disease modeling and nephrotoxicity screening, yet their limited structural complexity-particularly the underdevelopment of ureteric bud (UB) lineages-remains a major limitation. A novel differentiation protocol is developed that short-term activation of retinoic acid (RA) signaling during the early intermediate mesoderm (IM) stage, enabling co-induction of anterior and posterior IM lineages. This eliminates the need for UB co-culture and supports...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-driven whole-slide image analysis predicts chemo-resistance and motility subtypes in muscle-invasive bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Deep learning analysis of routine histological WSIs can serve as a practical, low-cost surrogate for molecular profiling, effectively capturing transcriptomic subtypes associated with chemoresistance in MIBC. This approach provides a viable method for patient stratification and establishes a foundation for future multi-modal precision oncology applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[33 Unresolved Questions in Nanoscience and Nanotechnology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Significant advances in science and engineering often emerge at the intersections of disciplines. Nanoscience and nanotechnology are inherently interdisciplinary, uniting researchers from chemistry, physics, biology, medicine, materials science, and engineering. This convergence has fostered novel ways of thinking and enabled the development of materials, tools, and technologies that have transformed both basic and applied research, as well as how we address critical societal challenges. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effective Strategies To Enhance Dehydration Kinetics in Metal Oxide Pellets for Thermal Energy Storage Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermochemical energy storage using Mg(OH)(2) is attractive due to its high energy density, low cost, and nontoxicity. However, its practical application is limited by the high dehydration temperature required to achieve sufficient reaction rates. Although metal salt additives are known to enhance dehydration kinetics, prior studies have mainly focused on powders, with limited research on pellets. Unlike powders, pellet manufacturing involves high-temperature sintering for mechanical stability,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of the performance of a point-of-care molecular assay for simultaneous detection of the agents of American foulbrood and European foulbrood in apiaries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[American foulbrood (AFB) and European foulbrood (EFB), caused by Paenibacillus larvae and Melissococcus plutonius, respectively, are severe bacterial diseases that significantly affect honey bee health and productivity worldwide. Rapid and accurate diagnosis is essential for effective disease management in apiaries. We developed and validated a multiplex point-of-care (POC) quantitative real-time PCR (qPCR) assay that enables simultaneous and rapid detection of P. larvae and M. plutonius...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905163/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revision of the velvet spiders (Araneae, Eresidae) with a new record from South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The genus Eresus Walckenaer, 1805, commonly known as the ladybird spiders, comprises 30 species primarily distributed in the Palaearctic, Afrotropical and Oriental Regions as well as South America, with only one species, E. kollari Rossi, 1846, recorded from South Korea.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding the multifaceted brain mechanisms of acupuncture based on neuroimaging studies: findings and insights from meta-analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mobile phone dependency and adolescent exercise participation: a CB-SEM and fsQCA study on the roles of self-control, time management, and health awareness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Mobile phone dependency undermines adolescent exercise primarily by eroding self-regulatory capacity, disrupting time structure, and diminishing health motivation. Nonetheless, strong personal resources can offset the risks of heavy phone use. Interventions should therefore adopt a dual focus: curbing excessive smartphone use while simultaneously enhancing self-control, time-management skills, and health awareness to sustain youths' exercise involvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refugial isolation and ecological niche differentiation promote genetic divergence of Oresitrophe and Mukdenia in Northeast Asia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Refugial isolation, climatic barriers, and niche differentiation likely influenced the genetic divergence of Oresitrophe and Mukdenia. Our study has implications for the structure of plant diversity in temperate deciduous forests of Northeast Asia and provides insights into conservation units worthy of protection and management for species of both genera.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250905033912&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Evaluation of Dual Microneedle Array Patch for Sequential Intradermal Delivery of Adjuvant and Antigen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Dual-Delivery MAP represents a novel, modular approach for skin-targeted vaccination. By separating antigen and adjuvant into distinct patches, it improves stability, maintains adjuvant efficacy, and enables personalized vaccine administration, offering a promising strategy for effective and safe vaccination.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asian Subgroup Analysis of Patients in the Phase 2 DeLLphi-301 Study of Tarlatamab for Previously Treated Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tarlatamab demonstrated durable responses and promising survival outcomes with a manageable safety profile in this post hoc analysis of patients from Asia with previously treated SCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908346/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A sickness benefit for all, leaving no one behind]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[South Korea's pilot sickness benefit program, launched in 2022 across six regions and currently operating in 14 regions as of 2025, represents a critical juncture in the country's social protection development. While ostensibly designed with inclusive eligibility criteria, the program reveals fundamental paradoxes that illuminate deeper structural inequalities within Korea's dualized labor market. This opinion piece examines how current design choices risk undermining universal health coverage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing statutory paid sick leave in South Korea: necessity and key considerations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[South Korea remains one of the few Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development countries without a statutory paid sick leave system or a public sickness benefit program. This paper examines the necessity of introducing statutory paid sick leave in South Korea and outlines key considerations for its implementation. The "right to rest when sick" is a fundamental health and labor right that ensures workers can recover from illness without risking job loss or income insecurity. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908260/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Introducing a Korean sickness benefit scheme: toward universal health coverage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Educational disparities in labor market participation among middle-aged Koreans with chronic diseases: evidence from the Korean Longitudinal Study of Elderly Employment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Education moderates the relationship between chronic diseases and labor non-participation, with greater disparities in severe or psychiatric illnesses and among wage workers. Low-educated workers are more vulnerable to early retirement due to ill health, highlighting the need for targeted policy interventions to support this group and prevent early exit from the workforce.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908258/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Appropriate extent of lymph node dissection in patients with muscle-invasive gallbladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: PSPLNs and nodes along the porta hepatis should be considered as regional nodes for gallbladder cancer and should be resected.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Integrative Analysis of Psychological Mechanisms Underlying the Effects of Online and Social Media Exposure on Drought Mitigation-Related Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change is an urgent environmental risk. This study examines an integrative model suggesting psychological pathways from drought-related information exposure through online and social media to drought mitigation behavioral intentions and support for drought management policies. The model proposes links between these variables through perceived risks, fear, anger, and hope, with institutional trust acting as a moderator. A two-wave panel survey was conducted in the context of drought due...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body Mass Index and Outcomes After Transcatheter Aortic Valve Replacement: Insights From the Transpacific-TAVR Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pre-TAVR BMI did not significantly affect clinical outcomes in this diverse cohort, challenging the obesity paradox. However, underweight patients exhibited subtle improvements in left ventricular remodeling and valve hemodynamics post-TAVR, highlighting a nuanced role for BMI in recovery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polysaccharide- and phenolic-rich Pinus patula extract-mediated TiO₂ nanoparticles for photocatalytic degradation of methylene blue and 4-nitrophenol]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional TiO₂ nanoparticle syntheses rely on high temperatures, toxic reagents and multi-step routes that impede scalability and sustainability. Here, we deliver the first green synthesis of TiO₂ nanoparticles (TiO₂ NPs) using polysaccharide- (42 mg GE g^(-1)) and phenolic-rich (78 mg GAE g^(-1)) Pinus patula leaf extract. GC-MS and LC-MS fingerprinting identify terpenoids, flavonoids and phenolic glycosides acting as simultaneous reducing, capping and stabilizing agents. X-ray diffraction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ubiquitin-specific protease 7 promotes the growth and oncogenic potential of acute myeloid leukemia cells through the deubiquitination and upregulation of LRRK2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leucine-rich repeat kinase 2 (LRRK2), a large protein with kinase and GTPase activities, regulates various cellular pathways, including autophagy, endocytosis, and mitochondrial dynamics. LRRK2, extensively studied in the context of Parkinson's disease, is functionally impaired in other pathological conditions as well, including inflammatory bowel disease, cancer, and cardiovascular diseases. Despite its critical functions, the mechanisms controlling LRRK2 protein stability are not fully...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Benchmarking deep learning-designed inlay restorations across operator experience: An in vitro comparison of time efficiency, contact intensity, and contour quality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: DL-based workflows may complement operator experience by improving time efficiency and reducing variability between technicians. Significant differences were observed in time efficiency, contact intensity, and contour quality across workflows, though human expertise remains crucial for both quantitative and qualitative outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of depression in chronic immune-mediated neuropathies: A nationwide cohort study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic inflammatory demyelinating polyradiculoneuropathy (CIDP) and multifocal motor neuropathy (MMN) are among the most common immune-mediated neuropathies, characterized by a chronic, disabling disease course. While depression significantly impacts outcomes in various neurological disorders, its risk remains underexplored in patients with CIDP or MMN. This study aimed to investigate the association between CIDP or MMN and new-onset depression using a nationwide cohort in South Korea. Patients...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of formaldehyde-induced hepatotoxicity based on proteometabolomic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Formaldehyde (FA) is a well-known environmental toxicant used in various industries, including biomedical, agriculture, and textiles, but poses significant health risks. Despite extensive research, the exact hepatotoxic mechanism of FA remains unclear. This study investigated FA-induced liver toxicity through an integrative analysis of proteomics and metabolomics in rat models, identifying 84 differentially expressed proteins and 66 metabolites. Using xMWAS and Reactome software, the study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two new polyketides and a new γ-lactone-derived furanone from a soil fungus Trichoderma spirale BHM2-5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two previously undescribed polyketides, bukhansanketides A (1) and B (2), along with a γ-lactone-derived furanone, (S)-(-)-bukhansanfuranone (3), were isolated from Trichoderma spirale BHM2-5, together with four known compounds (4-7). Their structures were elucidated by 1D and 2D NMR spectroscopy and HR-ESI-MS data, as well as DP4+ probability analysis, the modified Mosher's method, or VCD calculations. All isolated compounds (1-7) were evaluated for their cytotoxic activities against A549,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroprotective effects of Lactiplantibacillus plantarum and Pediococcus pentosaceus strains against oxidative stress via modulation of Nrf2-mediated antioxidation and anti-apoptosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxidative stress leads to neurodegenerative diseases such as Parkinson's, Alzheimer's, and Huntington's diseases. Therefore, we isolated Lactiplantibacillus plantarum and Pediococcus pentosaceus strains from kimchi and investigated the neuroprotective effects of their heat-killed lactic acid bacteria (LAB) strains against oxidative stress. All LAB strains demonstrated suitable probiotic characteristics. Heat-killed LAB strains exhibited strong antioxidant activities by effectively scavenging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socioeconomic factors affecting breast and cervical cancer screening compliance in Asian National Cancer Centers Alliance countries: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This systematic review identified multiple socioeconomic factors that shape breast and cervical cancer screening compliance in Asian countries. To reduce disparities in participation, tailored multi-strategy approaches adapted to each country's specific context are required. These findings may provide useful evidence for future research and policy initiatives aimed at addressing health equity issues.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Prognostic Value and Analytical Parameters of the Next-Generation Sequencing-Based Multigene Assay in Hormone Receptor-Positive, HER2-Negative Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We validated the prognostic ability of an NGS-based assay to stratify HR-positive/HER2-negative breast cancers and predict the risk of distant recurrence, and confirmed the requirement for stringent QC criteria to ensure its prognostic ability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907570/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthy Behaviors and All-cause Mortality among Korean Gastric Cancer Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The current study highlights the advantages of physical activity and smoking cessation in reducing mortality, and these benefits are even greater when patients improve their behavior after cancer diagnosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Target volume delineation of the neck for radiotherapy in nasopharyngeal carcinoma: CSTRO, CACA, CSCO, HNCIG, ESTRO, and ASTRO guidelines and contouring atlas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Chinese Society for Therapeutic Radiology Oncology, the Chinese Anti-Cancer Association, the Chinese Society of Clinical Oncology, the Head and Neck Cancer International Group, the European Society for Radiotherapy and Oncology, and the American Society for Radiation Oncology collaboratively developed evidence-based guidelines and a comprehensive contouring atlas for neck target volume delineation in nasopharyngeal carcinoma. These guidelines address five key challenges in modern...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907527/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Primary target volume delineation for radiotherapy in nasopharyngeal carcinoma: CSTRO, CACA, CSCO, HNCIG, ESTRO, and ASTRO guidelines and contouring atlas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Chinese Society for Therapeutic Radiology Oncology, the Chinese Anti-Cancer Association, the Chinese Society of Clinical Oncology, Head and Neck Cancer International Group, the European Society for Radiotherapy and Oncology, and the American Society for Radiation Oncology jointly developed evidence-based guidelines and a contouring atlas for primary target volume delineation for radiotherapy in nasopharyngeal carcinoma. The guidelines systematically address three crucial challenges: margin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning-based detection of ascending aortic dilatation on chest radiographs: A diagnostic study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AI algorithm detected AAD from a single PA CXR with robust AUC over 0.8 across different clinical thresholds and cohorts, outperforming human readers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Platinum/nitrogen-co-doped TiO<sub>2</sub> as photocatalyst and light-free catalytic adsorbent for gaseous formaldehyde]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platinum and nitrogen co-doped titanium dioxide (Pt/N-TiO(2), with 1 wt% Pt and an N/Ti molar ratio of 1) has been synthesized. This Pt/N co-doping strategy creates Schottky junctions, reduces the bandgap energy (3.25 to 2.12 eV), and introduces a new energy level (N 2p). The modified catalyst exhibits dual functionality, serving as both a photocatalyst under light irradiation (λ = 365 nm, 32 W) and a light-free catalytic adsorbent against gaseous formaldehyde (FA). The Pt/N-TiO(2) catalysts are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adverse childhood experiences and adult employment outcomes: Unpacking mechanisms across the life course]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adverse childhood experiences (ACEs) are increasingly recognized as determinants of long-term health and development, yet their effects on employment outcomes in adulthood remain understudied. This study examines the association between ACEs during adolescence and two employment outcomes in adulthood: unemployment status and precarious employment. Based on a life course framework, we also explored five potential mediators: educational attainment, locus of control, incarceration, depressive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the Severity of Pedestrian Traffic Crashes in South Australia: Age-based Insights and Safety Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pedestrian crashes are a global safety issue impacting all age groups, and despite extensive research, understanding the severity of crashes among different age groups has remained incomplete. Older and young pedestrians represent two distinct demographics with unique vulnerabilities. This paper examines the factors that impact the severity of pedestrian crashes resulting in Killed or Serious Injuries in South Australia over ten years (2012-2020) for two age groups, namely young pedestrians (age...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Explainable machine learning models based on clinical trial surrogate outcomes for predicting overall survival in head and neck cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Elastic Net model effectively bridges surrogate efficacy endpoints and median OS, facilitating the interpretation of early clinical trial outcomes and assisting in the prediction of OS benefit in R/M HNSCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contrasting seasonal variability of net community production between the Southern Yellow Sea and the Northern East China Sea during spring and summer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Yellow Sea (YS) and the East China Sea (ECS), which comprise continental shelves with depths of 200 m or less, are recognized as some of the most productive coastal areas globally. Although this high productivity can contribute to carbon sequestration, the spatiotemporal variability of the biological pump remains unclear. To investigate this variability, net community production (NCP(insitu)) in August 2020 was estimated based on high-resolution O(2)/Ar measurements. The study area was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing health outcomes and costs of home and community-based services (HCBS) versus institutional care (IC) for long-term care insurance beneficiaries in South Korea: Can the less severe benefit more?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[It is often considered that home and community-based services (HCBS) are better than institutional care services (IC) in terms of person's preferences and costs in long-term care (LTC) settings. However, this may not always be the case depending on the baseline health status of the person. Using nationally representative data from South Korea, we examined whether the effects of HCBS versus IC on health outcomes and costs differ according to the individual's baseline health status. Entropy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Electric Field on the Structural Dynamics of Water and Adsorbed Molecules near an Electrode Surface: Simulations of 2D IR Experiments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous catalysis involves the chemical transformation of molecules at an electrode surface, but experimentally probing the impact of the electric field on the structural dynamics of the molecules and any accompanying solvent dynamics remains a significant challenge. In this study, we conducted molecular dynamics simulations of a system comprising pure water in contact with gold (Au) electrodes coated with 4-mercaptobenzonitrile (4-MBN) molecules, as recently measured using 2D IR...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Peptide Antibiotic Targeting Gram-Negative Infections Designed from <em>Mycobacterium tuberculosis</em> Adenylate Kinase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We explored the lipopolysaccharide-binding properties of adenylate kinase from Mycobacterium tuberculosis (MtAdk) to facilitate the design of novel peptide antibiotics. Notably, we de novo designed 11-mer peptides derived from the AMP-binding domain (Lys44 to Asp54) of MtAdk. Among 71 designed peptides, DD-S067 was the most effective, especially against carbapenem-resistant Acinetobacter baumannii (CRAB), with minimal development of drug resistance. DD-S067 exhibited multiple antibacterial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changing landscape of steatotic liver diseases and liver fibrosis in the United States during the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study highlights a shift in SLDs in the United States during the COVID-19 pandemic, showing a decrease in MASLD and increases in MetALD and ALD, with an alarming increase in the prevalence of CSF, likely reflecting lifestyle changes, including physical inactivity and alcohol consumption.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving cosmological reach of a gravitational wave observatory using Deep Loop Shaping]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Improved low-frequency sensitivity of gravitational wave observatories would unlock study of intermediate-mass black hole mergers and binary black hole eccentricity and provide early warnings for multimessenger observations of binary neutron star mergers. Today's mirror stabilization control injects harmful noise, constituting a major obstacle to sensitivity improvements. We eliminated this noise through Deep Loop Shaping, a reinforcement learning method using frequency domain rewards. We proved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spin-selective transport through chiral ferromagnetic nanohelices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chiral crystals with well-defined handedness in atomic arrangements exhibit properties such as spin selectivity, asymmetric magnetoresistance, and skyrmions. Although similar geometry-induced phenomena in chiral organic molecule-based systems were observed, synthesizing uniform inorganic nanostructures with desired chirality using a scalable method remains challenging. We electrochemically synthesized chiral ferromagnetic cobalt-iron nanohelices from nanoparticles in anodized aluminum oxide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Public perception and changing attitudes toward antidepressants over a decade in social media: Lessons learned from online discussion using artificial intelligence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Negative perceptions toward antidepressants are prevalent on social media, mainly focusing on efficacy and side effects. However, a decade-long analysis shows a decline in negative sentiments, with an increase in neutral sentiments with a downturn in yearly proportion of side-effected related topics within each cluster. These trends and information may help improve strategies to address barriers to antidepressant use and adherence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating braking and propulsion forces during overground running in and out of the lab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating kinetic metrics, such as braking and propulsion forces, in real-world running environments enhances our understanding of performance, fatigue, and injury. Wearable inertial measurement units (IMUs) offer a potential solution to estimate kinetic metrics outside the lab when combined with machine learning. However, current IMU-based kinetic estimation models are trained and evaluated within a single environment, often on lab treadmills. The transferability of these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Lactobacillus amylovorus</em> KU4 inhibits adipocyte senescence in aged mice through necdin regulation of p53 activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previously, we reported that Lactobacillus amylovorus KU4 (LKU4) ameliorates diet-induced metabolic disorders by regulating adipose tissue (AT) physiology. Since metabolic disorders and age-related pathological conditions mutually exacerbate each other, this study hypothesizes that LKU4 may protect against adipose senescence during aging. Thus, this study demonstrates that LKU4 administration suppresses age-related metabolic dysfunction and aging phenotypes in AT of 24-month-old mice....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906540/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partial Deletion of the Carboxyl-Terminal Signal Sequence of the Cellular Prion Protein Alters Protein Expression via Endoplasmic Reticulum-Associated Degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellular prion protein (PrP^(C)) is a glycoprotein tethered to the plasma membrane via a GPI-anchor, and it plays a crucial role in prion diseases by undergoing conformational change to PrP^(Sc). To generate a knock-in (KI) mouse model expressing bank vole PrP^(C) (BVPrP^(C)), a KI targeting construct was designed. However, a Prnp gene sequence that encodes PrP^(C) lacking seven C-terminal amino acid residues of the GPI-anchoring signal sequence (GPI-SS) was unintentionally introduced into the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Study of the Therapeutic Effect of Cytokine-Preconditioned Mesenchymal Stem Cells and Their Exosomes in a Mouse Model of Psoriasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs) are a type of multipotent, non-hematopoietic cells of mesodermal origin. Due to their strong immunomodulatory, immunosuppressive, and regenerative potential, MSCs are used in cell therapy for inflammatory, immune-mediated, and degenerative diseases. Exosomes derived from MSCs have several advantages over MSC therapy, including non-immunogenicity, lack of infusion toxicity, ease of isolation, manipulation, and storage, cargo specificity, and the absence of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide polygenic risk score for estimated glomerular filtration slope predicts chronic kidney disease in a Taiwanese population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We constructed a genome-wide polygenic risk score for eGFR decline and externally validated its use in predicting CKD in another Taiwan population. Our eGFR slope polygenic risk score might be useful for clinical CKD risk assessment in future, especially for East Asians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ajuforrestin A Inhibits Tumor Proliferation and Migration by Targeting the STAT3/FAK Signaling Pathways and VEGFR-2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Natural products, characterized by their structural novelty, multi-target capabilities, and favorable toxicity profiles, represent a prominent reservoir for the discovery of innovative anticancer therapeutics. In the current investigation, we identified ajuforrestin A, a diterpenoid compound extracted from Ajuga lupulina Maxim, as a potent agent against lung cancer. In vitro, this compound markedly curtailed the proliferation of A549 cells. Mechanistic explorations revealed that ajuforrestin A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906092/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engaging Fathers in Child Nutrition: Exploring Intra-household Gender Dynamics in Nutrition Interventions in Ethiopia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to examine intra-household gender dynamics in response to a nutrition intervention (maternal Behaviour Change Communication (BCC), paternal BCC, and food vouchers) aimed at improving IYCF practices using qualitative methods. Participants were drawn from a subset of households enrolled in a larger cluster - randomized controlled trial (RCT) conducted in rural Ethiopia. A total of 40 participants (20 mother-father pairs) from intervention and control households were interviewed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Near Infrared-Responsive Xanthene Probes for Dual-Mode Cancer Treatment and Bioimaging]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence of cancer has escalated at a distressing pace, creating an urgent demand for advancements and breakthroughs in medical interventions. Amidst the multitude of approaches for diagnosing and managing cancer, fluorescence imaging, photodynamic therapy, and photothermal therapy have emerged as key approaches due to their unique advantages. Herein, two new xanthene-based probes, namely, JB-1 and JB-2, with D-π-A conjugated structures, are reported. JB-1 and JB-2 each feature...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the effects of total arch intrusion treatment in adolescents and adults: A pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TAI was an effective treatment option to improve the retrognathic profile. The adolescent group showed significantly greater anteroposterior skeletal improvement and profile changes than the adult group with TAI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905893/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Parkinson's Disease Among Breast Cancer Survivors: A Nationwide Cohort Study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Breast cancer survivors did not exhibit a significantly increased risk of PD overall. However, younger survivors showed a possible age-related elevation in risk over time.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of avalglucosidase alfa in infantile-onset Pompe disease with high anti-alglucosidase alfa antibody titers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refined Signal Organic Photodetectors via Transfer Lamination of pH-Controlled PEDOT:PSS for Durable In Situ Stress Monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a strategy for noise suppression and stability enhancement of organic photodetectors (OPDs) by introducing pH-neutralized and transfer-laminated poly(3,4-ethylenedioxythiophene):poly(styrenesulfonate) (PEDOT:PSS) as the hole-transporting layer (HTL). Although PEDOT:PSS is widely used as an HTL material, its intrinsic acidity and structural instability hinder the performance of the OPD. Here, imidazole-induced neutralization promotes a linear entangled structure, while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Bones That Wait for Ours: A Surgeon At the Capela dos Ossos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recovery effects of various skin lipid components and their structural derivatives on skin barrier damage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study compares the skin barrier recovery effects of skin lipid components, demonstrating that BA elicits a high skin barrier recovery effect similar to that of CER, which has known efficacy. BA also had an excellent sealing effect through lipid packaging, whereas CER had a combined sealing effect and increased the epidermal thickness and density. These results provide foundational evidence for formulating products that help restore the skin barrier by supplying lipids to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chalcogenide-Based Brain-Inspired Photo-Synapses for Neuromorphic Vision Sensor: An Experimental and Theoretical Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2D chalcogenide-based memristors have the potential to be used in artificial biological visual systems since their synaptic behavior can be optically and electrically modulated. Furthermore, 2D van der Waals materials such as SnS(2) can be used to integrate multifunctional optoelectronic devices by employing a rational design. Here, the simulation of a human biological visual system is reported by using multifunctional optoelectronic synaptic devices. First-principles-based DFT calculations show...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of obesity on palpation-guided distal radial access for coronary procedures: subgroup analysis of the multicenter, prospective KODRA registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this subgroup analysis of the KODRA trial, obesity was not associated with the success rate for palpation-guided distal radial artery cannulation, crossover rate, and DRA-related complications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Influence of Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease and Body Mass Index on the Incidence of Alzheimer Disease: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A normal/underweight BMI and the presence of MASLD synergistically increased the risk of AD. The lean MASLD group had a higher risk of developing AD than the overweight/obese MASLD group, suggesting that the clinical relevance of MASLD for incident AD differs based on the BMI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolving Strategies for the Optimal Management of Common Bile Duct Stones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Management of common bile duct (CBD) stones has evolved substantially with the advent of endoscopic techniques and dedicated high-end devices. Endoscopic retrograde cholangiopancreatography (ERCP) has become a widespread essential technique for managing CBD stones, with high success rates in standard cases. However, for patients with large stones, stones in an impacted state, and stones in anatomically challenging regions, advanced strategies using various dedicated devices may be needed....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905048/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applicability of current chronic kidney disease criteria for mortality and end-stage kidney disease in older diabetic populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study indicated that an eGFR of 45-59 mL/min/1.73 m2 possesses an elevated risk of composite events, which suggests that the current traditional eGFR criteria could be applicable to older patients with diabetes mellitus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tonsil-derived mesenchymal stem cells protect the kidney from gentamicin-induced acute kidney injury by incorporation into damaged renal tubules and amelioration of oxidative and endoplasmic reticulum stresses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study demonstrated that T-MSCs ameliorated GM-induced AKI by directly incorporating into the damaged renal tubules and exerting antiapoptotic and antioxidative effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905041/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a prediction tool for kidney function decline in children with chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A tool for predicting kidney function decline in children with CKD over a short period of time was developed using potential predictors and machine learning methods in a large Korean pediatric CKD cohort.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905038/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Left ventricular geometry and the risk of heavy coronary artery calcification in patients with pre-dialysis chronic kidney disease: the KoreaN Cohort Study for Outcome in Patients With Chronic Kidney Disease (KNOW-CKD)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Abnormal LVG patterns, such as concentric remodeling and concentric LVH, but not eccentric LVH, are significantly associated with the risk of heavy coronary artery calcification in patients with CKD. It is expected that the determination of LVG patterns may facilitate risk stratification in relation to the coronary evaluation strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905037/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From data to policy: addressing the economic burden of biopsy-proven kidney diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Causal effect estimation for competing risk data in randomized trial: adjusting covariates to gain efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The double-blinded randomized trial is considered the gold standard to estimate the average causal effect (ACE). The naive estimator without adjusting any covariate is consistent. However, incorporating the covariates that are strong predictors of the outcome could reduce the issue of unbalanced covariate distribution between the treated and controlled groups and can improve efficiency. Recent work has shown that thanks to randomization, for linear regression, an estimator under risk consistency...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of nurses' health beliefs about caring for older adults on their own preparation for old age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Improving preparation for retirement and health beliefs could promote preparation for old age. Department, desired retirement age, annual salary, and chronic disease need to be considered when developing and implementing interventions for improving preparation for old age. Nursing managers or nurses need pay attention to factors influencing preparation for old age of young nurses caring for older adult patients in general hospitals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic value of signet-ring cell carcinoma proportion in undifferentiated gastric cancer: Implications for endoscopic treatment decisions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher SRCC proportions in the PCC correlate with lower tumor aggressiveness and improved prognosis. Its role in EGC should be validated as a factor influencing therapeutic strategies, including endoscopic submucosal dissection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defining diagnostic thresholds for dissociation between caloric test and vHIT in Ménière's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Dissociation between caloric and vHIT results is a specific indicator of MD, aiding differentiation from BPPV. However, its utility for distinguishing MD from VS is limited.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population pharmacokinetics/pharmacodynamics analysis confirming biosimilarity of SB16 to reference denosumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The developed TMDD-QSS model with indirect response model adequately characterized the PK/PD profile of denosumab. Covariate effects, including study population (HV vs. PMO), age, and race showed no clinically meaningful impact on treatment outcomes. Covariate analysis and simulation results revealed no significant differences in PK/PD parameters between SB16 and DEN. The similarity in the PK profile and change in lumbar spine BMD between SB16 and DEN were demonstrated, supporting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904558/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can we predict neurological complications in patients with metastatic spinal tumors?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with metastatic spinal tumors, high-grade ESCC was a significant predictor of spinal cord injury within 1 year and was associated with an earlier onset of spinal cord injury. Radicular pain and unstable spines based on SINS categories were also strongly associated with the occurrence of spinal cord injury. This study provides valuable insights for predicting 1-year functional outcomes and determining management strategies for spinal metastases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904514/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rigid cationic ligands enable high-efficiency NIR-II photoluminescence in copper(i) iodide hybrid semiconductors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Near-infrared (NIR) luminescent materials are pivotal for advanced optoelectronic and biomedical applications, yet attaining efficient emission in the NIR-II region (950-1400 nm) remains challenging. Here, we introduce a ligand cationization strategy for designing copper(i) iodide-organic hybrid materials that emit in the NIR-II region (920-1120 nm) with PLQYs up to 8.58%. By incorporating rigid cationic ligands with CuI modules, we synergistically achieve bandgap narrowing (to 1.51 eV) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Association Between Melanoma and Autoimmune Diseases: A Nationwide Population-Based Study in the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few population-based studies have investigated the association between melanoma and autoimmune diseases in Asian populations. We conducted a population-based cross-sectional study using the South Korean National Health Insurance database to investigate the association between melanoma and autoimmune diseases in Asian individuals. Melanoma patients were identified, and birth year and sex matched controls were randomly selected at a 1:10 ratio. Multivariable logistic regression was used to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stimuli-Responsive Nanomaterials for Wireless and Precise Neuromodulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuromodulation is a highly promising technology for controlling neural circuits, treating nervous system diseases, and manipulating brain function. Conventional approaches, such as direct electrical stimulation or optogenetics, face challenges from their unstable therapeutic outcomes, invasive nature, and potential tissue damage. The emergence of stimuli-responsive nanomaterial-based wireless neuromodulation techniques offers tunability, minimal invasiveness, highly specific targeting, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Lordosis Distribution Index on Proximal Junctional Kyphosis and Clinical Outcomes in Patients Undergoing Thoracolumbar Fusion for Degenerative Flatback Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LDI correction alone did not affect PJK occurrence, but in conjunction with age-adjusted PI-LL overcorrection, LDI overcorrection significantly increased the risk of PJK. Clinical outcomes were affected by age-adjusted PI-LL correction with best outcomes in matched correction group but not by the LDI correction status. This lack of association between LDI and clinical outcomes may be attributable to the fact that LDI alone did not have a significant effect on determining spinopelvic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of a Novel HLA-DRB3 Allele, DRB3*03:85, in a Korean Individual]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DRB3*03:85 is distinguished from HLA-DRB3*03:01:01:01 by a single nonsynonymous substitution at codon 122 in exon 3.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904040/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Waist-to-Height Ratio Increases the Risk of Cardiovascular Outcomes in Adults with Type 1 Diabetes Mellitus: A Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High WHtR is associated with an increased risk of CV events in adults with T1DM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904015/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combining Microfluidic Assessment with Encoded Hydrogel Microparticle-Based Immunoassay for Anti-Interleukin Drug Repurposing of Pulmonary Fibrosis Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary fibrosis is a life-threatening disorder characterized by excessive extracellular matrix (ECM) deposition and progressive dysfunction. The disease progression is closely associated with increased ECM stiffness, which compromises normal tissue mechanics and leads to respiratory failure. Although its etiology is multifactorial, immune-mediated responses are central drivers of fibrotic remodeling through inflammatory cytokine release and aberrant tissue repair. Here, we present a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903905/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing male HPV vaccination in China: A narrative review of challenges and opportunities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human papillomavirus (HPV) poses significant health risks to men, including genital warts and HPV-related cancers. In China, the recent approval of HPV vaccination for males aged 9-26 marks an important step toward gender-inclusive prevention. However, challenges remain in promoting vaccine acceptance among men due to the perception of HPV as a "women's disease," limited public awareness, cultural stigma, and low perceived susceptibility, particularly among heterosexual men. Men who have sex...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methodology for Assessing Patient Centricity and Data Integrity in Clinical Trials With Decentralized Elements: A Pilot Trial on Mastic Gum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decentralized elements enhanced patient centricity by shifting trial-related activities outside traditional trial sites. On the other hand, remote data collection poses potential risks to data integrity. Although these two are critical aspects of decentralized elements, methodologies for assessing them remain limited. We proposed a method to measure patient centricity by subtracting the participant's self-rated burden for trial-related procedures with decentralized elements from their estimated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-Voltage-Driven Nonvolatile Electrochemical Active Control of Terahertz Transmission in Conductive-Polymer-Nanoresonator Hybrid Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Active manipulation of terahertz (THz) waves is important for future optoelectronic applications, but most approaches rely on volatile or slow actuation, limiting efficiency and stability. Here, we report a nonvolatile, low-voltage tunable THz transmission device based on electrochemical modulation of a conductive polymer thin film integrated with metallic nanoresonators. A thin film of PEDOT:PSS, deposited via a single-step spin-coating process onto the nanoresonator array, enables efficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Onnamides and a Novel Analogue, Onnamide G, as Potent Leishmanicidal Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Leishmaniasis is a neglected tropical disease posing significant global health challenges. Given the limited effective treatment options and associated constraints, many patients are unable to complete therapy. In this study, we report the remarkable leishmanicidal activity of onnamides derived from the marine sponge Theonella sp. against the promastigote form of Leishmania major (IC(50) = 0.2-140 nM) and demonstrate their selectivity through cytotoxicity assessments on human hepatoma HepG2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Components of particulate matter as potential risk factors for acute myocardial infarction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Short-term exposure to PM(2.5) is associated with an increased incidence of AMI. Future research prioritises the components of PM(2.5), with particular focus on whether a decrease in black carbon concentrations can mitigate the risk of future air quality-related AMI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ecological Risk Assessment and Management of Forest Fires in Tamil Nadu, India: A MaxEnt Model-Based Approach for Strategic Resource Allocation and Fire Mitigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Forest fires are integral to forest ecosystems as they influence nutrient cycling, plant regeneration, tree density, and biodiversity. However, human-induced climate change and activities have made forest fires more frequent, more intense, and more widespread, exacerbating their ecological and socioeconomic impact. Forest fires shape Tamil Nadu's diverse forest ecosystems, yet rising anthropogenic pressure and a warmer, drier climate have increased both their frequency and severity. We used a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of script-driven emotional imagery on postural control in healthy individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although emotions were successfully induced, they minimally affected postural control in healthy individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anconeus Tear: A rare cause of chronic elbow pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907965/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An Empirical Biasing Force Constant to Minimize Overfitting in Cryo-EM Flexible Fitting Refinement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reliable modeling of protein structures from a cryo-EM density map is one of the central issues in structural biology. Typically, the constructed model is refined using a flexible fitting method combined with molecular dynamics, where a biasing potential is introduced to guide the protein structure toward the density map. However, the appropriate force constant for the biasing potential is generally unknown a priori. Here, we propose an empirical force constant that enables flexible fitting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907958/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Periplasmic serine protease Prc is responsible for amyloid subunit CsgA degradation and proteostasis in Escherichia coli]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Escherichia coli synthesizes curli amyloid fibers extracellularly during biofilm formation and host colonization. The proteostasis network regulates the major curli subunit, CsgA, to prevent intracellular amyloid aggregation, yet the degradation mechanism remains elusive. Here, through a comprehensive investigation employing genetically engineered E. coli, multi-copy-suppressor screening, and biochemical analyses, we identify periplasmic serine protease Prc as a key player in CsgA degradation....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907937/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of a first time anterior shoulder dislocation: the decision-making process of a surgeon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings highlight the significant role of bony lesions, including glenoid bone loss and Hill-Sachs lesions, in shaping surgical treatment decisions. Younger surgeons are more likely to incorporate the glenoid track concept into their decision-making compared to their older counterparts. However, most surgeons adopt a comprehensive approach, considering not only bony pathology but also the type and level of sports played, as well as the patient's age. This reflects a growing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Alteration of alanine-327 in LXRα to LXRβ-type histidine deteriorates its subtype-selective activation by riccardin C]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Liver X receptors (LXRα and LXRβ) are nuclear receptors critical for lipid homeostasis and inflammation regulation, making them potential therapeutic targets for atherosclerosis and inflammatory diseases. While LXR agonists hold promise, their use is limited by adverse effects on hepatic lipogenesis. Riccardin C (RC) has shown promise as an LXRα partial agonist/ LXRβ antagonist with cell-type-selective properties. This study investigates the molecular mechanisms behind RC-induced LXRα...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extra-Virgin Olive Oil and Additional Cardiovascular Outcomes in the PREDIMED Trial: An Outcome-Wide Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: High consumption of EVOO is associated with a substantial reduction in the risk of an outcome-wide composite of CVD events among high-risk individuals. In contrast, COO, which lacks polyphenols, showed weaker associations, highlighting the importance of differentiating olive oil types in CVD prevention strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Decentralized pandemic response and health equity: an analysis of socioeconomic disparities in COVID-19 mortality in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The inverse relationship between area deprivation and COVID-19 mortality in Japan contrasts with global patterns. Although Japan's decentralized health system ensured equitable access to COVID-19 treatment, lower mortality in more deprived areas likely reflects additional protective factors, including population density patterns and community-specific adaptations. These findings underscore the complex interplay between socioeconomic conditions and health outcomes during global health...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute Respiratory Distress Syndrome Secondary to Miliary Tuberculosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diversity of Kryptoperidinium (Peridiniales, Dinophyceae): Morphological description and molecular phylogenetics of Kryptoperidinium secundum sp. nov]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kryptoperidinium belongs to a group of dinophytes hosting a diatom as an endosymbiont and is currently considered to comprise a single, putatively bloom-forming and harmful species only. Molecular phylogenetics indicate the existence of a second distinct lineage and therefore species new to science, which we here formally describe as Kryptoperidinium secundum sp. nov. We studied living and fixed material of unialgal strains in detail using light and electron microscopy and gained DNA sequences...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of social resources on readmission prevention and the influence of informal coercion in acute schizophrenia: a retrospective quasi-experimental cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Introducing social resources can prevent readmission for acute schizophrenia, but coercive introduction may negate this benefit. Medical staff should avoid informal coercion and adopt strategies that elicit motivation when introducing social resources.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eggshell membrane supplementation stimulates angiogenesis and promotes bone healing in a rat drill-hole injury model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of new adjunct therapies to support bone healing remains an important clinical challenge. Eggshell membrane (ESM), a natural biomaterial derived from chicken eggs, has recently attracted attention for its safety, biocompatibility, and cost-effectiveness. We aimed to evaluate the effects of ESM supplementation on bone healing in a rat tibial drill-hole injury model. Seven-week-old male Wistar rats, acclimated for one week prior to the experiment, were divided into three groups:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychotic-like experiences, sleep problems, and loneliness: A population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Research indicates that psychotic-like experiences (PLEs) are associated with sleep problems, which in turn may contribute to negative outcomes in individuals with PLEs. This study examined the association between sleep problems and PLEs in the Japanese general population, and whether sleep problems are linked to loneliness among individuals with PLEs. Data were analyzed from 3717 adults aged 18 and above who participated in an online survey in 2023. PLEs were assessed with the PRIME...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influenza vaccine effectiveness over 17 seasons in a large Japanese cohort: Analyses by age, virus type, underlying diseases and seasons before the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Seasonal influenza vaccines showed moderate effectiveness, especially in individuals < 40 years and those without comorbidities. Effectiveness declined with age, underscoring the need for improved vaccines and targeted strategies for older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biosynthesis of the Thiofuranose Core in Albomycin Requires a Versatile Enzyme AbmG That Catalyzes Net Dehydration via Cryptic Phosphorylation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Albomycins are unusual sulfur-containing nucleosides from the species of Streptomyces that exhibit potent antibiotic activities against both Gram-negative and Gram-positive bacteria including clinical pathogens. Previous studies demonstrated that the twitch radical SAM enzyme AbmM catalyzes an oxidative sulfur-for-oxygen swapping reaction converting CDP to a 4'-hydroxy-4'-thiocytidine 5'-diphosphate intermediate in the initial step of albomycin biosynthesis. However, the fate of this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40907032/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cerebrovascular Reactivity at Rest and Its Association With Cognitive Function in People With Genetic Frontotemporal Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Cerebrovascular reactivity (CVR) is an indicator of cerebrovascular health, and its signature in familial frontotemporal dementia (FTD) remains unknown. The primary aim was to investigate CVR in genetic FTD using an fMRI index of vascular contractility termed resting-state fluctuation amplitudes (RSFAs) and to assess whether RSFA differences are moderated by age. A secondary aim was to study the relationship between RSFA and cognition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid, low-temperature nanodiamond formation by electron-beam activation of adamantane C-H bonds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diamond and adamantane (Ad) share a T(d)-symmetric carbon skeleton, but converting Ad to diamond has been challenging because it requires selective carbon-hydrogen (C-H) bond cleavage and monomer assembly into a diamond lattice. Our approach differs from the conventional high-temperature, high-pressure diamond syntheses. We electron-irradiated Ad submicrocrystals at 80 to 200 kilo-electron volts and 100 to 296 kelvin in vacuum for tens of seconds. This process yielded defect-free nanodiamonds...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906847/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testis expressed 50 is essential for maintaining sperm acrosome integrity during epididymal transit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In mammals, sperm formation is completed in the seminiferous tubules within the testis, and sperm maturation occurs during the epididymal transit of the spermatozoa. Sperm morphology drastically changes when abnormal spermatozoa migrate from the testis to the epididymis. Detailed molecular mechanisms for sperm survival in the epididymis have not been determined yet. Globozoospermia is a cause of male infertility and is characterized by round-headed spermatozoa without acrosomes, an abnormal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transgenic mice overexpressing Pitx2 in the atria develop tachycardia-bradycardia syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sinoatrial node (SAN) dysfunction often accompanies supraventricular tachyarrhythmias such as atrial fibrillation (AF), which is referred to as tachycardia-bradycardia syndrome (TBS). Although there have been many studies on electrical remodeling in TBS, the regulatory mechanisms that cause electrical remodeling in the SAN and atrial muscles by chronic bradycardia or tachycardia have not yet been fully investigated. Here we hypothesized Pitx2c, a transcription factor that played a central role...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906746/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carbon Footprint of Minimally Invasive and Open Microdiscectomy: Emerging Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectiveTo quantify and compare the carbon footprint (CF) of open and MIS microdiscectomy.MethodsThe study included 161 patients undergoing primary 1 level open or minimally invasive surgery (MIS) for lumbar disc herniation between 2018 and 2022. Life cycle assessment (LCA) modeling was used to calculate the CF produced during the distribution, use and waste phases of each item used during surgery. Independent samples t-tests and Chi square or Fischer's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Breast cancer classification based on the integration of diagnostic algorithms for calcifications and masses using a mixture of experts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By integrating specialized algorithms for calcifications and masses, the MoRFSE model effectively emulates radiologists' diagnostic process. These findings suggest that MoRFSE has the potential to improve the accuracy of breast cancer diagnosis based on mammograms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906677/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biased and Inflexible Interpretations of Social Situations Predict Affect Intensity and Variability in Children and Adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adolescence is a developmental period characterized by heightened emotionality. Past research indicated that the biased interpretation of social situations (i.e., interpretation bias) might contribute to these aberrant affect dynamics in adolescents' daily life. Social situations are, however, constantly changing. Therefore, the ability to flexibly revise social interpretations (i.e., interpretation flexibility) might be equally important as interpretation biases for explaining affective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rare anatomical variation: analysis of an aberrant right subclavian artery in three cadavers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An aberrant right subclavian artery (ARSA) is a congenital vascular anomaly in which the right subclavian artery originates directly from the aortic arch distal to the left subclavian artery. Although often asymptomatic, ARSA can lead to clinical complications, such as dysphagia, upper respiratory issues, and vascular events. In this study, we examined the gross anatomical and histological characteristics of the ARSA based on three cadavers selected from a total of 7 ARSA cases identified among...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and efficacy of arsenic trioxide in intensification therapy for newly diagnosed childhood acute promyelocytic leukemia: results from the JPLSG AML-P13 study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Arsenic trioxide (ATO) in combination with all-trans retinoic acid (ATRA) has been shown to be effective in both adult and pediatric patients with acute promyelocytic leukemia (APL). Addition of ATO to conventional chemotherapy could lead to a reduction in the doses of cytotoxic agents, but the long-term safety of ATO is not fully understood, especially in children. The Japan Children's Cancer Group conducted a risk-stratified prospective study to investigate safety and efficacy of ATO in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40906031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[External validation of the revised lethal triad criteria for appropriate strategic decision making]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The revised lethal triad criteria demonstrated clinically sufficient sensitivity and appropriate specificity for predicting 28-day mortality in patients with severe trauma, suggesting their utility as indicators for adopting critical therapeutic strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905980/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Remote training of a reservoir computer via digital twins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing energy consumption required for information processing has become a significant challenge, leading to growing interest in optical and optoelectronic reservoir computing as a more efficient alternative. Trained reservoir computers are especially suited for low-energy applications near the edge. However, the computational cost of training the reservoir output weights, particularly due to matrix operations, adds potentially unwanted complexity to the architecture. To lift this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Noise-induced transitions in random Pomeau-Manneville maps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We introduce randomness to Pomeau-Manneville (PM) maps by incorporating dichotomous multiplicative noise that alternates between dynamics with an attracting and a repelling fixed point. We characterize the dynamical behavior by measuring the separation of two nearby orbits. Controlling the probability of selecting the repelling PM map, we find two noise-induced transitions. When the repelling map is selected with probability less than 1/2, orbits converge to the origin, which is an indifferent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Pseudomonas aeruginosa lasR</em>-deficient mutant contributes to bacterial virulence through enhancing the PhoB-mediated pathway in response to host environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pseudomonas aeruginosa is a major opportunistic pathogen that causes lung infections in patients with cystic fibrosis and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease. Loss-of-function mutations in the quorum-sensing regulatory gene lasR commonly arise during chronic infections, which are associated with exaggerated inflammation and accelerated decline in lung function. Here, in a murine cutaneous abscess model, infection with a ΔlasR mutant or a wild-type-ΔlasR mutant-mixed population resulted in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905672/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PU.1 and TGF-β signaling activate the cell-surface expression of CD103 in mast cells and dendritic cells: opposite roles of GATA2 in the expression of mucosal mast cell genes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mucosal mast cells (MMCs) are distinguished from connective tissue mast cells (MCs) by the specific cell-surface expression of integrin CD103 (also known as integrin αE/β7; αE is encoded by Itgae) and mast cell protease 1 and 2 (Mcpt1 and Mcpt2, respectively). Although the expression of the Mcpt1 and Mcpt2 genes is cooperatively regulated by the transcription factor GATA-binding protein 2 (GATA2) and transforming growth factor beta (TGF-β) signaling in MMCs, the transcriptional mechanism of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ni<sup>II</sup> and Cu<sup>II</sup> Complexes of 5-Oxa-, 5-Sulfa-, 5-Selena-, and 5-Telluracorroles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclization of α,α'-dibromo tetrapyrrolic Ni^(II) complex 4Ni with K(2)S, Na(2)Se, and Na(2)Te gave Ni^(II) 5-sulfacorrole, Ni^(II) 5-selenacorrole, and Ni^(II) 5-telluracorrole, respectively, as the first example of 5-heterocorrole. The corresponding Cu^(II) 5-heterocorroles were similarly synthesized from Cu^(II) complex 4Cu, while Ni^(II) 5-oxacorrole was synthesized by reaction of 4Ni with Ni(cod)(2) and 2,2'-bipyridine and subsequent oxygen-insertion reaction of molecular oxygen, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Timeline of Amelogenesis Imperfecta Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Amelogenesis imperfecta is a heterogeneous group of >100 different rare diseases. Affected individuals and families are facing diagnostic uncertainty and wandering and a therapeutic odyssey. Continuous multidisciplinary management from childhood to adulthood is essential, emphasizing the critical role of health care professionals. Clinical and genetic diagnoses and treatment options are still a matter of discussion and debate. This article, written by the European Reference Network ERN CRANIO...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Call for founding members of the European Organization For University Physical and Rehabilitation Medicine (UniPRM)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rehabilitation is increasingly recognized as a key component of health systems worldwide. To meet the growing demand for rehabilitation services, it is essential to strengthen academic capacity in Physical and Rehabilitation Medicine within universities. Academic structures are critical for training future physicians and professionals, and for advancing research and innovation in rehabilitation. In response to this need, a new European organization has been established: the European Organization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergence of Robust 1D Atomic and Electronic Textures in Mn Ultrathin Films via Antiferromagnet-Ferromagnet Interfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[1D electronic structures on 2D crystalline surfaces are crucial for investigating low-dimensional quantum phenomena and enabling the development of dimensionally engineered nanodevices. However, the inherent periodic symmetry of 2D atomic lattices generally leads to delocalized electronic band extending across the surface, making the creation of periodic 1D electronic states a significant challenge. Here, robust 1D electronic ordering is demonstrated in ultrathin Mn films grown on an atomically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905289/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of beam quality for lumbar spine imaging with heavy metal filters: a phantom model study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In radiological imaging, much research has been conducted on tube voltage and additional filters to reduce radiation exposure. In this study, the usefulness of heavy metal filters in lumbar spine imaging to maintain image quality and reduce radiation dose was investigated. A human-body phantom was irradiated with various combinations of tube voltages (70, 75, 80, 85, and 90 kV) and filters (Cu, Gd, Ho, Yb, W). For all beam qualities, the mAs value was adjusted so that the amount of CsI...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of intravascular lithotripsy according to the timing of stent failure: Insights from the COIL registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Procedural and clinical outcomes following IVL treatment for patients with SF were influenced by the timing of index stent implantation. Further studies are needed to better understand the mechanisms behind recurrent SF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40905087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of false feedback on state memory distrust towards commission and omission and recognition memory errors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memory distrust, the subjective appraisal of one's memory functioning, comprises two aspects: distrust over omission errors (e.g. forgetting) and distrust over commission errors (e.g. falsely remembering). Although these aspects have been studied, how they relate to memory validation (e.g. forming autobiographical beliefs) and memory reporting remains unclear. In this study, we experimentally examined how metacognitive appraisals influence memory validation and errors in memory reporting....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fuelling aortic stenosis: the integral role of 6-phosphofructo-2-kinase/fructose-2,6-biphosphatase 3-mediated glycolysis in Lp(a)-induced valve inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lipoprotein(a)-induced PFKFB3-mediated glycolysis in VICs sustains NF-κB-dependent inflammatory response. These insights into the inflammation-metabolic axis may offer a more refined approach to decrease valvular inflammation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aneurysmal bone cyst of the talus: a case report of local recurrence treated with adjuvant therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aneurysmal bone cyst (ABC) is a locally destructive benign tumour-like condition of the bones with blood-filled cystic cavities. The talus is an extremely rare site for an ABC, with <20 reported cases till 2012 based on a PubMed database search. Aneurysmal bone cyst recurrence in the talus after curettage and bone grafting is extremely rare. To the best of our knowledge, no detailed reports of resection and adjuvant therapy with artificial bone packing of recurrent ABC of the talus have been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes associated with use of makyokansekito, a Japanese herbal kampo medicine, in outpatients with community-acquired pneumonia: A retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The use of makyokansekito in outpatients with CAP was not associated with a reduction in hospitalization.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40904434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori Screening and Eradication in Junior High School Students in Yokosuka, Japan: Prevalence, Eradication Rates, and Challenges]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: H. pylori has low prevalence among Japanese junior high school students in an urban area, with modest eradication success. The low participation and dropout rates highlight the need for improved strategies to boost engagement and ensure comprehensive screening and treatment for better program outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pareidolic Illusions and Associated Lower Regional Gray Matter Volumes in Community-Dwelling Older Adults Without Dementia: The Arakawa 65+ Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pareidolic illusions were relatively common in community-dwelling older adults without dementia. These illusions may be an early marker of neurodegenerative changes affecting visuoperceptual pathways, and may be detectable using NPT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Martini 3 Coarse-Grained Models for Carbon Nanomaterials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Martini model is a coarse-grained force field allowing simulations of biomolecular systems as well as a range of materials including different types of nanomaterials of technological interest. Recently, a new version of the force field (version 3) has been released that includes new parameters for lipids, proteins, carbohydrates, and a number of small molecules, but not yet carbon nanomaterials. Here, we present new Martini models for three major types of carbon nanomaterials: fullerene,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extracellular Vesicles in Arthropods: Biogenesis, Functions, Isolation Methods and Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extracellular vesicles (EVs) are membrane-bound nanoparticles secreted by cells that are involved in multiple forms of intercellular communication and show promising potential for biotechnological applications. Arthropod-derived EV research remains relatively fragmented in contrast to the extensively studied mammalian EV field. In this review, we present a comprehensive synthesis of over 100 studies exploring EV biology across arthropods - including insects, arachnids and crustaceans....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ants and extrafloral nectary-bearing plants: A dataset of interactions and outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extrafloral nectaries (EFNs) are specialized plant glands that secrete nectar but are not related to pollination. Several ants feed on EFNs and, in exchange, they often attack herbivores, reducing the consumption of leaf tissue and floral parts, and enhancing plant performance. Although most empirical studies and reviews have demonstrated that ant visitation benefits EFN-bearing plants, many others have failed to show ants as protective partners. Despite the increasing number of papers dealing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chronotropic incompetence during exercise or pharmacological stress is associated with reduced survival in patients with chronic coronary syndromes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with chronic coronary syndromes, CI during exercise or pharmacological stress is a simple and objective predictor of survival.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steering CO<sub>2</sub> Electroreduction Pathway via Tuning Microenvironment of Cobalt Center in Molecular Catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Owing to its chemical stability and molecular-level structural tunability, the molecular electrocatalyst cobalt phthalocyanine (CoPc) demonstrates significant potential for the electrochemical reduction of CO(2) (CO(2)RR). However, the specific catalytic reaction process of CO(2)RR and the dynamic structural evolution mechanisms of CoPc remain a contentious subject. Elucidating the reaction pathways of CO(2) electroreduction to CO and tracking structural evolution pose substantial challenges. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RoAM: computational reconstruction of ancient methylomes and identification of differentially methylated regions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present a new and considerably improved version of RoAM (Reconstruction of Ancient Methylation), a flexible tool for reconstructing ancient methylomes and identifying differentially methylated regions (DMRs) between populations. Through a series of filtering and quality control steps, RoAM produces highly reliable DNA methylation maps, making it a valuable tool for paleoepigenomics studies. We apply RoAM to pre-and post-Neolithic transition Balkan samples, and uncover DMRs in genes related to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Positively Charged Polyurethane Scaffolds Reshape the Microenvironment to Promote Endogenous Regeneration after Brain Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traumatic brain injury (TBI) induces a prolonged inflammatory response throughout the damaged brain, which is exacerbated by the sustained accumulation of damage-associated molecular patterns (DAMPs), and consequently impairs endogenous neural regeneration significantly. To mitigate postinjury inflammation and explore the role of positively charged scaffolds in brain repair, two distinct structures of positively charged scaffolds were developed. Both scaffold types effectively reduce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do Patients Comply With 12-h Lithium Blood Level Timing? Findings From a Controlled Clinical Trial and a Real-World Clinical Setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Approximately half of lithium blood tests do not comply with guideline-based recommendations for 12-h trough levels, emphasizing the need for solutions to solve this clinical need.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Screening for non-invasive rsRNA biomarkers to assess embryo quality utilizing ultra-sensitive pandora sequencing combined with machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Specific rsRNAs, particularly 5.8S and 28-2S, may serve as non-invasive biomarkers for embryo selection in IVF. These findings highlight the potential roles of rsRNAs in embryonic development and provide a molecular basis for improving IVF outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Visual Abstract: Oncologic outcomes of intraoperative autologous blood transfusion for major oncologic resection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Visual Abstract: Exploring the Role of CDO1 in Breast Cancer: Insights into Tumor Biology and Therapeutic Potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40908448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250905033911&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>