<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 07:37:27 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FAR1-RELATED SEQUENCE 5 prevents photobleaching under short days by balancing chlorophyll biosynthetic gene expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plants must precisely regulate the expression of chlorophyll biosynthetic genes to prevent overaccumulation of photosensitive intermediates that cause photobleaching. GOLDEN 2-LIKEs activate the expression of certain chlorophyll biosynthetic genes, including HEMA1, but not others, such as HEMC, suggesting the involvement of additional regulatory factors to balance the expression of chlorophyll biosynthetic genes. We report that the Arabidopsis (Arabidopsis thaliana) far1-related sequence 5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Standard Reference Thermoelectric Module: Enhancing Durability and Reproducibility through Metallic Materials and Geometric Thermoelectric Leg Shapes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Reliable standard modules are critical to ensure reproducibility and comparability in thermoelectric measurements across research laboratories. In this study, the development of a standard reference thermoelectric module (SRTEM) is presented to address this unmet need by providing a reproducible calibration platform for cross-laboratory thermoelectric measurement standardization. The SRTEM comprises eight p-n thermocouple pairs formed from metallic alloys─p-type Ni(90)Cr(10) (Chromel) and n-type...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workplace Violence, Normalization of Violence, and Psychological Distress Among Korean Nurses: A Cross-Sectional Analytic Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Workplace violence remains prevalent during infectious disease outbreaks, with a substantial proportion of nurses normalizing these experiences. This normalization is associated with distinct patterns of psychological distress, underscoring the need for increased awareness and the provision of tailored psychological support. Enhancing workplace safety measures is essential to protecting nursing well-being.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between fish consumption and mortality risk from overall cardiovascular disease and its subtypes: a 20-year prospective cohort analysis by sex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We found that higher fish consumption is associated with a reduced risk of CVD mortality in Korean women. Sex-specific dietary strategies may be necessary for the effective prevention and management of CVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved Mechanical Stability and Proton Conductivity of Reinforced Membranes for Proton Exchange Membrane Fuel Cells (PEMFCs)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As one of the electrochemical systems based on green chemistry, the fuel cell (FC) demonstrates strong sustainability in generating electricity without CO(2) emissions. It operates primarily through the transportation of protons via a proton exchange membrane (PEM). However, the PEM requires high proton conductivity along with chemical and mechanical stability to improve FC performance. To develop PEMs at a low cost, researchers have explored various methods, including adding additives,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The regulatory role of CASZ1 in keratinocyte differentiation and skin barrier function in atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Genotypic Variations in the Anthocyanin Biosynthetic Pathway in Potatoes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anthocyanins are pigments that contribute to plant defense and adaptation to environmental stresses. Given their antioxidant properties and positive impacts on human health, enhancing anthocyanin biosynthesis in plants holds significant economic importance. In potato, several genotypes produce a high amount of anthocyanins, but the molecular mechanisms underlying the genotypic variation of anthocyanin content remain poorly understood. Here, key genes that may determine the genotype-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ERK-driven autophagy enhances synergy of eribulin and cisplatin in triple-negative breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC) remains one of the most aggressive subtypes of breast cancer with limited therapeutic options, especially in resource-limited settings. The present study investigated the mechanistic synergy of eribulin and cisplatin in TNBC, with a focus on ERK-driven autophagy. MDA-MB-231 TNBC cells were treated with eribulin and cisplatin. Viability, apoptosis, autophagy and ERK activation were assessed using Cell Counting Kit-8 assays, flow cytometry, western blotting and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of smartphone addiction on obesity in children and adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The objective of this study is to ascertain the long-term risk of obesity associated with smartphone addiction in children and adolescents. We utilized a 4-year dataset from the Korean Children and Youth Survey 2018 (2018-2021). At baseline, the sample comprised 2,607 4th-grade elementary school students and 2,590 1st-grade middle school students (mean age: 11.3 ± 0.3, 14.3 ± 0.3 years, respectively). Of these, 2,718 (52.3%) were boys. Obesity was defined as a body mass index Z-score of at least...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neoadjuvant CTLA-4/PD-(L)1 Blockade Versus Surgery +/- Chemotherapy in Deficient Mismatch Repair/Microsatellite Instability-High Resectable Gastroesophageal Adenocarcinoma: Individual Patient Data Pooled Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In resectable dMMR/MSI-H GEA, neoadjuvant ICIs significantly increase pathologic response and downstaging versus FLOT, with comparable EFS/OS with surgery with or without chemotherapy. The higher proportion of ypN0 and lack of ypT4 after neoadjuvant ICIs versus FLOT should drive preoperative treatment choices in clinical high-risk disease. The high proportion of pCR/MPR with ICIs provides rationale for exploring organ-sparing surgery or nonoperative management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021880/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Meaningful Activity Mediate the Relationship Between Social Support and Cognitive Health Among Community-Dwelling Older Adults?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the population continues to age, cognitive health becomes increasingly vital. Although social support and meaningful activities impact cognitive and psychological outcomes, how these factors are interrelated remains unclear. Using cross-sectional data from the Well Elderly II study (n = 460), this study examined (1) the effects of social support on cognitive health (measured by the Digit Symbol Substitution Test) and (2) whether engagement in meaningful activities mediates the relationship...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The combined effects of rTMS and upper extremity robotic therapy for restoring upper extremity function in patients with spinal cord injury: A randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study suggests that combining rTMS with upper extremity robotic therapy may have potential benefits for upper extremity function in patients with SCI. However, the addition of rTMS did not demonstrate clear superiority over robotic therapy alone. Further research with larger cohorts and optimized protocols is warranted to clarify its therapeutic value.Trial registration: Clinical Research Information Service, Republic of Korea identifier: KCT0004443.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021824/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current experiences with teclistamab in patients with multiple myeloma and renal impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Renal impairment (RI), defined as a creatinine clearance of < 40 mL/min, affects up to half of patients with multiple myeloma (MM). Patients with MM and RI historically had poorer outcomes, likely due to the limited access to novel treatments available through clinical trials. Strict eligibility criteria for MM clinical trials often exclude patients with RI, necessitating reliance on patient data acquired from real-world (RW) clinical practice to guide therapeutic decisions....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy of modified bloodless del Nido cardioplegia in isolated aortic valve replacement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to evaluate the safety and efficacy of a modified, bloodless Del Nido (DN) cardioplegia solution in patients undergoing isolated aortic valve replacement (AVR). A total of 370 patients who underwent isolated AVR between 2015 and 2022 were retrospectively analyzed. Patients were categorized into two groups based on the cardioplegia solution used: the bloodless DN group (N = 180) and the histidine-tryptophan-ketoglutarate (HTK) group (N = 190). To reduce selection bias and adjust...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gender-specific relationships between hearing loss, its rehabilitation, and quality of life in middle-aged and older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND SIGNIFICANCE: Republic of Korea Male patients with disabling HL experienced a greater decline in QOL and hearing aids might be associated with preserving vitality in males. Further research is required to elucidate greater vulnerability to HL in males.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatially resolved endothelial signaling via nampt-itga5 drives immune evasion in stem-like gastric cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study delineates spatially defined cellular programs that contribute to immune escape in stem-like GC, highlighting a novel VISFATIN-integrin signaling axis as a potential biomarker and therapeutic target in immunotherapy-resistant tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021026/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design and synthesis of advanced electrode materials: from Li-ion to Na-ion batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rising demand for lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) and sodium-ion batteries (SIBs) as power sources has increased the need for advanced electrode materials that offer improved electrochemical performance and structural durability. While research at the cell and pack system levels is essential to meet these requirements, material-level research plays a critical role and should be prioritized. This feature article presents a comprehensive overview of design and synthesis approaches for cathode and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021011/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting Curcumin in Cancer Therapy: Recent Insights into Molecular Mechanisms, Nanoformulations, and Synergistic Combinations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Curcumin has been extensively investigated as an anticancer agent, yet its clinical application remains constrained by low bioavailability, incomplete mechanistic understanding, and limited therapeutic optimization. In light of growing resistance to conventional chemotherapies and the demand for safer, multi-targeted agents, this review revisits curcumin with a contemporary lens. We critically evaluate the literature published since 2020, focusing on newly elucidated molecular mechanisms by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors for Emergence Agitation in the Postanesthesia Care Unit: A Propensity Score-Matched Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients who have undergone surgery under general anesthesia and present with the risk factors identified in this study should be regarded as high risk for EA. Nurses in the PACU should identify and effectively manage these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Study of Clinical Outcomes for Total Thyroidectomy/Lobectomy and Isthmusectomy in Patients with Isthmic Papillary Thyroid Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The optimal surgical extent for isthmus-confined papillary thyroid carcinoma (PTC) remains unclear. We aimed to evaluate the clinicopathological characteristics, surgical complications, and recurrence rates based on the extent of resection. Methods: This retrospective cohort study included 345 patients who underwent thyroidectomy for solitary isthmus-confined PTC at two affiliated tertiary centers from 2013 to 2022. Patients were excluded if they had multifocal PTC with lobar...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How We Do It: Optimal Fixation Technique for Donor Graft in Suction Blister Epidermal Grafting for Vitiligo Using One-Sided Adhesive Dressing Material]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020505/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct oral anticoagulants in very elderly and high bleeding risk patients with atrial fibrillation often excluded from oral anticoagulation therapy: a nationwide population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In very elderly, high-bleeding risk patients with AF, DOACs which were prescribed in usual clinical practice showed better effectiveness and positive net clinical benefit compared to no OAC treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological assessment and potential health risks of naturally occurring radioactive materials in Kuakata Sea Beach sand: implications for rare-earth resources and nuclear fuel cycle feasibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To assess the natural radioactivity levels and associated health risks in beach sand from Kuakata Sea Beach, this study performed a comprehensive radiological analysis of systematically collected sand samples using high-purity germanium (HPGe) γ-ray spectroscopy. The average (range) radioactivity levels of ^(226)Ra, ^(232)Th, and ^(40)K in the examined sand samples were 57 (37-105), 121 (76-231), and 210 (181-270) Bq kg^(-1), respectively, thus markedly higher than the world average values of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-Term Exposure to Fine Particulate Matter (PM<sub>2.5</sub>), Cause Specific-Mortality, and High-Risk Populations: A Nationwide Time-Stratified Case-Crossover Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Numerous studies have reported that short-term exposure to fine particulate matter (PM(2.5)) is associated with mortality risk; however, results on high-risk populations and regions have been mixed. This study performed a nationwide time-stratified case-crossover study to assess the association between short-term PM(2.5) and mortality in South Korea (2015-2019) by each cause of death and age group. A machine-learning ensemble PM(2.5) prediction model was used to cover unmonitored districts. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020063/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting the hypoxia signaling pathway with nanomedicine to reverse immunotherapy resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immunotherapy has emerged as a major therapeutic strategy for cancer; however, immunotherapy resistance remains a significant challenge. Hypoxia, a key hallmark of the tumor microenvironment resulting from the imbalance between the high oxygen demand of rapidly proliferating cancer cells and the limited supply from abnormal blood vessels, plays a central role in driving immunotherapy resistance. Hypoxia-inducible factor-1α (HIF-1α) and its downstream signaling pathways contribute to this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Affecting Workplace Bullying Perpetration Among Experienced Intensive Care Unit Nurses: A Secondary Analysis Focusing on Narcissistic Personality, Perfectionistic Self-Presentation, and Mentalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aim: Workplace bullying is a critical issue faced by nurses globally. This study aimed to examine factors influencing workplace bullying perpetration among experienced intensive care unit nurses in South Korea, while controlling for organizational culture. Specifically, it investigated how narcissistic personality, perfectionistic self-presentation, and mentalization affected bullying perpetration. Methods: In this cross-sectional secondary analysis, data were collected between July 1 and August...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth, chemical, and biochemical composition of <em>Conocarpus erectus</em> L. in response to NPK fertilizers and extracts of active dry yeast, seaweeds, and green tea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conocarpus erectus L. is one of the ornamental shrubs or trees that are utilized in different aspects in landscape (gardens, cities, roads, etc.). Fertilization program is an essential factor affecting the aesthetic characters of this plant species. Pots experiment was conducted in a randomized completed split plot design with the aim to study the effects of NPK fertilizers at the levels of 100%, 75%, and 50% of the suggested doses of 18, 12, and 6 g/plant from ammonium sulfate, calcium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional scaffolds design strategies for retinal repair and regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing strain placed on both society and the healthcare system due to an ageing population should not be underestimated. Age-related macular degeneration (AMD) is a leading cause of blindness worldwide and is projected to affect 288 million people globally by 2040. Current treatment options for AMD primarily focus on disease management rather than offering a definitive cure. Retinal tissue engineering, which aims to develop targeted regenerative strategies to restore or replace damaged...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endocrine complications after solid organ transplantation in childhood and adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that endocrine and metabolic complications are common in pediatric SOT recipients. Effective surveillance and management of these sequelae are crucial to improve long-term quality of life following SOT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Siegesbeckia Glabrescens</em> Extract Ameliorates Immobilization-Induced Muscle Atrophy by Regulating the Akt/mTOR/FoxO3a Signaling Pathways in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Siegesbeckia glabrescens, traditionally used for its anti-inflammatory properties and potential musculoskeletal benefits. In the present study, we investigated whether a standardized hot water extract of S. glabrescens (SGE), rich in the bioactive compound kirenol, could mitigate muscle atrophy caused by immobilization in a mouse model. Male C57BL/6J mice underwent hindlimb immobilization for 1 week to induce muscle atrophy, followed by 1 week of daily oral treatments with either saline or SGE...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let There Be Light for Photoproximity Labeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bioluminescence-assisted photoproximity labeling enables spatial proteome mapping in deep tissues.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019104/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunomodulatory peptide-drug conjugate MEL-dKLA suppresses progression of prostate cancer by eliminating M2-like tumor-associated macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prostate cancer is one of the most common malignancies in men and is frequently associated with tumor-promoting inflammation. Tumor-associated macrophages (TAMs) are known to facilitate cancer progression by suppressing antitumor immunity. Therefore, targeting TAMs represents a promising strategy for cancer therapy. This study aimed to investigate whether melittin-dKLA, a conjugated peptide consisting of melittin (MEL), which selectively binds M2-like macrophages, and the pro-apoptotic peptide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Analysis of Primary and Second Primary Multiple Myeloma: A Propensity Score-Matched Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with SPMM, most of whom had well-controlled primary cancers, received active treatment and demonstrated clinical outcomes not significantly different from those with primary MM. These findings support the use of aggressive treatment strategies for SPMM. Larger prospective studies are warranted to establish optimal treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Third eyelid flap for correction of proptosis-induced lateral strabismus in two dogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report describes the use of a third eyelid flap to correct proptosis-induced lateral strabismus in two dogs: a 3-year-old castrated male Pomeranian (Case 1) and a 2-year-old intact female Bichon Frise (Case 2). In both cases, the third eyelid was sutured to the dorsolateral conjunctiva using a horizontal mattress suture. However, conjunctival elongation at the suture site compromised flap function, necessitating reoperation. In Case 2, a second horizontal mattress suture was added to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Clinical evaluation of a novel fixed-dose combination tablet (Sentorpil<sup>®</sup> ForteGold) versus compounded powdered medications in dogs with myxomatous mitral valve disease: a randomized, double-blind study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fvets.2025.1622383.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018964/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-Asian consortium for treatment and research in ALS (PACTALS) guidelines for management of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Pan-Asian Consortium for Treatment and Research in ALS (PACTALS) guidelines were developed for the management of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) patients living in the Asia-Pacific countries, taking into consideration the ethnic, racial and economic diversity of the region. The majority of patients reside in low-income (limited-resource setting) and middle-income countries. Grading of Recommendations Assessment, Development, and Evaluation (GRADE) methodology was utilised for development...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-Guided Pharmacopuncture for Lateral Epicondylitis Initially Misdiagnosed Due to Incomplete Common Extensor Tendon Evaluation: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lateral epicondylitis is a common musculoskeletal condition caused by repetitive strain, most frequently affecting the extensor carpi radialis brevis (ECRB) muscle. Although musculoskeletal ultrasonography is a valuable diagnostic tool, limited scanning of the common extensor tendon (CET) might result in missed diagnoses. Therefore, accurate evaluation requires a comprehensive assessment of both superficial and deep tendon fibers. A 45-year-old woman presented with persistent right lateral elbow...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018875/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Status and Needs Analysis of Korean Medicine Doctors' Continuing Professional Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Findings indicate that KMDs desire increased practical training opportunities, competency-based standardized curricula, and expanded scope of practice through institutional support. Establishing competency frameworks across clinical departments and strengthening competencies required in modern healthcare environments are essential for advancing Korean Medicine practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Veratramine Inhibits Human Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer Cell Growth by Inhibiting the Hedgehog Signaling Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Veratramine suppresses lung cancer cell growth by inhibiting the Hh signaling pathway, suggesting its potential applicability in the treatment of NSCLC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018869/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI‑Enhanced Smartwatch AHI Estimation and AI‑Scored Polysomnography for Obstructive Sleep Apnea: Real‑World Validation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that the evaluated smartwatch-based AHI estimation algorithm shows high concordance with PSG-derived values, particularly for the detection and classification of moderate to severe OSA. However, it should be noted that this smartwatch algorithm tends to underestimate the AHI of OSA due to limitations in scoring unit and recording duration calculation. These findings support the clinical utility of wearable technology as a practical and scalable tool for early...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018852/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determinants of the lost to follow-up status among patients with tuberculosis who emigrated to the Republic of Korea: a mixed-method study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Tuberculosis (TB) remains a significant global health concern, with foreign migrants in the Republic of Korea (ROK) representing a particularly vulnerable group; despite comprising only 3.5% of the population, they account for over 5% of annual TB cases and exhibit disproportionately high rates of lost to follow up (LTFU) from treatment compared to native Koreans. This mixed-methods study aimed to identify key factors influencing non-adherence to treatment and LTFU among migrants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoparticle-assisted gene editing for genomic disorders in the central nervous system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HOS15 together with PWR-HDA9 positively regulates dark-induced senescence in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Senescence is a conserved phenomenon in all living organisms, including plants. The initiation and progression of leaf senescence can be triggered by natural internal factors or induced by external stress conditions. Over the past few decades, several transcriptional regulators, histone deacetylases/acetyltransferases (HDACs/HATs), signaling transduction pathway components, hormonal regulators, and other proteins have been extensively studied and reported to play a role in regulating leaf...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent technological advances in video capsule endoscopy: a comprehensive review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Video capsule endoscopy (VCE) originally revolutionized gastrointestinal imaging by providing a noninvasive method for evaluating small bowel diseases. Recent technological innovations, including enhanced imaging systems, artificial intelligence (AI), and improved localization, have significantly improved VCE's diagnostic accuracy, efficiency, and clinical utility. This review aims to summarize and evaluate recent technological advances in VCE, focusing on system comparisons, image enhancement,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applying small bowel endoscopy in inflammatory bowel disease management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease is classified into Crohn's disease (CD) and ulcerative colitis. Ulcerative colitis involves only the colon, whereas CD is characterized by small bowel involvement, which is a hallmark feature. However, the small bowel is the final frontier of endoscopic evaluation; therefore, small bowel involvement is considered a significant medical challenge in the diagnosis and treatment of patients with CD. Endoscopic visualization and biopsy sampling of the small bowel are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017552/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coordinated inhibition of M1 macrophage polarization by FIT2-mediated lipid droplet biosynthesis and FABP5]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid droplets (LDs) serve as dynamic organelles central to host immune response and bacterial infection resistance by recruiting multiple proteins and peptides with established antiviral and antibacterial properties. Although macrophage polarization is integral to both innate immunity and lipid homeostasis, the regulatory influence of LDs on this process remains unclear. In this study, augmentation of LDs via oleic acid (OA) treatment attenuated M1 polarization in RAW264.7 macrophages. Given...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of cell viability, apoptosis, and autophagy in pancreatic cancer cells using therapeutic ultrasound with microbubbles and gemcitabine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TUS combined with microbubbles and gemcitabine synergistically induces cell death in pancreatic cancer cells through mechanical bioeffects and enhanced drug delivery, mediated by both apoptosis induction and autophagy modulation. These findings highlight a promising strategy for improving pancreatic cancer treatment outcomes, warranting further in vivo and clinical studies to optimize parameters and assess translational potential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ECM-integrated hanging drop platform for spatially controlled assessment of immune cell regulated tumour invasion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The tumour immune microenvironment (TIME) plays a crucial role in tumour progression and metastasis. Although spheroids effectively model tumour invasion by mimicking in vivo 3D structures, their formation and subsequent mixing with the matrix make it difficult to control their position in the 3D matrix, leading to deep embedding and hindering the assessment of immune cell-mediated regulation of invasion. This paper introduces an extracellular matrix (ECM)-integrated hanging drop platform that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hwan Yung Chung : Founder of Korean Spinal Neurosurgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Professor Chung, an Emeritus Professor at Hanyang University School of Medicine, was a pioneering figure in Korean neurosurgery. After serving as an Army Surgeon during the Korean War, he specialized in neurosurgery, training under Professor Joo Geol Lee at Capital Medical College. Throughout his career, Professor Chung introduced numerous innovations in spinal surgery, including lumbar interbody fusion with metal support, anterior cervical foraminotomy, and the early adoption of microsurgery...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Naïve Dialecticism and Conceptions of Relationship Flourishing From an East Asian Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Academic AbstractThis paper challenges Western-centric models of relationship quality that deem satisfaction, steadiness in aspects of relationships (i.e., stability), and romantic dyads as ideal by incorporating naïve dialecticism rooted in East Asian philosophies. Naïve dialecticism encompasses the tolerance of contradictions, the anticipation of change, and holism. By examining how these principles manifest in relationship processes and functioning that diverge from Western models, we offer a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017252/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cytosolic fMet-Protein Synthesis as Source of Endogenous Ligands for Formyl Peptide Receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Formyl peptides, exemplified by the synthetic tripeptide formyl-Met-Leu-Phe (fMLF), are well-established ligands for formyl peptide receptors (FPRs), central to neutrophil chemotaxis, and innate immune signaling. Traditionally attributed to bacterial and mitochondrial origins, these peptides are now proposed to arise from an additional, stress-inducible source within the eukaryotic cytosol. Recent findings suggest that under specific stress conditions, eukaryotic translation can initiate with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017204/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[2025 Focused Update of the Seoul Consensus on Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease: Evidence-based Recommendations on Acid Suppressive Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD) is a chronic and relapsing gastrointestinal disorder characterized by the reflux of gastric contents into the esophagus, leading to troublesome symptoms and/or complications. Since the publication of the 2020 Seoul Consensus on GERD, significant new evidence has emerged, particularly regarding acid-suppressive therapies and diagnostic approaches. This 2025 focused update aims to refine GERD management strategies by incorporating the latest evidence on acid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological and Clinical Features of Regional Odontodysplasia in South Korean Pediatric Patients: A Multicenter Case Series Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This multicenter study provides the first comprehensive dataset on RO in Korean children and adolescents. These findings will contribute to the development of clinical guidelines and inform future healthcare policies for the management of rare dental anomalies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Simultaneous Multifrequency Modulated Wireless Information and Power Transfer for a Triboelectronic Monitoring System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound-driven triboelectric nanogenerators (US-TENGs) address energy supply challenges for implantable medical microsystems, underwater sensing and monitoring microsystems, etc., and are achieving increasingly important applications. In this work, multifrequency modulated simultaneous wireless power and information transmission (MF-SWIPT) technology is proposed for a US-TENG that allows both the power and information flows to be transmitted continuously without interruption. The deliberately...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune-Epigenetic Effects of Environmental Pollutants: Mechanisms, Biomarkers, and Transgenerational Impact]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental pollutants such as heavy metals, endocrine-disrupting chemicals, microplastics, and airborne particulates are increasingly recognized for their potential to influence immune function through epigenetic mechanisms. This review examines conserved pollutant-associated pathways at interfaces of immunity and epigenetics, with particular attention to Toll-like receptor-NF-κB signalling, NLRP3 inflammasome activity, and reactive oxygen species-driven cascades. Evidence from cellular,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>DeepPhysioRecon</em>: Tracing peripheral physiology in low frequency fMRI dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many studies of the human brain using functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI) lack physiological measurements, which substantially impacts the interpretation and richness of fMRI studies. Natural fluctuations in autonomic physiology, such as breathing and heart rate, provide windows into critical functions, including cognition, emotion, and health, and can heavily influence fMRI signals. Here, we developed DeepPhysioRecon, a Long-Short-Term-Memory (LSTM)-based network that decodes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative imaging of individual bacterial cells: <em>E. coli</em> and <em>B. subtilis</em> via terahertz scattering-type scanning near-field optical microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This technique offers a nonlabel, noninvasive method for bacterial identification, with promising implications for advanced biomedical applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fluorescence Modulation in UiO-66-NH<sub>2</sub> via Photooxidation and Selective Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-organic frameworks with emissive ligands offer tunable photophysical properties that are sensitive to their coordination environment and structural configuration. In this study, we demonstrate that the fluorescence of UiO-66-NH(2) can be modulated through photo-oxidation-induced quenching and subsequent solvent-mediated recovery. Upon visible-light irradiation, reactive oxygen species induce two distinct oxidation pathways: irreversible oxidation of the ligand and reversible oxidation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photoirradiation-Promoted <em>ipso</em>-Azidation of 1-Aryltriazenes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021912/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultraviolet (UV) irradiation (λ(max) = 370 nm) of a methanol solution of 1-aryltriazenes and azidotrimethylsilane promotes ipso-azidation. Optimization of the reaction conditions and a mechanistic study revealed that the hydrazoic acid generated in situ enabled efficient transformation. The high functional group tolerance of this reaction allowed for the transformation of a broad range of 1-aryltriazenes, including those introduced on a protein, to the corresponding aryl azides.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021912/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Statins for Oxaliplatin-Induced Peripheral Neuropathy: A Multicenter Retrospective Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chemotherapy-induced peripheral neuropathy, including oxaliplatin-induced peripheral neuropathy (OIPN), can have a negative impact on patient quality of life for months or even years after discontinuation of chemotherapy. Statins are commonly used for lowering cholesterol; however, evidence indicates that statins have multiple pleiotropic effects. Although statins are anticipated to exert neuroprotective actions against OIPN, no large-scale investigations have been conducted in real-world...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021349/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dimensionally Tunable Rod-Shaped Zirconia Particles via Bottom-Up Assembly]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The synthesis of anisotropic particles is highly desirable due to their broad potential applications. However, achieving well-controlled anisotropic morphologies without templates remains a significant challenge. In this work, we present a solvothermal approach utilizing cosolvent systems to synthesize uniform, monodispersed rod-like zirconia particles with precisely controlled dimensions. Comparative studies between single-solvent systems (water and ethanol) and water/alcohol cosolvent systems...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of pediatric chest CT examinations on lens exposure: a Monte Carlo simulation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of the study was to evaluate the degree of error between Monte Carlo simulations of pediatric lens dose outside the scan range and measured values obtained with a dosimeter. Two types of computed tomography (CT) equipment and three pediatric anthropomorphic phantoms were used, each with a nanoDot optically stimulated luminescence dosimeter (nanoDot OSLD; Landauer, Inc., Glenwood, IL, USA) mounted on its left and right lenses. The scatter dose measurements obtained from the nanoDot were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Playing Sports, Placing Sports Bets? Sports Club Membership, Gambling Norms and Sports Gambling Behavior among Flemish Youth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent years, gambling has become increasingly embedded in sports culture, a phenomenon known as "gamblification", raising concerns about youth exposure to sports betting. This study explores the role of descriptive norms (perceived peer gambling behavior) and injunctive norms (perceived peer approval) within Flemish sports clubs, assessing their impact on youths' (18-25 year old) online sports betting frequency. Using a quantitative cross-sectional survey (N = 1,290), results indicated that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracholecystic papillary neoplasm mimicking a submucosal tumor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intracholecystic papillary neoplasms (ICPN) are a rare type of gallbladder papillary neoplasms. They demonstrate more complex morphological and immunohistochemical features than intraductal papillary mucinous neoplasms or intraductal papillary neoplasms of the bile duct. Moreover, gallbladder tumors sometimes show an irregular appearance owing to Rokitansky-Aschoff sinus (RAS) involvement. Herein, we report a case of ICPN that mimicked a submucosal tumor. An 81-year-old man presented to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021177/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical performance of a hydrophobic acrylic toric intraocular lens with a double C-loop haptics in Japanese patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The PODEYE TORIC IOL with 1.00-6.00 D cylinder powers and double C-loop haptics effectively corrected corneal astigmatism in Japanese patients after cataract surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of a regenerative endodontic procedures model of mature mouse teeth and evaluation of the wound healing process]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the pulp regeneration for non-vital teeth is one of the ultimate clinical achievements, regenerative endodontic procedures (REPs) have become the most explored treatment modality. In this technique, periodontal tissue is guided from the apical region into the root canal and pulp chamber to promote attachment. It is well established that immature teeth are effective targets for treatment. However, the indications for this treatment have not yet expanded sufficiently to encompass mature teeth...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AtPrx71-mediated regulation of stem elongation, gravitropic response, and IAA accumulation in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We demonstrated that Arabidopsis peroxidase AtPrx71 inhibits stem growth and gravitropism response via IAA catabolism, and speculate that other vascular plants, including poplar, may have the same functional peroxidase. Poplar peroxidase CWPO-C, which exhibits significant substrate versatility, has been suggested to participate in IAA catabolism. We previously demonstrated that AtPrx71, which shares the highest amino acid sequence identity with CWPO-C (68%) among Arabidopsis thaliana...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced cerebrospinal fluid taurine is associated with nigrostriatal dopaminergic deficits in drug-naïve Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The relationship between plasma or cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) amino acid levels and the pathophysiology of Parkinson's disease (PD) remains unclear. We aimed to examine the association of plasma and CSF amino acid levels with the nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons and the clinical symptoms of newly diagnosed drug-naïve patients with PD. This was a cross-sectional study using the Jikei University PD registry. A total of 45 amino acids were measured in both plasma and CSF, and their associations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021023/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extensive LGE and FDG/PYP uptake mimicking infiltrative disease: A case of triple-vessel coronary artery disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic diversity of BoLA-DRB3 in Latin American Creole cattle: an update of the state of the art]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetic diversity of the bovine leukocyte antigen BoLA-DRB3 gene has been reported in cattle breeds due to its central role in immune response. However, the gene has been characterized in only a few Latin American native cattle breeds. In this study, we aimed to investigate the genetic diversity of this gene in other native bovine breeds from Argentina, Bolivia, Cuba, and Paraguay, thereby contributing to the global knowledge regarding BoLA-DRB3 diversity. The gene was genotyped using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrator Complex Subunit 6 Regulates Biological Nature of Hepatocellular Carcinoma by Modulating Epithelial-Mesenchymal Transition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is a leading cause of cancer-related death worldwide, with limited therapeutic options and frequent resistance to treatment. The integrator complex subunit 6 (INTS6), a regulator of RNA polymerase II transcription, has emerged as a potential tumor suppressor that modulates Wnt/β-catenin signaling and epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT). This study aimed to clarify the role of INTS6 in EMT regulation in HCC and to explore the therapeutic potential of small...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Production of dimethyldiselenide from methaneseleninic acid by soil bacteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We isolated 23 soil bacterial strains tolerating methaneseleninic acid (MSeA), an oxidized organoselenium metabolite. Among them, Pseudomonas sp. M10 exhibited the highest MSeA tolerance and converted MSeA into volatile dimethyldiselenide, consistent with a redox-driven, non-enzymatic process. This is the first report of bacterially mediated MSeA volatilization, revealing a previously unrecognized microbial contribution to selenium flux between terrestrial and atmospheric compartments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A ratiometric fluorescent probe with dual red/near-infrared emissions for monitoring lysosomal pH fluctuations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lysosomal pH is a crucial intracellular parameter for evaluating cellular metabolism, as even minor fluctuations are closely associated with various physiological disorders. Ratiometric fluorescent probes have been developed for monitoring lysosomal pH changes through molecular imaging. However, most of the reported probes suffer from limitations such as inadequate intracellular calibration and short excitation and emission wavelengths, which hinder their accurate pH quantification and restrict...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of real-time monitoring for administered activity during Lu-177 infusion by imaging the administration site using a pinhole gamma camera: a Monte Carlo study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Monte Carlo simulations demonstrated the feasibility of real-time monitoring of administered activity during Lu-177 infusion by imaging the administration site with our pinhole gamma camera.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Are insufficient diagnostic criteria for anastomotic leakage after esophagectomy harming our patients?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current diagnostic criteria for anastomotic leakage (AL) after esophagectomy are insufficient for early diagnosis and treatment because of their oversimplified binary approach to the complication. A diagnostic spectrum is proposed, introducing the category of possible leak (PoL), leading to increased consideration of AL exclusion, and justifying PoL treatment options.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogen Affinity in Intermetallic Electrides as a Key Indicator of Catalytic Performance in Ammonia Synthesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrides have emerged as promising catalysts or catalyst supports for efficient ammonia synthesis under mild conditions. ATmSi compounds (A = rare earth/alkaline earth, Tm = transition metal) with a tetragonal CeFeSi-type structure represent a class of intermetallic electrides, where lattice atoms serve as active sites, offering significant potential for catalytic applications. However, with over 25 ATmSi compounds, their catalytic performance variations and optimization strategies remain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020471/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Diffuse Midline Glioma-on-Chip Recapitulating Tumor Biophysical Microenvironment to Assess the Heterogeneity of Response to Therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite significant efforts, Diffuse Midline Gliomas (DMGs) remain incurable. Although promising results are obtained in preclinical studies, most approaches have failed to improve survival in these young patients. In this context, by integrating elements of the biophysical tumor microenvironment known to regulate the response to therapies, a new preclinical tool is developed to better evaluate the efficacy of antitumoral strategies. For this purpose, a novel DMG-on-Chip (DoC) is engineered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Variation of VP2 stoichiometry and deamidation of VP1 during production and their impacts on the transduction efficiency of AAV vectors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recombinant adeno-associated viruses (rAAVs) are a leading platform for in vivo gene therapy. However, limited information is available on the fluctuation of quality attributes (QAs), during manufacturing using the HEK293 suspension cell line system, which is suitable for small- to large-scale production using bioreactors. In this study, we evaluated 14 QAs and their variations, including the viral protein (VP) stoichiometric ratio and deamidation ratios of asparagine residues, of the products...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41020267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the type specimens of representatives of the subgenus Apterosoma Motschulsky, 1861 of the genus <em>Chrysolina</em> Motschulsky, 1861 (Coleoptera, Chrysomelidae)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Classification of the subgenus Apterosoma Motschulsky of the genus Chrysolina is fraught with several problems. In particular, the northern Japanese Apterosoma can be separated into at least 20 morphologically and/or genetically distinct, yet undescribed, "units". In this study, we examine type specimens of the three species included within the subgenus to determine their relationships to these units and to each other.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimally Invasive Endoscopic Transorbital Approach for Frontal Sinus Fractures: A Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The endoscopic transorbital approach is a safe, minimally invasive alternative to the bicoronal approach for selected anterior wall frontal sinus fractures. Proper patient selection and surgical experience are essential to achieving favorable outcomes. Studies with longer follow-up are required to assess potential late complications, such as the development of mucoceles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41019279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spine endoscopic surgery establishment for disc disease (Neurocore-SENSED): an open and decentralized consensus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Endoscopic spine surgery (ESS) has evolved considerably, yet there remains a lack of consensus on patient selection, technical specifications, and outcome reporting. This heterogeneity hinders collaborative efforts to establish comprehensive evidence-based practices.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endobronchial ultrasound-guided transbronchial cryobiopsy through a working channel potentially improving safety and efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endobronchial ultrasound (EBUS)-guided transbronchial cryobiopsy (TBCB) is a novel method for the biopsy of hilar and mediastinal lesions. Conventional cryobiopsy requires simultaneous removal of the cryoprobe and EBUS scope from the airway, resulting in delayed observation of the biopsy site and application of hemostasis, which may lead to an increased risk of complications, especially bleeding. Moreover, during repeated passes of the cryoprobe, re-identification of the lesion is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018725/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DNA Origami-Based Luminescent Biosensors Enabling Smartphone Detection of Nucleic Acid Sequences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA origami enables the precise assembly of complex nanostructures, facilitating the visual detection of various molecular targets. Previously, we developed DNA origami-based nanosensors, termed "pliers", which allowed the detection of inorganic and organic single-molecule targets through shape transitions. However, these methods require costly analytical instruments, such as atomic force microscopy and fluorescence detection. To establish a more accessible and quantitative detection approach,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018615/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving Hexose-Phosphates by LC-MS Leads to New Insights in PGM1-CDG Pathophysiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hexose-phosphates play a role in many metabolic pathways, such as glycolysis and glycosylation. To understand the molecular basis of diseases such as congenital disorders of glycosylation (CDG), information about the source and abundance of hexose-phosphates is imperative. Mass spectrometry (MS)-based tracer metabolomics can provide this information, but hexose-phosphates are structural isomers with similar physicochemical properties, which makes them difficult to differentiate using MS. Here,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018607/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyaluronic Acid Immersion Enhances Gamma-Ray-Irradiation Cross-Linking of the Fish-Derived Type I Collagen Membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fish-derived type I collagen is widely used in biomedical implants; however, its limited thermal and enzymatic stability necessitates cross-linking for clinical applications. This study investigated gamma-ray-induced cross-linking of collagen as a shape of membranes, with enhancement via polysaccharide-assisted immersion. Hydrated collagen membranes were irradiated at doses ranging from 15 kDa to 35 kGy to assess their dose-dependent effects. Irradiation at 15 kGy enhanced thermal and enzymatic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acidic pH Condition Enhances Femtosecond Laser Photoinjection of Plasmid DNA into Intact Tobacco BY‑2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In plant biology, targeted photoinjection is a promising approach to understand the role of individual cells in the context of the overall structure. In particular, photomechanical poration by a femtosecond laser combined with partial degradation of cell wall structure by an enzyme treatment has been shown to be a great advantage for the injection of macromolecules. To extend the femtosecond laser technique to plasmid DNA, the effect of the electrostatic interaction between plasmid DNA and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hematology and Plasma Biochemistry in Whale Sharks (<em>Rhincodon typus</em>): Baseline Reference Intervals Based on Captivity Status, Blood Sampling Sites, and Handling Methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to establish reference intervals for red and white blood cell counts, hematocrit levels, mean corpuscular volume, and 25 key plasma biochemistry parameters in captive and wild whale sharks (Rhincodon typus). Blood samples were collected from the caudal vein (CV) and dorsal cutaneous vein (DCV) of 30 wild sharks caught in fixed nets off the Kochi Prefecture coast, Japan, and from 24 captive sharks between 2007-2023. Samples were obtained from restrained captive and wild sharks as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conservative Management of a Massive Retroperitoneal Cyst in Pregnancy: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Asymptomatic or benign retroperitoneal cysts are typically subjected to observational management. Although rare, cases during pregnancy may present with symptoms such as abdominal pain and distension, or require diagnostic intervention, frequently necessitating surgical procedures. Notably, in pregnant women with cysts exceeding 20 cm, surgical or aspiration procedures are implemented, even if asymptomatic. This report presents a case in which a large retroperitoneal cyst complicating pregnancy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41018344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcriptome profiling of megakaryocytes and platelets: Application to <em>GP9</em>- and <em>IKZF5</em>-related thrombocytopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platelets are anucleate cells produced in the bone marrow and derived from large progenitor cells called megakaryocytes (MKs). Platelets receive RNA transcripts from their progenitorial MKs during thrombopoiesis. However, the correspondence between platelet and MK transcriptomes is poorly understood, particularly in the context of germline mutations that cause platelet formation defects or thrombocytopenia. We have studied the effects of two such mutations on MK and platelet transcriptomes. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Xq24/<em>IL13RA1</em> aberrations as key drivers of female bias in primary mediastinal large B-cell lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Female-biased incidence in primary mediastinal large B-cell lymphoma (PMBCL) is enigmatic and points to a potential contribution of the X chromosome in this disease. To elucidate the postulated involvement of X-linked factor(s), we profiled the X chromosome in 48 diagnostic PMBCLs of male (21) and female (27) origin. Molecular cytogenetic analysis detected copy number gain of X/Xq in all male patients and 59.3% (16/27) of female patients. The remaining female cases revealed either a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigating lanthanide complex stability through kinetic and thermodynamic competition with metal ions and DTPA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the stability of lanthanide(III) complexes is essential in applications and when determining molecular properties. Here, luminescence spectroscopy was used to examine the stability of europium complexes when challenged with biologically and chemically relevant metal ions (Y^(3+), Sr^(2+), K^(+), Na^(+), La^(3+), Lu^(3+)). We benchmark three ligand systems against well-characterized Eu·DOTA and Eu·DTPA complexes and check for human error by challenging with DTPA. Where thermodynamic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Leaf evolution: integrating phylogenetics, developmental dynamics, and genetic insights across land plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The acquisition of leaves represented a pivotal innovation in plant evolution, enabling more efficient photosynthesis and providing a foundation for the development of increasingly three-dimensional and morphologically diverse organisms. Paleobotanical studies have revealed that leaves did not arise from a single common origin; rather, they evolved multiple times independently during the diversification of land plants. Despite these insights, the precise evolutionary trajectories leading to leaf...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Advances in Sulfide and Halide Electrolytes for Commercialization of All-Solid-State Lithium Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-solid-state lithium batteries (ASSBs) outperform lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) in safety, energy density, and thermal stability. Their performance depends on high ionic conductivity, chemical/physical stability, and scalable manufacture of solid electrolytes (SEs). This study compares sulfide- and halide-based SEs, two promising next-generation energy storage options. Soft mechanics permit sulfides with high room-temperature conductivity, low activation energies, and processability, but...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of Ion Chromatography for Determination of Inorganic Ions and Sorbitol in Phosphate Syrup]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, ion chromatography (IC) methods were developed and validated for the determination of sodium, potassium, phosphate, and sorbitol in phosphate syrup. For the analysis of cations, an IonPac CS16 column was utilized, with a mobile phase of 50 mM methanesulfonic acid and a flow rate of 0.5 mL/min. For the analysis of phosphate and sorbitol, an IonPac AS19 column was employed, using a flow rate of 1.0 mL/min and mobile phases of 50 and 20 mM NaOH, respectively. In the validation tests,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41017190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[GAGM: Geometry-aware graph matching framework for weakly supervised gyral hinge correspondence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Achieving precise alignment of inter-subject brain landmarks, such as the gyral hinge (GH), would enhance the correspondence of brain function across subjects, thereby advancing our understanding of brain anatomy-function relationship and brain mechanisms. Recent methods mainly focus on identifying the correspondences of GHs by utilizing point-to-point ground truth. However, labeling point-to-point GH correspondences between subjects for the entire brain is laborious and time-consuming, given...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diosgenin glycosides from <em>Paris vietnamensis</em> (Takht) H.Li with cytotoxic and inhibitory NO production activities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Six compounds, including a new diosgenin glycoside named Parisvietnamoside A (1), together with five described ones, including physalolactone pennogenin (2), gracillin (3), paris saponin H (4), paris saponin VII (5), and pennogenin-3-O-α-ʟ-arabinosyl-(1→4)-β-ᴅ-glucsopyranoside (6), were obtained from the rhizomes of Paris vietnamensis (Takht) H.Li. The structures were elucidated based on extensive spectroscopic analyses, including 1D and 2D NMR as well as HR-ESI-MS data. Two compounds (3 and 4)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021975/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Barriers to Subspecialty Care Among Patients With Extremely Severe Obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Body Composition and Cardiometabolic Outcomes : A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Artificial intelligence-derived BC proportions were strongly associated with cardiometabolic risk, but after BMI and WC were accounted for, only VAT proportion and SMFF (both sexes) and SM proportion (males only) added prognostic information.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating a Combination HIV Prevention Intervention Into a Widely Used Geosocial App for Chinese Men Who Have Sex With Men: Protocol for a Single-Arm Pilot and Repeated Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This pilot study will provide preliminary evidence regarding the feasibility and acceptability of the Blued+ intervention. The study findings will provide evidence setting the foundation for future research that involves embedding prevention platforms into apps that are already widely used. If preliminary impact is observed, future research would include a hybrid effectiveness implementation trial of the intervention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autocatalytic Hydrolysis of Degradable Polyester Microspheres for Long-Lasting Release of BMP-2 Immunomodulates Bone Regeneration In Vitro]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Degradable polyester microspheres are commonly utilized in bone tissue engineering due to their excellent biocompatibility and controlled drug-release profiles. While poly(lactic-co-glycolic acid) (PLGA) microspheres offer rapid degradation but lack sufficient mechanical strength for prolonged implantation, polycaprolactone (PCL) microspheres, with their slower degradation rate and hydrophobic nature, are less suitable for short-term drug-release applications. In this study, PLGA-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual role of dietary tryptophan on memory regulation in male albino wistar rats - synergistic modulation of serotonergic signaling and kynurenine pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: This study investigates the impact of tryptophan metabolism on synaptic plasticity, neurogenesis, and memory consolidation using a combined biochemical and behavioral approach.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of child maltreatment and resilience in the association between caregiver anxiety and child anxiety: a longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to explore the development of child anxiety and examine multiple mediating roles of child maltreatment and resilience in the association between caregiver anxiety and child anxiety. The longitudinal study included 1595 preschool children and their caregivers in Anhui Province, China. Paired t-tests were employed to compare differences in child anxiety between the baseline and follow-up. Linear regression analyses were performed to explore predictive effects of individual and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FOXO1-NMNAT3 axis dysregulation promotes doxorubicin cardiotoxicity: NAD<sup>+</sup> replenishment as a redox-targeted antioxidant therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study establishes the dysregulation of the FOXO1-NMNAT3 axis as a key mechanism underlying NAD^(+) depletion in DIC. Targeting this axis through NAD^(+) replenishment, particularly by activating NMNAT3, offers a novel redox-based therapeutic strategy against DIC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021886/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aggressive Surgical Management for Acute Neonatal Endogenous Candida Endophthalmitis with Persistent Fetal Vasculature and Pars Plana Granuloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Early aggressive surgical intervention with lensectomy for lens abscess, complete vitrectomy with base shaving, Cryotherapy for fungal granuloma, and intravitreal and systemic antifungal agents for endogenous endophthalmitis plays a pivotal role in targeting localized fungal lesions to control their progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021882/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Health Comes First: A Qualitative Study of Empowerment in Women Facing Breast Cancer in Ghana and Ethiopia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We identified several factors that facilitate or obstruct the empowerment of women facing breast cancer in Ghana and Ethiopia. It is critical we recognize this unique aspect of the patient experience to frame how we think about designing potential solutions, such as the introduction of breast reconstruction, to improve care and quality of life among survivors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Retinal Layer Atrophy With Clinical and Radiologic Progression in People With Relapsing Multiple Sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Progression independent of relapse activity (PIRA) is the main driver of disability accumulation in relapsing multiple sclerosis (RMS). Retinal layer atrophy measured by optical coherence tomography (OCT) reflects neuroaxonal damage and is associated with PIRA. However, it remains unclear whether this association is driven by subclinical inflammatory activity or reflects true progression independent of acute inflammation. Here, we aimed to investigate the relationship...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Small-Area Lung Cancer Incidence and Mortality: Cross-Sectional Population-Based Study Using Hospital Discharge and Death Registration Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The cancer surveillance approach based on linked administrative data could provide up-to-date small-area estimates of cancer burden, when cancer registry data are not yet reported and for areas not covered by cancer registries. It could reveal disparity of cancer epidemiology, which provides leads for further investigation into the underlying causes and potential solutions for equity improvement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-Property Relationship in Lightly and Heavily Gas-Phase N-Doped TiO<sub>2</sub> Nanoparticles for Solar-Driven Photocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lightly and heavily nitrogen (N)-doped TiO(2) systems (LD-TO and HD-TO) were synthesized via ammonia (NH(3)) gas-assisted annealing at 450 and 750 °C. XRD patterns showed low- and high-angle shifts for LD-TO and HD-TO, indicating lattice expansion (LD-TO) and contraction in HD-TO, with a Ti-oxynitride (TiON) peak in HD-TO indicating secondary phase segregation. FESEM analysis shows spherical particles (∼30 nm for TO) growing to ∼40-50 nm with a layered structure in doped samples. BET surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling ignis fatuus: Microlightning between microbubbles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Will-o'-the-wisps, ghostly blue flames seen at night in marshlands and long attributed to methane cool flames, have remained scientifically unexplained, a mystery caused by the lack of a known ignition mechanism. Here, we demonstrate that spontaneous electrical discharges, termed "microlightning", can occur between rising methane-containing microbubbles in water. High-speed optical imaging reveals brief flashes between charged bubbles, arising from strong electric fields at curved gas-liquid...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tyrosine phosphorylation coupling of one-carbon metabolism and virulence in an endogenous pathogen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endogenous pathogens can constrain virulence to ensure survival in the host. Pathogenic state can be controlled by metabolic responses to the prevailing microenvironment; however, the coupling and effector mechanisms are not well understood. Flux through the one-carbon metabolism (OCM) pathway can modulate virulence of the oral pathobiont Porphyromonas gingivalis, and here we show that this is controlled by tyrosine phosphorylation-dependent differential partitioning of gingipain proteases. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging hemispheric asymmetry of Earth's radiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Twenty-four years of satellite observations from the Clouds and the Earth's Radiant Energy System show a northern hemisphere (NH) minus southern hemisphere (SH) trend difference of 0.34 ± 0.23 Wm^(-2) dec^(-1) (5 to 95% CI) in absorbed solar radiation (ASR) and a weaker trend difference of 0.21 ± 0.21 Wm^(-2) dec^(-1) in outgoing longwave radiation. The emerging darkening of the NH relative to the SH is associated with changes in hemispheric differences in aerosol-radiation interactions, surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mouse model of MEPAN demonstrates a role for mitochondrial fatty acid synthesis in iron-sulfur cluster and supercomplex formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[MEPAN (Mitochondrial Enoyl CoA Reductase Protein-Associated Neurodegeneration) is an early-onset movement disorder characterized by ataxia, dysarthria, and optic atrophy. Here, we report the creation of a mouse model of MEPAN with patient-similar compound heterozygous mutations in the Mecr gene. The MEPAN mouse recapitulates the major hallmarks of MEPAN, including a movement disorder, optic neuropathy, defects in protein lipoylation, and reduced mitochondrial oxidative phosphorylation in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wild canids and felids differ in their reliance on reused travel routeways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diverse factors, including environmental features and cognitive processes, can drive animals' movements and space use, with far-reaching implications. For example, repeated use of individual-level travel routeways (directionally constrained but imperfectly aligned routes), which results in spatial concentration of activity, can shape encounter-based processes including predation, mate finding, and disease transmission. However, how much variation in routeway usage exists across species remains...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of the protein corona on hematopoietic stem and progenitor cell uptake and macrophage clearance of membrane-wrapped nanoparticles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ideal delivery of therapeutic nanoparticles (NPs) to specific sites requires evading immune clearance and selectively binding target cells. Wrapping NPs in cell-derived membranes has shown promise in improving targeted delivery, but the mechanisms underlying this phenomenon are not fully understood. Protein corona (PC) formation on NPs can significantly alter their biological identity to influence biodistribution, making its characterization on membrane-wrapped NPs (MWNPs) and unwrapped NPs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular divergence and convergence of mammalian antibody responses to the influenza virus hemagglutinin stem]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antibody responses to the influenza virus hemagglutinin (HA) stem, a major target for broadly protective vaccine development, have been extensively characterized in humans. However, they remain largely elusive in other natural influenza hosts, including pigs, which are considered intermediate hosts for the emergence of pandemic strains. By leveraging single-cell variable, diversity, and joining (VDJ) sequencing, this study identified 25 porcine antibodies to the HA stem, including two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Europium(II) Ynolate Complex: Synthesis, Bonding, and Reactivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anionic ketenes [RCCO]^(-) exhibit two resonance forms: ketenyl anions and ynolate anions. While ketenyl complexes have been isolated and characterized, crystalline ynolate complexes remain elusive. Herein, we report the first lanthanide ynolate complex, namely, the europium ynolate complex. A σ-bond metathesis reaction of Me(3)Si(H)CN(2) with a europium(II) hydrido or alkyl complex yields a europium(II) nitrilimine, which reacts with CO to provide a europium(II) ynolate complex. Single-crystal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infrared Study of Electron-bombarded Phenanthrene (C<sub>14</sub>H<sub>10</sub>)/<em>Para</em>-H<sub>2</sub> Matrices: Isomers of Protonated Phenanthrene (1-, 3-, 4-, and 9-H<sup>+</sup>C<sub>14</sub>H<sub>10</sub>)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protonated polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons are potential carriers of the unidentified infrared (UIR) emission bands observed in interstellar space. Laboratory-generated infrared (IR) spectra of these protonated species can aid in identifying the molecular origins of these bands. In this study, a mixture of phenanthrene (C(14)H(10)) and p-H(2) was subjected to electron bombardment during deposition at 3.2 K, yielding new IR absorption features. These features decrease over time during...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021768/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gravity, Microgravity and Artificial Gravity: Physiological Effects, Implementation and Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gravity, the force that structures the cosmos, also shapes human physiology. It influences skeletal, muscular, cardiovascular, respiratory, and neurological systems, sustaining balance, blood circulation, and functional capacity. Unlike other senses, the brain lacks a dedicated gravity-sensing region and instead relies on a distributed vestibular network-graviception-to interpret gravitational cues. On Earth, gravity-driven blood pooling in the legs triggers compensatory responses that preserve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The non-steroidal MR antagonist Finerenone reverses Western diet-induced kidney disease by regulating mitochondrial and lipid metabolism and inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mineralocorticoid receptor (MR) overactivation plays a crucial role in the pathogenesis of chronic kidney disease, as well as several cardiovascular and arterial diseases. Current studies determined the mechanisms of the beneficial kidney effects of the non-steroidal MR antagonist Finerenone (FN) in a mouse model of western diet-induced obesity and insulin resistance. 10-week-old male C57BL/6J mice were fed a low fat (LF) or a western diet (WD) for 12 weeks followed by treatment with either...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of <em>N</em>-Sulfonyl Acetamidine Using Calcium Carbide as the Alkynyl Source and Ammonium Bicarbonate as the Amine Source]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new approach for the efficient synthesis of N-sulfonyl acetamidine via a one-pot multicomponent reaction at room temperature using calcium carbide as the alkyne source and ammonium bicarbonate as the amine source with sulfonyl azides is reported. The method efficiently constructed two bonds (C-N and C═N) in the aqueous system and has the advantages of cheap and easy availability of raw materials, mild conditions, simple operation, wide scope of substrates, convenient scale-up to gram scale,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting infusion rate limitations for continuous lumbar plexus blocks in children and adolescents with 0.2% ropivacaine: a pharmacokinetic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Pharmacokinetic modeling supports a bolus dose of 2mg/kg, continuous infusion rates of ropivacaine at 0.4mg/kg/h and 6hourly boluses of 0.2mg/kg in healthy children for lumbar plexus blockade for the first 24 hours. After that, with currently accepted toxic thresholds for ropivacaine and PPX, consideration should be given to dosing strategies that reduce or eliminate infusions and support timed boluses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of B97-Type Density Functional Approximation, Global Hybrid, and Range-Separated Hybrid Energy Functionals with the D4 Dispersion Corrections in TAO-DFT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For multireference systems, Kohn-Sham density functional theory (KS-DFT) with the conventional exchange-correlation functionals can yield qualitative failures. Recently, thermally-assisted-occupation density functional theory (TAO-DFT) [Chai, J.-D. J. Chem. Phys. 2012, 136, 154104] has been developed to address this challenge. In this work, to greatly improve the performance of the conventional density functional approximation (DFA), global hybrid (GH), and range-separated hybrid (RSH)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-Time Detection of Urban Atmospheric Micro-Nanoplastics and Their Chemical Mixing State Using Bioaerosol Single-Particle Mass Spectrometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atmospheric micro-nanoplastics (MNPs) serve as key vectors for the global dispersion of plastic pollutants and act as reactive interfaces for atmospheric species, modifying their physicochemical properties and influencing environmental transport dynamics. However, existing methods lack the temporal resolution and specificity to characterize MNP mixing states and pollutant interactions in real time. To address this gap, we developed an innovative approach employing bioaerosol single-particle mass...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anxiety in Caregivers of Chinese Children Under 3 Years Old with Cleft Lip or Palate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectivesThis study compared anxiety between Chinese caregivers of children with non-syndromic cleft lip (CL) or cleft palate (CP) at the time of their first surgery and control group as well as identifying factors associated with caregiver anxiety.DesignRetrospective, observational cohort study.SettingDepartment of Cleft Lip and Palate in West China Hospital of Stomatology, Sichuan University.ParticipantsCaregivers of children under 3 years old.Main Outcome MeasuresThe 7-item Generalized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting Calcium Regulation for Heart Failure and Arrhythmia Therapeutics: A Critical Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite advances in pharmacologic and procedural therapies, heart failure (HF) and cardiac arrhythmias remain significant global health burdens, highlighting the urgent need for novel therapeutic strategies. Defective Ca^(2+) handling in cardiac myocytes is recognized as a central pathogenic mechanism underlying both heart failure and atrial and ventricular arrhythmias. In this review, we critically assess the current state of research on Ca^(2+)-handling proteins and their role in causing heart...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sudden Cardiac Arrest and Death Secondary to Congenital Coronary Artery Abnormalities in Young Competitive Athletes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of clinical obesity versus BMI-defined obesity among US adults: a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying genetic determinants of outer retinal function in mice using a large-scale gene-targeted screen]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electroretinography (ERG) provides a noninvasive functional measure of multiple cell types of the outer retina. We conducted an ERG-based screen of 530 single-gene knockout mouse strains generated as part of the International Mouse Phenotyping Consortium, representing 2.5% of all protein-coding genes, to identify genetic variants affecting retinal function. We identified 30 strains with significantly altered ERG amplitudes. Two of the genes identified, Cfap418 and Syne2, have been previously...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does financial compensation matter for research participation in prevention trials in Tanzania? Perspectives of healthy volunteers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Financial compensation matters to certain participant subgroups, but its role varies. While some value monetary benefits, others prioritize altruism and trust in research oversight. A balanced, transparent compensation framework is needed to address financial needs while maintaining ethical integrity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021651/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The tegument protein VP22 of pseudorabies virus inhibits cGAS condensation by inducing nuclear-to-cytoplasmic translocation of DDX21]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclic GMP-AMP synthase (cGAS) is a pivotal DNA sensor that initiates antiviral responses, yet the mechanisms by which viruses evade cGAS-mediated innate immunity remain poorly understood. Here, we identified VP22, a tegument protein of pseudorabies virus (PRV), a member of the Alphaherpesvirinae subfamily, as a viral antagonist of the type I interferon (IFN-I) response through hijacking the host RNA helicase DDX21. Specifically, VP22 impairs 2'3'-cyclic GMP-AMP (cGAMP) synthesis by disrupting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fine-tuning OsTCP19 expression offers broad adaptation scenarios for nitrogen-use efficiency improvement in rice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inconsistent nitrogen application rates across global croplands necessitate the adaptation of different genetic alleles to optimize nitrogen-use efficiency (NUE) in agriculture. In rice (Oryza sativa L.), different TEOSINTE BRANCHED 1, CYCLOIDEA AND PROLIFERATING CELL FACTOR 19 (OsTCP19) alleles contribute to the geographical adaptation to soil fertility. The nitrogen-sensitive allele OsTCP19-H is predominantly found in low-nitrogen regions due to its superior tillering and yield accumulation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frontal and parietal planning signals encode adapted motor commands when learning to control a brain-computer interface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Perturbing visual feedback is a powerful tool for studying visuomotor adaptation. However, unperturbed proprioceptive signals in common paradigms inherently co-varies with physical movements and causes incongruency with the visual input. This can create challenges when interpreting underlying neurophysiological mechanisms. We employed a brain-computer interface (BCI) in rhesus monkeys to investigate spatial encoding in frontal and parietal areas during a 3D visuomotor rotation task where only...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early visual signatures and benefits of intra-saccadic motion streaks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eye movements routinely induce motion streaks as they shift visual projections across the retina at high speeds. To investigate the visual consequences of intra-saccadic motion streaks, we co-registered eye tracking and EEG while gaze-contingently shifting target objects during saccades, presenting either continuous, 'streaky' or apparent, step-like motion in four directions. We found significant reductions of secondary saccade latency, as well as improved decoding of the post-saccadic target...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inequities in breast cancer outcomes in Chile: An analysis of case fatality ratios and survival rates (2007-2018)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer is a leading cause of illness and death among women in Chile, yet national data on health outcomes remain limited in the absence of a cancer registry. This observational study examines disparities in breast cancer case fatality ratios and survival rates by health insurance provider and geographic region using national hospital discharge and mortality databases from 2007 to 2018. We analyzed 58,254 hospital discharges and 16,615 deaths related to breast cancer. Case fatality and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polycomb repressive complexes 1 and 2 independently and dynamically regulate euchromatin during cerebellar neurodevelopment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polycomb Repressive Complexes (PRCs) are known for chemically modifying histones to compact chromatin structure and repress transcription. Broadly speaking, PRC1 monoubiquitinates histone 2A at lysine 119 (H2AK119ub), and PRC2 methylates histone H3 lysine 27 (H3K27me3, H3K27me2 and H3K27me1), but the scope and functions of these activities is complicated by a multiplicity of factors involving distinct cellular contexts and compositions of both complexes. Because PRC dysregulation is associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opportunities and barriers arising from the COVID-19 pandemic for health campaign integration across immunizations, neglected tropical diseases, insecticide-treated bed nets, and vitamin A supplementation: A qualitative key informant interview study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In low- and middle-income countries, health campaigns play a crucial role in addressing high-priority health concerns such as neglected tropical diseases (NTDs), malaria, vaccine-preventable diseases and nutrition (vitamin A supplementation). Many health campaigns are conducted throughout the calendar year, resulting in multiple campaigns annually in some communities. Campaign integration offers an opportunity to increase efficiencies across programs and limit the strain on healthcare workers,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insulin resistance markers HOMA-IR, TyG and TyG-BMI index in relation to heart failure risk: NHANES 2011-2016]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TyG showed a stronger association with HF risk than HOMA-IR and TyG-BMI and outperformed HOMA-IR in predicting HF risk, particularly in specific subpopulations. These findings highlight the importance of further research into the clinical application of TyG for early identification and management of HF risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Awareness and vaccination willingness of middle-aged and elderly individuals in Southwest China toward to herpes zoster vaccine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The incidence of herpes zoster is increasing in China's aging society, and vaccination is the most effective preventive measure. However, vaccine hesitancy is a major obstacle. A survey was conducted among individuals aged 50 and above in Southwest China to assess their awareness and willingness to vaccinate against herpes zoster. The 3C model was used to analyze factors influencing vaccine hesitancy. Among 3,007 participants, vaccine hesitancy ranged from 62.7% to 68.9% across different...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal Artery Function and Histopathology Linked to Plasma and Fecal Metabolites in Heart Failure Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The gut microbiota and its associated host-microbe co-metabolites are increasingly recognized as key regulators of systemic metabolic balance and the cardiorenal axis, particularly within the context of cardiorenal syndrome. Although clinical evidence indicates that cardiac dysfunction may initiate or exacerbate renal pathological alterations, the key metabolic signaling molecules mediating the cardiorenal axis and their underlying mechanisms remain elusive. This study establishes a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Accounting for human-nature linkages in area-based conservation monitoring through social-ecological indicator bundles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the coverage of area-based conservation increases across the globe, it is critical to improve understanding of the social and ecological outcomes of such measures and the pathways to their outcomes. A social-ecological systems approach to monitoring and evaluation is increasingly advocated; yet, applications remain scarce. We sought to facilitate operationalization of this approach through prioritization of indicators when resources are scarce and to improve capture of social-ecological...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An inertial sensor-based comprehensive analysis of manual wheelchair user mobility during daily life in people with SCI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study employed three inertial measurement units to quantify the mobility characteristics of 12 manual wheelchair users with spinal cord injuries (SCI) over 7 consecutive days, revealing nuanced patterns of daily movement. Mobility metrics were calculated for measures of distance traveled, movement duration, and speed. A mobility profile was created to understand patterns of movement behaviors. Participants moved 65.54 ± 21.81 min daily, traveled 1488.15 ± 700.09 meters at an average speed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Olfactory bulbectomy-induced impairment of lipid utilization leads to abnormal glucose metabolism in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Increased lipid utilization after food odor perception is a recently identified Pavlovian cephalic phase response in fasted mice that serves to prevent diet-induced glucose intolerance. However, the impact of olfactory dysfunction on metabolic functions remains unclear. Since olfactory bulbectomized (OBX) rodents have been used as a model of irreversible complete anosmia, we investigated whether glucose, lipid, and energy metabolism change over time in OBX mice fed a normal chow diet (NCD) or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Loneliness, social isolation, and sleep problems: Findings from a 10-year longitudinal study of Chinese middle-aged and older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Social isolation, loneliness, and sleep problems have emerged as significant concerns in aging populations, yet longitudinal studies exploring their interconnections are limited. This study examined these relationships and performed subgroup analyses based on age and gender.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gender differences for the relationships between posttraumatic stress disorder, depression, and anxiety in postearthquake adolescents: A panel graphical vector autoregression model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings highlight the intricacy of mental health problems in postdisaster situations and underscore the importance of implementing gender- and time-specific approaches in psychiatric interventions. (PsycInfo Database Record (c) 2025 APA, all rights reserved).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-occurrence of racism-based trauma symptoms and depressive symptoms among college students of color]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our results underscore the importance of addressing stress and trauma responses from racial discrimination among young adult college students of color. (PsycInfo Database Record (c) 2025 APA, all rights reserved).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Smile and the world smiles (and trusts) with you: Happiness mimicry shapes first impressions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Numerous studies have shown that the processes underlying trait judgments can be influenced by concurrent affect processing. The present project explores the role of emotional mimicry in trait attribution. Across three experiments, we asked participants to assess social characteristics of faces expressing happiness, sadness, and anger. In Experiments 1 and 3, we used facial electromyography to predict participants' inferences about trustworthiness, confidence, and attractiveness (Experiment 1)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021491/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How social norms emerge: The interindividual actor-critic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Social norms shape a vast range of human behaviors, from everyday interactions to major life choices. Yet, existing theories of norm emergence typically focus either on why certain norms arise (substantive properties) or on how they spread and persist (dynamical properties), often making conflicting assumptions. Here, we propose a unified account in which norms prescribing how one ought to act emerge naturally from the fundamental algorithms that guide learning-whether in social or nonsocial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occupational social interaction is associated with reduced dementia risk: The Trøndelag Health Study (HUNT)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lifetime social engagement could build cognitive reserve and lower the risk of dementia through compensatory effects on brain health. We aimed to investigate whether social interaction at work is protective of later-life cognitive impairment. Data from 9,248 participants of the population-based Norwegian HUNT4 70+ Study (2017-2019), with cognitive assessments at or after age 70, were linked retrospectively to longitudinal registry-based employment information spanning ages 30-65 years. An...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021477/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of the number of teeth on the cognitive function of older adults: an intermediary analysis based on dietary diversity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In Chinese older adults, more teeth were associated with better cognitive function. Denture wearing reduced the risk of cognitive decline caused by tooth loss to a certain extent. Dietary diversity mediated the relationship between tooth number and cognitive function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase II trial of radiotherapy plus Huachansu in elderly or chemotherapy-ineligible patients with locally advanced esophageal squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with radiotherapy alone, concurrent radiotherapy with Huachansu injection did not improve the locoregional control rate or survival rate in elderly patients or chemotherapy-ineligible patients with locally advanced ESCC. The trial is registered with ClinicalTrials.org, NCT02647125.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41021440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250930033713&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>