<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:39:03 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The first South Korean data challenge for drug discovery using human and mouse liver microsomal stability data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Korea Chemical Bank (KCB) has generated a dataset containing metabolic stability data for approximately 4,000 compounds that have been tested on human and mouse liver microsomes. The first South Korea Data Challenge, named the Jump AI Challenge for Drug Discovery (JUMP AI 2023), was opened using the metabolic stability data of KCB in 2023. The objective of the JUMP AI 2023 was to promote and encourage the development of new drugs using artificial intelligence (AI) technology in South Korea....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics and management of mechanically ventilated patients in South Korea compared with other high-income Asian countries and regions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Despite higher age and patient-to-nurse ratios in South Korean ICUs, outcomes were comparable to those in other high-income Asian countries. The suboptimal use of sufficient PEEP with ARDS indicates potential areas for improvement. Additionally, the beneficial impact of respiratory therapists on mortality rates warrants further investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic Association Between Polymorphisms in lncRNA <em>ANRIL</em> and Gastric Cancer Susceptibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objective: Genetic variations of long noncoding RNAs are potential biomarkers for gastric cancer (GC). However, reports on the association between single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) in antisense noncoding RNA in the INK4 locus (ANRIL) and GC risk are few. This case-control study aimed to evaluate the association between SNPs in ANRIL, GC risk, and subgroups in a Korean population. Methodology: The TaqMan genotyping assay of six SNPs in ANRIL was performed in 419 patients with GC and 348...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903178/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification and application of promoters and terminators for plant synthetic biology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant synthetic biology is an emerging field that combines bioinformatics, computational gene circuit design, and plant science. It has the potential to be applied in various areas, including the production of pharmaceuticals, vaccines, biofuels, and various biomaterials, including plant natural products (PNP). This review highlights recent advancements in plant synthetic biology, particularly in the development and application of biological parts such as promoters and terminators, which play a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic potential of sulfasalazine for sarcopenia: Insights from mouse models and clinical data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sarcopenia, a disease marked by a progressive loss of muscle mass, increases the risks of disability and metabolic disorders, and decreases quality of life. Current therapeutic options are limited. YY1 transcriptional activity is augmented through an interaction with PHF20 at its promoter region, suppressing muscle differentiation. This study screened sulfasalazine, a medication for managing inflammatory bowel diseases (IBD), using the PHF20-YY1 promoter assay in C(2)C(12) myoblasts from an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902806/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A consensus HA DNA vaccine targeting clade 2.3.4.4 H5Nx influenza viruses provides broad cross-clade protection in mice and ferrets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recurrent outbreaks of highly pathogenic avian influenza (HPAI) H5Nx viruses in birds pose a threat to human health due to their zoonotic potential. This underscores the urgent need for effective vaccines to mitigate the pandemic risk from evolving H5Nx viruses. We developed a DNA vaccine encoding a consensus hemagglutinin (HA) from clade 2.3.4.4 H5Nx viruses [pGX-27/HA (2.3.4.4)] and evaluated its immunogenicity and protective efficacy in mice and ferrets. Vaccination elicited strong...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A robust cyanide sensor for multiphase detection: Enabling practical on-site applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new colorimetric and fluorimetric probe PBT, for the efficient recognition of cyanide ion was synthesized and characterized; the sensing properties were analyzed and used for various real-time applications. The probe consists of a D-π-A conception with a donor unit of phenothiazine and an acceptor unit of benzothiazole to make a molecule for the ease of charge transfer transition. The mechanism of recognition is confirmed by ¹H NMR and HRMS spectral analysis. The jobs method also confirms the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Meat intake and breast cancer risk from the Health Examinees study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our results suggest that processed meat intake is linked to a higher risk of breast cancer, whereas beef consumption may reduce the risk of breast cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[COSINE-100 full dataset challenges the annual modulation signal of DAMA/LIBRA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For over 25 years, the DAMA/LIBRA collaboration has claimed to observe an annual modulation signal, suggesting the existence of dark matter interactions. However, no experiment using different target materials has observed a dark matter signal consistent with their result. To address this puzzle, the COSINE-100 collaboration conducted a model-independent test using sodium iodide crystal detectors, the same target material as DAMA/LIBRA. Analyzing data collected over 6.4 years by the effective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901955/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of preoperative anemia on short- and long-term outcomes of sphincter-preserving rectal cancer surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Factors Influencing Quality of Life Among Patients With Hepatobiliary and Pancreatic Cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To improve the quality of life of patients with hepatobiliary and pancreatic cancers, we suggest providing appropriate psychosocial support, pain control, and nutritional management during the cancer treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Bacillus subtilis</em> pb2441 Ameliorates Hepatic Steatosis by Decoupling Liver and Fat Tissue Lipid Accumulation in a High-Fat Diet-Fed Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonalcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) is a global health issue, often associated with gut dysbiosis. In recent years, probiotics have gained attention as potential therapeutic agents for NAFLD. This study explored the effects of a single strain, Bacillus subtilis with high surfactin secretion, on C57BL/6 mice fed a high-fat diet (HFD), a model for NAFLD, for 13 weeks. We conducted efficacy assays over 13 weeks on liver fat accumulation and gut microbiome modulation. Bacillus supplementation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Accuracy of Serological Tests for <em>Mycoplasma pneumoniae</em> Infections in Children with Pneumonia, Based on Symptom Onset]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The time post-symptom onset significantly influenced the diagnostic utility of serological tests for pediatric MPP, which showed limited value during the early stage of illness. These findings emphasize the importance of symptom onset-based interpretation of serological test results and their utility in complementing PCR when optimizing MPP diagnosis in children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Reference Materials Prepared Following CLSI C37-A Be Utilized Without Commutability Assessment? Perspectives Based on Lipid Measurements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RMs prepared per CLSI C37-A were commutable with most MP pairs for TC and TG. Elevated TG levels affected HDL-C and LDL-C commutability, highlighting the need to consider TG concentrations during RM preparation and assess commutability to standardize laboratory tests.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wireless Acousto-Piezoelectric Conduit with Aligned Nanofibers for Neural Regeneration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peripheral nerve injury (PNI) represents a significant clinical challenge, leading to severe motor and sensory dysfunction, as well as irreversible tissue atrophy. Autograft has been commonly utilized as the clinical gold standard; however, it is limited by donor availability and secondary surgery requirements. Here, an ultrasound-responsive, highly aligned piezoelectric nanofiber nerve guidance conduit (APNF-NGC) is introduced for peripheral nerve regeneration. Fabricated from electrospun...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism of Contrasting Ionic Conductivities in Li<sub>2</sub>ZrCl<sub>6</sub> via I and Br Substitution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the complex structural and chemical factors that influence ionic conduction mechanisms is paramount for developing advanced inorganic superionic conductors in all-solid-state batteries, particularly halide solid electrolytes with excellent electrochemical oxidative stability and mechanical sinterability. Herein, contrasting ionic conduction behaviors in I^(-) and Br^(-) substituted Li(2)ZrCl(6) are revealed by combining experimental structural analyses and theoretical calculations....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MetaboGNN: predicting liver metabolic stability with graph neural networks and cross-species data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The metabolic stability of a drug is a crucial determinant of its pharmacokinetic properties, including clearance, half-life, and oral bioavailability. Accurate predictions of metabolic stability can significantly streamline the drug discovery process. In this study, we present MetaboGNN, an advanced model for predicting liver metabolic stability based on Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) and Graph Contrastive Learning (GCL). Using a high-quality dataset from the 2023 South Korea Data Challenge for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current status of the use of validated home blood pressure monitoring devices among Korean patients with hypertension]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The implementation of Home Blood Pressure Monitoring (HBPM) has improved the diagnosis and treatment of hypertension. Current clinical guidelines advocate the use of validated HBPM devices. However, few studies have examined the current use of validated HBPM devices. We aimed to investigate the current status of the use of validated HBPM devices in real-world hypertensive patients. This study was conducted on Korean patients with hypertension using CareforMe®, a smartphone healthcare application...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutritional support in critical care: estimating resting energy expenditure in the intensive care unit when indirect calorimetry is limited]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low vitamin C concentrations and prognosis in critically ill children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Vitamin C deficiency was associated with elevated inflammatory marker levels, increased mechanical ventilation durations, and PICU admission. Our results support the potential benefits of vitamin C administration in critically ill children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903412/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effects of restricted visitation on delirium incidence in the intensive care units of a tertiary hospital in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Complete restriction of ICU visitations during the COVID-19 pandemic was associated with a significant increase in delirium incidence. These findings suggest the importance of visitation policies on patient outcomes and suggest the need for alternative strategies, such as video visitation, to mitigate the adverse effects of visitation restrictions during pandemics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial arterial pH predicts survival of out-of-hospital cardiac arrest in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The predicting performance of models including arterial pH was comparable to models including low-flow time, and addition of arterial pH into low-flow time models could increase the performance of the models. Key Words: blood pH; hydrogen-ion con.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of medical crisis on the critical care system in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The medical crisis has led to major changes in the critical care system, including staffing shortages, increased workloads, and an expanded role for nurse practitioners. This is a critical moment to foster interest and engage in active discussions aimed at creating a sustainable and resilient ICU system.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of the Right Ventricle Overhaul Procedure in Comprehensive Management for Pulmonary Atresia With Intact Ventricular Septum　- A Magnetic Resonance Imaging-Based Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both RV size and TV annulus showed proportionate growth after mRVOh. mRVOh may be a viable option for facilitating sustainable RV and TV growth in selected patients with PA-IVS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of bronchitis variability on outcomes of COPD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with CB and IB exhibit a greater risk of exacerbations than those with NB, whereas lung function decline rates did not significantly differ between groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moving Beyond the Model: Our Perspective on Meaningful AI Research in Cardiovascular Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epstein-Barr Virus Corneal Endotheliitis and Uveitis in a Patient With Extranodal Natural Killer/T-Cell Lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EBV infection can cause severe corneal edema and uveitis. In patients with ENKTL, EBV should be considered a possible etiology of ocular involvement, and timely ophthalmic management may contribute to better visual outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to biologics along a gradient of T2 involvement in patients with severe asthma: a data-driven biomarker clustering approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: T2-targeting biologics have utility in the management of asthma with low T2 involvement, but more effective therapies are needed. Further research is warranted to identify specific pathogenic pathways at the lower end of the T2 spectrum that can be effectively targeted by biologics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902942/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TP53-Agnostic Lethality through Combined Pan-HDAC and CDK Inhibition in Acute Myeloid Leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor protein 53 (TP53)-mutated acute myeloid leukemia (AML) is characterized by poor outcomes and the quick development of treatment resistance. Here, we report that simultaneous inhibition of cyclin-dependent kinases (CDKs) and histone deacetylases (HDACs) with dinaciclib and CAY10603, respectively, eliminates the therapeutic response gap between TP53-mutant and TP53 wild-type AML. Biochemical profiling showed that CAY10603 is not only HDAC6-selective but also exhibits pan-HDAC activity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902843/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Patient-Specific Instrumentation, Navigation, and Mixed Reality Technologies for Accurate Glenoid Positioning in Reverse Total Shoulder Arthroplasty: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both PSI and NAV methods demonstrated improved accuracy compared to the CON method, with PSI showing superior accuracy and smaller deviations than NAV. While limited to cadaveric studies, MR showed greater accuracy than NAV but produced mixed results when compared to PSI. Further clinical studies on MR are needed to validate and generalize these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Picoliter ice particles by supersonic cryogenic jets for transdermal drug delivery: Extracellular vesicle application for skin diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transdermal drug delivery holds significant potential for treating skin conditions. Conventional methods utilizing needles or large unit drug delivery volumes often result in patient discomfort and inhomogeneous delivery. This study proposes a picoliter ice particle delivery (PIPD) technology that produces high-speed solid ice drug particles using controlled supersonic cryogenic jets for transdermal drug delivery. The proposed PIPD system simultaneously atomizes liquid drug to micro-droplets,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clopidogrel versus aspirin for secondary prevention of coronary artery disease: a systematic review and individual patient data meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Aspirin monotherapy is recommended indefinitely for patients with established coronary artery disease (CAD). The aim of this individual patient level meta-analysis was to provide a comprehensive evaluation of the comparative efficacy and safety of clopidogrel versus aspirin monotherapy in patients with established CAD, most of whom had undergone percutaneous coronary intervention or had acute coronary syndrome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immediate versus staged complete revascularisation during index admission in patients with ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction and multivessel disease (OPTION-STEMI): a multicentre, non-inferiority, open-label, randomised trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The optimal timing of complete revascularisation for patients with ST-segment elevation myocardial infarction (STEMI) and multivessel coronary artery disease remains unclear. We aimed to assess whether immediate complete revascularisation was non-inferior to staged complete revascularisation during the index admission.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A field-deployable lateral flow assay for rapid and sensitive detection of nanoplastics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastic pollution has emerged as a global concern, with nanoplastics posing a distinct threat due to their small size, high mobility, and persistence. However, conventional nanoplastic detection techniques often rely on sophisticated instruments and extensive preprocessing, limiting their on-site applicability. This study aimed to develop a rapid and portable lateral flow assay (LFA) for on-site detection of nanoplastics smaller than 200 nm in environmental water samples. Here, we present a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whitlockite nanoparticles: A multifaceted magnesium calcium phosphate ceramic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bioceramics are widely used in tissue engineering due to their tremendous potential in tissue regeneration and biomedical applications. Of all bioceramics, the "Whitlockite" is an ideal material with remarkable potential and distinctive properties. Over the past decade, Whitlockite (nWH), a magnesium-containing calcium phosphate, has gained intense attention in biomedical research. The synthesis of nWH was challenging due to its similarities with other Mg-containing Calcium phosphates. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photocatalytic Activation of Dealuminated Zeolite through In Situ Formation of Defective Graphene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adsorbents such as zeolite are widely used for volatile organic compounds (VOCs) removal, but a practical challenge is the decrease in VOCs removal efficiency under humid environment by competitive adsorption between water vapor and VOCs, which requires frequent regeneration using external energy. A combination of zeolites with photocatalytic materials can address this issue by oxidizing adsorbed VOCs from the zeolite surface to CO(2) gas under light irradiation. Herein, the in situ formation of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design of Automatic Tool Replacement Mechanism for Laparoscopic Surgical Robot Arm for Solo Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The mechanism developed for the automatic replacement of surgical tools is expected to address the shortage of surgical staff and skill level of surgical assistants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Risk Across Blood Pressure Categories Defined by the 2024 ESC and 2023 ESH Hypertension Guidelines: Insights from a Korean Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Elevated BP and hypertension, as defined by the 2024 ESC guidelines, were associated with increased risk of future cardiovascular events. While findings were directionally consistent with the 2023 ESH classification, the ESC framework identified a broader at-risk population. These results indicate that individuals with elevated BP, as defined by the 2024 ESC classification, have a modestly higher risk of cardiovascular events, particularly ischemic stroke, compared with those with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-term memory errors are strongly associated with a drift in neural activity in the posterior parietal cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the neural mechanisms behind short-term memory (STM) errors is crucial for unraveling cognitive processes and addressing deficits associated with neuropsychiatric disorders. This study examines whether STM errors arise from misrepresentation of sensory information or decay in these representations over time. Using 2-photon calcium imaging in the posterior parietal cortex (PPC) of mice performing a delayed match-to-sample task, we identified a subset of PPC neurons exhibiting both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative evaluation of four fully automated immunoanalyzers for the simultaneous detection of HBeAg and Anti-HBe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Inter-platform discrepancies observed may impact clinical interpretation. As these discrepancies primarily stem from systematic bias, they can be readily mitigated by adjusting the reference values. Overall, further harmonization efforts are essential to enhance inter-platform agreement and ensure consistency in clinical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Methods for Evaluating Drivers of Liking for <em>Yakju</em>: Ideal Napping versus the Check-All-That-Apply Method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Check-all-that-apply (CATA) and napping are cost- and time-efficient alternatives to conventional descriptive analysis for evaluating product sensory characteristics. This study introduces ideal napping as a novel sensory evaluation method that integrates the napping procedure with the concept of constructing an ideal product profile. Ideal napping was used to identify drivers of liking for 12 commercial yakjus (Korean rice wines). When comparing the product configurations generated by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-Obesity Effects of <em>Abeliophyllum distichum</em> Extracts via the AMPK Signaling Pathway in 3T3-L1 Adipocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obesity is a major public health concern because of its association with metabolic disorders (e.g., type 2 diabetes mellitus) and cardiovascular diseases. Natural compounds are increasingly being explored as safer alternatives to synthetic antiobesity drugs. In this study, the antiobesity effects of Abeliophyllum distichum extracts in 3T3-L1 adipocytes and their underlying mechanisms were investigated. Oil Red O staining was employed to assess the effects of A. distichum extracts on adipogenesis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual Effects of a Combination of <em>Scutellaria baicalensis</em> and <em>Nelumbo nuciferaon</em> Inflammation and Hyperuricemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study developed an effective combination of Scutellaria baicalensis and Nelumbo nucifera (SNE) and evaluated its anti-inflammatory and anti-hyperuricemic effects under in vivo conditions. First, the effect of SNE was tested on in vitro xanthine oxidase (XOD) activity. To investigate the anti-inflammatory effect of SNE, nitric oxide (NO) production was detected by Griess assay, and proinflammatory cytokines were measured by enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay in RAW264.7 cells. Next, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hemodynamic predictors of rupture in abdominal aortic aneurysms: a case series using computational fluid dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CFD-derived hemodynamic parameters, particularly ECAP was spatially correlated with AAA rupture sites. These findings support the utility of CFD in identifying rupture-prone regions and suggest its potential as a supplementary tool for risk stratification beyond diameter-based criteria.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High carbohydrate antigen 19-9 levels indicate poor prognosis in patients with bladder cancer following radical cystectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A high CA19-9 level is associated with a higher tumor burden in patients with bladder cancer. Furthermore, high CA19-9 levels are correlated to higher pathologic T and N stages after radical cystectomy and worse recurrence-free survival.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial gene expression profiling identifies prognostic features of residual tumors after neoadjuvant chemotherapy in triple-negative breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We identified some differentially expressed genes relevant to oncogenic signaling and immunosuppressive tumor-associated macrophages. These findings provide novel insights into factors affecting prognosis in patients with residual disease after NAC for early-stage TNBC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900789/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When politics meets policy: a realist review of how political context shapes the impact of public health legal interventions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This Realist Review underscores that legal interventions alone cannot guarantee public health improvements. Rather, their success relies on supportive political contexts, coherent enforcement strategies, and alignment with evolving social values. Policymakers and advocates should anticipate and address political barriers-from partisanship to lobbying to donor dependency-to design and implement resilient, evidence-based public health laws. Future research should refine these insights...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Social Media as an Emotional Barometer: Bidirectional Encoder Representations From Transformers-Long Short-Term Memory Sentiment Analysis on the Evolution of Public Sentiments During Influenza A on Sina Weibo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The phenomenon of social sharing of emotions provides valuable theoretical insights into the collective expression of emotions on social media and the reciprocal influences among individuals. The findings not only offer a novel perspective on the mechanisms of emotional transmission during public health events but also supply empirical evidence to inform public opinion and emotional management in the context of influenza A.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of high-risk plaque in refining cardiovascular event prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: High-risk plaque (HRP) features are commonly observed in patients with acute coronary syndromes (ACS); however, their individual predictive value remains limited. This review explores the importance of integrating anatomical and physiological assessments to enhance risk stratification and optimize therapeutic decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why are we still using the PHQ-9? A Historical Review and Psychometric Evaluation of Measurement Invariance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Patient Health Questionnaire-9 (PHQ-9) is a widely used tool for assessing depressive symptom severity and as a screening tool in the diagnosis of major depression. Designed as both a diagnostic instrument and a severity index, it is commonly used in primary care and research. However, findings regarding its reliability and validity for these dual purposes have been mixed. This study aimed to review the history of the PHQ-9, evaluate its factorial validity, and temporal measurement...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900414/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Mesenchymal Stem Cell-Derived Skeletal Muscle Cell Spheroids for Treating Dexamethasone-Induced Sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings demonstrate the therapeutic potential of TMSC-SKMC-spheroids in the DEX-induced atrophy rat model and suggest their promise as a valuable therapeutic resource for sarcopenia caused by various factors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning mammography-based breast cancer risk model, its serial change, and breast cancer mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Mirai model, developed to predict breast cancer incidence, was significantly associated with breast cancer-specific mortality. Changes in Mirai risk scores over time were also linked to breast cancer-specific mortality, supporting AI-based risk models in guiding risk-stratified screening and prevention of breast cancer-related deaths.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Chaste Gaze: Long Thick Eyelashes as a Symbol of Divine Chastity-From Ancient Greece to Now]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This narrative review explores the evolving symbolism of long, thick eyelashes from classic antiquity to the present, positioning them as cultural markers of virtue, beauty, and identity. Sparked by the author's observation of the finely sculpted eyelashes of the Charioteer of Delphi (circa 470 BCE), this study traces how eyelashes transitioned from signs of divine chastity to tools of performative beauty. In ancient Greece, eyelashes embodied sōphrosynē-moral restraint and inner harmony-rather...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900183/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anatomical-Based Diagnosis and Filler Injection Techniques: Nasolabial Folds]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nasolabial folds significantly impact facial appearance and are a common aesthetic concern. This article reviews anatomic considerations and filler injection techniques for treating these folds, with a focus on the Korean population. The dermal filler used in this study is Maili hyaluronic acid filler (Sinclair Pharma), derived from a novel proprietary manufacturing technology known as OxiFree™ technology (Kylane Laboratoires , Switzerland). The study analyzes various injection techniques,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term Outcomes of Hypertension and Antihypertensive Drugs in Healthy Young Adults: A Nationwide Population-Based Prospective Cohort Study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cardiovascular risk factors, including HTN, contribute to major cardiovascular disease incidence in young adults. Antihypertensive medications decreased the major cardiovascular disease incidence estimates.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local nonequilibrium thermodynamics of polymer collapse dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonequilibrium thermodynamics plays a crucial role in understanding a wide range of physical and chemical processes. While significant advances have been made through frameworks, such as the fluctuation theorem, it remains challenging to define thermodynamic quantities, such as energy, entropy, and free energy, at the local level during nonequilibrium processes. Recently, Jinwoo and Tanaka [Sci. Rep. 5, 7832 (2015)] have proposed a formalism (the JT formalism) that defines local thermodynamic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899938/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal Surgical Strategies in Patients With T1 and T2 Gallbladder Cancer: necessity of Lymph Node Dissection and Liver Resection: a Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Simple cholecystectomy is adequate for T1 GB cancer, regardless of LN dissection. For T2 GB cancer, simple cholecystectomy with LN dissection can be performed without liver resection in selected patients, particularly in T2a, provided adequate LN dissection is achieved.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-Parkinsonian 4-hydroxy-2-pyridones from an endolichenic fungus, Tolypocladium sp. (strain CNC14)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[4-Hydroxy-2-pyridone alkaloids have attracted considerable attention because of their intriguing structures and diverse bioactivities. In our previous study, 4-hydroxy-2-pyridone alkaloids were shown to exhibit potent activity against neuron-associated targets. To discover this class of neuroactive compounds, an array of endolichenic fungal extracts was screened by analyzing LC-UV-MS profiles. The screening yielded strain Tolypocladium sp. (strain CNC14), which produced compounds with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of a Single Treatment of Needleless Microsubcision With Hyaluronic Acid and Carbon Dioxide Pinhole Method for Atrophic Acne Scars]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that needleless microsubcision with HA shows a nonsignificant trend toward superiority than CO2 pinhole method in treating atrophic acne scars.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of a varicella vaccine introduction on the incidence of herpes zoster in Korean children, an ecological study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The vaccine introduction has resulted in a large-scale ongoing HZ outbreak in children in Korea. More studies are needed to assess the long-term impact of the vaccine on HZ incidence in vaccinated individuals.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chronic low water intake is associated with altered exercise-induced oxidative stress and immune cell responses: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Habitual low water intake was associated with elevated concentrations of free radical by-products in the resting state and impaired antioxidant capacity during acute exercise stress. In response to exercise stress, impaired redox balance in low-water drinkers resulted in accelerated cellular damage and increased myeloid cell recruitment. These findings highlight the importance of maintaining adequate habitual water intake to cope with exercise-induced oxidative stress and prevent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isotretinoin as a Multifunctional Anticancer Agent: Molecular Mechanisms, Pharmacological Insights and Therapeutic Potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite notable advancements in conventional cancer therapies, challenges such as drug resistance, adverse effects, and high treatment costs remain significant obstacles. This situation calls for exploring new therapeutic options. One promising approach is drug repurposing, which uses existing medications with known effects to identify new anticancer agents. Isotretinoin (13-cis-retinoic acid), a vitamin A derivative typically used to treat severe acne, shows considerable potential as an...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photooxidation of Natural and Waste Cr(III)-Bearing Hydroxides in Water and Ice: Cr(III)-O<sub>2</sub> Complex-Mediated Oxidation and the Effect of Natural Organic Matter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The photooxidative dissolution of Cr(III)-bearing hydroxides (Cr(OH)(3) and Fe(x)Cr(1-x)(OH)(3)) is proposed as a potential abiotic source of Cr(VI) in environments. Compared to the dark oxidation of Cr(OH)(3) by O(2), photoirradiation enhanced Cr(VI) production in both aqueous and frozen solutions. In the presence of natural organic matter (NOM), the photoproduction of Cr(VI) was significantly promoted in aqueous solution but hindered in frozen solution. Photosensitized NOM induced the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frailty in Patients With Parkinson's Disease in Community and Clinical Settings: A Scoping Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Recognizing the specific characteristics of PwP with frailty is important to identify at-risk individuals and initiate timely interventions. Considering that PwP requires regular monitoring, it is recommended to use frailty measures that can capture multidimensional and cumulative aspects of frailty.Trial and protocol registration:https://doi.org/10.17605/OSF.IO/CUGEY.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Salmon Nasal Cartilage-Derived Proteoglycans Alleviate Cartilage Degeneration in Osteoarthritis by Modulating Inflammation and Apoptosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoarthritis (OA) is a chronic degenerative joint disease characterized by progressive cartilage damage, inflammatory responses, and apoptosis of chondrocytes. In this study, we investigated the therapeutic potential properties of proteoglycans (PG) extracted from salmon nasal cartilage in both in vitro (HTB-94 human chondrocytic cells) and in vivo (monosodium iodoacetate-induced OA rat model) approaches. Rats were treated with PG, and key parameters related to cartilage integrity,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the letter to the editor: Body mass index as a potential confounder in dutasteride and fertility studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physician's Role in Managing Driver's Licenses for Older Adults: Implications for Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing proportion of older adult drivers presents a growing road safety challenge in Korea, highlighted by a significant rise in traffic accidents involving individuals aged 65 years and older. In response, Korean authorities have implemented mandatory cognitive and physical assessments for license renewal, complemented by community-based educational programs. However, international comparisons reveal that the involvement of physicians as gatekeepers in assessing driver fitness is more...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association between dexmedetomidine use and delirium in critically ill surgical patients: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dexmedetomidine was mainly used in high-risk, severely ill patients, reflecting its role in managing severe symptoms rather than preventing delirium. These results highlight the need for personalized sedation strategies to optimize dexmedetomidine use in the ICU setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of the 2024 medical-policy conflict on hepatocellular carcinoma management in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In 2024, a nationwide conflict between the South Korean government and the medical community, the medical-policy conflict, profoundly impacted healthcare delivery. This study aimed to evaluate the changes in the management of hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) following this crisis. We analyzed retrospective real-world data from university hospitals in the Seoul metropolitan area, supplemented with national healthcare data from the Health Insurance Review and Assessment Service. The analytical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899157/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of the Stage 4 Smart Insulin Pen DIA:CONN P8 for Glycemic Control in a Real-World Setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated whether a stage 4 smart insulin pen (SIP) provides superior glycemic control compared with a traditional insulin pen (TIP) in individuals with intensively insulin-treated diabetes. Forty-two adults with continuous glucose monitoring (CGM), multiple daily insulin injections, and no prior SIP use were included. After diabetes self-management education (DSME), the SIP group (n=21) initiated SIP, whereas the TIP group (n=21) continued their usual regimens. Glycemic metrics were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Triglyceride-Glucose Index: A Practical Tool for Enhanced Cardiovascular Risk Stratification in Type 2 Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898928/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thyroid Cancer Risk and the Next Generation of Diabetes Drugs: What Can We Learn from Incretin-Based Therapies?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing Blood-Based Biomarkers for Sarcopenia: Current Challenges and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Mechanical versus Bioprosthetic Aortic Valve Replacement in Patients Aged 50 to 70 Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The GRF‒GIF duo and AINTEGUMENTA act cooperatively for the meristematic competence of lateral organs in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Above-ground lateral organs, such as leaves and flowers, should grow to an optimal size and develop particular structures, which are primarily laid out on the meristematic activities of their primordia. The GROWTH-REGULATING FACTOR‒GRF-INTERACTING FACTOR (GRF‒GIF) transcriptional complex and the AINTEGUMENTA (ANT) transcription factor play key roles in the establishment of the meristematic competence of lateral organ primordia with highly overlapping expression patterns, and thus functional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two decades of diabetes prevention: Sustained benefits, heterogeneous effects, and implications for precision prevention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing Winter-Type Seasonality Criteria in East Asian Populations: A Machine Learning Approach Using the Seasonal Pattern Assessment Questionnaire]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study evaluated seasonality in a South Korean early-onset mood disorder cohort using SPAQ and Kasper's criteria. Incorporating atypical vegetative symptoms and reduced social activity improved winter seasonality classification accuracy. The revised criteria may facilitate more precise identification and management of seasonal symptoms in East Asia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large-Scale Implementation of Vertical Sidewall and Vertical Multi-Channel WS<sub>2</sub> Nanosheet Field-Effect Transistors for Area-Efficient Integrated Circuit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[2D materials have emerged as promising candidates for next-generation field-effect transistors (FETs) owing to the atomically thin geometry and excellent electrostatic gate control. Here, double-gate vertical sidewall FETs based on chemical vapor deposition-grown monolayer WS(2) are demonstrated and, for the first time, report vertical multi-channel nanosheet FETs (NSFETs). By implementing a dual-step sidewall profile, steep SiO(2) surfaces are obtained, which enabled seamless WS(2) adhesion and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antisense oligonucleotide therapy mitigates autosomal dominant progressive hearing loss in a murine model of human DFNA2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hearing loss is the most common sensory disorder, with a substantial proportion caused by genetic mutations. KCNQ4, a voltage-gated potassium channel highly expressed in cochlear outer hair cells, is a common genetic etiology implicated in autosomal dominant progressive hearing loss (DFNA2). The dominant-negative KCNQ4 p.W276S (c.827G>C) mutation represents a mutational hotspot in DFNA2, yet no effective treatments exist. Here, we developed allele-preferential antisense oligonucleotides (ASOs)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered virus-like particles for in vivo gene editing ameliorate hearing loss in murine DFNA2 model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although gene editing therapy is applicable to human diseases, its efficiency and safety require further investigation. Further, non-virus-mediated gene editor delivery is challenging in the inner ear. Here, engineered virus-like particles (eVLPs) were used for inner-ear delivery of SpCas9 and single-guided RNA to delete the Kcnq4 dominant-negative mutant allele, which causes progressive hearing loss in a non-syndromic hearing loss murine model. eVLP-delivered SpCas9 was administered to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A rare case report of epithelioid hemangioendothelioma of the left buttock: Challenges in diagnosis and management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RATIONALE: Epithelioid hemangioendothelioma (EHE) is a rare vascular malignancy which poses significant diagnostic and therapeutic challenges due to its variable course and lack of standardized treatment protocols. In this case, the lesion's benign appearance and ambiguous histology delayed definitive diagnosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospects of Nanoscience with Nanocrystals: 2025 Edition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanocrystals (NCs) of various compositions have made important contributions to science and technology, with their impact recognized by the 2023 Nobel Prize in Chemistry for the discovery and synthesis of semiconductor quantum dots (QDs). Over four decades of research into NCs has led to numerous advancements in diverse fields, such as optoelectronics, catalysis, energy, medicine, and recently, quantum information and computing. The last 10 years since the predecessor perspective "Prospect of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Absorbable Adhesive Composite Hemostatic Sponge Based on Decellularized Extracellular Matrix and Mussel Adhesive Protein for Internal Bleeding Control]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hemostatic biomaterials for internal applications require strong wet adhesion, reasonable degradability, and supportive biocompatibility for wound healing. However, clinically used topical hemostats such as Surgicel and Avitene may induce hemolysis, inflammation, or leave behind residual debris that impairs healing. Bioinspired materials, including decellularized extracellular matrix (dECM) and mussel adhesive protein (MAP), have emerged as promising alternatives for their hemostatic potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling Enhanced Superconductivity in Single-Layer FeSe through Substrate Surface Terminations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single-layer FeSe on SrTiO(3)(001) substrates shows a superconducting transition temperature much higher than that of bulk FeSe, which has been attributed to factors such as electron doping, interfacial electron-phonon coupling, and electron correlations. To pinpoint the primary driver, we grew single-layer FeSe films on SrTiO(3)(001) substrates with coexisting TiO(2) and SrO surface terminations. Scanning tunneling spectroscopy revealed a larger superconducting gap (17.0 meV) on the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Relationship Between the Experience of Rescue Activities in the 2024 Noto Peninsula Earthquake and Posttraumatic Stress Symptoms and Psychological Distress Among Medical Rescue Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study showed factors associated with PTSS and psychological distress among MRWs during the Noto Peninsula earthquake, which was an important finding for future research on the mental health of MRWs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of a ≥ 1000 μm Posterior Margin After Gerota's Fascia Resection in Distal Pancreatectomy for Resectable Pancreatic Cancer: A Single-Center Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In resectable pancreatic cancer without adrenal or kidney invasion, a posterior margin ≥ 1000 μm was not associated with improved survival, supporting the adequacy of this approach. Further investigation into systemic disease control via preoperative chemotherapy is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply to Comments on "KidsBrainIT: Visualization of the Impact of Cerebral Perfusion Pressure Insult Intensity and Duration on Childhood Brain Trauma Outcome"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903681/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apparent diffusion coefficient for distinguishing between benign and malignant lesions in submandibular and sublingual spaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The ADC could be effective for the objectively and quantitatively diagnosis of submandibular and sublingual malignant tumors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of treatment initiation for secondary fracture prevention in the older population: Japanese Bone-fracture Osteoporosis in Late-stage population Database study (J-BOLD) - emulation of a randomized target trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Early initiation and sustained use of osteoporosis medication significantly reduced the risk of secondary fractures, particularly hip fractures, in men and women aged ≥ 75 years.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New maps and new challenges in the post-genomic era]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recellularization of decellularized vascular grafts via aligned seeding of endothelial cells derived from human iPS cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of decellularized vascular tissues for tissue engineering and vascular implants presents a promising approach to creating functional blood vessels. However, effective endothelialization with human endothelial cells remains challenging. This study examined the endothelialization of decellularized porcine aortas using human induced pluripotent stem (hiPS) cell-derived endothelial cells. Various decellularization methods were used to create vessels with different luminal surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amide-Directed C-H Acetoxylation of Cubanes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, a palladium-catalyzed, amide-directed C-H acetoxylation of cubanes has been developed. The ortho positions of the amide directing group on cubanes were selectively acetoxylated without any stoichiometric strong bases. The number (1-3) of acetoxy groups introduced was determined by the amount of PhI(OAc)(2) used. Substitution at the C4 position of cubane dramatically affected the outcome of the acetoxylation reaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903292/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in malignant hyperthermia: novel insights into heat-induced Ca<sup>2+</sup> release as a thermal signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermoregulation is essential for maintaining homeostasis in mammals under various environmental conditions. Impairment of this function can result in severe conditions, such as fever, heat stroke, and malignant hyperthermia (MH). In this review, we will focus on the role of the type 1 ryanodine receptor (RYR1), a Ca^(2+) release channel that is crucial for excitation-contraction coupling in skeletal muscles. Mutations in RYR1 are associated with muscle disorders, including MH, which is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonal Variation in Diuretic-Induced Dehydration Using Spontaneous Reports of Adverse Events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diuretics have long been central to the treatment of heart failure (HF) and hypertension, and are widely used in clinical settings. Herein, we performed a retrospective analysis of seasonal variations in diuretic-induced dehydration (DID) using the Japanese Adverse Drug Event Report (JADER) database, a platform that presents data on real-world clinical practice. A total of 11 diuretics prescribed in Japan, categorized into six groups, were included. The monthly reporting ratio (RR) of DID in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903218/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonaqueous capillary electrophoresis of graphene suggesting charging and dispersion mechanism in certain organic solvents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Graphene, with its unique electronic, thermal, and mechanical properties, plays an important role in electronic devices and batteries. Current applications strongly rely on liquid-phase processing, which requires stable graphene dispersions. However, stabilizing graphene dispersions in a liquid phase remains challenging because graphene easily aggregates due to strong inter-sheet forces. Many studies have indicated that graphene dispersions can be prepared by the ultrasound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of health promotion interventions in supermarkets on dietary variety among Japanese older adults: a protocol for a cluster non-randomised parallel-group comparative trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: With an ageing population, prevention of frailty among older adults has become a critical public health issue. Dietary habits are one of the essential components in frailty prevention, which involves promoting changes in dietary behaviours, such as including dietary variety. However, community-level health promotion interventions face significant challenges, including limited spatial access to food, which is important as it is not easy to change the behaviour of older adults. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Imaging technologies in experimental pulmonary fibrosis research: essential tool for enhanced translational relevance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary fibrosis remains a devastating and often fatal condition due to the lack of effective treatments that halt disease progression. Rodent models of pulmonary fibrosis are crucial to identify candidate targets and novel therapeutic agents. However, the attrition rate of novel drug candidates in clinical trials remains high. This review suggests complementing traditional methods used to evaluate antifibrotic therapies in rodent models, such as histopathological and biochemical markers, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Capillary-Tube-Evaporative-Concentration (CTEC) method: a new protein-sparing approach to directly determine protein apparent solubility values for antibody developability assessments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solubility behavior is an important attribute to rank-order monoclonal and bispecific antibody (mAb, biAb) candidates during developability assessments. Current approaches to directly measure antibody solubility without adding precipitating additives (e.g., centrifugal ultrafiltration, protein powder rehydration) have limitations including high protein consumption (∼tens of mgs) and protein instability (e.g., aggregation or gel formation). In this work, we describe the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stable microclimates and autonomic modulation in horses housed in different stable architectures during monsoon in a tropical environment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results indicate that autonomic responses vary among horses in different stable designs, suggesting that stable architecture, microclimates, and the volume-to-horse ratio significantly influence horses' stress responses. Overall, these findings offer important insights for improving housing management to enhance the welfare of horses during the monsoon season in tropical environments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902952/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the letter to the editor: "Comparative effectiveness of romosozumab versus teriparatide for fracture prevention: A new-user, active comparator design"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contribution of vestibular afference to estimation of centre of mass state for stabilization of walking differs between anteroposterior and mediolateral directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Walking without falling requires correcting the deviations of the centre of mass (CoM) trajectory relative to the base of support. This process is partially under feedback control. We investigated whether vestibular afference contributes to estimating CoM state to stabilize walking. We disturbed the vestibular afference by electrical vestibular stimulation (EVS), which typically leads to responses coherent with the stimulus and directed opposite to movement direction encoded by the induced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Excellent adsorption performance of sulfated yeast for heavy metal ions: High capacity and selectivity for rare earth elements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study is to provide valuable knowledge for developing a biological material effective in recovering and removing metals from solutions. Yeast was used as the base material. Yeast, a homogeneous material with a rigid cell wall, is inexpensive, readily available (it can even be obtained from brewer's waste), and amenable to chemical and genetic modification. Since native yeast exhibits low adsorption capacity, yeast with numerous sulfate groups to enhance metal binding was prepared...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902781/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muscle activation variability in relation to functional internal rotation in reverse total shoulder arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lower-level patients tended to have an overactivation of certain shoulder girdle muscles leading to a limited fIR outcome. Muscle activations of some principal shoulder muscles are correlated with fIR outcome. Muscle activation patterns revealed that mainly the posterior deltoid, upper and lower trapezius, and teres major muscles are essential to reach high fIR levels. Lastly, an increased kinesiophobia and decreased internal rotator strength were correlated with lower fIR outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomarker-related phospho-tau217 appears in synapses around Aβ plaques prior to tau tangle in cerebral cortex of preclinical Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phospho-tau protein p-tau181 is a cerebrospinal fluid biomarker for Alzheimer's disease (AD), while p-tau217 is the most sensitive plasma biomarker for cerebral amyloid β (Aβ) load prior to tau pathology in preclinical AD. Diagnostic and prognostic use of these p-tau biomarkers requires neuropathological interpretation. Here, we analyzed the cellular localization of biomarker p-tau species in postmortem human brains harboring different extents of Aβ plaque and tau pathology. Signals for p-tau217...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Addressing Bias in machine learning feature importance for food quality assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Li et al. (2025) highlighted Random Forest's (RF) high accuracy and SHapley Additive exPlanations (SHAP)-derived feature importance for almond deterioration. However, concerns persist regarding the reliability of these interpretations, as high predictive accuracy doesn't guarantee valid feature rankings due to inherent biases in tree-based models, further amplified by SHAP's model dependency. To mitigate this, integrating robust statistical methods such as Spearman's rho, Kendall's tau, Total...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic disorders of dolichol synthesis and utilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The polyisoprenoid lipid dolichol is critical for eukaryotic glycosylation. It is used as the membrane anchor for mono- or oligosaccharides transferred during N-glycosylation, O/C-mannosylation and glycosylphosphatidylinositol anchor biosynthesis. Disorders affecting the synthesis or utilization of dolichol cause defective glycosylation and are therefore classified as Congenital Disorders of Glycosylation (CDG). CDG are a group of approximately 200 mostly autosomal recessive inherited metabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eco-friendly sonochemical synthesis of BaTiO<sub>3</sub>/Ag nanocomposite particles: Investigation of Ag-nanoparticle formation and growth behavior under ultrasound irradiation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study synthesizes BaTiO(3)/Ag nanocomposite particles using an eco-friendly sonochemical method and investigates the mechanism of Ag-nanoparticle deposition. BaTiO(3) and Ag(2)O were ultrasonically irradiated in methanol at 20 ˚C, and samples and solvents were characterized using X-ray diffraction, scanning electron microscopy, scanning transmission electron microscopy with energy-dispersive X-ray spectroscopy, ultraviolet-visible spectroscopy, Brunauer-Emmett-Teller method, X-ray...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stereotactic radiofrequency thermocoagulation selectively targeting the subiculum for mesial temporal lobe epilepsy -Treatment concept and preliminary results]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tailored ablation of the subiculum by MRgSRFTC with multiple trajectories and coagulations can provide effective seizure control with minimal damage to the surrounding tissues. Further evaluation with more patients is required to confirm the validity of the present surgical strategy and procedure.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "Symptom control and medication adherence in Japanese pediatric and adolescent asthma: A large-scale web-based cross-sectional survey" [Respir Invest, Volume 63, Issue 5, September 2025, Pages 1018-1025]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Daikin air purifiers on asthma control and pulmonary function: A multicenter, single-arm, observational pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Daikin air purifiers demonstrated the potential to reduce PM levels and improve pulmonary function and asthma symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Keap1-Nrf2 Protein-Protein Interaction Inhibitor Activating Intracellular Nrf2 Based on the Naphthalene-2-acetamide Scaffold, and its Anti-Inflammatory Effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nuclear factor erythroid 2-related factor 2 (Nrf2) and Kelch-like ECH-associated protein 1 (Keap1) axis is an attractive therapeutic target for various intractable diseases. Although protein-protein interaction inhibitors against Keap1-Nrf2 have been developed over the past decade, more structural expansion is needed to improve efficacy. In this article, several candidate compounds are designed and synthesized as novel Nrf2 activators and their intracellular Nrf2-activating effects are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of the crossover from quantum fluxoid to half-quantum fluxoid in a chiral superconducting device]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topological superconductors are one of the intriguing material groups from the viewpoint of not only condensed matter physics but also industrial applications such as quantum computers based on Majorana fermion. For real applications, developments of thin-film topological superconductors are highly desirable. Bi/Ni bilayer is a possible candidate for thin-film chiral superconductors where the time-reversal symmetry is broken. Here we report the phase shift of resistance oscillations by half flux...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peptide nucleic acids in parallel orientation form invasion complexes with double-stranded DNA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peptide nucleic acid (PNA) is a unique class of synthetic nucleic acids with a pseudo-peptide backbone, known for its high nucleic acid recognition capability and its ability to directly recognize double-stranded DNA (dsDNA) via the formation of a unique invasion complex. While most natural and artificial nucleic acids form duplexes in an antiparallel configuration due to the general instability of parallel configurations, PNA distinctively forms both antiparallel and parallel duplexes. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40901609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chiral molecular 4f qubits by post functionalization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We herein demonstrate the synthesis of a pair of enantiomerically pure Yb^(III) complexes by post-functionalisation of the parent Yb^(III) complex via condensation with an enantiomerically pure chiral amine. The enantiomeric pair is structurally characterised by single crystal and powder X-ray diffraction, showing that it crystalises in the P2(1)2(1)2(1) Sohncke space group with Flack parameters close to zero, which confirms their enantiopurity. Circular Dichroism (CD) and absorption...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900766/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facial Nerve Regeneration in Immunodeficient Rats Using a Bio 3D Conduit Fabricated From Human Dental Pulp Stem Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tumor surgery or trauma in the maxillofacial region may cause injuries to peripheral nerves, such as facial nerves. The gold standard of treatment for peripheral nerve injury has been autologous nerve grafting. Since new peripheral nerve regeneration technologies are required, three-dimensional (3D) structures fabricated only from cells by using Bio 3D printers are attracting attention. Dental pulp stem cells (DPSCs) are a promising option as a cell source because of their high clonogenic,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is Transient Mixed Hearing Loss a Distinct Audiometric Feature in Patients With Inner Ear Schwannoma?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In the early stage, the most common audiometric features in patients with IES are sensorineural hearing loss with a U-shaped or rising configuration with air-bone gaps at low to mid frequencies, followed by rapidly progressive hearing deterioration. Transient mixed hearing loss appears to be a distinct audiometric feature of patients with IES.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoluminal lacrimal duct recanalization for pediatric secondary acquired lacrimal duct obstruction following epidemic keratoconjunctivitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CCO and SDJ were the primary lacrimal pathway obstruction sites following EKC in children. ELDR combined with intubation using dacryoendoscopy demonstrated favorable outcomes, supporting its role as an effective treatment option for secondary EKC-derived SALDO in children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Music therapy preferences among breast cancer patients undergoing perioperative chemotherapy: from qualitative insight to quantitative evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: As patients' specific preferences have been clarified, we conclude that professionals may be more well-positioned and informed to devise more appropriate and effective MT programs to be incorporated into the treatment schedules of PWBC who are undergoing chemotherapy, with vital quality-of-life implications resulting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of National Diagnostic Reference Levels 2025 for nuclear medicine in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diagnostic reference levels (DRLs) are practical benchmarks for optimizing patient radiation exposure in medical imaging. In Japan, national DRLs, including those for nuclear medicine together and other radiological procedures, were first established in 2015 and revised in 2020. In this study, we revised the DRL values of nuclear medicine for the establishment of DRLs2025, based on data collected from institutions nationwide throughout Japan. Data were collected via an online survey from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900285/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term outcome of mycophenolate mofetil after a single dose of rituximab in childhood-onset refractory idiopathic nephrotic syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MMF after a single dose of rituximab is safe and effective in achieving a long relapse-free period and discontinuing a calcineurin inhibitor in patients with refractory FRNS/SDNS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of posaconazole as primary prophylaxis in allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We retrospectively analyzed the effectiveness of posaconazole (tablet and infusion formulations) and its correlation with blood concentration in preventing invasive fungal infections (IFIs) in 360 patients who underwent allogeneic hematopoietic stem cell transplant (allo-HSCT) between 2010 and 2023. A total of 61 patients received posaconazole, 102 received micafungin, and 197 received fluconazole for primary prophylaxis. By day 100 post-transplant, the cumulative incidence of IFIs was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light chain proximal tubulopathy in Sjögren syndrome: the critical role of tubular function tests in revealing a hidden threat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A 65-year-old female patient with Sjögren syndrome (SJS) and tubulointerstitial nephritis (TIN) confirmed by kidney biopsy results 7 years previously presented to our department with progressive kidney function deterioration. Laboratory findings revealed increased serum creatinine level accompanied with deterioration of tubular function. Although she already had signs of proximal tubular dysfunction due to TIN from 7 years before, deterioration of the proximal tubule related parameters was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900249/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[S100-positive stroma in salivary gland basal cell adenoma: recent progress and future perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Basal cell adenoma (BCA) with S100-positive stroma exhibits tricellular differentiation, consisting of bilayered epithelial cells and S100-positive spindle-shaped stromal cells. While the neoplastic nature of the stromal component has been supported by multiple lines of evidence, its myoepithelial origin, suggested by ultrastructural analysis, has not yet been confirmed by other methodological approaches. This mini-review summarizes the key findings of ultrastructural, immunohistochemical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Randomized crossover comparison of two teriparatide self-injection regimens for primary osteoporosis: final report of the Japanese Osteoporosis Intervention Trial 06 (JOINT-06)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patient satisfaction and efficacy were maintained with both teriparatide regimens over 104 weeks, and persistence improved during the patient-choice phase. Supporting patient preference may improve adherence to osteoporosis medications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response predictors and long-term outcomes of preprandial single-daily cyclosporine in children with steroid-dependent nephrotic syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Single-daily cyclosporine may offer a promising treatment option for children with steroid-dependent nephrotic syndrome caused by MCD, particularly for those who do not experience early relapse following nephrotic syndrome diagnosis and have lower prior relapse rate.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900209/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controlled Disassembly of Poly(methyl acrylate) Microparticle-Based Polymers using Ethanol-Water Mixtures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding and controlling the degradation conditions of polymers is essential to achieve an environmentally friendly recycling of polymeric materials without deterioration. In this study, we investigated the disassembly of microparticle-based polymer films into the individual microconstituents under mild conditions such as low temperature and aqueous solutions of ethanol. The solvation of the microparticles and the microparticle-assembled structures are key factors for controlling the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability and validity of the multidimensional impact of cancer risk assessment (MICRA) questionnaire: Japanese version]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to develop and validate a Multidimensional Impact of Cancer Risk Assessment questionnaire-Japanese version (MICRA-J) as an assessment of the psychosocial impact of genetic testing. The MICRA was translated into Japanese using standardized translation procedures. The reliability and validity of the MICRA-J were evaluated in individuals who underwent BRCA1/2 testing for hereditary breast and ovarian cancer diagnosis. The 72 respondents included patients with BRCA1/2 pathogenic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Grief and Depression Among Bereaved Parents Who Have Lost an Adult Child to Cancer: A National Death Follow-Up Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Parents who have lost their children to death often experience high levels of grief and depression. However, studies on the grief and depression experienced by parents who have lost an adult child to cancer are scarce. Objectives: To clarify the risk and characteristics of grief and depression in parents who have lost an adult child to cancer. Design: A nationwide mortality follow-back survey was conducted in Japan with participants identified using death certificate data for cancer....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40900165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-precision machine learning identifies a reproducible functional connectivity signature of autism spectrum diagnosis in a subset of individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A highly targeted prediction model can identify a subset of functional connectivity alterations that confer high risk for ASD at the individual level, which may be masked by traditional machine learning models due to ASD heterogeneity. Results could help disentangle the multitude of etiological pathways and behavioral symptoms that challenge our understanding of ASD by focusing on highly penetrant connectivity signatures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efferocytosis-Driven M2 Macrophage Impairs Fibrotic Encapsulation and Promotes Echinococcus multilocularis Growth in Cotton Rats (Sigmodon hispidus)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alveolar echinococcosis, caused by Echinococcus multilocularis, exhibits significant species-dependent susceptibility. This study compared the early hepatic tissue responses to E. multilocularis in highly susceptible cotton rats (Sigmodon hispidus) and laboratory mice (DBA/2 and AKR/N). Following oral administration of E. multilocularis eggs, cotton rats developed a greater number of hepatic lesions within 2 weeks, whereas mice required 4 weeks to develop smaller lesions. Histopathology revealed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling-Making-Modulating High-Entropy Alloy with Activated Water-Dissociation Centers for Superior Electrocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[High-entropy alloys (HEAs) have recently emerged as promising electrocatalysts for complex reactions owing to their tunable electronic structures and diverse, unique binding sites. However, their vast compositional space, in terms of both elemental variety and atomic ratios, presents a major challenge to the rational design of high-performance catalysts, as experimental efforts are often hindered by ambiguous element selection and inefficient trial-and-error methods. In this work, a bottom-up...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899870/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The <em>ATO</em> gene family governs <em>Candida albicans</em> colonization in the dysbiotic gastrointestinal tract]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fungal pathogen Candida albicans colonizes the human gut, where short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs) serve as a source of carbon. This fungus harbors one of the largest microbial families of ATO (acetate transporter ortholog) genes, which encode putative SCFA transport proteins. Here, we generate C. albicans null mutants lacking individual or all known putative SCFA transporter genes and compare their phenotypes in vitro and in vivo. We show that blocking ATO function in C. albicans impairs SCFA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jigsaw Puzzle Inspired Patterning of Gas Diffusion Layers for Enhanced Water Management in Polymer Electrolyte Fuel Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Under high current density operation, water generation at the cathode of polymer electrolyte fuel cells (PEFCs) floods the electrode, resulting in severe mass transport limitation and an associated voltage drop. Water management is thus of crucial importance in improving the overall performance of fuel cell systems. Gas diffusion layers (GDLs) with independent pathways for either gaseous oxygen or liquid water transport present a potential solution to this issue. Here a novel, simple, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899636/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concerted Reactive Adsorption and Photocatalytic Degradation of Bisphenol-S on Molybdenum Cluster-Modified Nanoceria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bisphenol-S (BPS) is a widespread toxic industrial pollutant and endocrine disruptor of growing environmental concern. This study investigates the use of porous nanoceria particles (CeO(2)) functionalized with octahedral molybdenum clusters (Mo(6)) for the removal of waterborne BPS through a combined mechanism of reactive adsorption and photodegradation. Although immobilization of Mo(6) cluster reduced the overall surface area of CeO(2), BPS adsorption and partial decomposition in the dark were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Anti-HIV Agents Isolated From Two Euphorbia Species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Four previously unreported tigliane diterpenes (1, 2, 4, and 6), along with two known tiglianes (3 and 5), were isolated from the latex of Euphorbia palustris and Euphorbia lucida. The structures of the isolated compounds were elucidated by spectroscopic techniques. Antiviral activity assays for compounds 1‒4 and 6 against HIV-1 and HIV-2 replication were performed on a CD4^(+) T cell line, MT-4 cells. The compounds were tested for their ability to inhibit infection by the HIV-1 strain NL4.3 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrafast nonradiative decay from higher-lying excited states in azulene-dimers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The anti-Kasha fluorescence nature of azulene has been explained by the large energy gap between the second excited state and the lowest excited singlet state. While such property is expected to be perturbed in the presence of electronic interchromophore interactions without a change in the S(n)-S(1) energy gap, the study of the excited-state dynamics of azulene assemblies or oligomers remains scarce. In this study, we designed dimers with diverse rigid bridge structures with controlled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899369/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What we cannot miss in clinical trials on compression therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundCompression therapy (CT) is widely prescribed for chronic venous disease (CVD), lymphedema, and lipedema despite robust evidence supporting its effectiveness only in a minority of clinical scenarios.AimProvide an overview of the methodological parameters essential for obtaining a high-quality scientific trial.MethodsThe International Compression Club (ICC) chairman prepared a preliminary list of the main methodological flaws in publications on CT, and a list of parameters to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899334/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An ionic binaphthyl-bridged imidazole dimer for fast visible-light-driven negative photochromism in aqueous media]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a binaphthyl-bridged imidazole dimer bearing alkylpyridinium groups that exhibit fast and visible-light-induced negative photochromism even in aqueous media. The introduction of ionic groups not only enhances water solubility but also induces charge-transfer absorption, enabling efficient blue-light activation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899195/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transition of Childhood Cancer Survivors into Adult Health Care: A Perspective from Adult Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose: The number of long-term childhood cancer survivors (CCSs) has been increasing, and the importance of transitioning from pediatric to adult care has been advocated. This study aimed to describe the health problems of adult CCSs from adult-care perspectives. Methods: We conducted a chart review of adult CCSs aged ≥18 years who visited a transition clinic in adult care between June 2019 and March 2024. Results: The study included 25 CCSs, with a median follow-up period of 14 months. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Preoperative Nutritional Status on Postoperative Clinical Outcomes of Patients with Metastatic Spinal Tumors: Japan Association of Spine Surgeons with Ambition Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Preoperative malnutrition was observed in 36% of patients with metastatic spinal tumors who underwent surgery and was associated with a poor postoperative survival prognosis and delayed physical recovery. However, surgical treatment improved motivation, QOL, and physical function 6 months after surgery. These findings highlight the importance of assessing the nutritional status preoperatively and considering both survival and functional prognoses when selecting surgical treatment for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40899098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision targeting of the melanocortin-1 receptor with radiopharmaceuticals in metastatic melanoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospective Comparison of Posterior Decompression and ACDF for 1-2-Level Degenerative Cervical Myelopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Both PD and ACDF provided comparable improvements in neurological function as measured by JOA and JOACMEQ scores, indicating similar efficacy in treating DCM. ACDF was more effective for alleviating neck and arm pain and enhancing physical health, while PD resulted in social functioning. Given similar complication rates, surgical strategy should be individualized based on each patient's clinical presentation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do Child Gender Stereotypes Mediate Associations Between Human Fathers' Testosterone Levels and Paternal Involvement? Two Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This preregistered study investigated whether human paternal testosterone levels predicted fathers' time spent with their child and their involvement in childcare and household tasks. Additionally, we examined whether associations were mediated by fathers' attitudes toward child gender stereotypes. Associations were tested in an exploratory sample (n = 70, M = 6.73 months postpartum, SD = 2.13) and a test sample (n = 80, M = 2.67 months postpartum, SD = 0.77). Testosterone was quantified from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bi-Zr-Modulated CO<sub>2</sub> Microenvironment Enables High-Rate CO<sub>2</sub> Electroreduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineering the local chemical environment is an emerging strategy to enhance the performance of electrochemical CO(2) reduction reactions (CO(2)RR). Bismuth-zirconium composite catalysts (Bi-Zr-KB, where KB = Ketjen Black) are developed to leverage Zr incorporation to modulate the local CO(2) microenvironment in an alkaline flow-cell system. Among the catalysts synthesized with various Bi/Zr ratios, the Bi-Zr-KB sample with a Bi/Zr ratio of 2 demonstrated the highest performance, achieving a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898712/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increasing Occurrence of Marburg Virus Outbreaks in Africa: Risk Assessment for Public Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this millennium, Marburgvirus (MARV) outbreaks with very high mortality but still small case numbers (< 400) were observed with increasing frequency in Africa. Ecologists identified Egyptian Rousettus bats (ERB) as viral reservoir species causing occasional zoonotic spillover events, mostly in humans intruding into their cave habitats as miners or tourists. So far only short human-to-human transmission chains have been documented. ERB can be experimentally infected with MARV but show no...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40898685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20250904033854&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal Chirality Enhances Long-Range Fluctuation-Induced Interactions in Active Fluids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding interactions between chiral active particles- self-propelling and self-rotating entities- is crucial for uncovering how chiral active matter self-organizes into dynamic structures. Although fluctuation-induced forces in nonequilibrium active systems can drive structure formation, the role of chirality remains largely unexplored. Effective fluctuation-induced forces between intruders immersed in chiral active fluids are investigated and revealing that the impact of chirality depends...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diversifying Substrates and Reaction Conditions for Polymerase Strand Recycling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cell-free biosensing systems are being engineered as versatile and programmable diagnostic technologies. A core component of cell-free biosensors is programmable molecular circuits that improve biosensor speed, sensitivity, and specificity by performing molecular computations such as logic evaluation and signal amplification. In previous work, we developed one such circuit system called Polymerase Strand Recycling (PSR), which amplifies cell-free molecular circuits by using T7 RNA polymerase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms and Pathophysiological Significance of Insulin Resistance in Offspring With Intrauterine Growth Restriction Mediated by Hepatic GR/miR-1224 Programming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Insulin resistance (IR) has fetal origin and gender preference. Here we traced glucose-insulin phenotypical changes of intrauterine growth restriction (IUGR) female offspring at different ages and explore the mechanism. The IUGR model was established by prenatal caffeine exposure (PCE): dams were orally administered caffeine [(30, 120 mg(kg.d)^(-1)] from gestational day 9 to 20. PCE offspring presented decreased basal serum glucose, insulin, and insulin resistance index, accompanied by improved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilizing the Laparoscopic Ovum Pick-Up Method for In Vitro Embryo Production in Prepubertal Anatolian Native Black Calves: A Promising Approach for Gene Banks and Endangered Species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in genomic technology have increased interest in using calves as oocyte sources through the laparoscopic ovum pick-up (LOPU) method, which shortens generation intervals and enhances genetic gain. This study aimed to produce embryos in vitro using oocytes from endangered Anatolian Native Black calves and to increase the number of embryos in the gene bank through LOPU, a method not previously studied in Turkey. Four Anatolian Native Black calves, approximately 3 months old,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of a 6-week semi-supervised exercise training program on physical fitness and mental health in post-COVID-19 healthcare workers: a randomized clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A six-week semi-supervised exercise training significantly improved functional muscle strength and endurance, and maximum rowing intensity in post-COVID-19 HCWs compared to controls, along with within-group reductions in depression and anxiety. No adverse events were reported. These findings suggest that exercise may be a safe and effective recovery strategy to prevent or alleviate post-COVID-19 conditions, although further research is needed to confirm long-term effectiveness and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40903785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20250904033855&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>