<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:21:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of Information Uses and Trust in COVID-19 and Influenza Vaccine Hesitancy Among Undergraduate Students in the United States and Republic of Korea: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: As the COVID-19 vaccine transitions into an annual immunization, it is important to understand the factors contributing to vaccine hesitancy and uptake. This study aims to examine how information source use and trust are associated with COVID-19 and influenza vaccine hesitancy and influenza vaccine uptake.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546603/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly Selective and Flexible HCl Sensor Enabled by Ag<sub>2</sub>O-Functionalized Graphene Micropatterns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Graphene is considered one of the most attractive materials for next-generation gas sensor platforms owing to its high performance at room temperature, transparency, and flexibility. However, graphene exhibits inherent low selectivity and irreversible behavior in gas sensing. While various methods such as doping, grain control and metal decoration have been extensively employed to functionalize graphene, graphene sensors for strong acids have remained underexplored. Here, we present...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546538/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Hidden Photoinduced Phase-Transition Pathway in Strain-Engineered VO<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoexcitation provides a versatile route to drive quantum materials into nonequilibrium states, opening opportunities for phase engineering beyond conventional tuning parameters such as temperature, magnetic field, pressure, or chemical doping/substitution. VO(2), a prototypical correlated oxide, has long served as a model system for understanding photoinduced insulator-metal transitions, yet the sequence of structural and electronic transitions remains intensely debated. Here, we uncover a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Upconversion Luminescent Nanocarrier for Effective Tumor-Targeted Photodynamic Therapy Combined with Immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Combination cancer therapy, a treatment modality combining two or more therapeutic strategies, has attracted attention for treating various types of cancer. In this study, we produced near-infrared (NIR)-induced multi-shell upconversion nanoparticle (MUN)-based therapeutic nanocarriers co-loaded with chlorin e6 (Ce6) and indoximod (IND) (FMUN3-Ce6/IND) to combine tumor-targeted photodynamic therapy (PDT) with immunotherapy. Upconversion nanoparticles doped with rare-earth elements are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The International Collaborative Animal Study of The Carcinogenicity and Genotoxicity of Mobile Phone Radiofrequency Radiation: The Korean Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A chronic bioassay investigating radiofrequency (RF) carcinogenicity, intentionally designed to be conducted simultaneously in Korea and Japan, using the same research protocol and experimental environment. The study aimed to assess the potential carcinogenicity of Code Division Multiple Access (CDMA)-modulated 900 MHz RF signals at a whole-body specific absorption rate (SAR) of 4 W/kg, which is the reference level of the international human safety guideline, and to verify the key findings from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-difference in chewing difficulty and the risk of obstructive sleep apnea among middle-aged and older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In females, higher levels of chewing difficulty were associated with increased OSA risk. These findings suggest that chewing difficulty could be explored as a potential factor in identifying individuals at higher risk of OSA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546801/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polydeoxyribonucleotide (PDRN) in Dentistry: Narrative Review for Mechanisms and Emerging Clinical Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although these findings highlight broad therapeutic potential, current evidence remains limited. Most reports derive from preclinical experiments or small-scale clinical studies, and well-designed randomized controlled trials are needed to validate efficacy of PDRN and define its optimal clinical indications in evidence-based dental protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution and correlation of trace elements in Eurasian otters (Lutra lutra) from South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As an apex predator, the Eurasian otter (Lutra lutra) encounters trace element pollutants in freshwater ecosystems. Our study assessed the accumulation of arsenic (As), cadmium (Cd), mercury (Hg), lead (Pb), selenium (Se), copper (Cu), manganese (Mn), and zinc (Zn) in the lung, liver, and kidney tissues of Eurasian otters collected from five regions in South Korea between 2018 and 2024. Comparisons with prior South Korean and European studies indicated regional variations in Se and Mn levels,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546773/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic performance of multiparametric imaging markers in differentiating local recurrence from post-treatment change in head and neck cancer surveillance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ADC(mean) and SUV(max) showed excellent performance in differentiating recurrence from post-treatment changes. TBV maps may offer complementary diagnostic value in cases with compromised ADC quality due to artifacts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbubble-Mediated Synthesis of Smart Spindle Microfibers for Fog Harvesting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fog has significant potential as a water resource, offering a solution for alleviating the global risk of freshwater scarcity. Spindle-knotted microfibers are highly effective for fog collection, though the complexity of fabricating such structures remains a significant challenge. In this study, a simple microfluidic method using microbubbles is introduced for the fabrication of smart spindle microfibers (SSMs). The combination of microbubbles of varying sizes, induced by pulses from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postsurgical Rotational Flare Between the Proximal and Distal Segments of the Mandible Following Mandibular Setback Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The PS exhibited counterclockwise rotational flare and anterior-outward/posterior-inward yawing in relation to the DS. Incorporating surgical compensation for anticipated rotational flare-related relapse may enhance the predictability of mandibular setback outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546467/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Improvement of IL-23 Inhibition Revealed by Single-Cell RNA Sequencing in Concurrent Psoriasis and Systemic Lupus Erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacing and Growth Pathways of Metal-Organic Frameworks with Morphological Evolution]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hybrid metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) that integrate multiple components or structures via MOF-on-MOF growth offer promising avenues for constructing highly valued MOFs. However, understanding and controlling the anisotropic MOF-on-MOF growth that occurs between MOFs with mismatched lattices remain challenging, particularly when designing hybrid MOFs that integrate highly mismatched structures. In this study, interfacing and growth behaviors of MOFs during anisotropic MOF-on-MOF processes were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrophobic Metal-Organic Frameworks Enable Superior High-Pressure Ammonia Storage through Geometric Design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrophobic metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) are typically overlooked for ammonia storage due to weak host-guest interactions. Here, we demonstrate that four structurally analogous aluminum-based MOFs exhibit a counterintuitive behavior whereby framework geometry, rather than ligand hydrophilicity, determines high-pressure NH(3) adsorption performance. The hydrophobic CAU-23 achieved an exceptional capacity matching hydrophilic analogs despite its poor low-pressure uptake. This pressure-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age at first marriage, menopause status and cervical cancer risk in a middle eastern country: a national cancer registry-based case-control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Younger age at first marriage, being in menopause, and unawareness of HPV vaccine availability were independently associated with an increased risk of cervical cancer. These findings should be regarded as preliminary and hypothesis-generating, offering a foundation for further research on this important women's health issue in Kuwait and comparable settings. Larger studies are warranted to confirm these results and to identify additional determinants of cervical cancer risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond routine: evidence and uncertainty in intraoperative oxygen titration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546833/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SnapShot Freeze 2.0, a second-generation motion-correction algorithm, improves mitral valve image quality in preoperative cardiac computed tomography for mitral regurgitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atmospheric dynamics of glyphosate and AMPA in agricultural areas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The atmospheric dynamics of glyphosate and AMPA was investigated in an agricultural area in the Netherlands over eight weeks following glyphosate application to sandy soil. Airborne sediment was collected every two weeks, at five different heights, and analyzed for glyphosate and AMPA. Results showed that the glyphosate content in the samples was initially high, almost 6000 µg kg^(-1) two weeks after application, decreasing to about 2300 µg kg^(-1) eight weeks after application. AMPA content...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-activity Relationships of Triterpenoid Saponins Across Phylogenetically Diverse Organisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Saponins are structurally diverse bioactive metabolites found in more than 100 plant families and are synthesized by plants as protection against insects, fungi, and other organisms. The mode of action is related to their interference with membranes, and particularly the membrane sterols. As membrane sterol composition varies across kingdoms and species, species-specific differences in toxicity may therefore be expected. The aim of this study was to elucidate the structure-activity relationships...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aggressive stone removal in octogenarian bedridden elderly patients: analysis of safety and impact on the reduction of recurrent stone-related events]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inflammatory pain alters colorectal motility via spinal oxytocinergic pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastrointestinal motility is regulated primarily by the enteric and the central nervous systems. Our previous studies revealed that central circuits regulating colorectal motility partially overlap with those involved in pain modulation, suggesting functional interactions between the nociceptive modulatory pathway and the autonomic regulatory pathway of colorectal motility. Here, we examined whether peripheral inflammatory pain alters the neural components of the descending pathway regulating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Angle-resolved Cathodoluminescence Microscopy on Plasmonic Crystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Controlling electromagnetic modes in nanostructures is vital for developing advanced optical devices. Metal surfaces with periodic structures, so-called plasmonic crystals (PlCs) form band structures of surface plasmon polaritons (SPPs), providing highly controllable confinement of SPPs and conversion to far-field light. Angle-resolved cathodoluminescence (CL) spectroscopy, where emitted light upon electron beam irradiation is analyzed with angle selection, can be combined with electron...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IGF2BP3 in Multi-System Diseases: Molecular Mechanisms, Pathological Roles and Translational Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546815/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced Gaze-Stimulus Synchrony to a Rhythmic Children's Song in Young Children With Autism: A Recurrence Quantification Analysis Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight reduced visual engagement and gaze-stimulus synchrony in young children with ASD compared to their TD peers, and indicate that gaze-based metrics may serve as potential objective markers of developmental functioning. The results underscore the utility of diverse analytic approaches, such as RQA, in uncovering temporal characteristics of gaze behavior. Future research should include nonsocial stimuli to determine whether reduced gaze-stimulus synchrony reflects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision breeding in a changing climate: unlocking resilience through omics and gene editing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climate change, rising global food demand, and shrinking resources require transformative innovations in crop breeding. This review outlines recent advances in new breeding technologies (NBTs), including molecular markers, genome-wide association studies (GWAS), genomic selection (GS), next-generation sequencing (NGS), and gene editing (GE) tools such as the clustered regularly interspaced short palindromic repeat (CRISPR/Cas), base editing, and prime editing. These methods enable the accurate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546796/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Umbilical Cord Mesenchymal Stem Cells and Wnt Pathway Modulation: A Novel Therapy for Liver Cirrhosis and Steatosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Umbilical cord mesenchymal stem cells were used to treat cirrhosis, ranging from end-stage to early stages, in methionine-deficient rats by modulating the Wnt pathway. It can inhibit the progression of steatosis-related inflammation and fibrosis, further depresses cirrhosis in mice and humans, and underscores the significance of umbilical stem cells in public health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546791/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the check-up: how well-child exams, pediatric specialists, and provider recommendations can close HPV vaccine gaps for Chinese American Teens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Provider recommendations and pediatric care are crucial for improving HPV vaccination rates among CA adolescents. Addressing regional disparities and implementing targeted interventions, including enhanced provider training focused on culturally sensitive communication, are essential to dismantle systemic barriers and improve comprehensive vaccination coverage in this underserved population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urinary metabolites of 1,3-butadiene, benzene and toluene and colorectal cancer incidence: a clinical case-control study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MHBMA3 (a metabolite of 1,3-butadiene) was associated with a higher incidence of CRC independent of smoking and other CRC risk factors. Non-smoking sources of 1,3-butadiene, such as environmental sources, may contribute to increasing CRC incidence. Additional epidemiologic studies are needed to confirm this observation. Further laboratory studies are required to identify potential biologic mechanisms specific to MHBMA3 and colorectal carcinogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546763/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Tobacco Use, Experiences and Knowledge among Indigenous Mexican Agricultural Workers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of growth trajectories from birth to two years of age with adolescent blood pressure: the mediating role of current BMI in the follow-up of an antenatal micronutrient supplementation trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While early-life growth patterns are thought to be pivotal for long-term cardiovascular health, their specific links to adolescent blood pressure (BP) and potential mediators remain unclear. We aimed to examine the associations of growth trajectories from birth to age two with systolic and diastolic BP in adolescence, and to quantify the proportion mediated by concurrent adolescent BMI. In a prospective birth cohort in rural China, we repeatedly measured infant weight and length at birth and at...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative approaches to river ecosystem assessment and restoration: a review of methodologies and strategies for coherent implementation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[River ecosystems are vital to Earth's biogeography and environmental health by facilitating material cycling, energy transfer, and information exchange. However, human activities, including hydraulic engineering, land use changes, industrial and agricultural expansion, and overfishing, have significantly disrupted natural river morphology and ecological patterns. These interventions have altered the river's physical and chemical properties, resulting in biodiversity loss and ecosystem services...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phototropin monitors actual temperature, not temperature difference, to regulate temperature-dependent chloroplast movement via cis-trans autophosphorylation mode switching in Marchantia polymorpha]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In liverworts, phototropin senses the actual temperature rather than temperature differences and switches from cis- to trans-autophosphorylation to trigger the cold-avoidance response of chloroplast movement. Blue-light (BL)-induced chloroplast movement in plant cells is temperature-dependent. At standard growth temperatures, chloroplasts move toward weak BL-irradiated regions (accumulation response), maximizing photoreception, whereas at lower temperatures they move away from the irradiated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546717/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contraceptives in chronic lymphocytic leukemia (CLL): a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546716/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acetylcysteine combined with budesonide nebulized inhalation for the treatment of pneumonia in children: a meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of short-term efficacy after conservative treatment of bowel obstruction on long-term survival of patients with malignant tumors of the digestive system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Short-term outcome of pharmacological conservative treatment after bowel obstruction in malignant tumors of the digestive system influences patients' long-term survival but is not an independent prognostic factor. Staging and previous tumor surgery are independent prognostic factors influencing survival in patients with malignancies of the digestive system combined with bowel obstruction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age- and sex- specific dose coefficients to convert ingested <sup>90</sup>Sr activity into cumulative dose in active marrow]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546688/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High incidence of intrahepatic cholangiocarcinoma in end-stage renal disease patients in Taiwan: analysis of a nationwide database with molecular insight of aristolochic acid exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrahepatic cholangiocarcinoma (iCCA) is the second most common primary liver cancer. Its association with chronic kidney disease (CKD) and end-stage renal disease (ESRD) is unclear. Using Taiwan's National Health Insurance Research Database (NHIRD), we analyzed the relationship between iCCA and CKD/ESRD. Molecular alterations were explored through whole-exome sequencing (WES) and Archer FusionPlex in 24 surgical specimens from 22 CKD/ESRD patients. Aristolochic acid (AA)-related DNA adducts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546685/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of deep learning-based methods for automatic detection and segmentation of brain metastases in T1-contrast MRI for stereotactic radiosurgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The nnU-Netv2 allows precise segmentation of lesion areas in T1-contrast MRI, while U-Mamba provide effective detection of brain metastasis, potentially aiding in treatment planning for SRS.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prenatal Shwachman-Diamond Syndrome: Diagnostic Challenges in Two Unrelated Cases With a Rare Clinical Presentation and Pseudogene Interference, and a Review of the Literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This report describes two unrelated prenatal cases of Shwachman-Diamond syndrome (SDS) presenting primarily with severe skeletal anomalies. SDS is a rare autosomal recessive disorder characterized by a triad of bone marrow dysfunction, skeletal abnormalities, and exocrine pancreatic dysfunction. The most common postnatal features include faltering growth, short stature, and neutropenia resulting in recurrent infections. Prenatal presentations could be scarce as the most common features are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546657/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atrial Fibrillation Ablation Using 3D Artificial Intelligence Module Integration with Intracardiac Echocardiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI FAM was associated with incremental but significant procedural advantages over conventional contouring via reduced total procedure time and LA dwell time, without compromising acute and long-term safety and rhythm control efficacy. AI FAM integration with PFA will mark another step towards making AF ablation more streamlined and accessible.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ready for battle: histone modifications shape rice intergenerational memory to protect against nematode attack]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Accumulating scientific insights reveal the ecological and evolutionary implications of phenotypic plant plasticity in response to biotic and abiotic stress factors. This study confirms that root-knot nematode infection leads to intergenerational acquired resistance (IAR) in rice offspring. Genome-wide and targeted gene expression analyses demonstrated that offspring of nematode-infected rice plants are better prepared to fight against such attack through 'spring loading' of hormone-related...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low T3 syndrome in children with aggressive mature B-cell non-Hodgkin lymphoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low triiodothyronine (T3) syndrome, also known as non-thyroidal illness syndrome (NTIS), was one of the common endocrinopathies in critical illness. The potential impacts of low T3 syndrome on survival, endocrine function, and nutritional status of patients with aggressive mature B-cell non-Hodgkin lymphoma (NHL) needed to be explored. We enrolled 225 patients. T3 levels were captured when starting chemotherapy, finishing chemotherapy, and at the first follow-up visit from 6 months after...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Exercise Duration and Intensity on Maximal Exercise Capacity Over 6 Months in Coronary Heart Disease and Type 2 Diabetes-A Secondary Analysis of the LeIKDTrial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exercise training is recommended in coronary heart disease (CHD) and type 2 diabetes (T2DM) patients alike; however, uncertainty remains on the influence of exercise intensity and duration in older patients with both entities. To address this, we performed a secondary analysis including 201 patients (67.9 ± 8.2 years; 84.1% men) from the LeIKD trial (NCT038359), which introduced 6 months of home-based telemedicine-supported exercise intervention in patients with CHD and T2DM. We assessed the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibiogram profiles and genetic characteristics of Streptococcus pneumoniae clinical isolates from Pakistan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings underscore the growing prevalence of antibiotic-resistant S. pneumoniae in Pakistan and highlight the urgent need for enhanced antimicrobial stewardship, improved surveillance systems and preventive measures to address the rising threat of resistant strains and shifting serotype distribution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms underlying the therapeutic effects of Dendrobium officinale in treating metabolic syndrome based on clinical datasets, network pharmacology, molecular docking and enzyme kinetic assay]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Dendrobium officinale effectively improves MetS parameters. Vicenin II and Schaftoside are identified as key active constituents, likely exerting therapeutic effects through potent PTP1B inhibition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protective effects of Cynanchum auriculatum Royle ex Wight on testicular reproductive decline in naturally aging male rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that C. auriculatum effectively delays reproductive function decline in the testicular tissues of naturally aging rats, likely by inhibiting DNA damage, modulating the P53 signaling pathway, and reducing reproductive cell apoptosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of different topical spironolactone treatments for acne vulgaris: A meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This meta-analysis demonstrates that topical spironolactone is an effective and well-tolerated monotherapy for mild-to-moderate facial acne, with its efficacy varying by formulation and concentration. These findings provide clinicians with evidence-based insights for selecting alternative topical treatments. Future studies with larger sample sizes and longer follow-up are warranted to confirm these results.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546576/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urokinase plasminogen activator inhibitory and anti-breast cancer activity of Cananga odorata and Lantana camara leaf extracts from optimization of ultrasound-assisted extraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that LC extract effectively suppresses uPA activity while exerting cytotoxic effects on breast cancer cells, indicating its potential as a anticancer and chemoprevention agent.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Local Structure Strategies Promoting Lead-Free Dielectric Energy-Storage Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dielectric capacitors are essential for high-power, fast-response electronics, but their performance is limited by trade-offs between high polarization, low hysteresis loss, and high breakdown strength. The urgent need for eco-friendly materials has spurred intense interest in lead-free oxide dielectrics. Recent advances in synthesis and advanced characterization have revealed that atomic- and nanoscale local structures exert a profound influence on energy-storage performance. Specifically,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumour-host interactions in Drosophila: mechanisms in the tumour micro- and macroenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Traditionally, cancer has been viewed largely as a disease of the cell, with extensive research centred on how mutations in driver genes trigger cellular transformation. Beyond cell-intrinsic changes, cancer unfolds as a systemic disease driven by an intricate dialogue between malignant cells and the host's organs and tissues. Modelling this multilayered phenomenon is challenging, as it requires recapitulating coordinated interactions within and across multiple organs, inside an organism that is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Attapulgite Template for Oxygen Vacancies Boost of Manganese Dioxide Nanozymes With High Oxidase-Like Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Manganese dioxide (MnO(2)) nanozymes have high oxidase-like activity (OXD-like activity), and template methods are widely used to introduce oxygen vacancies (O(v)) for further improvement of OXD-like activity. However, the current precise templates with high cost and poor biocompatibility impart resistance to MnO(2) nanozymes in biocatalysis applications. Therefore, the development of green templates with economy, biocompatibility, and even edibility is urgently necessary. In this study,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Antibiogram: A Novel Multi-Task Machine Learning Framework for Simultaneous Prediction of Antimicrobial Resistance Profile with Enhanced Detection of Carbapenem Resistance in Enterobacteriaceae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A multi-task XGBoost framework can accurately predict individualized resistance profiles for common Gram-negative pathogens, outperforming conventional antibiograms and single-target models. Personalized antibiograms may enhance the selection of empiric therapy, including the detection of carbapenem resistance in low-endemicity settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Butyrate Alleviates Diabetic Periodontitis by Suppressing Macrophage M1 Polarization and PANoptosis-Like Cell Death]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dysbiosis of the gut microbiota in diabetes is accompanied by reduced levels of short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), including butyrate, a four-carbon SCFA with immunomodulatory activity. Inflammatory stimulation drives macrophage polarization toward an M1 phenotype and can induce concurrent activation of markers associated with pyroptosis, apoptosis, and necroptosis, consistent with a PANoptosis-like cell death phenotype that may exacerbate periodontal destruction. Here, we investigated whether...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facile Synthesis of Sodium Titanate Nanosheets as Promising Electrode Material for High Power and Energy Density Supercapacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sodium titanate nanosheet-based electrode material is prepared via a solid-state high-temperature sintering method, and its energy storage performance is evaluated for supercapacitor applications. The material characterization studies confirmed the formation of sodium nanosheets, and the electrochemical studies (three-electrode system) exhibit excellent charge storage performance by achieving the specific capacitance of 670 F/g @ 1 A/g, and 175 F/g@10 A/g along with adequate stability (5000...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metallic Transport in Pseudocubic Quaternary Diamondoid Thermoelectric Semiconductor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently diamondoid semiconductors have attracted significant attention for thermoelectric applications due to their intrinsic low thermal conductivity and unique electrical transport properties. However, because of their compact tetrahedral coordination and strong chemical bonding, diamondoid materials are typically difficult to dope, resulting in low electrical conductivity, generally below 200 S cm^(-1). In this work, we report an unusual metallic transport behavior in CdSe-doped pseudocubic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546509/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aramid Nanofiber-Based Multifunctional Phase Change Film for Photo/Electro-Thermal Energy Conversion, Harvesting and Storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phase change materials (PCMs) are extensively utilized in energy storage and thermal regulation due to their superior energy density, tunable response temperature, and environmental friendliness. However, the leakage susceptibility, inferior electrical conductivity, and solar harvesting ability significantly limit their practical application. To address these issues, we propose encapsulating PCMs with aramid nanofibers/MXene hybrid shells by Pickering emulsion templates to prevent leakage, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546503/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychotherapy Process Dynamics and Their Relation to Treatment Success Do Not Differ Across Diagnoses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psychotherapy process research increasingly uses intensive longitudinal monitoring to capture dynamic patterns of change in patients. In this study, 283 psychiatric inpatients diagnosed with depression (n = 70), PTSD (n = 148), dissociative disorders (n = 26) or personality disorders (n = 39) completed the Therapy Process Questionnaire each evening over an average of 81.5 days per patient, yielding a total of 23,074 assessment days. We computed eight dynamic process characteristics, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Considerations for Collecting Public Health Data on Justice-System Involvement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved Outcomes for Older Children, Adolescents, and Young Adults With Neuroblastoma in the Post-Immunotherapy Era: An Updated Report From the International Neuroblastoma Risk Group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: For patients ≥547 days old, any age cut-off ≤40 months discriminated younger (superior EFS/OS) versus older patients; no cut-off was optimal. OCAYA diagnosed 2010-2022 (post-immunotherapy era) had superior outcomes versus 2003-2009. Stratification by comprehensive molecular biomarkers will likely best inform novel therapeutic strategies for OCAYA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geographic Distance to Care and Financial Toxicity During Pediatric Cancer Treatment: A Qualitative Framework Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Families of children with cancer perceived geographic distance to care as an important factor that intensified financial toxicity. Interventions are needed to mitigate the development and effects of financial toxicity, and geographically distant families may require supplementary solutions tailored to their specific support needs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Geminiviral C2 proteins promote virus transmission by subverting plant defenses upon infestation of non-vector herbivores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrates that geminiviral C2 proteins suppress JA- and SA-mediated defenses induced by non-vector herbivores, thereby facilitating whitefly-mediated virus transmission. © 2026 Society of Chemical Industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconciling links between diversity and population stability across global plant communities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Maintaining ecological stability is essential for sustaining ecosystem functions and the benefits they provide to society. Ecological theory predicts that plant diversity destabilizes local populations, yet empirical studies report variable effects. We hypothesize that this discrepancy arises at least in part from differences captured by different diversity (average vs cumulative richness, i.e. the mean annual richness vs the cumulative richness across years) and stability metrics...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hundred-Nanosecond Equivalent Pixel Dwell Time for Deep-Tissue 3D Three-Photon Fluorescence Microscopy via Sparse X-Y-Z Reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Three-photon fluorescence microscopy (3PFM) enables high-resolution volumetric imaging in deep tissues but is fundamentally constrained by a trade-off among imaging speed and spatial resolution, due to low photon flux and prolonged laser exposure. We present DeepR-SXYZ, a deep learning framework that achieves pixel dwell time equivalent to hundreds of nanoseconds (0.168-0.38 µs) through sparse X-Y-Z reconstruction for 3PFM. Trained on paired datasets consisting of sparsely acquired...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Double E─H Bond Activation of Ammonia and Water by Cyclic Gallaphosphene L(OCP)GaPGaL]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cyclic gallaphosphene L(PCO)GaPGaL 1 (L = HC[C(Me)NAr](2); Ar = 2,6-i-Pr(2)-C(6)H(3)) selectively reacts with NH(3) and H(2)O at ambient temperature with twofold N─H and O─H bond activation and formation of compounds LGa(μ-PH)(μ-NHC(O)PH)GaL 2 and LGa(μ-PH)(μ-OC(O)PH)GaL 3. Both nucleophilic P atoms of 1 are protonated in these reactions, while the electrophilic carbon atom of the bridging PCO unit binds to the remaining NH group / O atom. The formation of heterocycles 2 and 3, which were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dismantling the Necroptotic Engine: An Oral Theranostic Nanosponge for Ulcerative Colitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ulcerative Colitis (UC) treatments often lack target specificity and have significant side effects. A key pathological driver is the excessive necroptosis of intestinal epithelial cells (IECs), which disrupts the gut barrier. To address this, we designed an intelligent oral theranostic nanoplatform, CurN@I, to dismantle the necroptosis-inflammation axis. CurN@I consists of a barium sulfate (BaSO(4)) core for computed tomography (CT) imaging, encapsulated within a pH-responsive silk protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vaccination Literacy and Its Determinants in Hungary: Results of a Cross-Sectional Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We recommend using the vaccination literacy instrument to identify individuals with inadequate vaccination literacy. Interventions focusing on social support and education to promote vaccine-related information would contribute to enhancing vaccination literacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546391/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An FDA analysis of the association of tumor growth rate, overall survival and progression-free survival in patients with metastatic NSCLC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The g value, as a volumetric measurement of tumor growth rate, may provide an additional or supplementary approach to assess the potential clinical activity of an agent. Prospective studies are needed to further assess the association of the g value derived from early tumor measurements with long-term outcomes in patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-resolution spin-polarized scanning tunneling spectroscopy using a functionalized superconducting tip]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Detecting spin states of electrons at the atomic scale has been at the heart of progress in condensed matter physics. Spin-polarized scanning tunneling microscopy and spectroscopy (SP-STM/STS) has provided important insights into understanding the nature of various spin-dependent phenomena, owing to its capability to visualize energy- and spin-resolved local density-of-states with atomic resolution. This review provides an overview of recent progress in SP-STS using functionalized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Glycaemic Status Modifies the Association Between Cardiometabolic Index and Cardio-Kidney Outcomes: A Multi-Cohort Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CMI is a simple, robust predictor of cardio-kidney risk especially in earlier metabolic states, with particularly strong prognostic value in normoglycaemic individuals where excess risk appears at lower CMI levels.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring the impact of a leadership in academic medicine program on faculty advancement and leadership attainment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Participation in LAMP significantly improved promotion rates, retention, and leadership attainment, particularly for nontenure-track and female faculty. These findings demonstrate the program's effectiveness in supporting faculty development and career advancement.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of an intervention to reduce stigma towards people with skin diseases among health and body care professionals - a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The seminar improved skin disease-related stigmatizing beliefs and attitudes of HBCPs. Its integration into vocational training curricula or delivery in workshops to increase knowledge about skin diseases and to reduce prejudices in various professional groups is promising.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546158/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of treatments for propranolol toxicity: a systematic review of current approaches and evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multiple interventions, including glucagon, HDIET, ILE, calcium, and ECLS, have demonstrated benefits in managing propranolol toxicity. However, owing to the low level of evidence and wide variability in patient presentations and treatment protocols, no single therapy exhibits universal efficacy. Individualized multimodal treatment remains essential, and high-quality clinical studies are necessary to establish standardized evidence-based protocols.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive study of the crystal structure and dynamics of [N(C<sub>3</sub>H<sub>7</sub>)<sub>4</sub>]<sub>2</sub>Cd<sub>2</sub>Cl<sub>6</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single crystals of the organic-inorganic hybrid compound [N(C(3)H(7))(4)](2)Cd(2)Cl(6) were synthesized by an aqueous solution method, and their structural and dynamic properties were systematically investigated. Thermal analyses revealed phase transitions at 321 K (T(C1)) and 445 K (T(C2)), followed by melting at 476 K. Single-crystal X-ray diffraction indicated that the compound crystallizes in a triclinic system with space group P[Formula: see text], showing variations in lattice parameters...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustainable production of battery-grade nickel via hydrogen reduction of saprolite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nickel production from saprolite-a major laterite source-is critical for the electric vehicle battery supply chain but is currently constrained by the high carbon footprint of the conventional Rotary Kiln-Electric Furnace (RKEF) process. Hydrogen-based reduction offers a sustainable alternative; however, optimizing the reaction kinetics and phase separation efficiency remains a challenge for industrial application. In this study, we investigated the hydrogen reduction behavior of saprolite ore...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of left ventricular systolic dysfunction in left bundle branch block using a fine-tuned ECG foundation model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Left bundle branch block (LBBB) is an important electrocardiographic (ECG) finding strongly associated with left ventricular systolic dysfunction (LVSD), a condition linked to poor clinical outcomes. Although early LVSD detection is crucial, standard diagnosis via echocardiography may not always be immediately accessible. In this study, we propose a fine-tuned ECG foundation model (FM) to enhance LVSD detection specifically in patients with LBBB. We conducted a retrospective multicenter analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances, challenges and prospects of origami and kirigami optoelectronics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Switchable between 2D and 3D forms, origami and kirigami have emerged as a versatile platform for deformable optoelectronic devices. Unlike electronic devices, whose electrical properties remain largely unchanged during transformation, the optoelectronic properties of these systems can vary significantly, offering opportunities for optical tunability but also introducing design challenges. Developing such devices requires careful consideration of electrical, mechanical, and optical factors. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oleanolic acid prevents ferroptosis and enhances oocyte competence during in vitro maturation in a porcine model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The in vitro production of porcine embryos is a valuable model for livestock biotechnology and human reproductive research. However, oocyte quality is often compromised during culture by ferroptosis, which is an iron-dependent form of cell death driven by lipid peroxidation and redox imbalance. This study induced ferroptosis using RSL3 during porcine oocyte maturation to evaluate the protective potential of oleanolic acid (OA), an antioxidant triterpenoid compound. Exposure to RSL3 increased...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acupuncture as adjunctive treatment for schizophrenia: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Acupuncture combined with standard-dose antipsychotics may provide pragmatic benefits, though lack of superiority over sham acupuncture indicates uncertainty about specific effects. High-quality trials are needed to establish definitive clinical recommendations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544539/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hierarchical approach reveals site-scale drivers of nematode assemblages on the west coast of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study was performed to assess the spatial variability of free-living marine nematode assemblages in tidal flats along the west coast of Korea to understand natural and anthropogenic factors shaping nematode community structures. Sediment and nematode samples were collected in August and September 2023 using a hierarchical sampling design comprising three regions, each with three sites (W1-W9), and three patches within each site. Significant differences in nematode density, diversity, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Point-Deeponet: Predicting nonlinear fields on non-Parametric geometries under variable load conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nonlinear structural analyses in engineering often require extensive finite element simulations, limiting their applicability in design optimization and real-time control. Conventional deep learning surrogates often struggle with complex, non-parametric three-dimensional (3D) geometries and directionally varying loads. This work presents Point-DeepONet, an operator-learning-based surrogate that integrates PointNet into the DeepONet framework to learn a mapping from non-parametric geometries and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544498/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Material-Independent Film Formation of Zr<sup>4+</sup>-Trimesic Acid Metal-Organic Complexes and Their Antifouling Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Interface-active, metal-organic complexes (MOCs) have been extensively exploited for interface engineering due to their material-independent coating properties. However, the MOC-based films often face some challenges, such as dark coloration and synthetic difficulty in organic-ligand derivatives, limiting their functional potential and expandability. This paper reports the fabrication of transparent MOC films, composed of Zr^(4+) ions and trimesic acid (BTC), under mild aqueous conditions and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544234/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circadian and Diurnal Regulation of Plant Lipid Metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Circadian rhythms, driven by an endogenous biological clock, align physiological processes with the Earth's 24-hour light-dark cycle, enabling organisms to adapt to diurnal environmental changes. In plants, the circadian clock regulates key physiological and metabolic processes, such as photosynthesis, nutrient uptake, and stress responses, thereby optimizing growth and development. Recent studies reveal that lipid metabolism is significantly influenced by the circadian clock and diurnal rhythm,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3-Dimensional Microlens Printing of Quantum Dot/Siloxane Hybrid Color-Converter for Highly Efficient and Stable Full-Color Micro-Light-Emitting Diode Display]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quantum dots (QDs) are promising color-converting materials for full-color micro-light-emitting diode (micro-LED) displays, but have poor stability and poor scalability, which hinder their practical application. We report a hybrid color-converting layer (CCL) composed of QDs, fumed silica nanoparticles (FSNs), and siloxane matrix that exhibits high optical performance and long-term stability under various environmental conditions. The QD-FSN/siloxane incorporates uniformly dispersed QDs within a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A new alkaloid glycoside and antifungal metabolites from the aerial parts of <em>Argemone mexicana</em> Linn. collected in Vietnam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A new benzophenanthridine alkaloid glycoside (1), named nitrotyrasanguinarinoside, together with twelve known compounds (2 -13), was isolated from the dichloromethane extract of the aerial parts of Argemone mexicana Linn. Their structures were elucidated using IR, HR-ESI-MS, 1D and 2D NMR, and ECD spectroscopy, as well as by comparison with the published data. The dichloromethane extract exhibited in vivo antifungal activity against Colletotrichum coccodes with 80% inhibition at a concentration...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of extraction solvents on cytotoxicity and high-resolution LC-MS profiling of red yeast rice extracts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With increasing public interest in health-promoting foods, appropriate safety assessment of functional food ingredients is essential. In vitro toxicity testing typically requires extraction of food materials, and the choice of solvent can substantially influence the resulting chemical composition and toxicological profile. This study investigated the effects of solvent polarity on extraction yield, cytotoxicity, and also the chemical composition of red yeast rice (RYR) extracts. Using ten...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542872/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rewiring Steroidal Metabolic Pathways for Diosgenin Production in Solanum nigrum]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diosgenin is a key starting material for the synthesis of steroidal drugs, such as corticosteroids and sex hormones. While the primary commercial source of diosgenin is the tubers of Dioscorea spp., identifying alternative plant hosts capable of diosgenin biosynthesis could enhance its production. In this study, we present Solanum nigrum, a widely distributed species of the Solanum genus, as a novel platform for diosgenin production. S. nigrum naturally accumulates high concentrations of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Experimental Evidence for Reverse Internal Conversion in the Relaxation Pathway of the Excited Anions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report here direct experimental evidence of reverse internal conversion taking place in the excited nitrobenzene anion, revealed by photoelectron spectra acquired by electron detection at the much-delayed time with respect to the laser-anion interaction time along the time-of-flight. Especially, autodetached photoelectrons from the dipole bound states which are in quasi-equilibrium with vibrationally hot anions have been clearly observed concurrently with thermionic emission at the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing technofunctional properties of an emulsion-type meat analog formulated with mealworm and TVP: mushroom incorporation at the optimal concentration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mushrooms are commonly used as functional additives in meat products and show promise in alternative protein development. This study evaluated the impact of five mushroom species-Ganoderma lucidum, Pleurotus eryngii, Pleurotus ostreatus, Agaricus bisporus, and Lentinula edodes-at 3% concentration on the quality of emulsion-type meat analogs made with textured vegetable protein and mealworm. Quality parameters including pH, color, viscosity, proximate composition, water holding capacity (WHC),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541738/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive review on mycoprotein-based meat analog production: nutritional, functional, physicochemical, and safety aspect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycoproteins derived from filamentous fungi have emerged as alternative meat proteins. This study reviews mycoprotein production and nutritional and functional characteristics. The quality properties of mycoprotein-based meat analogs and meat products are compared, and their safety is addressed. Fusarium spp., Aspergillus spp., and Neurospora spp. are safe, edible fungi capable of producing mycoproteins. Mycoprotein nutritional properties vary with the fungal strain, production substrate, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541736/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Panorama: a database for the oncogenic evaluation of somatic mutations in pan-cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Somatic mutations, key alterations in cancer development, exert differential effects across tissues and biological layers, such as transcriptomes, proteomes, and post-translational modifications (PTMs). Although previous pan-cancer studies have characterized the molecular landscape of cancer, the effects of individual somatic mutations across different tissues remain insufficiently explored. Here, we developed Panorama to evaluate the oncogenic potential of single somatic mutations across all...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Randomized, Double-Blind, Active-Controlled, Parallel, Phase 3 Clinical Trial for Evaluating the Efficacy and Safety of Zastaprazan in Patients with Gastric Ulcers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: An 8-week therapy involving zastaprazan 20 mg demonstrated noninferiority to lansoprazole 30 mg in the cumulative rate of healing of gastric ulcers at 8 weeks, and the two demonstrated similar safety profiles. (ClinicalTrials.gov identifier NCT05448001).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, Korea University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Mechanism-Based Multi-Level Population PK/PD Model for Potassium-Competitive Acid Blockers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Potassium-competitive acid blockers (PCABs) are emerging alternatives to proton pump inhibitors for the treatment of acid-related diseases. However, due to the complex, nonlinear interaction between drug exposure, food intake, and physiological rhythms, optimizing dosing strategies remains challenging. A multi-leveled population analysis was conducted using published pharmacokinetic and pharmacodynamic data on four representative PCABs: tegoprazan, YH4808, fexuprazan, and vonoprazan. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stress Shielding Effects of Short Stem Alignment and Bone Density in Reverse Shoulder Arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Short-stem humeral implants in reverse total shoulder arthroplasty (rTSA) are increasingly adopted because they preserve bone stock and reduce stress shielding. However, their shorter length raises the risk of malalignment, and outcomes may be further affected by osteoporosis, which is common in rTSA patients. This study investigated how humeral stem alignment (neutral, varus, valgus) and bone mineral density simultaneously influence stress distribution in the proximal humerus using finite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540670/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-performance photothermal GA-MoSe<sub>2</sub> nanosheet for rapid and sensitive point-of-care detection of C-reactive protein]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the aftermath of the global COVID-19 pandemic, there is a critical need to develop rapid and sensitive diagnostic devices for point-of-care testing (POCT). Despite the numerous benefits of paper-based colorimetric lateral flow immunoassays (LFAs) in rapid onsite diagnosis, their sensitivity and quantitative analysis capability are limited. To overcome the limitations of the current assays, we developed a new rapid diagnostic method that utilizes glycyrrhizic acid-molybdenum diselenide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540408/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FGF12 induces aberrant mechanosignaling in aortic smooth muscle cells during thoracic aortic aneurysm formation in Marfan syndrome mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Marfan syndrome (MFS), caused by mutations in the FBN1 gene, predisposes individuals to thoracic aortic aneurysm (TAA), a life-threatening complication. Recent studies have suggested that dysregulated mechanosignaling in aortic smooth muscle cells (SMCs) plays a pivotal role in TAA pathogenesis in MFS. However, the key molecular drivers remain largely undefined. Here we identify fibroblast growth factor 12 (FGF12) as a novel mediator of aberrant mechanosignaling in aortic SMCs during TAA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41540272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NGO ameliorates psoriasis by modulating mitochondrial function and suppressing pSTAT3-IL-17-expressing CD8<sup>+</sup> TRM cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Psoriasis is a chronic autoimmune skin disorder characterized by keratinocyte hyperproliferation, persistent inflammation, and frequent relapse. Tissue-resident memory T (TRM) cells, particularly IL-17- and phosphorylated STAT3 (pSTAT3)-expressing CD8^(+) subsets, have been established as central drivers of disease persistence and recurrence. These pathogenic TRM cells maintain local inflammatory circuits that are poorly targeted by current therapies, which helps to explain the limited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of lumbar spinal epidural abscess using biportal endoscopic approach: a case series]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41546034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immediate effects of upper cervical spinal manipulation on cervical sensorimotor control in individuals with chronic primary cervical pain: an exploratory randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Activation of the pituitary adenylate cyclase-activating polypeptide type I receptor promotes neuroblastoma proliferation and migration through distinct G protein pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative visual and refractive analysis of two enhanced monofocal intraocular lenses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported health utility of stroke and gastrointestinal bleeding related to DOACs in atrial fibrillation: a vignette-based substudy of a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global burden of amphetamine, cannabis, cocaine and opioid use in 204 countries, 1990-2023: a Global Burden of Disease Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug use disorders (DUDs) are emerging global public health challenges. Here we investigated the global and regional estimates of the prevalence and burden of DUDs, including amphetamine, cannabis, cocaine and opioid use disorders, from 1990 to 2023 for 204 countries and territories by using the Global Burden of Disease Study 2023. Overall, trends in global age-standardized disability-adjusted life-years of DUDs increased from 169.3 (95% uncertainty interval (95% UI), 134.4-203.9) per 100,000...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545593/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of choroid plexus volume with brain atrophy and glucose metabolism in multiple system atrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The choroid plexus (CP), a component of the glymphatic system, is essential in homeostasis and producing cerebrospinal fluid. Role of CP in multiple system atrophy (MSA) remains unclear. This study aimed to investigate the implication of the CP in MSA. This retrospective cross-sectional study included 87 MSA patients who underwent the Unified MSA Rating Scale (UMSARS), brain MRI, and^(18)F-fluorodeoxyglucose PET scan, along with 84 healthy controls (HCs). Multivariate linear regression analyses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and safety of minimally invasive distal pancreatosplenectomy in resectable and borderline resectable pancreatic cancer following neoadjuvant chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Minimally invasive distal pancreatectomy is a safe and oncologically sound option for selected patients with advanced PDAC after neoadjuvant chemotherapy. With careful patient selection, MIS may be effectively applied even in technically challenging cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545569/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DrugBank mining with machine learning reveals novel candidates for BCL-2 inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Apoptosis, also known as programmed cell death, is a fundamental biological process essential for development and cellular homeostasis. An imbalance in the levels of pro- and antiapoptotic proteins of the BCL-2 family can inhibit apoptosis and contribute to tumor formation. Although small-molecule inhibitors targeting BCL-2 proteins have been developed, their clinical efficacy remains limited, highlighting the need for new approaches to discover effective inhibitors. In this study, we used a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence based prediction of first recurrence in neovascular age related macular degeneration with validation by 19 experts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to investigate the value and difference in predictive performance between ophthalmologists and a previously developed and validated artificial intelligence (AI) model, and to evaluate how AI assistance influences expert decision-making in reliably assessing recurrence prediction of neovascular age-related macular degeneration (nAMD) after anti-vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF) treatment. 19 experts (nine retinal specialist ophthalmologists and ten non-retinal specialist...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545508/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative ketorolac use and postoperative acute kidney injury in elderly patients undergoing noncardiac surgery: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The use of nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, particularly ketorolac, in elderly patients is not recommended due to concerns about acute kidney injury (AKI). However, the effect of perioperative ketorolac use on postoperative AKI in elderly patients remains uncertain. We retrospectively reviewed patients aged ≥ 60 years who underwent noncardiac surgery lasting ≥ 1 h and were hospitalized for more than 2 days after surgery between January 2011 and June 2019. The ketorolac group included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cultural memory semiotics and function behavior structure model for digital inheritance and innovation in AI generated Huizhou woodcarving images]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asthma-mediated control of optic glioma growth via T cell-microglia interactions: A mathematical model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optic glioma, a slow-growing tumor, is associated with Neurofibromatosis type 1 (NF1) mutations and increased midkine (MDK) production. A connection between asthma and optic glioma has previously been observed, but the mechanisms are unclear. To elucidate the role of asthma in the regulation of glioma formation, we investigated the role of T cells and the subsequent pathways in the regulation of microglia, a key player in the glioma tumor microenvironment (TME). While asthma is often linked to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A compact dual-band antenna using a gap-coupled monopole branch for Wi-Fi 6/6E/7 applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spin-state engineering of single titanium adsorbates on ultrathin magnesium oxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Single atomic adsorbates on ultrathin insulating films provide a promising route towards building bottom-up quantum architectures based on atomically identical yet individually addressable spin qubits on solid surfaces. A key challenge in engineering quantum-coherent spin nanostructures lies in understanding and controlling the spin state of individual adsorbates. In this work, we investigate single titanium (Ti) atoms adsorbed on MgO/Ag(100) surfaces using a combined scanning tunneling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545365/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional evaluation of wax-based oleogels as solid fat replacers for designing low saturated fat plant-based meat analogues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Meat analogues have gained global attention as consumer demand increases for healthier and more sustainable food products. However, research aimed at replacing solid fats in meat analogues to lower saturated fat content remains very limited. Canola oil was structured with three natural waxes (candelilla wax, carnauba wax, and beeswax) and their potentials as solid fat replacers were evaluated for low saturated fat meat analogues. The wax-based oleogels retained solid fat at higher temperatures...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduction of RAD23A extends lifespan and mitigates pathology in a mouse model of TDP-43 proteinopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Protein misfolding and aggregation are cardinal features of neurodegenerative disease (NDD) and they contribute to pathophysiology by both loss-of-function (LOF) and gain-of-function (GOF) mechanisms. This is well exemplified by TDP-43 which aggregates and mislocalizes in several NDDs. The depletion of nuclear TDP-43 leads to reduction in its normal function in RNA metabolism and the cytoplasmic accumulation of TDP-43 leads to aberrant protein homeostasis. A modifier screen found that loss of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Associations of Total and Added Sugar Intake With Frailty in Older Adults: Analysis From a National Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: Higher total sugar intake and moderate added sugar intake were associated with lower frailty risk in older Korean adults. These findings highlight the importance of considering both the amount and source of dietary sugars when developing nutritional guidelines for healthy aging. Future policies should focus on nuanced dietary recommendations rather than universal restriction for the elderly population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41545003/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution and microstructure of the endothelial glycocalyx in the blood-brain barrier]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urban Soils Encounter More Severe Per- and Polyfluoroalkyl Substance Contaminations and Associated Exposure Risks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFASs), as persistent hazardous contaminants, have been increasingly identified in diverse environmental media. To date, however, information regarding the distribution and risks of PFASs in soils, particularly across urban-rural gradients, remains scarce. Therefore, this study performed high-resolution monitoring of PFASs at 119 sampling sites in the Qinhuai River Basin. The findings revealed that 18 targeted PFASs were identified in all soil samples, except...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544951/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean Dioxin Risk Patterns: Modulation by Dietary-Socio-Demographic and Behavioral Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Socio-demographic and behavioral factors may play an important role in modulating the non-carcinogenic risk associated with dietary dioxin exposure. Changes in dioxin risk patterns across such factors warrant further examination through additional investigation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal Comparison of Health-Related Quality of Life at 3 and 12 Months Post-Stroke Using Patient-Reported Outcome Measures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Predictors and trajectories differed between PH and MH groups, supporting separate assessment. PROMIS-10 exhibited better discriminatory capacity of milder disability at 12 months by distinguishing physical and mental dimensions, supporting tailored care basis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544683/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid microneedle patch for administration of measles and rubella vaccine with an on-patient medical record]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Decentralized on-patient medical record (OPMR) storage would enable medical staff to access patients' medical information on demand, especially in low-resource settings lacking centralized recordkeeping infrastructure. We incorporated near-infrared (NIR) microparticles into microneedle patches (MNPs) to invisibly encode medical information in the skin for OPMR using a specialized reader. NIR particles were co-encapsulated with inactivated polio vaccine in the same microneedles without loss of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544667/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[C2-Involving Cervical Ossification of the Posterior Longitudinal Ligament (OPLL): Dome-like Laminoplasty Versus Laminectomy With Fusion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectivesTo compare the outcomes of C2 dome-like laminoplasty (C2-Dom LP) and C2 laminectomy with fusion (C2-LF) in patients with C2-involving ossification of the posterior longitudinal ligament (OPLL) and to identify radiological predictors that guide optimal surgical selection.MethodsA retrospective analysis of 143 patients (C2-Dom LP, 71; C2-LF, 72) was performed. Radiological evaluations were C2 cross-sectional area (CSA), cervical range of motion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time-series evaluation of an ED-based syndromic alarm system before and during the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ED-based SyS can offer timely and specific early warning for seasonal respiratory outbreaks, particularly in pediatric populations. However, its utility is limited during sustained pandemic waves. Future surveillance systems must incorporate adaptive models, dynamic thresholds, and multiple data streams to remain effective under evolving epidemiological baselines.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishing practical predictors of collection efficiency for optimized chimeric antigen receptor T-cell apheresis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CE2 during CAR-T apheresis is strongly influenced by pre-apheresis hematologic parameters, particularly WBC. Establishing CE2 predictors may refine estimation of processing volumes and improve planning for centers initiating CAR-T manufacturing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D-printable, heat-resistant polycaprolactone-based polymer scaffold for sustained NO release in tissue engineering applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study entailed the development of a nitric oxide (NO)-releasing, 3D-printable, heat-resistant polymer scaffold to support angiogenesis and osteogenesis for tissue engineering applications. A scaffold synthesized with poly(nitrocarbonate)-poly(ε-caprolactone) random copolymer (PNC-ran-PCL) enabled controlled NO release, addressing the rapid diffusion limitations found in conventional NO delivery systems. The thermoplastic properties of PNC-ran-PCL facilitate the creation of biomimetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment preferences and values in chronic tinnitus patients: A cross-sectional survey study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tinnitus patients strongly prefer non-invasive treatments while harboring unrealistic expectations for cure. These findings underscore the importance of structured education and shared decision-making to align clinical care with patient values and promote more effective tinnitus management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distribution and prognostic impact of LymphGen subtypes in Korean diffuse large B-cell lymphoma using clinical NGS panel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Several molecular subclassifications of diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (DLBCL) with prognostic and therapeutic potential have been proposed; however, their validation in diverse populations and real-world clinical settings remains limited. We investigated the genetic subtypes of Korean DLBCL using the LymphGen classifier and an institutionally developed targeted NGS panel for clinical use comprising 121 lymphoma-related genes. We further assessed quality control (QC) metrics, copy-number...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CiFGNA: Comprehensive information-based functional gene network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous gene networks capture coordinated gene activities and systemic disruptions in complex biological processes and diseases, but extracting biologically meaningful insights from these large-scale networks remains challenging due to limited interpretability of existing methods. To address this gap, we have developed comprehensive information-based functional gene network analysis (CiFGNA), a novel computational methodology that systematically detects functional pathways enriched with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Grouped-Bath Configuration Interaction for Transition-Metal Complexes by L-Edge X-ray Spectra Calculations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We assess the accuracy and limitations of the grouped-bath configuration interaction (GBCI), formerly termed the grouped-bath ansatz for the spin-flip nonorthogonal configuration interaction (SF-GNOCI), by calculating L-edge X-ray absorption spectroscopy (XAS) spectra and 2p3d resonant inelastic X-ray scattering (RIXS) spectra of transition-metal complexes. We compare the computed GBCI spectra with those from the spin-flip complete-active-space (SF-CAS) method and experiment. These comparisons...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Evaluation of the Hemostatic Efficacy and Safety of a Biodegradable Hemostatic Agent, Hemogram: A Comparative Study with Arista™ AH]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundHemogram is a novel biodegradable powdered hemostatic agent developed by binding calcium ions (Ca²^(+)) to carboxymethyl starch (CM-starch) and applying granulation technology to enhance blood absorption and hemostatic efficacy. This study aimed to evaluate the clinical efficacy and safety of Hemogram compared with the commercially available agent Arista™ AH in patients undergoing gastrectomy.MethodsThis randomized controlled trial was conducted at Samsung Medical Center and included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41544004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indirect Associations of Perceived Stress and Sleep Quality in the Relationship Between Andropause Symptoms and Quality of Life Among Middle-Aged Men: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the associations between andropause symptoms, perceived stress, and sleep quality, and determined the indirect pathway of perceived stress and sleep quality in the relationship between andropause symptoms and quality of life (QoL) among middle-aged men. This cross-sectional study employed a quantitative mediation analysis design. In total, 186 middle-aged men completed questionnaires, including the Androgen Deficiency in Aging Males Scale, Perceived Stress Scale, Pittsburgh...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Lymphoscintigraphy and SPECT/CT After Vascularized Lymph Node Transfer in Lymphedema Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lymphoscintigraphy with SPECT/CT may serve as a valuable prognostic tool for evaluating surgical outcomes following VLNT in lymphedema treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Invisible Text Injection and Peer Review by AI Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Quality of Evidence of and Engagement With Video Medical Claims]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this quality improvement study, a substantial credibility-evidence gap was found in physician-generated video-sharing content, where medical authorities often legitimized claims lacking robust empirical support. These findings emphasize the need for evidence-based content guidelines and enhanced science communication training for health care professionals to maintain scientific integrity in digital health information.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Selective Growth of Bi<sub>2</sub>SiO<sub>5</sub> for Uniform UV-B Photodetector Arrays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce Bi(2)SiO(5) (BSO), an intrinsically UV-B selective oxide with a 4.17 eV bandgap (297 nm), and present a cost-effective, scalable conversion approach for its synthesis. A single-step reaction between Bi(2)O(3) vapor and SiO(2) in fused silica converts the glass directly into crystalline BSO. To enable scalable integration, SiO(2) is first patterned on Al(2)O(3); the same conversion then proceeds exclusively within those patterns, yielding pixel-defined BSO films with sharply...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gynostemma pentaphyllum Hydrodistillate and Damulin B Prevent UVB-Induced Photoaging In Vitro and In Vivo via ROS Suppression and Restoration of MAPK/AP-1 and TGF-β/Smad Signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photoaging of the skin, driven by ultraviolet B (UVB) radiation, is characterized by the upregulation of matrix metalloproteinases (MMPs), accelerated collagen degradation, diminished hyaluronic acid (HA) content, and disruption of extracellular matrix (ECM) integrity, culminating in wrinkle formation, and structural damage. Nutritional and plant-derived compounds have garnered increasing attention as promising therapeutic agents for skin aging. In this study, we explored the anti-photoaging...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Viscoelastic Phase Transition of Polyborodimethylsiloxane (PBDMS) for Mechanical Pass Filters and Noise Fading Sensor]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous monitoring of physiological signals is inevitably disrupted by motion artifacts and ambient mechanical noise. Signal processing is typically required to extract genuine physiological signals from motion artifacts, yet the signals can be distorted and classified incompletely. Previously, we presented a noise-selective damper based on gelatin hydrogel and chitosan, however, the hydrogel is unstable due to dehydration. In addition, various types of mechanical filters, such as high-pass,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543211/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Standardization of MR Electrical Properties Tomography: A Guideline From the ISMRM Electro-Magnetic Tissue Properties Study Group]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41543109/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to discussion forum: Prognostic implications of moderate aortic stenosis with concomitant aortic regurgitation in degenerative aortic valve disease: insights from a multicentre cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural insights into promoter recognition by Aca7]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CRISPR-Cas systems provide adaptive immunity to bacteria, although bacteriophages counter these defenses with anti-CRISPR (Acr) proteins. Acr expression is frequently regulated by anti-CRISPR associated (Aca) proteins, which repress transcription by binding inverted repeat (IR) sequences in operon promoters. Here, we report the first identification of an IR motif within the AcrIF11-Aca7 operon promoter from Halomonas caseinilytica and present the crystal structure of Aca7 bound to this IR DNA....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering delivery platforms for controlled nitric oxide release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitric oxide (NO) is a versatile gaseous signaling molecule with broad therapeutic potential in cardiovascular regulation, immune modulation, oncology, antibiotics, and tissue regeneration. However, its clinical application is severely constrained by physicochemical limitations, including poor aqueous solubility, rapid degradation, and the lack of spatiotemporal control over its release. To address these challenges, a diverse array of NO donors, ranging from spontaneous-release compounds to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JAK Inhibition Restores Epidermal Homeostasis and Modulates Immune Responses in Dermatomyositis Skin: A Spatial Transcriptomic Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure preserving t-SNE of matrix framed data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Across various fields, we can align data elements into a matrix frame with both row and column indices, forming what we refer to as matrix-framed data. These elements can take various forms, such as scalars, vectors, time series, matrices, or arrays. Existing data visualization methods aim to represent data elements of different groups without considering the underlying two-dimensional structure present in matrix-framed data. To address this limitation, we introduce a novel visualization method...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationship between Fish Consumption and Undernutrition among Young Indian Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Encouraging fish consumption through public initiatives like the National Nutrition Mission could be a valuable strategy for mitigating the burden of anemia among young children. Further research utilizing detailed food consumption data, including fish intake, is warranted to investigate its impact on child health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41542028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cannula is safer than needle in filler injection?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The choice between cannulas and needles for dermal filler injection has direct implications for safety, efficacy, and patient experience. This narrative review synthesizes evidence from randomized controlled trials, observational studies, cadaveric/anatomical work, and expert consensus to compare complication profiles and practical use-cases. Across multiple studies, cannulas-by virtue of their blunt tips and gliding technique-are associated with lower rates of bruising and a reduced signal for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541903/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasound-guided injection of ankle contouring with botulinum neurotoxin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Ultrasound-guided botulinum toxin injections appear to be a safe and effective minimally invasive approach for ankle contouring, achieving clinically meaningful reductions in muscle bulk with high patient satisfaction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Developing a strategic action plan for reducing the burden of stroke in Africa: report of the first African Stroke Leaders' Summit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sustained reduction of stroke burden in Africa requires the adaptation of best practices to the African context, building the capacity of African stroke care professionals and using available resources with political support. Improving stroke literacy in African communities is a complementary strategy to reinforce healthy lifestyle choices and improve screening and detection of hypertension and other modifiable stroke risk factors. This process will culminate in a strategic African...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of stroke in adolescents and young adults (aged 15-39 years) in South East Asia: a trend analysis from 1990 to 2021 based on the global burden of disease study 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study highlights significant progress in managing ICH and SAH, especially among younger populations and females. However, ischemic stroke remains a growing challenge, particularly for males, necessitating targeted interventions to reduce the overall stroke burden.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541851/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Povetacicept for IgA Nephropathy and Primary Membranous Nephropathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Povetacicept had substantial, sustained UPCR reductions with stable eGFR, significant Gd-IgA1 reductions, hematuria resolution, clinical remission, with favorable safety in IgAN. Similar results were observed in pMN. By inhibiting both BAFF and APRIL, povetacicept targets the underlying cause of disease and has potential to provide a significant therapeutic advancement for autoimmune glomerular diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of soy protein isolate-soybean oil emulsion-aggregated gels with enhanced elasticity and structural stability using vacuum-autoclave treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the structural and functional characteristics of soy protein isolate (SPI)-based emulsion-aggregated gels produced at different SPI-to-oil ratios with or without vacuum-assisted (VA) treatment. VA treatment markedly enhanced gel cohesion, reduced porosity, and produced denser, smoother microstructures, as confirmed by SEM analysis. Optimal formulations (S3O7 and S4O6) exhibited balanced textural properties, superior freeze-thaw stability, and higher absolute zeta...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary interactions of emulsification and gelation in aggregated pea protein-soybean oil emulsion gels: insights for developing plant-based cream cheese analogs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to develop a plant-based cream cheese analog using pea protein isolate (PPI) and soybean oil by adjusting the protein-to-oil ratio to assess the impact of balancing interactions between emulsification and gelation. Emulsion gels with varying PPI-to-oil ratios were prepared and evaluated, with commercial dairy cream cheese as the control. Formulations with intermediate PPI-to-oil ratios exhibited optimal characteristics, including balanced spreadability, minimal fluid loss, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering meat-like performance in plant-based burger patties: focusing on structural, cooking, and textural properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the structural, cooking, and textural properties of beef and plant-based burger patties to identify factors governing meat-like behavior. Commercial and experimental plant-based burger patties were compared, and modified variants were developed by adjusting the particle size and content of textured vegetable protein (TVP) and by varying starch-based binders (potato starch, tapioca starch, and glutinous rice flour). Finer TVP particles increased cooking loss but improved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41541737/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260117142120&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>