<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:36:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perceptions of newborn care among North Korean refugee women in South Korea: a qualitative study using focus group interview: comparison between pregnant and non-pregnant groups]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study revealed differences in childrearing perceptions among North Korean refugee women based on their pregnancy status. It underscores the necessity for developing customized education programs that consider life stages and psychological readiness, as well as the importance of establishing social support systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electric Stimulation Therapy for Bell's Palsy in the Acute Stage: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction: Bell's palsy, an idiopathic peripheral facial palsy, often resolves naturally but can benefit from electric stimulation therapy. However, efficacy and safety during the acute stage remain controversial and understudied. Objective: To measure the effectiveness of electrical stimulation therapy as an add-on treatment for patients in the acute stage of Bell's palsy, as measured by incomplete recovery rates. Methods: We searched nine databases for randomized controlled trials comparing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167647/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A high-quality genomic catalog of the human oral microbiome broadens its phylogeny and clinical insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The oral microbiome is increasingly linked to human health. To further examine this microbial community, we present the human reference oral microbiome (HROM), with 72,641 high-quality genomes from 3,426 species, including 2,019 previously unidentified species, improving metagenomic sequence read classification over existing catalogs. Notably, HROM unveils 1,137 previously uncharacterized candidate phyla radiation (CPR) species, establishing Patescibacteria as the most prevalent phylum in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167188/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polystyrene microplastics activate NF-κB/MAPK signaling in synovial fibroblasts, promoting inflammation and joint destruction in rheumatoid arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics (MPs) are emerging environmental contaminants, yet their impact on autoimmune diseases such as rheumatoid arthritis (RA) remains unclear. We report that polystyrene microplastics (PS-MPs) are detectable in synovial fluid samples from RA patients and that exposure to 5 μm PS-MPs directly promotes the pathogenic activation of RA fibroblast-like synoviocytes (RA-FLSs), key effector cells in synovial inflammation and joint destruction. High-resolution imaging confirmed PS-MPs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive Role of Baseline Peripheral Lung SUVmax on PET/CT for Immune-Related Pneumonitis and Adverse Events in Lung Cancer Patients Treated with Immune Checkpoint Inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Baseline peripheral SUVmax on PET/CT may serve as a noninvasive biomarker for predicting immune-related pneumonitis and other irAEs in NSCLC patients receiving ICIs, supporting early risk identification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166927/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Digital Twins for pervasive healthcare: A scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Human Digital Twins (HDTs) have recently emerged, especially in the context of healthcare. With the growing emphasis on preventive healthcare beyond diagnosis, pervasive sensing has become essential which enables continuous monitoring through real-world data captured from wearables and/or mobile devices. Objective: This scoping review investigates how pervasive sensing technologies have been utilized in the implementation of HDTs for healthcare, with a focus on understanding the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasensitive Detection of PD-L1-Expressing Extracellular Vesicles via Reflection-Mediated Ellipsometry: From Nanoscale Optical Modeling to Immunotherapy Response Prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Programmed death-ligand 1 (PD-L1) expression in extracellular vesicles (EVs) has emerged as a promising biomarker for predicting responses to immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs), but current detection methods lack the sensitivity needed for clinical translation. Here, a reflection-mode solution-immersed silicon (R(p)-SIS) ellipsometry sensor is adapted, originally developed for thin-film measurements, for the ultra-sensitive detection of PD-L1-expressing EVs. Computational and experimental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catalytic Electron-Driven Non-Equilibrium Phase Transition in Quantum Electronic Heterostructures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Thermodynamic phases of matter are defined by temperature, pressure, and particle number while their changes in solids are known to induce phase transitions. It is demonstrated that in heterostructures with an extra degree of freedom-two different electron pathways across the interface-electron flow creates new thermodynamic phases. Topological insulators (TIs) are used with two distinct electronic states: topological surface and confined insulating bulk states. The electrons can flow from a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural analysis of dual specificity phosphatases, the only type of protein tyrosine phosphatases found in humans and across diverse microorganisms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual specificity phosphatases (DUSPs), a subfamily of the protein tyrosine phosphatase (PTP) family, dephosphorylate not only phosphotyrosine but also phosphoserine and phosphothreonine residues. Beyond the 26 members of this family in humans, DUSPs represent the only type of PTPs found across a wide range of microorganisms, including bacteria, archaea, and viruses. This review presents a comprehensive structural analysis of human and microbial DUSPs. These proteins commonly share core features,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A unified Erdős-Pósa theorem for cycles in graphs labelled by multiple abelian groups]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In 1965, Erdős and Pósa proved that there is an (approximate) duality between the maximum size of a packing of cycles and the minimum size of a vertex set hitting all cycles. Such a duality does not hold for odd cycles, and Dejter and Neumann-Lara asked in 1988 to find all pairs ( ℓ , z ) of integers where such a duality holds for the family of cycles of length ℓ modulo z. We characterise all such pairs, and we further generalise this characterisation to cycles in graphs labelled with a bounded...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164012/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stage-specific cardiotoxicity induced by bisphenol A using human pluripotent stem cell-derived 2D- and 3D-cardiomyocyte models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bisphenol A (BPA), a widely used industrial chemical with endocrine-disrupting properties, raises developmental and cardiotoxicity concerns. We established a stage-specific cardiotoxicity platform using human pluripotent stem cell (hPSC)-derived cardiomyocytes in two-dimensional and three-dimensional (3D) cultures. BPA exposure at ⩾10 µM significantly reduced cell viability and downregulated pluripotency and cardiac lineage markers such as OCT4, NKX2-5, and cTnT in a stage-dependent manner....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ferroelectric-Induced Phase Change Device with Polymorphic Mo<sub>1-x</sub>W<sub>x</sub>Te<sub>2</sub> for Neuromorphic Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[While phase change devices have emerged as promising candidates for implementing artificial synapses, conventional phase change materials have faced challenges such as high-power consumption and limited reliability, originating from their Joule heating-driven phase transition mechanisms. Here, a phase change device based on a 2D material, Mo(0.95)W(0.05)Te(2) is demonstrated, which exhibits a phase transition between semiconducting 2H and semimetallic 1T' structural phases, facilitated by a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genetic insights into the major histocompatibility complex class I BF2 gene of Korean native chickens in relation to the LEI0258 microsatellite marker and the 90-SNP panel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The chicken major histocompatibility complex (MHC) represents a "minimal essential MHC" consisting of classical class I (BF) and class II (BL) molecules that present peptides to CD8^(+) cytotoxic and CD4^(+) helper T cells, respectively. Class I molecules, primarily encoded by the BF2 gene, are central to immune responses against pathogens. Moreover, these molecules show enormous genetic diversity driven by a molecular arms race with pathogens that determines peptide binding to the polymorphic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162782/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing MobileNetV3 for multimodal eye gaze and emotion recognition via advanced pruning and quantisation techniques]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study introduces an innovative approach for optimising visual understanding by leveraging MobileNet V3 for eye-gazing, eye-blinks, and emotional expressions recognition. The importance of visual cues, such as gaze direction, blinking patterns, and facial expressions, in various applications, including human-computer interaction and behavioural analysis, is driving the need for efficient and accurate models that operate effectively in resource-constrained environments. MobileNet V3 offers a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162428/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of a virtual reality program and simulation training for nursing students on the measurement of vital signs in children: a mixed-methods study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The VR program was as effective as high-fidelity simulation training in improving nursing students' ability to measure children's vital signs. Moreover, VR program offered additional benefits in addressing limitations of simulation-based learning. These findings suggest that VR program can serve as a valuable educational tool to enhance pediatric nursing skills.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurses' perceptions of end-of-life care in neonatal and pediatric intensive care units in Korea: a qualitative descriptive study using thematic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The findings highlight that delivering quality end-of-life care in neonatal and pediatric intensive care units requires supporting families' emotional needs, strengthening relational and systemic support, and addressing practical challenges. Further research is needed to develop and test practical strategies (e.g., specialized education in compassionate communication, standardized protocols, and supportive care environments) that can improve the quality of end-of-life care for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring perception types regarding the effects of energy drink consumption among South Korean male adolescents: a Q-methodology study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: By typifying the subjective perceptions of Korean male high school students regarding energy drink consumption, this study provides a foundational understanding of how adolescents interpret and respond to such health behaviors. These insights can guide the development of tailored health education programs that address the unique needs and attitudes of each group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors influencing the family management of children with atopic dermatitis: an integrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Family management of pediatric AD is shaped by a complex interplay of child- and family-related factors. Therefore, interventions should be designed to strengthen coping resources, enhance social support, and reduce the management burden, promoting child well-being and family resilience.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exclusive liver/serosa invasion as a better prognostic indicator in T3 gallbladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Gallbladder cancers confined to the liver and serosa exhibited a more favorable prognosis, highlighting needed subclassification within T3 gallbladder cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial profiling of patient-matched HER2 positive gastric cancer reveals resistance mechanisms to targeted therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results delineate multiple acquired resistance mechanisms to trastuzumab and T-DXd in HER2+ GC in vivo. This information may guide trials combining trastuzumab or T-DXd with new agents to enhance the efficacy and durability of HER2 blockade.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of nicotinamide supplementation in normal-tension glaucoma: a crossover placebo-controlled randomised clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Oral NAM supplementation in NTG participants induced functional improvement, as measured by PhNRPT and B-wave amplitude. Given that NTG is characterised by lower IOP, which may show a weaker correlation with electrophysiological activity and a slower progression rate compared with high-tension glaucoma, further long-term studies are needed to clarify the effects of NAM in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced Pain Responses With a Digital Automatic Syringe: Behavioral and Molecular Evidence in a Rodent Formalin Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The I-ject™ automatic syringe markedly reduced both behavioral signs of pain and molecular markers of nociceptive activation in this rodent formalin pain model. These findings support the potential of this digital automatic injection system as a safer and more consistent alternative to conventional manual syringes in both preclinical research and clinical settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinicopathological Characteristics of Atypical Polypoid Adenomyoma of the Uterus in Association With Endometrial Atypical Hyperplasia and Endometrioid Carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In APA, meticulous pathological evaluation is essential to detect concurrent AH/EIN or EC. Although conservative management may be appropriate for selected patients, close surveillance is necessary to monitor for persistence or recurrence. Hysterectomy remains a definitive and reliable therapeutic option.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Survival Outcomes and Toxicities Between Volumetric-modulated Arc Therapy and Conventional Radiotherapy in Early Glottic Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: VMAT demonstrated comparable survival outcomes to CvT while significantly reducing the incidence of hypothyroidism and potentially lowering carotid artery events. VMAT may be considered a preferred modality to improve quality of life in patients with early glottic cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Association of Number of Retrieved Lymph Nodes with Oncologic Outcomes in Patients with Papillary Thyroid Cancer with Lateral Cervical Nodal Metastasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The number of retrieved lymph nodes (rLN) is an important surgical metric associated with survival in cancer. However, its association with oncological outcomes in patients with papillary thyroid cancer (PTC) with lateral lymph node (LN) metastasis (N1b disease) has not been investigated. Methods: This retrospective cohort study included patients with PTC and N1b disease (N = 1003) who underwent lateral neck dissection and categorized them by total number of rLNs. We investigated the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interobserver agreement among clinicians in the treatment recommendations for patients with unruptured intracranial aneurysms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study shows that the level of interobserver agreement was very high for treatment versus no-treatment decisions, but moderate regarding the strength of the recommendations. Further studies are needed to clarify the detailed reasons for the similarities and differences in clinicians' recommendations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Accuracy of a Humphrey 24-2C Protocol for Simultaneous Parafoveal and Pericentral Hydroxychloroquine Retinopathy Screening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The Humphrey 24-2C protocol offers a reliable, time-efficient, and single-test solution for screening both parafoveal and pericentral HCQ retinopathy, with diagnostic performance comparable to that of the 10-2 protocol for parafoveal retinopathy and 30-2 protocol for pericentral one.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167525/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dark fermentation of cheese whey - supplement materials control the conversion pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study explores changes in biological conversion pathways of cheese whey due to supplementation of dark fermentation (DF), including additives such as fly ash (FA), biochar (BC), and geopolymer (GP) to improve the biohydrogen (bioH(2)) production. Among these, FA (10 g/L) produced the highest bio-H(2) giving 316.68 ml/g yield, showing an increase of 86 % compared to control. The promoting role of FA is attributed to strong buffering due to its high oxide and hydroxide contents, enhancing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167362/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Significance of Change in Left Atrial Strain During Weaning from Venoarterial Extracorporeal Membrane Oxygenator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LARS improvement during ECMO weaning trial might be useful as a predictor of successful weaning from VA ECMO when combined with conventional echocardiographic parameters.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does age-adjusted pelvic incidence minus lumbar lordosis overcorrection truly increase the risk of proximal junctional failure? A confounder-adjusted multivariate analysis in adult spinal deformity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overcorrection relative to age-adjusted PI-LL target does not independently increase PJF risk when key confounders are considered. Surgeons should focus on individual patient and surgical factors-particularly age, thoracic alignment, and prophylactic strategies-rather than relying solely on PI-LL correction thresholds in ASD surgical planning.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abemaciclib plus abiraterone in patients with metastatic castration-resistant prostate cancer (CYCLONE 2): a randomised, double-blind, placebo-controlled, phase 3 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Abemaciclib, a potent CDK4 and CDK6 inhibitor, has shown antitumour activity in prostate cancer models and in patients with metastatic castration-resistant prostate cancer (mCRPC) who have been heavily treated. We aimed to evaluate the safety and efficacy of abemaciclib in combination with abiraterone in patients with mCRPC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global and regional burden of neonatal disorders (preterm birth, encephalopathy, jaundice, and sepsis), 1990-2021 and projections to 2050]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although the overall burden of neonatal disorders has decreased, substantial disparities have persisted across SDI levels with the highest burden observed in low-SDI countries. Among the subtypes, a preterm neonatal birth accounted for the highest burden, whereas a low birthweight was the most significant risk factor. To achieve global child health targets, it is essential to address regional disparities and promote equity in access to healthcare services and health outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic understanding of heat stress in cattle reproduction toward pharmacological strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heat stress is a major environmental challenge that compromises reproductive performance in cattle, particularly under the intensifying conditions of global climate change. This review provides a comprehensive overview of how heat stress impairs bovine reproduction at the physiological, cellular, and molecular levels and explores practical strategies for mitigation. In females, heat stress disrupts hormonal regulation, estrous behavior, and ovulation, and diminishes oocyte and embryo quality,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gallic acid mitigates cadmium-induced reproductive damage: Effects on sperm, antioxidants, and apoptosis in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cadmium is a well-known reproductive toxicant found in many industrial wastes. The gallic acid impact on the recovery of reproductive ability of mice exposed to cadmium was investigated. The experiment involved six groups of male mice, designated as Groups 1 through 6, each receiving specific treatments: Group 1 received distilled water, Group 2 received water containing gallic acid with a concentration of 50 mg/kg, Group 3 received water containing gallic acid with a concentration 100 mg/kg,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167100/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "A peptide derived from the core β-sheet region of TIRAP decoys TLR4 and reduces inflammatory and autoimmune symptoms in murine models" [eBioMedicine 52 (2020) 102645]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Korean Pubertal Development Scale (PDS-K): a non-invasive self-report tool for epidemiological use]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As the average age of pubertal onset continues to decline, the need for reliable and culturally appropriate tools to assess pubertal development has become increasingly important. However, no validated, non-invasive, self-report instrument has been available for use in Korea. This study aimed to translate, culturally adapt, and evaluate the Korean version of the Pubertal Development Scale (PDS-K). The original PDS was translated using a forward-backward translation procedure and reviewed by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166957/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Study Protocol for the Korean Human Exposure Safety Survey (KoHESS): A National Biomonitoring Program for Food and Consumer Product Safety]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This protocol paper describes the design and methodology of the Korean Human Exposure Safety Survey (KoHESS), a three-year national biomonitoring program (2023-2025). Korea's Act on Risk Assessment of Products for Human Use necessitates scientific evidence for aggregate exposure assessment and cumulative risk evaluation of hazardous substances in food and consumer products. Existing biomonitoring programs primarily focus on environmental exposures, limiting comprehensive assessment of products...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Outcomes and Histologic Subtype-Specific Patterns in Oligometastatic Soft Tissue Sarcoma of the Extremities and Trunk Wall: Implications for Curative Local Ablative Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Oligometastatic STS represents an intermediate disease state in which LAT can provide meaningful survival benefit. Subtype-specific differences in metastatic behavior and survival outcomes would support individualized, multimodal, and potentially curative treatment strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vasorelaxant and antihypertensive effects of the Cibotii Rhizoma hydroethanolic extract via the PI3K/AKT/eNOS Pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The major active components of the Cibotii Rhizoma hydroethanolic extract, including quercetin, kaempferol, and naringenin induce vasorelaxation and reduce the blood pressure via the PI3K/AKT/eNOS pathway. Therefore, Cibotii Rhizoma acts as a potential agent for standalone or adjuvant treatment of hypertension. However, further investigation of its pharmacokinetics, extract standardization, and effects on different forms of hypertension are necessary to facilitate its clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting oxcarbazepine-induced hyponatremia in adult epilepsy patients: A multicenter machine learning analysis using real-world CDM data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: XGBoost demonstrated robust predictive performance for OXC-induced severe hyponatremia using multicenter CDM data. SHAP-based interpretation revealed clinically relevant risk factors, supporting the implementation of personalized monitoring strategies in epilepsy care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Scene with an Invisible Wall-Navigational Experience Shapes Visual Scene Representation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human navigation heavily relies on visual information. Although many previous studies have investigated how navigational information is inferred from visual features of scenes, little is understood about the impact of navigational experience on visual scene representation. In this study, we examined how navigational experience influences both the behavioral and neural responses to a visual scene. During training, participants navigated in the virtual reality (VR) environments, which we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effects of Virtual Reality on Anxiety, Pain, and Physiological Parameters During Invasive Coronary Angiography: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Invasive coronary angiography (ICA) can provoke considerable anxiety, pain, and physiological stress, which may affect patient outcomes. Virtual reality (VR) is a nonpharmacological intervention that may help alleviate these adverse responses. This study evaluated the effects of VR on anxiety, pain, and physiological parameters in adults undergoing ICA. We searched PubMed, Cochrane, Web of Science, Scopus, Embase, and Google Scholar from inception to April 21, 2025, for randomized controlled...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural dissection of αβ-tubulin heterodimer assembly and disassembly by human tubulin-specific chaperones]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microtubule assembly requires a set of chaperones known as tubulin-binding cofactors (TBCs). We used cryo-electron microscopy to visualize how human TBCD, TBCE, TBCC, and guanosine triphosphatase (GTPase) Arl2 mediate αβ-tubulin assembly and disassembly. We captured multiple conformational states, revealing how TBCs orchestrate tubulin heterodimer biogenesis. TBCD stabilizes monomeric β-tubulin and scaffolds the other cofactors. Guanosine triphosphate (GTP) binding to Arl2 induces conformational...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of a short-term thalassotherapy on chronic pain, health-related QOL, and stress in older workers: A preliminary mixed-methods study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundChronic musculoskeletal pain is a prevalent health concern among older workers affecting their quality of life and overall well-being.ObjectiveThis study aimed to assess the combined effects of a short-term intervention involving sea mud application with local heat and complex exercises in a sea pine forest (SPF) setting, compared to a physical modalities group receiving regular physical modality (PM) intervention with stretching exercises.MethodsThe study focused on assessing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166406/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chronic central retinal artery occlusion: Clinical manifestations, ocular neovascular complications, and risk of stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Central retinal artery occlusion (CRAO) is a vision-threatening emergency that can lead to chronic ischemic complications. This retrospective cohort study investigated clinical characteristics, neovascular complications, and stroke risk in patients with chronic CRAO defined as the post-acute phase state characterized by FA-confirmed persistent retinal ischemia ≥1 month after acute onset. We reviewed medical records of 570 eyes initially diagnosed with acute non-arteritic CRAO between September...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Methodological considerations and challenges in zoster vaccination and cardiovascular research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166138/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors associated with employment outcomes in cancer survivors: a systematic scoping review spanning a decade of international research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Modifiable and nonmodifiable factors associated with employment outcomes require screening and targeted interventions in clinical settings as well as the development of healthcare delivery, workplace, and national policies and resources. Future research should address gaps in people with advanced cancer, vulnerable groups, and lower resource settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Consistent Adherence to Physical Activity Guidelines and Digestive System Cancer Risk and Mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this study, traditional dose-response analysis suggested that approximately 50 MET-hours/week was associated with optimal DSC risk reduction. After incorporating long-term consistency, maintenance of a moderate level approximately 17 MET-hours/week over 3 decades was associated with achieving optimal benefit in reducing DSC risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165664/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Open-Source AI Model for Predicting Respiratory Mortality in COPD from Chest Radiographs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose To evaluate the clinical utility of artificial intelligence (AI) scores in years derived from chest radiographs (CXR-Lung-Risk scores) in predicting respiratory mortality in a cohort of patients with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD). Materials and Methods This retrospective single-center study included patients with COPD from a tertiary center between January 2011 and December 2015. CXR-Lung-Risk scores were derived from chest radiographs using an open-source AI algorithm....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defect engineering in OH-functionalized carbon nanotubes for visible-light-driven ROS-mediated anticancer therapy and high-performance photocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon nanotube (CNT)-based therapies are emerging as powerful tools in oncology due to their ability to selectively target cancer cells while minimizing damage to healthy tissues. Leveraging the critical role of reactive oxygen species (ROS) in cancer progression, this study explores ROS-mediated photodynamic strategies to enhance therapeutic efficacy. We present a systematic design of five CNT derivatives-CNT-OH, Ti-doped CNT-OH, NaBH(4)-treated Ti-doped CNT-OH, Cr-doped CNT-OH, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165254/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dementia risk across blood pressure categories: a South Korean nationwide study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Based on the 2024 ESC BP classification, both elevated BP and hypertension were associated with an increased risk of dementia, especially VaD. These findings support the clinical relevance of 2024 ESC criteria and highlight midlife adults and women as potential priority targets for early BP management to preserve cognitive health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pb-S coordination-assisted <em>in situ</em> ligand engineering of CsPbBr<sub>3</sub> nanocrystals using (3-mercaptopropyl)methyldimethoxysilane for enhanced robustness and optoelectronic properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The surface chemistry of perovskite nanocrystals (NCs) is a key determinant of their quantum yield (QY), stability, and defect passivation. However, the rapid growth kinetics and pronounced sensitivity of CsPbBr(3) to moisture and thermal stress result in structural and optical degradation, hindering its practical applications. To address these limitations, we developed a ligand exchange-assisted strategy using (3-mercaptopropyl)methyldimethoxysilane (MPMDMS), a short-chain silane ligand bearing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex differences in chronotype distribution and their association with insomnia in a nationwide Korean survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Insomnia, a prevalent sleep disorder, affects 6-10% of the global population and causes significant functional impairments. Chronotype, individual diurnal preferences, influences health outcomes and varies by sex. However, evidence on sex-specific chronotype distribution and its relationship with insomnia in Asian populations remains limited. This study aimed to examine how chronotype is distributed differently between men and women, and to explore its relationship with insomnia symptoms using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bidirectional genetic associations between chronotype and shift work: A Mendelian randomization study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shift work, particularly night shifts, disrupts circadian rhythms and contributes to various adverse health outcomes. However, the degree of individual adaptability varies considerably, suggesting complex interactions between genetic factors, such as chronotype, and shift work exposure. To explore these interactions, we conducted a bidirectional Mendelian randomization (MR) analysis using genome-wide association study (GWAS) data from European populations. We examined causal associations between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165028/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>In situ</em> polypyrrole coating on copper foam <em>via</em> femtosecond laser-irradiation for supercapacitor applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing need for fast, efficient, and durable energy storage, especially in electric vehicles and renewable energy systems, has made supercapacitors (SCs) increasingly important. Their ability to charge rapidly, deliver high power, and withstand thousands of cycles makes them a strong alternative to traditional batteries. In this study, we present a simple and effective method for the in situ polymerization of polymerize polypyrrole (PPy) on copper (Cu) foam using femtosecond (Fs) laser...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improved patient comfort and procedural efficiency using chlorhexidine-coated hydrophilic urethral catheters: a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Chlorhexidine-coated hydrophilic urethral catheters significantly reduced pain, shortened the procedural time, and improved clinician satisfaction. These findings suggest potential clinical benefits for both patients and clinicians.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lactobacillus crispatus KBL693 alleviates atopic dermatitis symptoms through immune modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atopic dermatitis (AD) is a widespread inflammatory skin condition that affects the population worldwide. Given the implication of microbiota in AD pathogenesis, we investigated whether human-derived Lactobacillus strains could modulate AD. In this study, we identified Lactobacillus crispatus KBL693 as a probiotic candidate for AD treatment. In vitro, KBL693 suppressed mast cell degranulation and IL-4 production by T cells, suggesting its ability to attenuate key type 2 immune responses....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mannose phosphotransferase system subunit IID of Streptococcus mutans elicits maturation and activation of dendritic cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Streptococcus mutans is a Gram-positive pathogen that causes dental caries and subsequent pulpal infection leading to pulpitis. Although dendritic cells (DCs) are known to be involved in disease progression and immune responses during S. mutans infection, little is known about the component of S. mutans responsible for the DC responses. Although the mannose phosphotransferase system (Man-PTS) is the primary sugar transporter of S. mutans, it is also a potential virulence factor. Since Man-PTS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164961/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cryo-EM structure of the glycosylated protein CgeA in the crust of Bacillus subtilis endospores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Bacillus subtilis spore crust is an exceptionally robust proteinaceous layer that protects spores under extreme environmental conditions. Among its key components, CgeA, a glycosylation-associated protein, plays a critical role in modifying crust properties through its glycosylated moiety, enhancing spore dispersal in aqueous environments. In this study, we present the high-resolution cryo-electron microscopy structure of the core region of CgeA at 3.05 Å resolution, revealing a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CO-free selective hydrogenation of CO<sub>2</sub> to value-added formate under low-temperature aqueous conditions using a heterogenized Ru-PNP catalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Considering that potassium hydroxide (KOH) is well known for its strong carbon dioxide (CO(2)) capture capability, a comparative study was conducted on low-temperature heterogeneous hydrogenation catalysts operable under CO(2)/hydrogen (H(2))/KOH conditions. A series of Ru-based heterogeneous catalysts, supported on commercial activated carbon or coordinated with NN, PP, and PNP ligands were tested under identical conditions. Among them, the PNP ligand-based catalyst, Ru-MACHO-POMP (porous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164859/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renal hyperfiltration with and without metabolic syndrome: differential implications for cardiovascular events, kidney failure, and mortality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The clinical significance of RHF differs based on MetS status, with their coexistence posing the highest risk for CV events, ESKD progression, and all-cause mortality. A synergistic interaction between RHF and MetS was evident in the risk of CV events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Select Each Component of CO<sub>2</sub> Electrolyzers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrochemical CO(2) electrolyzers are increasingly recognized for their potential to convert CO(2) into valuable chemical feedstocks, addressing critical environmental and economic challenges. Traditionally, the catalytic properties of the cathode, where CO(2)RR directly occurs, have been the main focus of research due to their control over product selectivity. More recently, however, membrane-based electrolyzers-commonly used in fuel cells and water electrolyzers-have shown substantial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes of WHO 2022 and ICC MDS entities with risk stratification by IPSS-R and IPSS-M]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Not available.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-Solvent Strategy Enables High-Performance Printing Organic Thermoelectric via Synergistic Modulation of Crystallinity and Film Homogeneity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic thermoelectric (OTE) hold great promise in printed electrical generator and portable devices, whereas scalable coating is rarely concerned in fabricating high-performance OTE for the hurdles of coordinating high crystallization and flow homogeneity. In this work, a co-solvent strategy assisted blade-coating achieves power factor (PF) breakthrough for P3HT through synergistically modulating the crystallization kinetics and rheological property. By incorporating orthogonal solvent n-hexane...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163563/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stem Cell-Derived Embryo Models: Potential Platforms for Investigating Early Development and Embryotoxicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stem cell-derived embryo models (SCDEMs) create opportunities to investigate the morphological dynamics and underlying mechanisms of embryonic development, implantation, and post-implantation progression by recapitulating pre-and peri-implantation stages in vitro-an area that conventional in vivo approaches struggle to investigate. This review provides a comprehensive overview of SCDEMs, detailing the methodologies used to generate synthetic embryos and the diverse types of stem cells employed....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of (4-Phenyl-cyclohexyl)acetate-Derived Tyrosylprotein Sulfotransferase 2 (TPST2) Inhibitors with Potent Anti-Tumor Activity for Immuno-Oncology Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tyrosylprotein sulfotransferase 2 (TPST2) was recently reported to mediate the post-translational sulfation of interferon γ (IFNγ) receptor, contributing to immunosuppression in tumor microenvironment. Herein, we report the discovery of 77c with an IC(50) value of 946 nM as a novel TPST2 inhibitor through the structure-activity relationship (SAR) studies and optimization of a hit compound, 44a, identified in the enzyme-based screening of 6868 compounds from Korea Chemical Bank (KCB) library. 77c...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163312/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facial Rash Events in Dupilumab Phase 3 Atopic Dermatitis Trials: A Pooled Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Since dupilumab approval for moderate-to-severe atopic dermatitis (AD) in 2017, facial rash reports appeared in literature. Objective: To report facial rash treatment-emergent adverse events (TEAEs) incidence in dupilumab clinical trials for moderate-to-severe AD. Methods: Data were pooled from 14 randomized, placebo-controlled dupilumab clinical trials in pediatric (6-17 years) and adult (≥18 years) patients and were searched for facial rash TEAEs occurring during study treatment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In vitro biomimetic development of artificial dental calculus: a proof of concept study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Artificial calculus synthesized through this novel biofilm mineralization model demonstrated structural and chemical characteristics consistent with early-stage human dental calculus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biopsychological pattern underlying the psychosomatic symptoms of patients with Hwabyung from a universal perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Hwabyung is a psychiatric syndrome originally described in Korea that presents as chronic psychosomatic distress with emotional dysregulation and heightened somatic arousal. However, no objective analysis to clarify its progressive mechanism within a universal biopsychological framework has as yet been done that incorporates insights from traditional East Asian medical psychology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunometabolic reprogramming in lung cancer: interplay between immune and stem-like cells in immune checkpoint inhibitor resistance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mesenchymal stem cell derived extracellular vesicles reverses neural aging via OSKM modulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study represents a pioneering achievement in regenerative medicine, demonstrating the potential of micro RNAs in EVs to stimulate OSKM, a significant stride forward in addressing neural aging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of mechanical and clinical outcomes between cement-augmented and conventional cephalomedullary nailing in osteoporotic trochanteric fractures: a propensity score-matched cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cement augmentation of a cephalomedullary nail demonstrated comparable mechanical outcomes in terms of cut-out and excessive sliding, as well as similar 1-year mortality and functional outcomes to conventional fixation. This process with a cephalomedullary nail appears to be a safe and effective option for older patients with a trochanteric fracture and shows no postoperative complications. Further large prospective studies are needed to identify patients expected to benefit most...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting ESM-1 inhibits spinal metastasis by disrupting tumor-endothelial adhesion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162808/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinct senotypes in p16- and p21-positive cells across human and mouse aging tissues]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Senescent cells drive age-related tissue dysfunction via the induction of a chronic senescence-associated secretory phenotype (SASP). The cyclin-dependent kinase inhibitors p21^(Cip1) and p16^(Ink4a) have long served as markers of cellular senescence. However, their individual roles remain incompletely elucidated, particularly in vivo. Thus, we conducted a comprehensive examination of multiple single-cell RNA sequencing datasets spanning both murine and human tissues during aging. Our analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined Computed Tomography and Amylase Criteria for Early and Precise Recognition of Anastomotic Leakage After Esophagectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The cCTA-AL is a reliable method for diagnosing AL, comparable to endoscopy. The cCTA-AL could be considered depending on local resources and expertise.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electromagnetic interference shielding using metal and MXene thin films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electronic passivation of small-form-factor devices requires a fundamental change in electromagnetic interference (EMI) shielding, transitioning from bulky metal cans to conformal thin films^(1-4). However, reducing the thickness induces poor shielding performance associated with the skin depth of shielding materials^(5,6). To overcome the performance limitations of thin-film shields, absorption during multiple internal reflections should be driven⁷. For absorption during multiple internal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validity of a ramp protocol based on whole-body climbing-specific exercise for peak oxygen uptake in physically active adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The present study aimed to verify the validity of peak oxygen uptake ([Formula: see text]O(2peak)) between climbing-specific walking (CLIMIT) and cycling tests in physically active adults. A total of 101 physically active adults participated in this study. Participants were randomly assigned to either cycling or CLIMIT test. The cycling test included an initial period of 2 min at a constant load of 50 watts. The workload was increased by 25 watts every 30 s. During the CLIMIT test, an initial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative use of fentanyl and tramadol in pediatric distal humerus fractures: a 15-year retrospective cohort study in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Longitudinal data on perioperative opioid use for pediatric orthopedic fractures are sparse. This study evaluated 15-year trends in perioperative opioid use for pediatric distal humerus fractures in Korea. Population-based medical data from 51,638,809 subscribers to the Health Insurance Review and Assessment Service were analyzed to assess perioperative opioid use patterns. We reviewed patients aged 2-12 years who underwent closed reduction and percutaneous pinning between 2007 and 2021. A total...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162485/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protracted late Paleozoic volcanic arc activity along the Northeast Asian continental margin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Northeast Asia is a complex tectonic collage bounded by Paleozoic-Mesozoic internal and peripheral orogens, whose distribution and continuity are obscured by later deformation and magmatic overprinting. Here we present zircon data from granites and xenoliths in the Yeongdeok area, southeastern Korea, which suggest the presence of a long-lived (ca. 30 Myr) late Paleozoic volcanic arc system. Zircon cores yield U-Pb ages of 278-255 Ma, while rim ages cluster around 250 Ma, corresponding to the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interpretable deep multimodal-based tomato disease diagnosis and severity estimation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant diseases pose a significant threat to global food security, particularly in regions that rely heavily on crops that are vulnerable to disease, such as tomatoes. This research addresses the inefficiencies of traditional farming solutions by presenting a novel multimodal deep learning algorithm. The algorithm leverages EfficientNetB0 for image-based disease classification and utilizes Recurrent Neural Networks (RNN) to predict disease severity based on environmental data. By integrating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondrial DNA variants and susceptibility to anti-tuberculosis drug-induced liver injury in Korean patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[It has been proposed that mitochondrial DNA variations can affect mitochondrial function, increasing the risk of drug-induced liver injury. This study aims to explore the association between mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA) variants and anti-tuberculosis drug-induced liver injury (ATT_DILI) in Korean tuberculosis patients. Whole mitochondrial genomes from 185 patients (61 with ATT_DILI and 124 without liver injury) were sequenced. Comparative analyses examined mtDNA variants, variant counts, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct current generation in triboelectric nanogenerators through ionic dynamics and electrode polarization effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient conversion of mechanical energy into direct current remains a significant challenge for current energy-harvesting devices. In ionic tribomaterials, the displacement and polarization of mobile ions can dynamically control both the magnitude and direction of generated charges. This process shares similarities with semiconductor-based tribovoltaic systems but differs from conventional dielectric triboelectric devices, where electrical conductivity and charge retention are often in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence for precision medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This review offers both an introduction to AI and a practical overview of how it is being used, and where its limitations lie, in precision medicine, with the goal of helping healthcare professionals understand these evolving tools and use them efficiently and responsibly in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167996/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wheel Running in Digital Ventilated Cages<sup>®</sup> Is Impaired in a Model of Cancer-induced Bone Pain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Wheel running behavior appears to be affected by the development of metastatic breast cancer. Wheel running in a Digital Ventilated Cage^(®) may be a useful behavioral assessment of spontaneous pain-like behavior of CIBP and may be useful to assess analgesic efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Latex Serum-Derived Supramolecular Networks Enable Toughening of Natural Rubber]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Natural rubber (NR), derived from renewable latex, offers a sustainable alternative to petroleum-based elastomers and exhibits exceptional toughness via strain-induced crystallization (SIC). However, as a kinetically governed process, SIC manifests only below specific thresholds of temperature and strain rate, limiting its effectiveness under demanding conditions. Expanding this SIC-active regime remains a long-standing challenge. Here, we demonstrate that reintroducing dried latex serum (DS)-a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167626/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acute and Transient Change in Brain Water Content Induced by A Single Electroconvulsive Therapy Session]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A single ECT-induced seizure induces a transient increase in extracellular water content without evidence of cytotoxic edema indicative of cellular injury. Our findings suggest that ECT-related brain water shifts are reversible and unlikely to reflect permanent damage to brain tissue.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167555/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lysine potentiates insulin secretion via AASS-dependent catabolism and regulation of GABA content and signaling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lysine is an essential amino acid with insulinotropic effects in humans. In vitro, it enhances glucose-stimulated insulin secretion (GSIS) in β-cell lines and rodent islets. While lysine is thought to act via membrane depolarization similar to arginine, the role of its intracellular metabolism in β-cell function remains unexplored. Here, we show that lysine acutely potentiates GSIS and that genes encoding enzymes in the lysine degradation pathway, including Aminoadipate-semialdehyde synthase...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corticospinal motoneuronal synaptic plasticity induction can modulate the speed of learning ballistic finger movements: possible use in rehabilitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paired corticospinal motoneuronal stimulation (PCMS) applying transcranial magnetic stimulation (TMS) over the primary motor cortex paired with peripheral electrical nerve stimulation (PNS) can induce bidirectional associative plasticity at the corticospinal motoneuronal synapses. Direction of the induced plasticity depends on the interstimulus interval (ISI) between TMS and PNS, and the voluntary motor output is modulated in the same manner. Here we investigated the effects of PCMS on the motor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The interplay of visual short-term memory, attention, and consciousness: A PRISMA systematic review of behavioral and neuroimaging studies with partial report and change detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Selective attention, visual short-term memory (VSTM), and visual consciousness are longstanding core domains in cognitive psychology and neuroscience. Recent findings using partial report and change detection paradigms suggest that VSTM involves multiple stages, each engaging distinct attentional processes. Crucially, the interplay between selective attention and VSTM lies at the heart of prominent theories of visual consciousness, such as the Recurrent Processing Theory (RPT) and the Global...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enzyme-powered micellar nanoreactors enable tumor-specific, cascade-amplified prodrug activation for synergistic oxidation-chemo-immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Prodrug cancer nanomedicines have emerged as promising strategies to enhance drug solubility, reduce systemic toxicity, and improve tumor accumulation. However, the therapeutic efficacy of prodrug systems remains limited by suboptimal in vivo activation, resulting in non-functional accumulation at disease sites. Herein, we report the design of enzyme-powered, ultra-pH-sensitive micellar nanoreactors that orchestrate a tumor-specific, cascade-amplified prodrug activation mechanism for synergistic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coexistence of Domains Composed of Intercellular Lipids in Stratum Corneum as Studied by X-Ray Diffraction and Differential Scanning Calorimetry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The intercellular lipid matrix of stratum corneum is composed of many lipid components, including ceramides, free fatty acids, and cholesterol, which nonetheless form regularly arranged structures; short- and long-period lamellar structures, and hexagonal and orthorhombic hydrocarbon-chain packing structures. From the viewpoint of compatibility among the structures, there should be a correlation between a lamellar structure arranged periodically along the long axis of the lipid molecules and a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autistic Traits and Temporal Integration of Auditory and Visual Stimuli in the General Population: The Role of Imagination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autistic individuals experience temporal integration difficulties in some sensory modalities that may be related to imagination difficulties. In this study, we tested the hypotheses that among Japanese university students in the general population, (1) higher autistic traits and (2) greater imagination difficulties are associated with lower performance in tasks requiring temporal integration. Two tasks were used to assess their temporal integration abilities: a speech-in-noise test using noise...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Abdominal shielding not recommended for diagnostic imaging with ionising radiation during pregnancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic insights into band broadening in MOF-based liquid chromatography: Role of sub-nanopore diffusion and packing heterogeneity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) have emerged as a promising class of porous materials for liquid chromatography (LC) stationary phases, owing to their exceptional structural tunability. However, the fundamental understanding of separation efficiency in MOF-packed columns remains limited. In this study, we systematically investigated the contribution of intra-particle diffusion to chromatographic band broadening using a sub-nanoporous MOF, [Zn(2)(ndc)(2)(ted)](n) (ndc =...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrophilic additives enhancing electrospray ionization of oligonucleotides in hexafluoro-2-propanol-free reversed-phase ion-pair liquid chromatography/mass spectrometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The characterization of oligonucleotide therapeutics is commonly performed by liquid chromatography/mass spectrometry (LC/MS) using reversed-phase ion-pair (RP-IP) chromatography with 1,1,1,3,3,3-hexafluoro-2-propanol (HFIP) and triethylamine (TEA) due to its efficient electrospray ionization (ESI) performance. However, HFIP poses several challenges, including environmental concerns as a per- and polyfluoroalkyl substance (PFAS), limited mobile phase stability, and high reagent costs....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41167064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends in daytime and nighttime dust aerosols over the Dust Belt revealed by IASI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The "dust belt", extending from North Africa through the Middle East to Asia, is the dustiest region in the world. While many studies have examined the trends in dust aerosols in these regions, little is known about their long-term variations in the diurnal cycle. Using dust products from the Infrared Atmospheric Sounder Interferometer (IASI) instrument aboard the MetOP-A satellite, this study examines the interannual variations and trends in dust optical depth (DOD) and dust layer altitude...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166977/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pyrrolizidine alkaloids in honey: occurrence and profile analysis in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigated the amounts of 15 types of pyrrolizidine alkaloids (PAs) and 12 corresponding N-oxides (PANOs) in honey samples purchased from retail stores, supermarkets, and internet stores in Japan using LC-MS/MS with a new sample preparation method. Among the 129 honey samples analysed, 93.8 % contained detectable levels above the limit of quantification, with concentrations ranging from 0.012 to 69.8 μg kg^(-1), and mean and median values of 3.92 and 0.49 μg kg^(-1),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulating electronic transport properties of wafer-scale vapor-liquid-solid grown tungsten nitride by a vacuum gentle heating method]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We study the electronic transport properties of W5N6 by vacuum gentle heating methods, which are useful ways to probe the electronic transport properties in highly sensitive 2D materials. Importantly, we found stable nearest-neighbor hopping behaviour and E-S VRH behaviour by accumulating vacuum gentle heating time, which is highly consistent with previous results in paramagnetic W5N6 to pave the way for applying to future magnetic sensing devices in industrial production aspects due to its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elucidating the Free Carrier and Exciton Ultrafast Dynamics in 2D Perovskites with Alternating Cations in the Interlayer Space]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An emerging class of two-dimensional (2D) layered perovskites with alternating cations in the interlayer space (ACI) offers tunable dimensionality and enhanced chemical stability, furnishing new opportunities for perovskite-based optoelectronic devices. In order to optimize the macroscopic device performance, a fundamental understanding of the fate and dynamics of photogenerated charge carriers (e.g., free carriers or excitons) is essential. Terahertz spectroscopy unveils unique intrinsic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166743/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutron crystallography of the covalent intermediate of β-glucosidase reveals remodeling of the catalytic center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anomer-retaining glycoside hydrolases (GHs) generally catalyze a double displacement reaction via a covalent intermediate. However, neutron crystallography of glycoside ligand-bound states has not been performed. In this study, we investigated β-glucosidase Td2F2 from GH family 1 as a model enzyme for anomer-retaining GHs. We determined joint X-ray/neutron structures of Td2F2 in ligand-free form, covalent intermediate with a 2-deoxy-2-fluoro glucoside (2F-Glc) inhibitor, and glucose product...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase I/II Study of AXL-Specific Antibody-Drug Conjugate Enapotamab Vedotin in Patients With Advanced Solid Tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: EnaV had an acceptable safety profile; however, because the evaluation of antitumor activity did not show clinically meaningful responses, clinical development of EnaV was discontinued.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of full glycation on structure and function of human serum albumin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human serum albumin (HSA) is the most abundant protein carrier found in blood. The level of glycated human serum albumin (GHSA) can be used as a diabetes biomarker. Therefore, many attempts have been made to design selective GHSA detection methods. GHSA has been found to show unique characteristics. Glycation has been found to impair albumin structure and function, where a microscopic explanation is limited. Thus, in this work, molecular dynamics simulations were performed to capture the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Partial blue light blocking glasses at night advanced sleep phase and reduced daytime irritability, disruptive behavior and improved morning mood, but did not alter salivary melatonin secretion in Japanese male schoolchildren]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In modern society, delayed sleep patterns among schoolchildren present challenges to academic attendance and performance. The impact of nighttime light exposure, especially blue wavelength light, on sleep delay has long been acknowledged. We investigated the effects of using partial blue light blocking glasses (JINS Screen Lens Heavy [40% cut]) on salivary melatonin levels, sleep patterns, sleep circadian phase, and daytime behavior in 39 male schoolchildren aged 10-12 who regularly wear glasses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dermal, respiratory and neurological effects following workplace exposure to diisopropylcarbodiimide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Three workers experienced contact dermatitis, occupational asthma, severe neurological sequelae, as well as new-onset obstructive sleep apnoea syndrome after occupational exposure to diisopropylcarbodiimide. The close temporal association to a single presumably high-level exposure suggests a possible causal relationship. To prevent such health consequences, workers with potential exposure to peptide couplers must be made aware of their hazards and adequately protected.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166101/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forgetting as an active process: Attentional withdrawal following a forget instruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intentional forgetting, commonly studied using a directed forgetting paradigm, can disrupt memory performance. Beyond verbal report, attenuation of physiological fear responding to emotional associations has also been demonstrated following a simple instruction to forget. Discussion nevertheless persists about the mechanisms underlying this directed forgetting effect, and, by extension, the active or passive nature of forgetting. In recent years, the body of research suggesting that forgetting...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measurement of gamma-ray dose rate distribution at the Kindai university reactor using the thermoluminescent properties of BeO ceramic plates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The gamma-ray dose rate distribution at the Kindai University Reactor (UTR-KINKI) was measured using the thermoluminescent (TL) properties of beryllium oxide (BeO) ceramic plates. The reactor, operating at an extremely low thermal power of 1 W, is widely used for nuclear research, including radiation biology and detector development. In neutron-gamma mixed fields, determining the gamma-ray dose rate accurately is technically challenging due to the neutron sensitivity of conventional dosimeters....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41166054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SLC39A14 is Required for Iron Loading of the Anterior Pituitary of Mice with Genetic Iron Overload]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patients with iron overload disorders frequently accumulate iron in the pituitary and adrenal glands, leading to endocrine dysfunction. Although this iron loading is well documented, the specific molecular mechanisms of iron accumulation are not well understood. Under normal conditions, most tissues, including pituitary and adrenal gland, acquire iron from circulating transferrin. In iron overload, however, transferrin levels become saturated with iron, resulting in plasma non-transferrin-bound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of <sup>18</sup>F-FDG radioactivity outside the field of view on image quality in a SiPM-based time-of-flight dedicated breast PET scanner: a phantom study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggested that the presence of radioactivity outside the field of view increases reduces small-lesion contrast at the centre of the detector ring of the SiPM-based db positron emission tomography scanner.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The N-terminal domain of precursor IL-1α enhances IL-6 expression via an intracrine mechanism in oral squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings delineate a non-canonical intracrine mechanism by which pIL-1α, via its N-terminal NLS-containing domain, translocates to the nucleus and regulates IL-6 gene expression independent of IL-1 receptor signaling. This study provides new insights into the intracellular functions of IL-1α in inflammatory and tumorigenic processes and suggests potential therapeutic avenues targeting its nuclear trafficking.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cost-utility analysis of treatment strategies for chronic constipation in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The lubiprostone-elobixibat-PEG formulation strategy showed the most favorable cost-effectiveness profile. In addition, novel treatment options, including lubiprostone, linaclotide, elobixibat, and PEG formulation, were found to be cost-effective compared to MgO. Further research is warranted to confirm these findings and support their application in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relation of pulmonary diffusing capacity changes to HRCT chest and V/Q SPECT findings at short-term and intermediate follow-up after COVID-19: a prospective cohort study (The secure study)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The severity-dependent reduction in D(L,COc) at short-term follow-up, associated with restrictive lung function pattern, GGO and fibrosis on HRCT, and ventilatory disturbances on V/Q SPECT, showed spontaneous recovery by intermediate follow-up. However, the restrictive ventilatory disturbances and associated morphological changes persisted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence Supported Analysis of Anal Sphincter and Levator Ani Muscle Using Medical Imaging Techniques: A Systematic Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AI shows potential in assisting pelvic floor imaging, especially for segmentation tasks. However, most models are not yet ready for widespread clinical adoption. Future studies should focus on improving dataset diversity, external validation, and reporting transparency to enable safe and effective clinical translation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial: Special Issue on Photosynthesis - the basics, mechanisms and applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbial production of polyhydroxyalkanoate from soy sauce oil, a byproduct of soy sauce manufacturing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cupriavidus necator is capable of producing substantial amounts of polyhydroxyalkanoates (PHAs) from various feedstocks. Nevertheless, no documented accounts exist on the utilization of soy sauce oil. C. necator cultured in a soy sauce oil-supplemented (1.5 wt%) nitrogen-limited mineral salt medium at 30°C for 4 days yielded a maximum poly(3-hydroxybutyrate) content and production of 63.7 ± 2.45 wt% and 2.3 ± 0.17 g/L, respectively. Recombinant C. necator PHB¯4 harboring PHA synthase from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165726/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic resection for small rectal neuroendocrine tumors: stretching the budget with band ligation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interindividual variations in peak alpha frequency do not predict the magnitude or extent of secondary hyperalgesia induced by high-frequency stimulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background Previous studies have shown an association between interindividual variations in the frequency of alpha-band EEG oscillations such as estimates of peak alpha frequency (PAF) and pain sensitivity. Whether differences in PAF also influence the susceptibility to develop central sensitization (CS) is unknown. Objective This study aimed to determine if the PAF of vision- and sensorimotor-related alpha-band activity is associated with the magnitude and extent of secondary mechanical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intra-leukemic interferon signaling suppresses expansion and mediates chemoresistance in human AML]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intra-tumoral heterogeneity can impact the competitive fitness and chemoresistance of individual cancer cells. In acute myeloid leukemia (AML), both genetic and functional heterogeneity contribute to chemoresistance, resulting in relapse. While the role of cell-extrinsic factors has been described for AML relapse, whether interactions between cancer cells affects chemoresistance is not fully known. Here, we demonstrated that a dominant leukemic fraction can suppress the proliferation and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid and Reversible Visible-Light-Induced Helix Inversion in Chiral Liquid Crystals Doped with a Negative Photochromic Molecule]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Light-induced helix inversion in chiral nematic liquid crystals (N*LCs), where helicity reverses under photoirradiation, has emerged as a promising strategy. However, existing systems often suffer from slow response times and limited reversibility, primarily due to inefficient photoisomerization. Here we report a binaphthyl-bridged imidazole dimer (BN-ImD) as a negative photochromic chiral dopant that enables rapid, visible-light-driven, and fully reversible helix inversion in N*LCs within...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domoic acid biosynthesis and genome expansion in <em>Nitzschia navis-varingica</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Production of the neurotoxin domoic acid (DA) by benthic diatom Nitzschia navis-varingica poses considerable health and economic concerns. In this study, we employed whole genome sequencing and transcriptomic analyses of regionally distinct N. navis-varingica strains to unravel the genomic underpinnings of DA biosynthesis. Our analyses revealed sizable genomes-characterized by an abundance of repetitive elements and noncoding DNA-that exceed the size of any other pennate diatoms. Central to our...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165336/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential recovery of chain-elongating bacteria: comparing droplet, plating, and dilution-to-extinction methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial chain elongation via reverse β-oxidation offers a more sustainable route to produce medium-chain fatty acids like caproate, commodity chemicals typically produced via (petro)chemical processes. Thermophilic anaerobic microbiomes allow production at a high rate and selectivity but remain poorly understood due to the limited cultivability of their members. To better access functional taxa from a thermophilic chain-elongating reactor community, we applied multiple isolation strategies:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pattern of extra-diaphragmatic respiratory muscle activity during exercise in patients with unilateral diaphragm dysfunction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Whether extra-diaphragmatic respiratory muscle output is altered in patients with unilateral diaphragm dysfunction (UDD) remains unclear. We compared respiratory pressures and muscle activity during symptom-limited cardiopulmonary exercise testing (CPET) in 10 patients with UDD and 10 matched controls. Ventilatory variables, dyspnea, and electromyography (EMG) of the diaphragm, scalene, sternocleidomastoid, and parasternal intercostals were assessed at iso-ventilation and peak ventilation....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165227/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Draft genome sequence of <em>Stenotrophomonas maltophilia</em> strain TUM26315, a bloodstream isolate resistant to cefiderocol and to aztreonam combined with ceftazidime-avibactam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Here, we report the draft genome sequence of Stenotrophomonas maltophilia TUM26315, which exhibits resistance to cefiderocol and to aztreonam combined with ceftazidime-avibactam, despite no prior exposure. The isolate belonged to genomic group 6 and carried bla(L1B) and bla(L2B) β-lactamase genes. It also had a frameshift mutation in the cirA gene.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165115/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Finding of Phase Transition of Ice XI to Ih in 20 wt % Bovine Serum Albumin Aqueous System and Assignment of Thermal and Dielectric Relaxation Processes in the Binary System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report calorimetric evidence of ice XI formation in protein aqueous systems, representing a breakthrough in biological ice physics. Adiabatic calorimetry and dielectric spectroscopy of 20 wt % BSA aqueous solutions revealed that rapid cooling enables ice XI to ice Ih transition at 72 K, while slow cooling suppresses this phenomenon. The mechanism involves secondary hydration shells facilitating accelerated proton reorientation through L-type Bjerrum defects─previously observed only in alkali...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A chiroptical switcher: helical inversion of twisted porphyrin macrocycle synergistically controlled by combined stimuli of solvent and pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, we report the unprecedented discovery of 1 that possesses dynamically tunable chiroptical properties under hydrostatic pressure. Upon hydrostatic pressurization, the g factor inverts from negative to positive. These chiroptical switches are based on pressure-induced conformational change governed by the interplay between macrocyclic flexibility and solvent polarity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41165002/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VPS35 mutation inhibits PINK1/parkin-mediated mitophagy via increased LRRK2 kinase activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The p.D620N mutation in VPS35 causes an autosomal dominant form of Parkinson's disease via mechanisms that are poorly understood. PINK1 and parkin, two proteins whose loss of function underlies autosomal recessive Parkinson's disease, cooperate to mediate mitophagy, a quality control pathway for selective elimination of damaged mitochondria. PINK1/parkin-mediated mitophagy is disrupted by LRRK2 mutations, which are the most prevalent cause of autosomal dominant Parkinson's disease. Here, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Case of Hypoxemic Primary Cytomegalovirus Disease Shortly After Recovery From Coronavirus Disease in a Young Immunocompetent Man]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cytomegalovirus (CMV) reactivation has been identified as a significant predictor of death in patients hospitalized with coronavirus disease (COVID-19). However, reports of concurrent or subsequent primary CMV disease in young immunocompetent patients with COVID-19 are rare. We present a rare case of primary CMV disease manifesting as pneumonia and acute respiratory failure in a young immunocompetent man, which developed shortly after recovery from moderate COVID-19. A 19-year-old...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Programmable synthesis of alkaloidal frameworks integrating Michael acceptor generates covalent probes for targeting POLE3 in HBV replication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing need for effective HBV treatments and lead compounds with novel mechanisms prompted us to explore synthetic strategies for generating skeletally diverse alkaloidal Michael acceptors. Our approach uniquely embeds Michael acceptors directly within multicyclic alkaloid-inspired frameworks, exploiting the azepinoindole scaffold-a privileged structure in indole alkaloids. A single-step assembly between the versatile intermediate 13 with methyl propiolate 14 or its derivatives enabled the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced red-light-driven hydrogen evolution by a diplatinum photocatalyst by the larger wavefunction leakage of iodide coordinated to the platinum center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The single-molecular photocatalyst Pt(2)(bpia)Cl(3) (bpia = bis(2-pyridylimidoyl)amido), recently proven to promote red-light-driven hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) in water via singlet-to-triplet (S-T) transitions (Angew. Chem. Int. Ed., 2025, 64, e202418884), is shown to gain a significantly improved photocatalytic performance upon ligating iodide instead of chloride to give Pt(2)(bpia)I(3). Upon iodide ligation, the absorption and emission energies both show a red shift basically due to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-pot synthesis of sequence-controlled macromonomers <em>via</em> living anionic addition reaction and subsequent acyclic diene metathesis polymerization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We developed a new synthetic approach for sequence-controlled polymers through a 1 : 1 addition reaction, living anionic addition reaction (LAAR) of 1,1-diphenylethylene (DPE) derivatives and acyclic diene metathesis (ADMET) polymerization. Divinyl-functionalized sequence-controlled BAAB-type oligomers were synthesized in high yield by sequentially reacting potassium naphthalenide (K-Naph) with 1,1-bis(4-tert-butyldimethylsilyloxyphenyl)ethylene (OSi, A), DPE (H, B), and an alkyl halide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Probing Nanomechanics by Direct Indentation Using Nanoendoscopy-AFM Reveals the Nuclear Elasticity Transition in Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The assessment of nuclear structural changes is considered a potential biomarker of metastatic cancer. However, accurately measuring nuclear elasticity remains challenging. Traditionally, nuclear elasticity has been measured by indenting the cell membrane with a bead-attached atomic force microscopy (AFM) probe or aspirating isolated nuclei with a micropipette tip. However, indentation using a bead-attached probe is influenced by the cell membrane and cytoskeleton, while measurements of isolated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular exploration of host-pathogen interactions in severe <em>Pseudomonas aeruginosa</em> infection through a multi-level data integration approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Understanding host-pathogen interactions is crucial for explaining the variability in sepsis outcomes, with Pseudomonas aeruginosa (PA) remaining a significant public health concern. In this work, we explored PA-human host interaction mechanisms through a data integration workflow, focusing on protein-protein and metabolite-protein interactions, along with pathway modulation in affected organs during severe infections.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41164165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chromosome-scale genomes of two wild flowering cherries (Cerasus itosakura and C. jamasakura) provide insights into structural evolution in Cerasus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Flowering cherries (genus Cerasus) are iconic trees in Japan, celebrated for their cultural and ecological significance. Despite their prominence, high-quality genomic resources for wild Cerasus species have been limited. Here, we report chromosome-level genome assemblies of two representative Japanese cherries: Cerasus itosakura, a progenitor of the widely cultivated C. ×yedoensis 'Somei-yoshino', and Cerasus jamasakura, a traditional popular wild species endemic to Japan. Using deep PacBio...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring <em>In Vivo</em> Anti-Diabetic Potential of 2,3 and 2,6-dichloroindolinone: Biochemical and Histological Evidences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In short, both compounds exhibit acute safety, oral glucose tolerance, and antidiabetic effects in biochemical and histological amelioration.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal exercise modalities for post-intervention motor function changes in stroke survivors: a pairwise and network meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Resistance training and robot-assisted therapy appear most effective for enhancing walking capacity after stroke. Task-oriented training benefits postural balance. Evidence for upper and lower limb recovery remains inconclusive due to the small number of trials and wide confidence intervals. These findings can inform individualized, modality-specific rehabilitation strategies for older adults recovering from stroke.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socioeconomic disparities in in-hospital mortality and 30-day hospital readmission rates among people with eating disorders: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: People with eating disorders from higher SES backgrounds had higher readmission rates but lower in-hospital mortality, potentially indicating that these people may be receiving a more intensive level of outpatient care. Higher readmission rates may paradoxically indicate continued engagement in follow-up care. However, this interpretation remains speculative and further research is needed to explore the mechanisms behind these disparities, particularly focusing on access to care for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163118/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health literacy among populations in and from war and armed conflict zones: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This review highlights a critical gap in the literature: although conflict-affected populations face unique mental health challenges, existing studies often assess MHL using frameworks developed in the global north and non-conflict settings and without incorporating the context of war or displacement. There is an urgent need to reconceptualize MHL frameworks and tools to reflect the lived experiences, needs, and sociopolitical realities of individuals in crisis settings....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41163112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of severe infections in patients with triple-negative breast cancer treated with atezolizumab plus nab-paclitaxel: a real-world, postmarketing database study in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overall, our results did not indicate a significant increase in the risk of severe infections with atezolizumab plus nab-paclitaxel in daily clinical practice. Further research is required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162823/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Revisiting the relationship between cardiorespiratory fitness and biological aging: insights from DunedinPACE analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DunedinPACE quantifies the pace of biological aging. No study has examined its association with cardiorespiratory fitness (CRF). Additionally, the physiologically relevant CRF thresholds associated with slow aging remain unclear. The purpose of this study was to investigate the association between CRF and the pace of epigenetic aging, as measured by DunedinPACE, and to identify a CRF threshold indicative of slower biological aging. Here, we analyzed data of 144 older men (aged 65-72 years)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonal differences in cardiac prognosis in incident hemodialysis patients: a finding from Japanese multicenter dialysis cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hemodialysis initiation in autumn may be a potential indicator of subsequent cardiac events. Further studies are required to elucidate the underlying pathophysiological mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162692/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the comparability of toxic emissions reduction from heated tobacco aerosols relative to cigarette smoke: a scientific approach to bridging datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Heated tobacco products (HTPs) offer a reduced risk potential by avoiding combustion, thereby lowering toxic emissions. This study evaluated 34 heated tobacco stick (HTS) variants, each with different tobacco blends, using two heating devices to assess the comparability of 51 toxic emission reductions compared to combustible cigarette smoke. Aerosols and 1R6F reference cigarette smoke were generated under standardized conditions, and droplet or particle size distributions were measured. Toxic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How disconfirmatory evidence shapes confidence in decision-making]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[When assessing our decisions, the normative strategy involves giving equal weight to each evidence sample when computing confidence. However, recent findings suggest that the brain tends to overweight decision-congruent information when forming confidence judgements (i.e., positive-evidence bias; PEB). Here, we re-analyzed nine datasets (total N = 176) from human participants who judged the average color of eight shapes and gave their confidence. This task precisely allowed us to disentangle the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allele-specific gene expression in F1 hybrid mice reveals structural variants affecting macrophage characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetic diversity underlies the foundation for variations in gene expression, resulting in diverse phenotypic traits. In this study, we investigated the effect of genetic variation on macrophage function using two genetically distinct mouse strains, C57BL/6 (B6) and Japanese Fancy Mouse 1 (JF1), which exhibit substantial genetic polymorphisms. Gene expression analysis of macrophages derived from B6, JF1, and their F1 hybrids revealed strain-specific allelic expression of immune-related and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathogenic characteristics of an unencapsulated Streptococcus suis serotype 31 strain isolated from a patient in Thailand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Streptococcus suis is a zoonotic pathogen that causes invasive infections in individuals who are in close contact with infected pigs or contaminated pork-derived products. An unencapsulated S. suis serotype 31 strain 43640 (sequence type 221) was first isolated from a human in Thailand in 2015; however, the mechanisms underlying host-cell interactions and virulence in animal models of this serotype are still limited. This study aimed to determine the virulence of the human unencapsulated S. suis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162466/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A red fluorescent genetically encoded biosensor for in vivo imaging of extracellular L-lactate dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[L-Lactate is increasingly recognized as an intercellular energy currency in mammals, but mysteries remain regarding the spatial and temporal dynamics of its release and uptake between cells via the extracellular environment. Here we introduce R-eLACCO2.1, a red fluorescent extracellular L-lactate biosensor that is superior to previously reported green fluorescent biosensors in in vivo sensitivity to increases in extracellular L-lactate and spectral orthogonality. R-eLACCO2.1 exhibits excellent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prelimbic cortex to ventral tegmental area projection regulates early social isolation stress-potentiated heroin seeking in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early-life adversities increase vulnerability to substance use disorders, which are characterized by persistent, uncontrollable drive to seek drugs, often leading to relapse. Previously, we reported that early social isolation (ESI) during adolescence potentiates heroin-seeking in mice. However, the underlying neurobiology remains unknown. Here, we found that ESI aggravated heroin-induced neuronal dysfunction in prelimbic cortex (PrL) to ventral tegmental area (VTA) projecting neurons....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41162376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251031033621&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of Midwife-Led Colposcopy for Female Genital Schistosomiasis Screening at Primary Level of Care in Rural Madagascar: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Midwives can detect female genital schistosomiasis with high sensitivity but limited specificity when compared to expert gynaecologists, revealing variation in performance between environments as well as the influence of practice and workload. This study suggests that implementing midwife-led colposcopy at primary care level for female genital schistosomiasis screening is feasible but requires appropriate quality assurance measures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168099/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic post-translational modification genome wide identifies therapeutic targets for Alzheimer's disease: evidence from multi-cohort analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings from this study not only enhance our comprehension of the underlying mechanisms of AD but also serve to inform and direct future initiatives in drug discovery. By focusing on TRIM47, the work paves the way for identifying innovative therapeutic strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety and efficacy of intratumourally administered INT230-6 in adult patients with advanced solid tumours: results from an open-label phase 1/2 dose escalation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Systemic chemotherapeutics have limited efficacy in many advanced solid tumours. This study evaluated the safety and tolerability of INT230-6, a unique intratumoural (IT) formulation of cisplatin, vinblastine, and 8-((2-hydroxybenzoyl)amino)octanoate (SHAO), an amphiphilic cell-penetration enhancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond beta rhythms: subthalamic aperiodic broadband power scales with Parkinson's disease severity-a cross-sectional multicentre study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Parkinson's disease is linked to increased beta rhythms (13-30 Hz) in the subthalamic nucleus, which correlate with motor symptoms. However, findings across studies are inconsistent. Furthermore, the contribution of other frequencies to symptom severity remains underexplored.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41168073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251031033620&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>