<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 19:21:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ionic Defect Analysis and Suppression for Highly Efficient and Stable Perovskite Solar Cells and Mini-Modules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solution-processed organohalide perovskite solar cells have pushed power-conversion efficiencies to new heights, but solution routes also introduce a significant number of defects that limit both the performance and stability. In particular, lattice point defects in perovskites serve as nonradiative recombination centers, introduce midgap states, and accelerate device degradation. Although surface-passivation and shallow-trap mitigation have driven marked PCE gains, deep-level traps lurking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A model of the microtubule cytoskeleton of the axon-initial-segment in mixtures of tubulin, tau, and GTP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review is part of a special memorial issue in honor of Erich Sackmann's remarkable research career, in particular, on the biophysics of equilibrium and living membranes. Erich's large body of discoveries firmly established him as a giant in the field of biophysics. In our review, we describe structural studies of microtubules (MTs) in the presence of the microtubule-associated protein (MAP) tau, an intrinsically disordered protein confined to the axon of mature neurons in vertebrates. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Michaelis-Menten: Evaluation of a tQSSA-Based IVIVE Approach for Predicting In Vivo Intrinsic Clearance From Hepatocyte Assays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The classical Michaelis-Menten model, under the standard quasi-steady-state approximation (sQSSA), is widely used in in vitro-in vivo extrapolation (IVIVE) studies using hepatocyte or human liver microsomal (HLM) assays to predict intrinsic hepatic clearance ( Cl int , vitro $$ {\mathrm{Cl}}_{\operatorname{int},\mathrm{vitro}} $$ ). However, the approximation that enzyme concentration ( E T $$ {E}_T $$ ) is much lower than the Michaelis constant ( K M $$ {K}_M $$ ) does not always...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between the finger-ring test and quality of life in community-dwelling older women: cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The finger-ring test may indicate both reduced muscle mass and strength, along with reduced HRQoL. These findings suggest that the finger-ring test is a useful preliminary rule-out screening tool to exclude individuals unlikely to be at risk, and it may also help predict health-related quality of life.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predation effects of <em>Lutzia vorax</em> (Diptera: Culicidae) larvae on mosquito communities in treehole ecosystems in central Korean forests]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lutzia vorax Theobald (Diptera: Culicidae) is a ferocious predator of small container habitats in the forests and rural areas of the eastern Palearctic and Oriental regions. Owing to its consumption of various invertebrates, including mosquito larvae, it is considered a potential biological control agent of vector species. However, studies on the general biology of Lt. vorax are scarce; thus, our understanding of its role in natural habitats is limited. To elucidate its ecological role with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking drug development: the distinctive roles of PET and SPECT imaging from molecular kinetics to therapeutic response]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug development is a multifaceted and time-intensive process that spans candidate discovery, formulation, pharmacokinetics (PK), and evaluation of therapeutic efficacy and safety. Nuclear medicine imaging-particularly positron emission tomography (PET) and single-photon emission computed tomography (SPECT)-enables noninvasive, quantitative, and dynamic assessments of drug behavior at the molecular and systemic levels. These modalities visualize real-time biodistribution, tissue PK, target...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Different intraocular pressure-lowering effects of latanoprostene bunod across glaucoma subtypes: a 12-month real-world clinical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LBN demonstrated differential IOP-lowering effects across glaucoma subtypes, with a notably enhanced effect on PXFG. This superior efficacy in PXFG, likely due to LBN's dual mechanism overcoming pseudoexfoliative outflow resistance, suggests that switching from latanoprost may help delay the need for surgical intervention in this challenging patient population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420784/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacokinetic-Pharmacodynamic Modeling and Simulation of Merigolix, a Nonpeptide Gonadotropin-Releasing Hormone Antagonist]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gonadotropin-releasing hormone (GnRH) antagonists inhibit estrogen synthesis and secretion, making them promising treatment options for estrogen-dependent diseases, such as endometriosis. This study developed a population pharmacokinetic/pharmacodynamic (PK/PD) model for merigolix, a novel oral GnRH antagonist, to determine its optimal dosing in the treatment of endometriosis. Population PK/PD modeling was performed using NONMEM 7.4, incorporating data from phase I clinical studies involving...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond diagnosis: deep-learning-based analysis of hospitalization using abdominal radiographs in the emergency department]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Deep learning significantly improved the clinical utility of AXR in screening for hospitalization risk, achieving higher sensitivity and F1-scores than radiologists. While these models require further improvement for clinical implementation, they can potentially extract predictive patterns from traditionally limited imaging studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mild Reduction-Mediated NK Cell Membrane Modification for ROS Scavenging Efficacy Overcome Immunosuppressive Tumor Microenvironment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid tumors are characterized by a metabolically dysregulated tumor microenvironment (TME) enriched with reactive oxygen species (ROS), which suppresses immune cell function. Natural killer (NK) cells are promising effectors in cancer immunotherapy due to their intrinsic cytotoxicity without prior antigen sensitization. However, oxidative stress impairs NK cell cytotoxicity by reducing degranulation, interferon-γ production, and survival. Therefore, maintaining NK cell redox balance is a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effects of Pain Controlling Agents on Paediatric Tonsillectomy: A Systematic Review and Network Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: While ibuprofen appeared to be the most effective in managing postoperative pain, paracetamol showed favourable trends in reducing postoperative bleeding, PONV, and the need for additional analgesics. Ketorolac tended to be associated with a lower incidence of PONV but showed a tendency toward a higher incidence of postoperative bleeding. However, further well-designed, standardised studies would be needed to confirm these conclusions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420409/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liquid Metal Microrobots for Magnetically Guided Transvascular Navigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft microrobots, compared with their rigid counterparts, offer superior adaptability in dynamic and confined biological environments. Here, magnetically-guided liquid metal microrobots composed of gallium-indium alloys embedded with Fe nanoparticles are introduced. The unique combination of magnetic maneuverability, high surface tension, intrinsic radiopacity, and deformability allows liquid metal-based microbots to overcome limitations of both hard microrobots and fragile droplet-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420352/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low-Field Terahertz Quantum Tunneling in Metal-TiO<sub>2</sub>-Metal Nanogaps via Schottky Barrier Engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Light-driven quantum tunneling offers an attractive platform for coherent electron control at ultrafast time scales; however, sustainable operation remains challenging due to the high electric fields required for quantum tunneling, often leading to thermal damage caused by Joule heating. Here, we experimentally investigate how quantum barrier engineering influences the nonlinear terahertz (THz) quantum tunneling response across tailored nanometer-scale junctions. By integrating lower-band-gap...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Initial proteinuria reduction and adverse kidney outcomes in IgA nephropathy: an analysis from the J-IGACS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Proteinuria reduction within the first-year post-diagnosis is independently associated with lower risk of adverse kidney outcomes and a slower decline in kidney function in patients with IgAN. These results support the use of proteinuria reduction as a surrogate endpoint in both clinical trials and disease management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fabrication of a low-adhesion metallic cell culture surface by nanosecond laser processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, we developed a reusable low-adhesion metallic cell culture surface having microscale structures using nanosecond pulsed laser processing. Titanium alloy disks were mirror-polished and laser-processed to create microstructures with a pitch of 15 μm, smaller than typical cell size. The cytocompatibility of the developed surfaces was confirmed, showing comparable viability to standard plastic dishes. On the other hand, the cells on the laser-processed surfaces exhibited suppressed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acoustic analysis in the assessment of postoperative speech impairment in oral cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Acoustic analysis was potentially useful as an objective speech assessment for the patients who underwent oral cancer surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of baseline regular magnesium oxide administration on chemotherapy-induced constipation during cisplatin-containing treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The present study suggests that patients with baseline regular magnesium oxide administration exhibit less chemotherapy-induced constipation than those without the administration in cisplatin-containing treatments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A new macromolecular crystallography endstation at NanoTerasu for accelerating structural biology and drug discovery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Since the fiscal year 2022, `Support Program for Life Science and Drug Discovery Research (BINDS Phase II)', funded by the Japan Agency for Medical Research and Development (AMED), has been supporting structural analysis research in Japan, promoting the further development of various advanced structural analysis technologies. The BINDS project aims to offer more timely and cutting-edge support by establishing a new macromolecular crystallography endstation (MX-ES) at NanoTerasu, Japan's first...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility and Adherence to Home-Based Intensive Treatment Programs for Chronic Radiation-Associated Dysphagia in Head and Neck Cancer Survivors-The HIT-CRAD Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study confirms the feasibility of high-volume strength and skill training with HD-tDCS in patients with C-RAD. Proactive adherence-supporting factors facilitate high adherence in this population. Both real and sham HD-tDCS proved safe, feasible, and well tolerated.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of heart failure and bleeding risk on clinical outcomes in patients after percutaneous coronary intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of Liquid-to-Solid Phase Transition in Coacervates for Neurodegenerative Disease Treatments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coacervates formed through liquid-liquid phase separation represent a fundamental model for protocell and serve as a membraneless organelle in living cells, modulating various biological processes. During aging or under stress, protein misfolding and oligomerization trigger aberrant liquid-to-solid phase transition (LSPT), a process driven by multivalent interactions. These phase transitions disrupt cellular equilibrium, leading to neurodegenerative diseases such as Alzheimer's disease,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valence-Engineering of CeO<sub>2</sub> Redox Modulator Boosts the Oxygen Electrocatalysis Performance in Fe/Co Dual-Atom Catalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual-atom nitrogen-doped carbon catalysts have garnered considerable interest as air electrodes for rechargeable zinc-air batteries (ZABs), owing to their outstanding bifunctional oxygen electrocatalytic activity. Nonetheless, their practical implementation is hindered by durability issues during the oxygen reduction reaction (ORR), as the active sites are degraded by the oxidative by-products. Furthermore, the sluggish electron transfer obstructs the oxidation state transitions of Co/Fe centers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420828/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrafast Dense Immobilization of Noble Metal Nanoparticles on Customizable Multifunctional Polymer Microspheres for Heterogeneous Catalysis and Multiplexed Biodetection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Constructing colloidal particles into designated hierarchies with integrated functionalities offers insights into bottom-up material fabrication. However, the arbitrary and controllable assembly of individual nanoscale and microscale particles remains highly challenging due to their diverse structural properties. Here, a general paradigm for the robust co-assembly of plasmonic noble metal nanoparticles and multifunctional polymer microspheres through thermodynamically driven heterocoagulation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of older adults with and without neurocognitive impairment in the auditory verbal learning test: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The AVLT, particularly delayed recall, may be a robust tool for distinguishing among normal aging, mild and major ND. However, variability in AVLT administration reduces the diagnostic potential of AVLT. The diagnostic potential of process-based indices has not been explored adequately. Future research should prioritize the standardization of AVLT protocols and the integration of process-based indices to maximize its clinical utility in detecting and tracking neurocognitive decline.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body Temperature of the Yellow-Headed Amazon Parrot (<em>Amazona oratrix</em> sp)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The yellow-headed Amazon parrot (Amazona oratrix sp) is an endangered species because of habitat loss and illegal trafficking. Currently, there is no data on body temperature available for this species, and this makes a complete clinical examination for determining its health status difficult. The objective of this study was to compare 2 methods for measuring body temperature (digital rectal thermometer, skin infrared thermometer) in 22 yellow-headed Amazon parrots. Over multiple measurements,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420802/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Short-Term Efficacy of Lebrikizumab Versus Dupilumab in Combination with Topical Corticosteroids in Adults with Moderate-to-Severe Atopic Dermatitis: Matching-Adjusted Indirect Comparison]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Lebrikizumab plus TCS was comparable to dupilumab plus TCS across all efficacy endpoints at week 16.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell and bulk transcriptome analysis reveals the impact of inflammatory microglia on prognosis and immunotherapy response in primary glioblastoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Inflammatory microglia-based stratification reveals key biological heterogeneity in GBM and may guide prognosis and therapeutic decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wearable sensors: in situ detection tools for plant physiological markers and growth environment information]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant health is a fundamental aspect of agricultural production, intimately linked to crop yield and quality. The precise acquisition of plant physiological information is vital for modern farmland management. This information encompasses plant biomarker information and details about the plant's growth environment. Traditional detection methods are limited by lengthy intervals between measurements and time-consuming detection processes. Wearable sensors, attached to the surface of plants,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating real-time OUR monitoring with adaptive feeding for enhanced antibody production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Fed-batch culture is a well-established and widely adopted platform for industrial antibody production using Chinese Hamster Ovary (CHO) cells. However, conventional fixed feeding strategies often fall short in meeting the dynamically changing nutrient demands of cells, leading to metabolic imbalance and suboptimal productivity. Oxygen Uptake Rate (OUR), as a real-time indicator of cellular respiratory activity, is tightly coupled to nutrient metabolism and holds strong potential for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the headache: autonomic reflex dysfunction and heightened sensory sensitivity contribute to orthostatic intolerance in migraine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Increased headache frequency correlates with increasing ANS reflex dysfunction. The high prevalence of OI in patients with migraine may be due to both autonomic reflex dysfunction and an abnormal cardiovascular response to tilt (i.e., concordant OI) and heightened sensory sensitivity (i.e., discordant OI).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420770/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Effectiveness of Long Acting Injectable Versus Oral Naltrexone in Patients with Co-Occurring Posttraumatic Stress Disorder and Alcohol Use Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our analyses suggest that LAI naltrexone provides no benefits in improving PTSD or AUD outcomes compared to its oral counterpart among patients with comorbid PTSD and AUD. In fact, our results suggest that oral naltrexone may provide an increased probability of clinically meaning PTSD improvements if a high level of medication adherence is maintained.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420765/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Neuroprotective Role of the Sulfonamide Derivative KM11 in Ethidium Bromide-induced Demyelination in Zebrafish Model Through Modulation of Antioxidant and Inflammatory Cytokine Pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiple sclerosis (MS) is a hypersensitivity reaction with increased inflammation, which leads to demyelination and neuronal degeneration. Currently, there are limited medications to improve the remyelination capacity. This study aimed to evaluate the neuroprotective and remyelinating potential of a novel sulfonamide derivative, KM11 [N-(7-hydroxy-1,3-benzothiazol-2-yl)-4-methylbenzene-1-sulfonamide], in ethidium bromide (EtBr)-induced demyelination models in zebrafish. KM11 was synthesised in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Double-antigen sandwich ELISA based on S1 for cross-species detection of Porcine deltacoronavirus antibodies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Porcine deltacoronavirus (PDCoV) is an emerging enteric coronavirus causing high mortality in neonatal piglets and posing a significant threat to the swine industry. Evidence indicates that PDCoV has cross-species transmission potential and may pose a zoonotic risk, emphasizing the need for reliable serological tools for epidemiological surveillance and vaccine evaluation. Here, we developed a double-antigen sandwich enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (DAgS-ELISA) based on the PDCoV S1 protein,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-mediated remote regulation of peripheral blood platelets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The role of platelets in blood coagulation and vascular repair is well known. In recent years, extensive attention has been given to the fact that the impact of tumors on peripheral blood platelets plays a key role in cancer progression. This review systematically summarizes the latest research progress on how tumors regulate the quantity, volume, composition, and activation status of peripheral blood platelets through multiple mechanisms. First, tumor cells can induce excessive platelet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TLRs and NLRs modulate oral microbiome involvement in Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) is the most common and irreversible type of dementia, accounting for more than half of all dementia cases. Early diagnosis of AD plays a role in slowing the progression of the disease and also preserving the quality of life of patients. However, there is often a time lag of several decades between the biological onset of the disease and the time of clinical diagnosis. At the time of diagnosis, the patient often has noticeable cognitive decline, which reduces the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420750/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association of co-exposure to polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons and phthalates with surrogate indicators of insulin resistance: a panel study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PAHs and phthalates co-exposure may contribute to insulin resistance (IR), but evidence remains limited. In this repeated-measure pilot study of 127 Chinese adults, we assessed urinary metabolites of PAHs and phthalates and five IR surrogate indicators. During each survey, first-morning urine samples were obtained for 4 consecutive days and fasting blood was drawn on the 4th day. We determined 10 urinary PAH metabolites and 10 urinary phthalate metabolites by gas chromatography-tandem mass...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ZAR1 pathogenic variants disrupt maternal mRNA storage and cause oocyte maturation defects in humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420714/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antipsychotic load during olanzapine mono- versus polytherapy and in relation to age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420713/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polyoxometalate-Mediated Photoinduced Electron Transfer and Photocatalytic Activity of Donor-Acceptor Hybrid Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Donor-acceptor hybrid materials, recognized as a special class of hybrids, have garnered considerable attention due to their ability to achieve efficient electron-hole separation under light irradiation, accompanied by variations in their chemical and physical properties. To elucidate the effect of the inorganic component on the photochromism and photocatalytic activity of these donor-acceptor hybrids, two isostructural perylenediimide-based materials, PDI-PW and PDI-PMo, featuring different...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420711/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing analytical sensitivity in upstream bioprocess using time-gated Raman spectroscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Upstream bioprocessing is a very complex system and requires rapid responses to process deviations. Mammalian cell culture processes are conventionally monitored for process-related and cell growth-related parameters, including pH, dissolved oxygen, viable cell density, cell viability, and key analyte concentrations that serve as primary indicators of the metabolic state of the cell culture. Raman spectroscopy (RS) has been increasingly applied as a viable inline process analytical technology...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420703/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical course and perinatal management of fetuses and newborns affected by trisomy 13 and 18: a retrospective single-centre cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives Trisomy 13 (T13) and 18 (T18) are lethal chromosomal abnormalities. While the prognosis is generally poor, recent evidence suggests that some infants with T13 and T18 are able to survive longer than previously supposed. These findings underline the importance of an individualised approach to perinatal/neonatal care. Methods This retrospective study included 193 pregnancies with T13 and T18 in a single tertiary center between 2005 and 2023. Fetal and maternal characteristics, overall...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a screening model for early diagnosis of biliary atresia in neonates with cholestasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Machine learning-based models, particularly the RF model, show great potential for the early diagnosis of BA in cholestatic neonates. The implementation of a dedicated online platform may facilitate timely identification and assist clinicians in decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Key Stakeholders' Knowledge, Opinions, and Interests on Real-World Evidence in the Regulatory Process-Results of an EU-Wide Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Real-world data (RWD) and real-world evidence (RWE) are increasingly gaining attention in supporting drug regulatory decision making. This study assessed knowledge, opinions, and usage patterns of key stakeholders regarding the status of RWD/RWE and AI implementation in health technology assessment (HTA) and drug regulation and aimed to identify the primary obstacles hindering adoption of these technologies. Four surveys tailored to different stakeholders were created and disseminated online to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Venting the Venous Circulation: A Novel Approach to Decongestion in Heart Failure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Sensitivity, All-Organic Piezoelectric Skin Enabled by a Phytic Acid-Assisted Molecular Engineering Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electronic skin (e-skin), which mimics the tactile and multimodal sensing functions of human skin, is emerging as a key technology for wearable healthcare and human-machine interfaces. All-organic piezoelectric composites owing to their intrinsic flexibility and skin conformability represent attractive candidates for e-skin development. However, achieving a high piezoelectric performance, long-term stability, and mechanical compliance simultaneously remains a critical challenge. Here, we report...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420639/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating miRNA Sequencing and Integrative Proteomics for Identifying Plasma miRNAs as Potential Pharmacodynamic Biomarkers of IFNβ-1a Biologics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We used miRNA sequencing to identify candidate plasma pharmacodynamic (PD) biomarkers of interferon beta-1a (IFNβ-1a) biologics and explored miRNA-mRNA targeted protein relationships and networks to support identified miRNA candidates. Plasma samples from 36 healthy subjects from a placebo-controlled randomized single-dose clinical study with IFNβ-1a and pegIFNβ-1a were used. Mature miRNAs were measured using an in-house miRNA-seq workflow at baseline, at 9 timepoints over 6 days in the IFNβ-1a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacial and Thermo-Mechanical Characteristics of Epoxy/Hexagonal Boron Nitride Composites from Molecular Simulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polymer composites, enabled by improvements in matrix performance using fillers, are widely used across diverse fields, yet the molecular-level characteristics of matrix-filler interfaces have not been fully understood. Here, we study in detail the fundamental interfacial molecular characteristics of epoxy/hexagonal boron nitride (h-BN) composites by using molecular dynamics and density functional theory. We investigate the structural, thermodynamic, and thermal/mechanical properties for systems...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How do Hydrological Variability and Human Activities Control the Spatiotemporal Changes of Riverine Nitrogen Export in the Upper Mississippi River Basin?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Excessive nitrogen export from agricultural watersheds remains a critical water quality challenge, with the Upper Mississippi River Basin (UMRB) significantly contributing to downstream eutrophication and hypoxia in the Gulf. This study investigates the spatiotemporal dynamics of riverine nitrate plus nitrite (NO(3)^(-) + NO(2)^(-)-N) export across the UMRB at high spatial resolution (12-digit Hydrologic Unit Codes or HUC12 subwatershed scale) during 2001-2020 and quantifies the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fast Parametrization of Martini3 Models for Fragments and Small Molecules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coarse-grained molecular dynamics simulations, such as those performed with the recently parametrized Martini 3 force field, simplify molecular models and enable the study of larger systems over longer time scales. With this new implementation, Martini 3 allows more bead types and sizes, becoming more amenable to studying dynamical phenomena involving small molecules such as protein-ligand interactions and membrane permeation. However, while solutions existed to automatically model small...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420562/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasmon-Enhanced Hydrogen Evolution over an <em>In Situ</em> Constructed Pt Nanoparticles-Ti<sub>3</sub>C<sub>2</sub> MXene Hybrid Electrocatalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The electrocatalytic hydrogen evolution reaction (HER) is widely recognized as a promising pathway for sustainable energy conversion and storage. Recently, plasmonic enhancement has attracted increasing attention as an effective strategy to improve HER performance by harvesting incident light. However, most metal nanoparticles (NPs) with excellent HER catalytic activity, such as Pt, exhibit a negligible localized surface plasmon resonance (LSPR) effect, thereby limiting their overall efficiency....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Influence of Menstrual Cycle Phase on the Physiological and Perceptual Responses to Low-Intensity Continuous and High-Intensity Interval Sessions in Endurance Trained Women: The FENDURA Project]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The influence of the menstrual cycle (MC) on the acute responses to endurance training remains unclear. This study aimed to investigate the effect of the MC on the physiological and perceptual responses to standardized low-intenstiy continuous (LIT) and high-intensity interval sessions (HIT). Naturally menstruating endurance-trained women performed a standardized LIT (n = 23) and/or HIT (n = 23) session during the early-follicular (EFP), ovulatory (OP), and mid-luteal (MLP) phases of 2 MCs....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of intraoperative mean arterial pressure with postoperative organ dysfunction in elderly hypertensive patients: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Maintaining intraoperative MAP within 75-85 mmHg appears to reduce postoperative stress and preserve cardiac and renal function in elderly hypertensive patients. Neurologic outcomes did not differ significantly, but avoiding excessively low MAP may help minimize potential neurological risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Physiologically Based Pharmacokinetic (PBPK) Simulation Model for Nicotine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tobacco is a major cause of chronic diseases such as lung cancer, cardiovascular disease, and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease worldwide. Nicotine, the primary psychoactive component in tobacco, is highly addictive and while not the primary driver of such tobacco-related diseases, poses various health risks, particularly those affecting the cardiovascular and pulmonary systems. Although nicotine-based therapies, such as nicotine replacement products, are widely utilized in smoking cessation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Arrest to Recovery: The 2025 ERC Guidelines Redefine the Chain of Survival]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interaction Between Activating Transcription Factor 4 and Interleukin 6 Dictates Osteoclast Differentiation and Activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoclast functioning determines homeostasis of bone texture, healing speed after bone injury, and integrity after bone remodeling. Osteoclastogenesis is tightly controlled by transcriptional factors and cytokine-mediated signaling. The activating transcription factor 4 (Atf4) and interleukin 6 (IL6) have been considered to be involved in osteoclastogenesis, but their interaction on osteoclast differentiation is still largely unclear. Here we aimed to investigate their interaction on osteoclast...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420529/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Building the Ryan White HIV/AIDS program bench in Kentucky: inspiring sustainability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Ryan White HIV/AIDS program (RWHAP) is governed by legislative and programmatic guidelines that ensure comprehensive services are provided to persons with HIV (PWH) across the United States. Comprehensive training and skill building opportunities for programmatic staff are rare. RWHAP funding recipient organizations may struggle to acquire and retain essential program-specific knowledge, with downstream impact on patient care and treatment.We designed a comprehensive 11-session...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Equity-focused implementation to enhance access to rare disease genomic research and understand diverse perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overall, our equity-focused initiative enabled enrollment of participants from populations previously underrepresented in rare disease genomic research and offers insight into potential motivators.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in 23-valent pneumococcal polysaccharide vaccination rate and associated factors in 2022 and 2024 among community-based older adults in Shanghai, China]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pneumococcal vaccination effectively reduces the incidence of pneumococcal pneumonia and the associated mortality rates in older adults. Understanding trends in coverage and the influencing factors is essential for optimizing future vaccination programs. Two cross-sectional surveys were conducted in October 2022 and September 2024 among residents aged 60 and above in Pudong New Area, Shanghai. Data on demographic characteristics, pneumococcal vaccination status, and reasons for either receiving...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stimulus Novelty Inhibits Reward Evaluation: EEG Evidence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rewards frequently occur in novel contexts, yet whether novelty facilitates or inhibits reward evaluation remains unclear. Using EEG, we investigated how stimulus novelty affects reward evaluation across two experiments. Participants performed a monetary guessing task where gains and losses were delivered in either novel or familiar forms. In experiment 1 (N = 49), stimulus novelty was integrated into feedback valence as a feedback attribute; in experiment 2 (N = 50), it was separated from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emotional Challenges in Pediatric Intensive Care Unit Nurses' Postmortem Care: A Qualitative Exploration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Pediatric intensive care unit (PICU) nurses are regularly exposed to high-stress situations, particularly when dealing with patient death and postmortem care. While much attention has been paid to the physical demands of their role, the emotional and psychological impacts of these experiences are often overlooked. Understanding how nurses regulate their emotions in such high-pressure environments is essential for improving their well-being and providing better care. Objective: This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UITOTO: a software for generating molecular diagnoses for species descriptions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Millions of species remain undescribed, and each eventually will require a species description with a diagnosis. Yet, we lack software that can derive state-specific and contrastive molecular diagnoses and allows the user to validate them based on all available sequences for the taxon under study. Here we introduce UITOTO, which addresses this shortcoming by facilitating the identification, testing, and visualization of diagnostic molecular combinations (DMCs). The software uses a weighted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computer Vision Analysis for Objective Motor Assessment in Parkinson's Disease: A Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CV-derived tapping variability features objectively discriminated PD from healthy subjects and tracked motor severity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Worldwide Research Trends on Substance Use Disorder-Related Inflammatory Imbalances: A Bibliometric Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This bibliometric study delineates the foundational knowledge structural and mapping of the "SUD-inflammation" field over the past 25 years. The findings provide a comprehensive and data-driven perspective on the evolving research landscape, offering valuable insights for future investigations and resource allocation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Personalized Spine Surgery in Adult Deformity: Reoperation Rates and Mechanical Complications Following Customized Planning and Interbody Implant Use]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignRetrospective cohort study.ObjectivesPrior studies have shown that adult spinal deformity (ASD) patients undergoing revision surgery due to mechanical complications had less radiographic improvement and worsening patient-reported outcomes scores. The combination of customized 3D planning and personalized implants has been shown to contribute to improved achievement of alignment goals. This study aimed to determine whether such improved correction also results in a correspondingly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cognitive-Motor Conflict During Step Initiation: Neural and Biomechanical Insights Into Freezing of Gait in Parkinson's Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Freezing of gait (FoG) is a disabling motor symptom in Parkinson's disease (PD) characterized by brief episodes of inability to step, often triggered by cognitive-motor conflict. Step initiation (SI) involves anticipatory postural adjustments (APAs), which are critical for balance and movement preparation. This study aimed to investigate the neural and biomechanical correlates of FoG during SI under congruent and incongruent conditions, focusing on the supplementary motor area (SMA) and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420410/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Predictive Value of Inflammatory Markers in the Severity and Mortality Risk of Stevens-Johnson Syndrome/Toxic Epidermal Necrolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Red blood cell distribution width-to-platelet ratio (RPR), red blood cell distribution width-to-hemoglobin ratio (RHR), red blood cell distribution width-to-albumin ratio (RAR), and prognostic nutritional index (PNI) have been implicated in disease severity and prognosis. However, their role in predicting severity and mortality in Stevens-Johnson syndrome/toxic epidermal necrolysis (SJS/TEN) remains unclear. This study aimed to investigate the association between RPR, RHR, RAR, PNI and both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coexistence of HBsAg and Anti-HBs Predicts Severe Hepatic Fibrosis in Untreated Children With Hepatitis B Virus Infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[An unnatural serological pattern has been reported, exhibiting the simultaneous presence of hepatitis B surface antigen (HBsAg) and antibody against HBsAg (Anti-HBs). However, its association with severe hepatic fibrosis have not been understood. This study aimed to examine the association between concurrent HBsAg and anti-HBs seropositivity and severe liver fibrosis in untreated children with hepatitis B virus infection. We conducted a cross-sectional study on 318 untreated children with HBV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[T cell-intrinsic PRR signaling in immunity and pathology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The immune system orchestrates a delicate balance between robust defense against pathogens and restraint to prevent tissue damage, with T cells serving as central mediators of adaptive immunity. The canonical pathway for T-cell activation hinges on the precise recognition of peptide antigens presented by major histocompatibility complex (MHC) molecules via the T-cell receptor (TCR), which is complemented by essential co-stimulatory signals. However, this model alone cannot fully explain the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420400/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unheard Voices from Earth: A Fable from 2184]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fables are a form of storytelling that convey moral, social, and philosophical lessons through carefully constructed allegories and metaphorical characters. Often set in imaginary worlds or distant times, they use fictional protagonists and exaggerated circumstances to illuminate contemporary real-world struggles. They invite readers to recognize and critically reflect on enduring patterns of systemic inequities and power dynamics in ways that are both accessible and thought-provoking....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing reactivation of multiple sclerosis during treatment with natalizumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This exploratory study indicates that switching to anti-CD20 therapies following natalizumab failure is associated with a >50% reduction in relapse risk. No differences were seen in secondary outcomes, despite consistent trends. Clinicians may consider anti-CD20 therapies following natalizumab failure, noting further research is needed to confirm differences in MRI and disability outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420376/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multifunctional CeO<sub>2</sub>-Modified Dual-Network Freeze-Dried Sponge for Infected Wound Healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Bacterial-infected wounds face delayed healing due to excessive inflammation and oxidative stress, impairing tissue regeneration, which is a significant global health challenge. Traditional wound dressings, while partially promoting healing, often lack the integrated functions of antibacterial properties, antioxidant capabilities, and inflammation regulation, making them insufficient for complex wound environments. This study developed a freeze-dried dual-network sponge by cross-linking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling Physical and Chemical Changes in All-Solid-State Battery: An Operando Synchrotron Chemical Imaging Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the dynamics of complex heterogeneous battery materials under realistic operation conditions with micrometer spatial and relevant temporal resolutions remains challenging. This work presents a synchrotron-based operando chemical imaging methodology using microfocus X-ray diffraction (µ-XRD) scanning imaging. The approach is applied to an all-solid-state battery (ASSB) with high-energy lithium-rich nickel manganese cobalt layered oxide (Li-rich NCM) as active cathode material,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bio-Inspired Micro/Nanostructured Antibacterial Surfaces: Antibacterial Mechanisms, Design Principles, and Fabrication Methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The accelerated development of drug-resistant bacteria is a serious threat to public health. Inspired by nature's antimicrobial topographies, micro/nanostructured mechano-antibacterial surfaces have been widely studied. This review summarizes the materials and antimicrobial effects of various natural and biomimetic micro/nanostructured surfaces, and their antifouling and bactericidal mechanisms are elucidated systematically. The synergistic antifouling and bactericidal surfaces are also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420340/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase-Separated Patch With Dual-Functional Interfaces Enables Antiadhesive Tension-Free Hernia Repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The clinical demand for novel patches that prevent adhesion and enable tension-free repair continues to motivate biomaterials research. Inspired by the Janus nature of the peritoneum, we developed a phase-separated patch with distinct functional interfaces through a straightforward layer‑by‑layer molding process. By fusing two sol layers with different polyvinyl alcohol (PVA)-polyethylene glycol (PEG)-dimethyl sulfoxide (DMSO)-water ratios, in situ phase separation and PEG‑induced plasticization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of MOF-Based Biomaterials in Skin Wound Healing: Antibacterial, Immunomodulatory, Angiogenic, and Neurogenic Effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The skin functions as the body's primary barrier against external environmental insults, rendering it particularly susceptible to injury and in need of effective wound management strategies. To date, metal-organic framework (MOF)-based biomaterials, mainly composed of metal ions or clusters coordinated with organic ligands, have offered exceptional advantages in wound dressing biomaterials due to their biocompatibility, high porosity, tunable structure, and intrinsic multifunctionality, enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420337/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Catalytic Generation of Nitrosocarbonyls Under Mild Conditions: Advances, Challenges, and Opportunities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrosocarbonyl species (NOCs), also known as acylnitroso species, are highly reactive nitrogen-containing electrophiles. Since their first reports in the 1970s, they have shown significant synthetic potential for the preparation of aminated substrates. Their widespread adoption as versatile amination reagents began in the 2000s, driven by the development of new organometallic and organocatalytic systems. NOCs are typically generated in situ from stable precursors, such as hydroxamic acids and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420296/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tissue Proteomics of Feline Mammary Carcinoma: Differences in Protein Profiles Among Histological Grades Using Liquid Chromatography-Tandem Mass Spectrometry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mammary carcinomas are aggressive neoplasms and a significant cause of mortality in female cats. Despite surgical removal, feline mammary carcinoma (FMC) often recurs or metastasizes. Specific tumour biomarkers are necessary for early detection, prognosis and therapy selection. This study aims to identify candidate biomarkers for FMC by comparing tissue proteomic profiles among grades of 31 FMC cats and six normal mammary tissues (control) using liquid chromatography coupled with tandem mass...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Socioeconomic disparities in the trends of inpatient utilization for middle-aged and older adults in China: the perspective of international comparison from four cohorts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Inpatient utilization rates among middle-aged and older adults in China have experienced excessive growth over the past decade. Low SES was associated with high inpatient utilization, likely attributable to the poorer health status of low-SES groups. This association persisted in people covered by URRBMI. Policy reforms should prioritize the development of primary care, targeted health management, and equitable adjustments to health insurance. These measures are essential for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reference-guided computational framework identifies microenvironment metabolic subtypes and targets using pan-cancer single-cell datasets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: MetroSCREEN is a robust and scalable approach for characterizing metabolic heterogeneity and pinpointing metabolic regulators at single-cell resolution, unveiling novel antitumor targets for future metabolic interventions. The source codes of MetroSCREEN is available at the Github site https://github.com/wanglabtongji/MetroSCREEN .]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining streetscape visuals and emotional responses through social media and street view image analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings underscore the association between streetscape visuals and public emotions and demonstrate that social media platforms provide substantial data for studying these effects. This research offers valuable insights for urban planners and managers to understand resident and tourist preferences, providing an objective foundation for enhancing urban streetscape quality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420239/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fentanyl, Amphetamine-type Stimulants, Heroin, and xylazine in drug residues in two Northern border Mexican cities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Illicitly manufactured fentanyl (IMF) and amphetamine-type stimulants (ATS) are driving the fourth wave of the opioid crisis in the United States and Canada. Accordingly, the aim of this paper was to determine the presence of heroin, fentanyl, ATS, xylazine, and other substances in Tijuana and Mexicali, Baja California, two cities on the US-Mexico border. We also tested the positive predictive value of fentanyl and ATS test strips. To do this, we randomly selected 300 drug residues from syringe...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life course socioeconomic trajectories and chronic disease risk in later life among 30,055 older adults across 27 European countries (the SHARE study)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study revealed five distinct life course SEP trajectories in a sample of European individuals aged 50 years or older. Two trajectories were associated with chronic disease risk later in life, with more advantageous trajectories associated with reduced chronic disease risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420228/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CT-based morphometry and Mimics-guided virtual implantation of a facet-fusion-integrated posterior cervical semi-open-door system: an anatomical feasibility study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dissecting the pathogenic effects of ambient air pollution exposure and its blood DNA methylation markers on cardiovascular disease risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study confirms a significant association between air pollution, DNAm and CVD risk, and provides new insights into the pathogenic effects of air pollution on CVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420191/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Baseline exposure-response assessment of metals from dried blood spots and personal household air pollution concentrations among pregnant women in Rwanda: household air pollution intervention network trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: While associations were not statistically significant, the directionally consistent increases in blood Pb and Cd with increased PM₂.₅ and BC exposures align with existing evidence and underscore the need for continued research and policy action to reduce household air pollution exposures and protect maternal and fetal health.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Greater ambient air pollution exposure is associated with worse respiratory symptoms in men and women with HIV and chronic lung disease: a cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: CDK4/6 inhibition enhances T-cell immunotherapy on hepatocellular carcinoma cells by rejuvenating immunogenicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Silver nitrate functionalized rice husk-derived graphene oxide as a nanocarrier for pH-responsive drug delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, graphene oxide (GO) derived from rice husk was functionalized with silver nitrate (AgNO(3)) through a chemical co-precipitation method, and its biomedical applications were systematically investigated. Drug release experiments revealed a pH-responsive profile, where at pH 4.0 the cumulative release reached 32.6 ± 1.6% after 24 h, compared to 12.4 ± 1.8% at pH 7.4, highlighting its potential for targeted delivery to cancer cells. Reactive oxygen species (ROS) analysis and flow...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gas-Phase Integration of Trophically Distinct Microbial Cultures for Net-Reduced CO<sub>2</sub> and Enhanced Metabolite Production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The continued increase in atmospheric CO(2) concentrations has intensified global efforts to develop sustainable biotechnologies that capture and reutilise carbon rather than releasing it. While photosynthetic microorganisms provide a renewable route for CO(2) fixation into organic products, heterotrophic fermentation remains the industrial standard due to its high productivity, controllability and scalability. Consequently, integrating the carbon efficiency of autotrophic processes with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420442/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Photobiomodulation Therapy Irradiation Intensity, Frequency, and Duration on Pain, and Functional Improvements in Patients with Temporomandibular Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Purpose: To systematically review and meta-analyze the efficacy of photobiomodulation therapy (PBMT) for temporomandibular disorders (TMDs), focusing on the influence of intensity, frequency, and duration on pain reduction and functional improvement. Methods: Through a systematic search of PubMed, Cochrane, and EMBASE, we identified randomized controlled trials (RCTs) involving adults with TMD who were treated with PBMT. Ultimately, 40 RCTs were included, and a meta-analysis was conducted using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Scalable Production of Tailor-Designed MXene-Hydrogel Core-Shell Fibers via Dual Stress-Guided Alignment during Thermal Drawing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Large-scale production of two-dimensional MXene-based functional fibers, while preserving their outstanding material properties, remains challenging. Here, we present highly aligned Ti(3)C(2)T(x) MXene fibers integrated into tens of meters-long fibers via in situ stress-induced alignments during thermal drawing. In the proposed liquid injection-assisted thermal drawing, MXene flakes in aqueous dispersion are continuously injected into hollow channels of fibers and subsequently aligned by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning enables scalable and systematic hierarchical virus taxonomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although virus ecogenomics has expanded access to and understanding of the virosphere, existing classification tools lack taxonomic resolution and are unable to scale to modern discovery-based datasets or classify previously unknown sequence space. Here we develop vConTACT3-a machine learning-based tool that improves scalability and accuracy of virus taxonomy. By optimizing gene-sharing thresholds and leveraging adaptive, realm-specific cut-offs, vConTACT3 expands classification to both...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A quantum chemical dataset of interacting molecular pairs for chemical reaction studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding molecular interactions beyond single-molecule properties is critical for studying real-world chemical systems. Quantum chemical calculations of molecule-molecule interactions are computationally demanding, making large, publicly available datasets scarce. Here, we present an efficient framework for generating initial configurations of molecular interaction systems and construct a molecular interaction dataset, containing 49,620 individual molecules and 247,741 molecular pairs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419920/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Dataset of Lipid Nanoparticle Compositions and Properties for Nucleic Acid Delivery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipid nanoparticles (LNPs) have emerged as the leading delivery platform for nucleic acid therapeutics, with clinical success demonstrated in mRNA vaccines and therapeutic applications. However, rational design of LNP remains challenging due to the complex relationships among LNP composition, physicochemical properties, and biological performance, as well as the scattered experimental data across the literature. Here, we present LNP Atlas, a comprehensive dataset containing LNP formulations...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring potential of Turing pattern classification through convolution maps]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the classification potential of nonlinear Turing patterns by employing convolutional features. Classifying spatial heterogeneity caused by Turing instability, observed in natural phenomena such as animal coat patterns and neural models, remains a challenging problem due to the difficulty in learning the parameters governing such pattern formation. We consider a minimal structure of a convolutional neural network including convolutional layers, activation functions, and pooling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Longitudinal changes in each retinal layer thickness in diabetic retinopathy patients treated with pan-retinal photocoagulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The thickness of each retinal layer of patients who underwent PRP changed differently over time, and these changes were significantly associated with changes in visual acuity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural configuration of sustainable sports industry based on deep learning and genetic algorithm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the structural imbalances and sustainability challenges faced by the sports industry in its high-quality development transformation, and to overcome the shortcomings of existing research in dynamic modeling, multi-objective optimization, and quantitative solutions, this paper constructs an intelligent optimization framework integrating deep learning (DL) and genetic algorithms (GA). This framework uses a one-dimensional convolutional neural network to extract deep features and predict...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantum electrodynamics of photonic time crystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photonic time crystals host a variety of intriguing phenomena, from wave amplification and mixing to exotic band structures, all stemming from the time-periodic modulation of optical properties. While these features have been well described classically, their quantum manifestation when coupled to an atomic electric dipole has remained elusive. Here, we introduce a quantum electrodynamical model of photonic time crystals that reveals a deeper connection between classical and quantum pictures: the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limits on WIMP Dark Matter with NaI(Tl) Crystals in Three Years of COSINE-100 Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report limits on weakly interacting massive particle (WIMP) dark matter derived from three years of data collected by the COSINE-100 experiment with NaI(Tl) crystals, achieving an improved energy threshold of 0.7 keV. This lowered threshold enhances sensitivity in the sub-GeV mass range, extending the reach for direct detection of low-mass dark matter. Although no excess of WIMP-like events was observed, the increased sensitivity enabled a model-insensitive comparison between the expected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418194/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[β-Decay Half-Lives of Neutron-Rich Sulfur to Potassium: Evolution of the N=32 and 34 Subshell Closures below Calcium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The half-lives of 24 isotopes ranging from sulfur to potassium were measured using the ZeroDegree Advanced Decay Station at the Radioactive Isotope Beam Factory, including six of the most neutron-rich-^{47}S, ^{48,49}Cl, ^{51,52}Ar, ^{55}K-for the first time, while the precision for ^{48}Ar and ^{53,54}K was significantly improved. Two prominent features are found: First, a half-life drop at ^{54}K_{35} relative to ^{52,53}K, supporting the persistence of the N=34 subshell closure in potassium...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth hormone is required for hippocampal engram cell maturation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memory is stored in specialized cells known as engram cells, but the molecular mechanisms underlying this process remain unclear. We discovered that the initial translation leading to growth hormone (GH) synthesis in engram cells is required for their maturation in the mouse dentate gyrus. Time-course experiments with a translation inhibitor suggested that the key molecule is immediately translated during learning. We identified GH as the crucial factor, specifically translated within the first...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combined Outerbridge-Kashiwagi Procedure and Supercharged Anterior Interosseous Nerve Transfer for Elbow Arthritis With Ulnar Neuropathy: Refinements in Surgical Aspects of the Combined Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This combined approach addresses both mechanical impingement and motor deficits, offering a feasible and effective strategy for restoring upper extremity function in this patient population. Preoperative electrophysiologic assessment plays a key role in optimizing candidate selection and outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Maribacter algae</em> sp. nov., <em>Maribacter spongiae</em> sp. nov., <em>Maribacter corallii</em> sp. nov., <em>Maribacter aquimarinus</em> sp. nov. and <em>Maribacter taeanensis</em> sp. nov., isolated from marine habitats in the Republic of Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Five novel bacterial strains, designated as 2210JD10-5^(T), 2304DJ31-5^(T), 2307UL18-2^(T), 2307ULW6-5^(T) and 2308TA10-17^(T), were isolated from diverse marine samples in the Republic of Korea, including algae, sponge, coral and seawater. The five novel strains affiliated with the genus Maribacter were taxonomically characterized using a polyphasic approach. The cells were catalase- and oxidase-positive and rod-shaped. The five novel strains were revealed as mesophilic, neutrophilic in pH and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasensitive Detection of Multiple Foodborne Pathogens Using CRISPR-Cas12a on a Finger-Actuated Microfluidic Device Integrated with a Modular Pressurizing Pump]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Foodborne pathogens pose a serious threat to global health and the economy, causing gastrointestinal illnesses and potentially leading to fatalities. Here, we present a recombinase polymerase amplification (RPA)-CRISPR-Cas12a-based method for the detection of foodborne pathogens using target-specific CRISPR RNAs (crRNAs) on a reusable, reconfigurable finger-actuated microfluidic device. Unlike previous finger-actuated pushbutton-based microfluidic devices, the device incorporates a modular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coffee Consumption and Colorectal Cancer Survival: A Dose-Response Meta-Analysis by Coffee Type and Disease Stage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Coffee consumption is associated with improved survival and reduced recurrence in CRC patients in a dose-dependent and stage-specific manner.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41416862/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamical dark energy in light of the DESI DR2 baryonic acoustic oscillations measurements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding whether cosmic acceleration arises from a cosmological constant or a dynamical component is a central goal of cosmology, and the Dark Energy Spectroscopic Instrument (DESI) enables stringent tests with high-precision distance measurements. Here we analyse measurements of baryon acoustic oscillations in DESI Data Release 1 and Data Release 2 and consider type Ia supernovae and a distance prior for the cosmic microwave background. With the larger statistical power and wider redshift...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415972/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Case Report: Temporary supratrochanteric plating for the management of subtrochanteric femoral fracture in an immature dog]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This case report describes the successful management of a subtrochanteric femoral fracture in a 2-month-old dog using temporary supratrochanteric plate fixation, performed prior to the development of the greater trochanter apophysis. A tibial plateau leveling osteotomy plate was applied to the proximolateral femur and subsequently removed following radiographic evidence of bridging callus formation. At the 21-month follow-up, the dog exhibited normal limb function, symmetrical femoral length,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world treatment outcome and toxicity analysis of inotuzumab ozogamicin in adult patients with relapsed or refractory B-cell precursor acute lymphoblastic leukemia: multicenter prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: INO represents a potent salvage option for R/R BCP-ALL. However, substantial toxicities highlight the critical need for careful patient selection and dose optimization strategies to maximize its therapeutic benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepKinome: quantitative prediction of kinase binding affinity by a compound using deep learning based regression model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DeepKinome offers a promising approach for understanding kinase inhibition and compound binding.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41415030/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and validation of a dual-purpose 60K SNP chip for simultaneous genotyping of chicken and duck]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We successfully developed and validated the first poultry SNP chip incorporating chicken-duck pooled samples. This chip provides reliable genotyping performance for both species and offers a cost-effective solution for large-scale SNP chip development in the livestock industry.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41414840/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancements in the molecular understanding of major depressive disorder uncovering novel targets with therapeutic promise: focus on recurrence of illness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Major depressive disorder (MDD) is a neuro-immune-metabolic-oxidative stress (NIMETOX) disorder. A significant proportion (50%) of individuals with MDD experience recurrence of episodes and suicidal behaviors. Recurrent MDD is characterized by greater severity of depression and increased functional impairments. Recently, the recurrence of illness (ROI) index was introduced as a quantitative metric for assessing this recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Soil organic matter dynamics under changing precipitation regimes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current and predicted changes in global precipitation regimes, characterized by increasing extreme events and wet-dry cycles, present critical uncertainties for terrestrial biogeochemical cycling and soil organic matter (SOM) dynamics. Here, we highlight individual and interactive effects of abiotic and biotic factors on SOM dynamics under changing precipitation amount, timing, and frequency. Particularly, we identify the mechanisms and magnitude by which changes in precipitation regimes alter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41420125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychometric evaluation of a Korean-language version of the Nursing Home Survey on Patient Safety Culture (K-NHSPSC)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419898/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aldolase a coordinates macropinocytic nutrient scavenging and lysosomal degradation in lung cancer by interacting with V-ATPase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study identifies a novel, non-enzymatic function of ALDOA as a critical regulator of lysosomal degradation of macropinocytosed proteins via interaction with V-ATPase. This mechanism is essential for metabolic adaptation and growth of KRAS-mutant tumors under stress conditions. Targeting ALDOA offers a promising therapeutic strategy for cancers that rely on extracellular nutrient scavenging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a laboratory-scale apparatus and experimental investigation of fluid property effects on pipe wear in slurry shield TBM operations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Managing pipeline wear is critical for maintaining excavation efficiency during slurry shield tunnel boring machine (TBM) operations. Yet, the effects of carrier fluid properties on pipe wear in slurries containing coarse particles remain insufficiently understood. To address this gap, this study developed a laboratory-scale test apparatus to simulate slurry flow in the discharge pipelines of a slurry shield TBM, focusing on the influence of carrier fluid viscosity and density on pipe wear....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pressurized intraperitoneal aerosol chemotherapy enhances cisplatin efficacy in colorectal cancer organoids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pressurized Intraperitoneal Aerosol Chemotherapy (PIPAC) is an emerging method that delivers chemotherapeutic agents as aerosols directly into the peritoneal cavity to overcome poor tissue penetration. Although early clinical outcomes are promising, challenges remain, such as variable patient responses and the lack of appropriate preclinical models. In this study, we investigated the efficacy of PIPAC combined with three cytotoxic agents (Cisplatin, Oxaliplatin, and Paclitaxel) using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MIDAS: rapid, multiplexed molecular profiling for integrated host-pathogen analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Addressing the need for integrated molecular analysis in complex infectious conditions requires technologies that rapidly quantify both pathogens and host responses. This is particularly relevant in sepsis research, where existing tools typically measure either microbial or host biomarkers. Here, we present MIDAS (Multiplexed Intelligent Diffraction Analysis System), a proof-of-concept platform that integrates shape-encoded hydrogel particles with lens-free diffraction imaging and deep...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trajectories of post-discharge cognitive function and associated risk factors in ICU survivors: a secondary analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419567/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[USP11 promotes colorectal cancer progression by stabilizing EGFR and TRAF6: a potential therapeutic target in EGFR- and TLR-driven tumorigenesis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ubiquitin-specific proteases (USPs) are key regulators of protein homeostasis and have been implicated in various aspects of cancer development, including colorectal cancer (CRC). In this study, we investigated the role of USP11 in CRC pathogenesis. RNA-seq analysis of tumor and matched normal tissues from 35 CRC patients identified USP11 as significantly overexpressed in tumor samples. Elevated USP11 expression was correlated with reduced patient survival, suggesting its prognostic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The São Paulo International Consensus on Minimally Invasive Pancreatic Surgery for Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Although minimally invasive surgery is widely accepted across surgical disciplines, its role in pancreatic cancer continues to be debated. The objective of the São Paulo Consensus on Minimally Invasive Pancreatic Surgery (MIPS) was to establish consensus statements on the use of MIPS for pancreatic cancer, integrating contemporary evidence and recent advances.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Specific glutamatergic projection to claustrum for regulating methamphetamine abstinence anxiety-like behaviors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Methamphetamine (METH) abstinence anxiety is a common METH abstinence symptom, which drives METH relapse. Our previous study found that claustrum (CL) is involved in coding abstinence anxiety-like behaviors caused by adolescent cocaine experiences. Here, we aim to investigate the role of CL in the development of METH abstinence-induced anxiety, especially exploring the related glutamatergic projections to CL. We found that 14 days of METH abstinence heightened anxiety-like behaviors in male...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419329/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International consensuses and guidelines on multifocal intraocular lenses (IOLs) by the Academy of Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intraocular Lenses (IOLs) have revolutionized cataract surgery, evolving from simple monofocal designs to advanced multifocal technologies that aim to reduce dependence on glasses after surgery. However, multifocal IOLs remain one of the most debated topics in ophthalmology, with passionate advocates and critics. This controversy stems from the balance between their potential benefits and limitations. The Asia-Pacific Academy of Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO) formed an international panel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunohistological characterization of minced dental pulp transplant in an ectopic mouse model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This preliminary in vivo mouse study suggests the feasibility of MP transplantation and its potential for dentin-pulp complex regeneration, though further studies are needed to assess long-term outcomes and clinical applicability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence, Progression, and Clinical Impact of Stem Notching in Ceramic-on-Ceramic Total Hip Arthroplasty: A Minimum 15-Year Follow-Up Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Stem notching in CoC THA is a relatively common, but often overlooked phenomenon. Most notches remained stable over time and were not associated with inferior functional outcomes. Although hips with notches showed a higher rate of ceramic-related noise and head fractures, these differences were not statistically significant. Clinicians should recognize this finding, maintain routine follow-up, and reassure patients that a notch alone does not pose any immediate problem.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41419031/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Good clinical outcome of nonoperative treated low grade medial collateral ligament injuries combined with primary anterior cruciate ligament reconstruction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Similar patient-reported, functional, and return-to-sport outcomes were found for nonoperatively treated grade I and II MCL injuries combined with ACL reconstruction compared to those of isolated ACL reconstruction at the 2-year follow-up.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418997/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Levan-stabilized Prussian blue nanoparticles targeting the CD44 receptor for the effective treatment of acute kidney injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute kidney injury (AKI) is a prevalent disease characterized by sudden loss of renal function. Nanozymes have emerged as promising therapeutic candidates because of their intrinsic reactive oxygen species (ROS)-scavenging capabilities and anti-inflammatory efficacy. However, their clinical translation has been hindered by limited bioavailability and lack of targeted tissue specificity. In this study, ROS-scavenging Prussian blue nanozymes were stabilized with levan polysaccharide (L-PB) to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418953/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Liver cancer chronically exposed to palmitate acquires ferroptosis resistance via the downregulation of glutamine-driven hepcidin expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study uncovers a previously unrecognized type of palmitate-induced metabolic reprogramming that confers resistance to ICB-induced ferroptosis on HCC, and propose a therapeutic strategy to overcome ferroptosis resistance under free fatty acid-rich conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418943/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex Differences in Platelet Reactivity and Five-Year Outcomes With Extended Dual Antiplatelet Therapy After Drug-Eluting Stent Implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Female patients with HPR tended to have lower ischemic event rates than males, without an increase in bleeding events; however, this finding should be interpreted as hypothesis-generating.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cell-surface RNA forms ternary complex with RNA-binding proteins and heparan sulfate to recruit immune receptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent discoveries have shown the presence of ribonucleic acid (RNA) on the cell surface, defying the view that RNA only functions intracellularly. However, how RNA is presented on the cell surface and what its biological relevance is are poorly understood. We established Toll-like receptor 7 (TLR7) as a cell-surface RNA (csRNA) probe. Employing it in a genome-wide knockout screening, we identified heparan sulfate (HS) as a crucial factor for csRNA presentation. Cell-surface proximity labeling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418757/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphological changes of the preserved discoid lateral meniscus on serial magnetic resonance imaging following partial meniscectomy and repair: A comparison between immediate and 2-year postoperative findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The meniscal width of the anterior and posterior horns of DLM in the sagittal plane increased from the immediate postoperative state through to 2 years following partial meniscectomy and meniscus repair. Although the height of the anterior horn, midbody, and posterior horns remained consistent, the mid-height of these structures decreased at the 2-year follow up compared with the immediate postoperative status.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimization of NIRS-based models for predicting quality and gas production traits of fresh alfalfa silage via machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Near-infrared spectroscopy (NIRS) prediction models offer an expeditious method for assessing the nutritional value of feedstuffs, however, developing high-performance models using undried and unground samples remains challenging. This study aimed to explore strategies to improve NIRS models for predicting silage quality and gas production of fresh alfalfa using machine learning approaches. A total of 348 spectral samples were collected for modeling 15 parameters of alfalfa silage. The modeling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutralizing endocan reduces blood pressure and improves endothelial function in angiotensin II-induced hypertensive mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endocan (endothelial cell-specific molecule-1) has emerged as a potential biomarker of endothelial dysfunction in hypertension. This study investigates the role of endocan in blood pressure regulation and vascular dysfunction, aiming to clarify its contribution to the pathophysiology of hypertension. Eight-week-old male C57BL/6 mice were treated with saline, endocan (0.6 mg/kg), or angiotensin II (Ang II, 1000 ng/kg/min) for 4 weeks. Ang II-induced hypertensive mice were further treated with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantification differences between supine and prone CT in interstitial lung disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Prone CT measurements demonstrated high reproducibility and comparable correlation with PFT parameters, relative to supine CT measurements, with fibrosis extent variability of approximately 2 %. Prone CT may be reliable for single-time-point assessment; however, caution is warranted for longitudinal comparisons in advanced or GGO-dominant ILD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanisms of oil droplet detachment by cavitation bubbles in ultrasonic cleaning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient removal of oily contaminants from solid surfaces remains a significant challenge in various engineering applications. While ultrasonic cleaning mechanisms for solid particles are well established, the detachment of oil droplets is less understood due to the distinct interfacial and viscous characteristics of oils. Here, we experimentally investigate oil droplet removal under ultrasonic excitation, focusing on the role of cavitation bubble dynamics. High-speed visualizations reveal that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mental health, coping and related risk factors during the first 2 years of the COVID-19 pandemic in children: Nationally representative, multi-wave, cross-sectional results from 12 countries from the global COH-FIT study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Few multinational studies have assessed risk factors and coping strategies associated with the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic on children's mental health over time. The Collaborative Outcomes study on Health and Functioning during Infection Times (COH-FIT) is the largest transcontinental, multi-wave, cross-sectional survey collecting multi-nation data on well-being and psychopathology during the pandemic. We analyzed country-specific, general-population-based, representative COH-FIT data of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interferon-γ-responsive theranostic nanoplatform for adaptive antibacterial therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Developing intelligent theranostic strategies capable of real-time infection assessment and adaptive treatment remains a significant challenge in wound management. Here, we present a smart theranostic nanoplatform (Apt-Ag^(+)-GNR) that integrates fluorescence-guided detection, real-time adaptive silver ion (Ag^(+)) release, and photothermal therapy (PTT) for the precise treatment of infections. This system utilizes interferon-γ (IFN-γ), an inflammation-specific biomarker with high detection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent short-term and long-term outcomes of massive pulmonary hemorrhage in extremely low birth weight infants: A nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The incidence and in-hospital deaths of massive pulmonary hemorrhage in ELBW infants have decreased in recent years. However, improved survival may be accompanied by increased in-hospital morbidity and adverse neurodevelopmental outcomes, underscoring the need for ongoing monitoring and strategies to mitigate short- and long-term complications in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal analysis of mangrove vegetation changes in Cà Mau, Vietnam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mangrove ecosystems provide essential coastal ecosystem services, including shoreline protection, carbon sequestration, and biodiversity conservation, but are increasingly affected by climate change, aquaculture expansion, and coastal development. These pressures have intensified marine pollution, which alters water chemistry, reduces oxygen levels, and disrupts root-sediment interactions that are crucial for mangrove survival and regeneration. This study examined spatiotemporal changes in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of anti-inflammatory constituents of <em>lindera glauca</em> using cell extraction coupled with lC-QTOF MS/MS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lindera glauca, an edible medicinal plant native to Northeastern Asia, has been reported to possess various pharmacological activities. This study employed cell extraction (CE) in conjunction with LC-QTOF-MS/MS to identify bioactive components that bind to target cells. The 80% MeOH extract of L. glauca exhibited significant nitric oxide (NO) production inhibitory activity in BV2 cells and was applied to the CE coupled with the LC-QTOF MS/MS method. New compound...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418301/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Search for New Physics in Jet Multiplicity Patterns of Multilepton Events at sqrt[s]=13 TeV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A first search for beyond the standard model physics in jet multiplicity patterns of multilepton events is presented, using a data sample corresponding to an integrated luminosity of 138 fb^{-1} of 13 TeV proton-proton collisions recorded by the CMS detector at the LHC. The search uses observed jet multiplicity distributions in one-, two-, and four-lepton events to explore possible enhancements in jet production rate in three-lepton events with and without bottom quarks. The data are found to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Underutilization of GIS in health research in Pakistan: A literature review of Pakistani medline indexed journals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the spatial dimension of place, alongside time and personal characteristics, is essential in epidemiology. The current narrative review was planned to analyse articles from all three Medline-indexed general medical journals in Pakistan that reported on the use of Geographic Information System or the Global Positioning System. From 2011 till October 2024, a total of 20 studies were published; 18(90%) of them in the Journal of Pakistan Medical Association, including the first article...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and Psychometric Testing of the Self-Efficacy for Heart-Healthy Lifestyle Behaviors (SE-HeartLife) Scale in Cardiovascular Disease Prevention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 35-item SE-HeartLife scale is a psychometrically robust instrument for assessing self-efficacy in the integrated practice of multiple heart-healthy behaviors aimed at preventing cardiovascular disease.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41418018/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reconstruction after distal gastrectomy and alkaline gastritis: a multi-center three-arm randomized trial comparing Billroth-II, Billroth-II Braun, and Uncut Roux-en-Y (SDR-02)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Uncut R-Y is superior to B-II and B-II Braun in reducing bile reflux and related symptoms after distal gastrectomy. These findings support the adoption of uncut R-Y as a preferred reconstruction method for long-term QOL improvement in gastric cancer patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417990/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances in Transmission Electron Microscopy to Image Nanocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in transmission electron microscopy (TEM) have substantially expanded our capability to observe nanocrystals at unprecedented spatial and temporal resolutions. Innovations in TEM instruments, specimen preparation, and imaging modality have overcome historical limitations related to radiation damage, weak contrast for light elements, 2D projection limitations, and high-vacuum constraints. Additionally, advanced image processing techniques, particularly those incorporating...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417973/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Cognitive Function and Somatic Psychological Symptoms Are Correlated with Greater Risk of Delirium After Total Knee Arthroplasty: A Prospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study comprehensively evaluated preoperative cognitive function and psychological symptoms in patients undergoing TKA. Even subclinical cognitive and somatic symptoms were linked to POD, emphasizing the need for preoperative identification of high-risk patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How similar should collaborators be in inter-organizational learning: Optimal cognitive proximity and knowledge complexity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Effective knowledge exchange is critical for innovation in knowledge-intensive sectors, yet the relationship between cognitive proximity and collaborative innovation remains underexplored in complex knowledge environments. While prior studies confirm a non-linear, inverted U-shaped relationship where moderate similarity balances absorptive capacity and novelty, how this relationship changes with increasing knowledge complexity is poorly understood. This study investigates how knowledge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417844/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Vertical Molecular Synaptic Transistor with Redox-Induced Analog States]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report a three-terminal, ion-gel-gated, redox-active molecular transistor that exhibits synaptic plasticity and analog conductance states. The device was composed of a ferrocene-terminated alkanethiolate self-assembled monolayer as the active channel, vertically sandwiched between a monolayer graphene source and a Au drain, and the channel conductance was modulated by an ion-gel gate. Gate voltage pulses induce an electric double layer at the ion-gel/graphene interface, triggering dynamic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toxicity and Safety of Nanomaterials in Food Packaging Applications: A Dimension-Based Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nanomaterials are increasingly used in food packaging polymers to enhance barriers, strength, and antimicrobial properties, raising important questions about their migration into food and potential health risks. Driven by these concerns, this review evaluates the toxicity and safety of nanomaterials in food packaging from a dimensional perspective. It explores how dimensionality (0D, 1D, 2D, and 3D) influences nanoparticle transport, gastrointestinal transformation, biological fate, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of combining empagliflozin in people with type 2 diabetes mellitus uncontrolled with metformin and sitagliptin: A randomised, double-blind, multicentre, therapeutic confirmatory phase 3 clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These results suggest that coadministration of empagliflozin safely improves glycemic control in Korean patients with T2DM uncontrolled by sitagliptin and metformin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417560/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacological inhibition of Ubiquitin-Specific Peptidase 10 (USP10) with spautin-1 attenuates adipogenesis through CCAAT/Enhancer-Binding Protein Beta (C/EBPβ) destabilization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pharmacological control of lipid accumulation in white adipose tissue (WAT) is a key area of focus in obesity research, yet the role of deubiquitination in adipocyte lipid storage remains underexplored. We found that spautin-1, an inhibitor of the deubiquitinases ubiquitin-specific peptidase 10 (USP10) and 13 (USP13), suppressed lipid accumulation during adipogenesis. Therefore, we investigated whether blocking deubiquitination restricts adipogenesis and acts as the underlying mechanism....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41417444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251220142114&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>