<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 07:38:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[School adjustment and mental health among adolescents: a network analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: "Anxiety (SCL-5)" plays a central role in the symptom network of school adjustment and mental health among adolescents. This study fully capture the complex interactions and networked relationships between these two psychological traits, and suggest potential intervention targets by targeting core and bridge symptoms in the symptom network.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184842/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Secular trends in age at menarche among Han Chinese females in Shanghai: a large-scale community-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184836/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning algorithm for predicting rapid progression of abdominal aortic aneurysm by integrating CT images and clinical features]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) progression carries a significant rupture risk, demanding accurate prediction models beyond traditional methods that rely on limited clinical parameters and often overlook complex factor interplay. We aimed to enhance prediction by developing and validating an end-to-end multi-modal deep learning (DL) model that integrates features extracted using ResNet from computed tomography (CT) images, geometric features derived from radiomics based on CT annotations, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct and residue-free patterning of sub-5 µm CVD monolayer graphene with highly enhanced conductivity and pattern fidelity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional photolithography-based patterning of monolayer graphene inevitably causes delamination and contamination when fabricating sub-5 μm patterns, rendering electrical characterization impossible. Here, we develop a one-step free patterning of graphene (OFP-G) method, which selectively converts C = C/C-C bonds into C-O bonds, enabling robust micro-sized pattern fabrication without delamination. OFP-G achieves intact 5 μm and 20 μm-wide patterns with resistances of 11.5 ± 2.8 Ω and 9.4 ±...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Collagen I is the effective therapeutic target for treating desmoid tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Desmoid tumors, known as aggressive fibromatosis, are derived from connective tissues, and local invasion is usually observed. Despite intensive efforts have been performed to investigate the novel anticancer agents in desmoid tumors, effective clinical management for treating desmoid tumors has not been developed yet. Additionally, the molecular mechanisms involved in the tumorigenesis of desmoid tumors have not been elucidated. In this study, given the frequent mutations of Wnt components and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting PGC-1α by miRNA-374 Simultaneously Improve β-Cell Dysfunction and Suppress Hepatic Glucose Overproduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Based on these findings, we propose that Ex-4-CCL-miR-374 as a promising therapeutic approach to reverse β-cell dysfunction and improve hepatic insulin resistance in type 2 diabetes mellitus.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183804/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Untargeted Serum Metabolomic Profiling Reveals Metabolic Inflammation Induced by <em>Stutzerimonas stutzeri</em> PM101005 Isolated from Atmospheric Particulate Matter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Particulate matter (PM), a major pollutant of air pollution, contains a complex mixture of chemical and biological elements that pose significant threats to human health. Among the biological components, Stutzerimonas stutzeri PM101005 (PMSS), a bacterium isolated from fine dust, has been identified as a contributor to respiratory damage through inflammation. However, the mechanisms underlying its pathogenicity, particularly in comparison to environmental strains such as S. stutzeri (SS), remain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synovial exosomal type II collagen as a biomarker for osteoarthritis Progression: From molecular evaluation to AI-powered SERS-based diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoarthritis (OA) is a degenerative joint disease which lacks reliable biomarkers for monitoring disease progression. Current assessment methods rely primarily on radiographic Kellgren-Lawrence (K-L) grading and symptom-based scores, which often show poor concordance with underlying molecular changes. Here, we present a label-free diagnostic strategy for classifying OA severity based on type II collagen in synovial exosomes, using surface-enhanced Raman spectroscopy (SERS). Exosomal surface...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Capillary-Driven Plastic Deformation in Silver Nanowires: Finite Element Analysis of Size-Dependent Mechanics and Contact Behaviours]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Capillary forces, arising from surface tension and wetting interactions, play a crucial role in nanoscale material behavior, particularly during solvent evaporation in nanowire-based systems. In this study, capillary-induced deformation in silver nanowires is analysed through a simplified two-step finite element model using ANSYS Static. The effects of these forces during the film formation and moisture treatment stages are investigated for silver nanowires with diameters of 25 nm, 40 nm, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183398/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicted molecules followed by experimental validation for protecting human neurons from oxidative stress-induced cytotoxicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer neurodegenerative disease (AD) has had a major impact worldwide, with no effective drugs for treatment. We discovered and reported earlier that neurotrophic factor-α1 (NF-α1)/carboxypeptidase E (CPE) reversed neurodegeneration and cognitive dysfunction in AD mouse models. We then predicted computationally and validated experimentally that CPE interacts with a pharmacophore of six residues on the 5-HT1E receptor (HTR1E) to activate the ERK-BCL2 signaling pathway leading to protection of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183202/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global diversification of coastal Cafius rove beetles (Coleoptera: Staphylinidae) driven by ocean currents since the early Miocene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As our understanding of abiotic factors continues to grow, along with insights into the biological traits of organisms, so too does the sophistication of studies exploring global diversification and spatio-temporal distribution patterns. The global distribution of coastal Cafius rove beetles, combined with the endemic distribution patterns observed in its subclades, suggests repeated colonization of new regions via ocean surface currents, followed by local diversification and speciation. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myopic Shift Induced by Omidenepag Isopropyl 0.002% in Patients with Primary Open-Angle Glaucoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: OMDI 0.002% eyedrops were associated with a notable incidence of myopic shift in patients with POAG. Ciliary muscle spasm is a possible underlying mechanism of myopic shift.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182070/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Copper-Catalyzed Enantioselective Synthesis of <em>N</em>-Heterocycle-Substituted Quaternary Carbon Stereogenic Centers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The enantioselective construction of all-carbon quaternary stereogenic centers adjacent to N-heterocycles remains a long-standing challenge in asymmetric catalysis. Herein we report a copper-catalyzed enantioselective hydropyridylation of 1,1-disubstituted allenes with 2-halopyridines that proceeds via a nucleophilic aromatic substitution (S(N)Ar) pathway. This transformation enables the efficient synthesis of α-quaternary N-heterocyclic compounds with a broad substrate scope in high yields (up...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Halogenases and dehalogenases: mechanisms, engineering, and applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Halogenated organic compounds (HOCs) are essential building blocks in pharmaceuticals, agrochemicals, and advanced materials. However, their conventional chemical synthesis often relies on hazardous reagents and generates significant environmental waste. Harnessing nature's solutions, halogenases and dehalogenases offer selective, eco-friendly alternatives for the biosynthesis and degradation of HOCs. Halogenases, including electrophilic (e.g., haloperoxidases, flavin-dependent), radical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181914/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nurses' perceptions of shared decision-making with older adults using home care services in South Korea: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Results highlighted the need for support for nurses to address the difficulties faced by older adults in making healthcare-related decisions about their place of residence and indicated comparable involvement in SDM between nurses working in long-term care centres and hospital home visiting centres.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NRF2 Activation Suppressed Methylglyoxal-Lysine Dimer-Induced Oxidative Stress and Inflammatory Paracrine Interaction between Macrophages and Adipocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macrophage infiltration is closely associated with adipocyte-related inflammatory response in obesity. In this study, we explored methylglyoxal-lysine dimer (MOLD)-induced inflammatory responses and metabolic disorders during macrophage and adipocyte interactions using an in vitro conditioned co-culture medium-based. MOLD significantly increased the levels of advanced glycation end products (AGEs) and receptor for AGEs and induced the levels of nitric oxide and prostaglandin E2 in RAW 264.7...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Cinnamomum longepetiolatum</em> (Kosterm.) Extract Modulates Inflammatory Responses and Oxidative Stress in Lipopolysaccharide-Stimulated RAW 264.7 Macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although inflammation is a protective response to maintain homeostasis, chronic or excessive inflammation is closely associated with various pathological conditions, including autoimmune diseases, cancer, and chronic inflammatory disorders. Therefore, the present study aimed to evaluate the anti-inflammatory activity of Cinnamomum longepetiolatum (Kosterm.), a medicinal plant from Vietnam, at the cellular level. Although C. longepetiolatum is widely used in traditional medicine, its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesized Depside Molecules Suppress the Progression of Colorectal Cancer by Binding VDAC1/PHB/MMP9 Being at the Crossroads of Stemness, Motility, Apoptosis, and Metabolism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lichen secondary metabolites have shown potential in cancer therapy, but strategies to enhance cancer-specific selectivity are needed. Here, we synthesized depside compounds structurally related to tumidulin (TU) and diffractaic acid (DA) and screened them in vitro, identifying SB4 and SB5 as potent hits. Affinity-based proteomics revealed direct binding to voltage-dependent anion channel 1 (VDAC1), prohibitin (PHB), and matrix metalloproteinase-9 (MMP9), which regulate cancer stemness,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the Electrochemical Reversibility of Multielectron Redox in s-Tetrazine Derivatives for Large-Capacity Electrode Materials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[1,2,4,5-tetrazine (s-tetrazine) is a promising redox center for organic electrode materials due to its low molecular weight and ability to undergo two-electron redox reactions. However, in practice, the irreversibility of the second-electron transfer has often limited the specific capacities of the s-tetrazine-based electrodes in metal-organic cells. Herein, electrochemically reversible two-electron-transfer processes from the s-tetrazine core are demonstrated by introducing electron-withdrawing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanical Environment Afforded by Engineered Hydrogel Critically Regulates Survival of Neural Stem Cells Transplanted in the Injured Spinal Cord via Piezo1-Mediated Mechanotransduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neural stem cell (NSC) transplantation is a promising therapeutic approach for spinal cord repair, but poor graft survival remains a critical challenge. This work reports that the mechanical properties of the transplantation environment play a crucial role in NSC survival in the injured spinal cord. While this previously developed engineered hydrogel effectively creates extracellular matrix preventing cystic cavity formation, NSCs transplanted as a complex with 10% hydrogel exhibits poor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Practical Guidelines for Smartphone-Based Hearing Aid Application and Personal Sound Amplification Device Usage to Correct Hearing Loss in Korea Based on a Randomized Controlled Trial by the Patient-Centered Clinical Research Coordinating Center]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The prevalence of mild-to-moderate hearing loss is increasing due to noise exposure and an expanding elderly population. Despite the benefits of hearing aids, many individuals avoid them due to cost and incomplete awareness, opting instead for smartphone-based hearing aid applications (SHAAs) and personal sound amplification products (PSAPs). However, these devices are currently lacking official approval for medical use. The study results, together with roundtable discussions organized by the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generality-Driven Optimization of Enantio- and Regioselective Mono-Reduction of 1,2-Dicarbonyls by High-Throughput Experimentation and Machine Learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The longstanding quest for substrate generality stems from the unpredictability of single-model optimization. Leveraging high-throughput experimentation (HTE), we present a practical multi-substrate screening strategy for the general asymmetric mono-reduction of 1,2-dicarbonyls. Quantitative ¹H NMR spectroscopy combined with simultaneous chiral analysis by ^(19)F NMR for pooled crude mixtures accelerated the workflow eightfold. Robust screening of 31 chiral oxazaborolidinium ion (COBI) variants...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178232/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Coupling of Host and Electrolyte Achieving 1270 Wh L<sup>-1</sup> in Anode-Free Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anode-free lithium metal batteries (LMBs) represent a promising avenue for maximizing energy density by eliminating excess lithium (Li), yet their practical implementation is impeded by limited Li reversibility and pronounced interfacial instability. Herein, a synergistic coupling strategy is reported that integrates a highly reversible host (RH) with a rationally designed, carbonate-rich electrolyte (DEL) to concurrently address these fundamental challenges. The RH spontaneously induces the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178147/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring collaborative practice between conventional and Korean medicine: a qualitative study of Korean medicine doctors' experienced barriers and strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Qualitative content analysis of KMD interviews at Korean hospitals explored CPCK processes, identified barriers and facilitators, and examined KMDs' perspectives and attitudes toward collaboration. KMD-only sampling limits generalizability. Nonetheless, by detailing day-to-day CPCK procedures and challenges, the study highlights that true partnership and preservation of professional identity remain major concerns for KMDs striving to advance CPCK. Future studies should include...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184826/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reference values for the PROMIS<sup>®</sup> physical function item bank version 2.0 in the general population: a multinational comparison study (Korea, Netherlands, and US)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Considering the cultural differences between Western and Asian countries, we recommend establishing country-specific reference values on a global scale.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patch-Wise Approach with Vision Transformer for Detecting Implant Failure in Spinal Radiography]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spinal implant failures are becoming more common due to the increasing number of surgeries and an aging population. Early detection is crucial but often missed on radiographs due to subtle features and limited radiologist availability. This study aims to develop and validate a vision transformer-based deep learning model for detecting spinal implant fractures and to assess its impact on radiologist performance. The training and testing datasets included 9924 spinal radiographs (3492 studies)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Amivantamab-Chemotherapy in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer with EGFR Exon 20 Insertions: Impact of Treatment Crossover and Other Endpoints from the Phase III PAPILLON Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In PAPILLON, TTD and TTST were substantially longer for amivantamab-chemotherapy versus chemotherapy at primary analysis (cut-off on 3 May 2023). Crossover-adjusted analyses of the planned interim overall survival demonstrated a greater benefit for amivantamab-chemotherapy versus chemotherapy, further supporting amivantamab-chemotherapy as the first-line standard of care in EGFR exon 20 insertion-mutated non-small cell lung cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experimental study of nose-tip bluntness effects on hypersonic boundary-layer transition in a shock tunnel]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study experimentally investigates the effects of nose-tip bluntness on boundary-layer transition over a 7 ∘ half-angle cone at Mach 6.76, using the Seoul National University Hypersonic Shock Tunnel. Transition characteristics were examined through high-speed schlieren visualization, surface heat flux measurements, and high-frequency surface pressure measurements for varying nose-tip radii (0.1 mm, 1 mm, and 2 mm) and unit Reynolds numbers. Increasing nose-tip bluntness effectively delayed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biogeographic barriers and environmental gradients reveal distribution limits in Hynobius salamanders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the biogeographic barriers and environmental gradients that influence the distribution and niche segregation of seven Hynobius salamander species in South Korea. Using Ecological Niche Models (ENMs) developed with the Maxent software and 48 environmental variables, we conducted four niche overlap tests for each species pair: niche identity tests and background similarity tests to assess niche differentiation, lineage-breaking tests to evaluate species boundaries in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of infectious disease specialist consultations on antibiotic treatment and outcomes of fracture-related infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The management of fracture-related infections (FRIs) is complex and requires collaboration among various specialists, including trauma and orthopedic surgeons, infectious disease (ID) specialists, and microbiologists. This study aimed to investigate the effects of ID consultations on antibiotic treatment and FRI outcomes. We conducted a retrospective chart review of data from adult patients with microbiologically diagnosed FRIs at a tertiary care hospital. In total, 123 patients with FRIs were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shear bond strength of zirconia orthodontic brackets depending on surface pretreatment of bonding base]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated the shear bond strength (SBS) of zirconia orthodontic brackets under different surface pretreatment protocols to identify an optimal bonding strategy for clinical applications. Zirconia brackets (n = 94) were fabricated using 3 mol% yttria-stabilized zirconia powder and a ceramic injection molding technique. The bracket base was treated using one of the following: no treatment (Control), traditional alumina sandblasting (Group I), traditional alumina sandblasting with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AI-powered spatial cell phenomics enhances risk stratification in non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Risk stratification remains a critical challenge in non-small cell lung cancer patients for optimal therapy selection. In this study, we develop an artificial intelligence-powered spatial cellomics approach that combines histology, multiplex immunofluorescence imaging and multimodal machine learning to characterize the complex cellular relationships of 43 cell phenotypes in the tumor microenvironment in a real-world retrospective cohort of 1168 non-small cell lung cancer patients from two large...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeting cancer glutamine dependency with a first-in-class inhibitor of the mitochondrial glutamine transporter SLC1A5_var]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mitochondrial glutamine transporter SLC1A5_var plays a central role in the metabolic reprogramming of cancer cells by facilitating glutamine import into mitochondria for energy production and redox homeostasis. Despite its critical function, the development of effective and selective inhibitors targeting SLC1A5_var has remained a significant challenge. Here, we introduce iMQT_020, a selective allosteric inhibitor identified through structure-based screening. iMQT_020 disrupts the trimeric...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[FBXW7-mediated CHK2 regulation modulates DNA damage response and cellular stability in Huntington's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA damage activates the DNA damage response (DDR) machinery. However, aging impairs DDR in neurons, thereby increasing susceptibility to neurodegenerative diseases, such as Huntington's disease (HD). The mutant huntingtin (mHTT) protein interferes with DNA repair, leading to DNA lesions and a feedback loop of cellular stress that accelerates neurodegeneration. Although the individual roles of FBXW7, ATM, and checkpoint kinase (CHK) are well-known in DDR, their combined roles in HD remain...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrating a new chapter in international collaboration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184205/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kinetics Control of Mithrene Formation in a High-Pressure Inert Environment: A Robust Solvent-Free Route to Superior-Quality Films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metal organic chalcogenolates (MOCs) constitute a promising class of materials for optoelectronic applications owing to their unique 2D layered hybrid structure and inherent environmental stability. Among these materials, mithrene (silver phenylselenolate, AgSePh) is particularly compelling because of its sharp blue emission and notable anisotropic excitonic properties. However, conventional solvent-assisted mithrene synthesis methods are often associated with the introduction of chemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KIST, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SHPro<sup>®</sup> (mixture of <em>Angelica gigas</em> and <em>Astragalus membranaceus</em>) in men with lower urinary tract symptoms: A randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled clinical trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: After taking the trial product (SHPro^(®)) for 12 weeks, the total and incomplete emptying IPSS improved, as did the IIEF, which indicated subjective improvements. And its safety was confirmed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Descriptive analysis of initial experience with partial nephrectomy and retroperitoneal organ surgery using supine anterior retroperitoneal approach with the da Vinci SP robotic system: Pilot cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The SARA technique using the da Vinci SP robotic system is a safe and feasible approach for PN and various retroperitoneal procedures. It allows for minimal invasiveness, low complication rates, and rapid recovery. Further studies are needed to validate these findings and define the learning curve.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The staging of re-TURB is crucial in predicting the response to BCG therapy in patients with T1 high-grade bladder cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The pathological results of re-TURB play a critical role in determining the BCG response in patients with T1 high-grade bladder cancer.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low minimal alveolar concentration general anesthesia for pain control in percutaneous radiofrequency ablation: Influence on long-term outcomes of renal cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Low-MAC general anesthesia during RFA procedures is appropriate for precise RCC targeting. This type of pain control could influence the long-term outcomes of RCC patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic Mastectomy: A Cost-Effective and Time-Efficient Alternative to Robotic Mastectomy With Comparable Oncologic and Safety Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EM is a more time-efficient and cost-effective surgical technique than RM. Our findings indicate no significant safety advantage of RM over EM, highlighting the need for individualized surgical decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183868/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oncologic Outcome of Immediate Breast Reconstruction Following Mastectomy in Patients With Ipsilateral Breast Tumor Recurrence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results suggest that IBR after TM is a feasible treatment option for patients with IBTR from a prognostic perspective. Nonetheless, the selection of suitable candidates is crucial, considering the observed increase in complications and potential biases inherent in this study.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concomitant Ablation of Atrial Fibrillation in Redo Heart Valve Surgery]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Concomitant AF ablation during redo valve surgery was associated with improved rhythm outcomes, survival, and freedom from thromboembolic events, supporting its consideration as a reasonable option even in this high-risk group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in General Thoracic Surgery Volume during the Medical-Political Conflict in South Korea by Institutional Type and Surgical Complexity: An Analysis of National Health Insurance Claims]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The 2024 healthcare crisis caused significant disruption to surgical capacity in South Korea. Although some redistribution occurred, the government's reallocation strategy did not fully achieve its intended goals. Recovery of pre-crisis surgical capacity, especially for high-complexity procedures, remains incomplete.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183856/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commentary: Revisiting the Radiation Dose in Neoadjuvant Therapy for Esophageal Cancer: Insights from a High-Dose Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commentary: Prognostic Implications of <em>EGFR</em> Exon 20 Insertions in Resected Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183854/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating Treatment Response Thresholds for Cost-Effective Treatment in Metabolic-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Long-term sustained durability of the hypothetical drug, patient distribution based on baseline fibrosis stage, as well as initial treatment response rate are key factors that influence the cost-effectiveness of new MASLD drugs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183809/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a RuHAP-Packed-Bed Reactor for Continuous Flow Aerobic Oxidation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aerobic oxidation of alcohols is valuable but often limited by toxic reagents, waste, and harsh conditions. Using a Ru^(3+)-hydroxyapatite (RuHAP)-packed-bed reactor under low-pressure O(2), we achieved efficient, reproducible oxidations with TONs of >18,000 after two catalyst regenerations. A two-step continuous flow process integrating oxidation and Knoevenagel condensation delivered products in excellent yields, demonstrating a scalable, safe, and sustainable method with high selectivity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to: Gut Microbiome-Based Strategies for the Control of Carbapenem-Resistant Enterobacteriaceae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ruptured Internal Mammary Artery Aneurysm in Marfan Syndrome with Hemothorax: Concomitant Aneurysmal Involvement of Multiple Medium-Sized Arteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183776/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of novel indoline derivatives as potent small molecule PD-L1 inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The immune system plays a critical role in cancer control, but tumor cells often evade immune responses by exploiting inhibitory molecules like PD-1/PD-L1. Monoclonal antibodies targeting PD-1/PD-L1 interaction blockade have shown remarkable success in reactivating T-cell function in various advanced cancers, but they face limitations such as long half-life and immune-related adverse events (irAEs). In this study, we identified a new class of indoline-based scaffold through molecular docking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Impact of Ultra-Processed Food Intake and Genetic Predisposition on Psychological Well-being in a General Adult Cohort with Cancer Subgroups: The KoGES Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both high UPF intake and a genetic predisposition to it are independently associated with increased psychological distress in a general adult cohort, with subgroup analyses for incident and persistent cancer cases. These associations vary by cancer type and status, highlighting the need for personalized nutritional and psycho-oncological interventions to improve quality of life in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183613/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of climate change anxiety and environmental sustainability attitudes on pro-environmental behaviors among nursing students: A cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher environmental sustainability attitudes and lower levels of cognitive anxiety are associated with an increase in pro-environmental behaviors. To boost such behaviors among nursing students, enhancing environmental sustainability attitudes and effectively managing climate change anxiety, specifically cognitive impairment, are essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Path Analysis of Career Decision-Making Among Nursing Students: A Descriptive Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Career decision-making self-efficacy and nursing competence are crucial factors in nursing students' career decisions. The proposed model provides a foundation for developing strategies to enhance nursing students' career decision-making. Nursing educators and institutions can use this model to design and implement a tailored career education curriculum that empowers nursing students to manage and advance their careers effectively.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PSYCHOMETRIC PROPERTIES OF THE KOREAN VERSION OF THE ADVANCE CARE PLANNING ENGAGEMENT SURVEY]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Korean version of the Advance Care Planning Engagement Survey demonstrated strong validity and reliability in assessing advance care planning engagement within the Korean context. By reflecting cultural nuances, this instrument supports cross-cultural comparisons and contributes to evidence-based end-of-life care policies. It also aligns with global healthcare needs, facilitating culturally informed research and enhancing patient-centered care. Additionally, it aids in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An in situ immunogenicity-amplifying payload delivery system for immunotherapy of Kirsten rat sarcoma viral oncogene homolog-mutant cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Kirsten rat sarcoma virus (KRAS)-mutant colorectal cancer remains a major clinical challenge due to its resistance to conventional therapies and an immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment (TME) that limits immunotherapy efficacy. To overcome these barriers, we have engineered MPD1, designed to execute a precise, multi-stage attack. MPD1 features a dual-action mechanism: an albumin-binding moiety hijacks the intrinsically high macropinocytosis rates of KRAS-mutant cells for selective uptake,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial Clusters of Condyloma Acuminata and the Regional Risk Factors in South Korea: Bayesian Spatial Regression Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We identified significant geographic hotspots of CA and several community-level risk factors driving these patterns in South Korea. These findings highlight the importance of spatial surveillance and targeted public health interventions in high-risk areas. Adapting STI prevention programs to address local social determinants may help reduce the spread of CA in the identified hotspots.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183243/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Posterior Cruciate Ligament (PCL) Versus Combined PCL and Posterolateral Corner Reconstruction in Isolated PCL Grade-III Injuries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with an isolated grade-III PCL injury who underwent isolated PCL reconstruction showed significant improvements in subjective and objective outcomes. No significant difference was observed between patients who underwent isolated PCL reconstruction and those who underwent combined PCL and PLC reconstruction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of volumetric responses to different corticosteroid administration methods in IgG4-related ophthalmic disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Compared with oral Pd, IV methylPd yielded better and more sustained radiological responses in patients with LG-involving IgG4-ROD. Local TA injection was also an effective alternative treatment option.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Burden of Central Nervous System Cancer in the United States, 1990-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: These findings provide valuable insights into the CNS cancer burden across the US by age, sex, location, and SDI, enabling better public health status assessments, health care policy restructuring, and resource redistribution for improved care.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparisons of optical characteristics between 3D printed dental resins and resin composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE: To compare the optical characteristics of 3D-printed resins and conventional resin composites, focusing on color differences, whiteness index, and translucency under varying specimen thicknesses and polishing conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182710/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Stratification Strategies and Implementation of Exercise Training in Patients with Multiple Myeloma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: This review aims to explore key clinical considerations for prescribing exercise in individuals with multiple myeloma (MM) and to evaluate current evidence to develop exercise regimens that prioritize both safety and efficacy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182654/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors and Incidence of Reoperation in Direct-to-Implant Breast Reconstruction Surgery Among Patients with Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In patients with breast cancer undergoing DTI reconstruction, age, radiotherapy, and lymphedema were significant risk factors for capsular contracture. These findings highlight the importance of individualized preoperative planning and counseling to reduce the risk and improve outcomes. Further research should focus on developing strategies to manage these identified risk factors and prevent capsular contracture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor microenvironment remodeling across thyroid cancer differentiation states revealed by spatial transcriptomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that dedifferentiation in thyroid cancer is associated with an immunosuppressive TME that promotes tumor progression. Therapeutic strategies targeting JAK-STAT and VEGF pathways, or enhancing NK cell activity, may hold promises for aggressive thyroid cancers. Further studies with larger cohorts are necessary to validate these findings and develop targeted therapies for aggressive thyroid cancers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transitions into and out of child maltreatment: differential effects on depressive symptoms and gender differences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite well-established evidence on the mental health consequences of child maltreatment, prior research is limited by the assumption that changes in maltreatment status have symmetrical impacts. This study investigated the association between child maltreatment and depressive symptoms, distinguishing transitions into and out of abuse and neglect. Potential gender differences were also examined. This study used six waves of longitudinal data from the nationally representative Korean Children...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182375/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Swept-source optical coherence tomography analysis of retinal and choroidal structures in school-aged children after laser photocoagulation for type 1 retinopathy of prematurity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: School-aged children treated with laser photocoagulation for ROP showed increased retinal vascular tortuosity and thickness in the central foveal to parafoveal regions, while choroidal thickness and vascularity remained unchanged in the central 1500 μm zone on SS-OCT device. These findings suggest localized retinal changes with preserved choroidal integrity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182356/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence in Acupuncture: Recommendations from the Society for Acupuncture Research Special Interest Group Artificial Intelligence and Digital Health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Cognitive Trajectories in Isolated REM Sleep Behavior Disorder: Effects of Sex and Longstanding Disease Duration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Gradual cognitive decline in attention/working memory and memory may represent a natural course of neurodegeneration in men with iRBD, without necessarily indicating imminent phenoconversion. Women with iRBD appeared to show greater resilience to cognitive decline compared to men.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182247/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving falsely elevated vancomycin levels in KIMS immunoassay due to monoclonal IgM interference]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given its narrow therapeutic index and risk of nephrotoxicity, vancomycin requires accurate concentration monitoring. While immunoassays such as the Kinetic Interaction of Microparticles in Solution (KIMS) are widely used for their speed and simplicity, they are susceptible to interference by paraproteins such as monoclonal immunoglobulins. Here, we present the first case of falsely elevated vancomycin concentrations measured by KIMS due to monoclonal IgM interference, indicated by a 'kinetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182036/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A systematic review of psychological difficulties among elite sports coaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This systematic review examined the psychological difficulties experienced by elite sports coaches, focusing on their causes, consequences, and potential interventions. Despite increasing recognition of the challenges faced by coaches, limited attention has been paid to understanding their psychological difficulties and available support systems.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The association between the adenoid microbiome and chronic otitis media with effusion in children differs according to age]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Chronic otitis media with effusion (COME) can adversely affect childhood development, and while the adenoid has been considered a reservoir for bacterial pathogens contributing to the pathogenesis of COME, the role of the adenoid microbiome in COME remains unclear. This study analyzed both the adenoid and gut microbiome in children with and without COME to identify their potential roles in the disease's pathogenesis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum NOTCH3 Extracellular Domain in Patients With CADASIL]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Cerebral autosomal dominant arteriopathy with subcortical infarcts and leukoencephalopathy (CADASIL) is a hereditary small vessel disease caused by variants in the NOTCH3 gene. The extracellular domain of NOTCH3 (N3ECD) has been proposed as a potential serum biomarker for CADASIL. However, its diagnostic utility remains uncertain. The aim of this study was to evaluate serum N3ECD levels in patients with CADASIL and assess their potential as a diagnostic or prognostic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gradient mesoporosity in hierarchical ZIF-8 by temperature-modulated soft-templating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Engineering hierarchical porosity in metal-organic frameworks (MOFs) is critical for improving mass transport and expanding their utility in catalysis, separation, and adsorption. We report a temperature-controlled soft-templating method for precise tuning of mesopore size in zeolitic imidazolate framework-8 (ZIF-8), employing a single amphiphilic block copolymer as the structure-directing agent. Systematic variation of the synthesis temperature yields a distinctive gradient mesoporous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181224/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A20 mRNA therapeutics ameliorate systemic sclerosis by suppressing TRAF-6/NF-KB signaling and DREAM expression and exerting antifibrotic effects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Systemic sclerosis (SSc) is a chronic autoimmune disorder characterized by progressive fibrosis, vascular abnormalities, and immune dysregulation. Decreased expression of A20 (TNFAIP3), a key negative regulator of inflammation, has been shown to aggravate SSc pathogenesis by enhancing fibroblast activation and promoting collagen production. This study explores the therapeutic efficacy of A20 mRNA-lipid nanoparticle (LNP) delivery in restoring A20 expression and mitigating fibrosis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Serum gamma-glutamyl transferase level is associated with the risk of pancreatic cystic neoplasms: A nationwide retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Higher GGT level is associated with increased risk of PCNs. Therefore, serum GGT levels might have a role as a biomarker for the development of PCNs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Isatuximab in combination with chemotherapy for pediatric patients with relapsed/refractory acute lymphoblastic leukemia or acute myeloid leukemia: The ISAKIDS study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children with relapsed acute leukemia have a poor prognosis; current relapse treatments are toxic, and novel treatments are needed. The anti-CD38 antibody isatuximab is approved for relapsed-refractory multiple myeloma in adults. We present results of the ISAKIDS study (NCT03860844) investigating isatuximab in children with relapsed-refractory acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL) or acute myeloid leukemia (AML). This Phase 2, single-arm, multicenter, open-label study enrolled children aged 28 days...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential effects of physical activity on behavioral and prefrontal responses during repetitive inhibitory control in older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Regular physical activity may enhance cognitive adaptability and selective inhibition in older adults. Behavioral improvements were more evident than neural differences between the groups, highlighting the potential of everyday physical activity to support cognitive resilience in aging. This study provides neurophysiological evidence supporting the integration of physical activity into cognitive intervention strategies for older populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood Pressure Reduction During Anesthetic Induction with Remimazolam versus Propofol in Elderly Patients: Pharmacodynamic Modeling of Remimazolam]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In elderly patients undergoing general anesthesia with remimazolam, the relationship between dose and MBP reduction during induction was well characterized using a modified logistic model, with body weight as a significant covariate. TCI may represent an effective dosing strategy for maintaining hemodynamic stability during anesthetic induction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PKPy: a Python-based framework for automated population pharmacokinetic analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present PKPy, an open-source Python framework designed to automate population pharmacokinetic analysis workflows. The framework emphasizes user accessibility by minimizing the need for manual parameter initialization while maintaining analytical rigor. PKPy implements both one-compartment and two-compartment pharmacokinetic models (with and without first-order absorption) with integrated capabilities for parameter estimation, covariate analysis, and comprehensive diagnostics. The framework's...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of predictive and evaluation models for the retro reflectivity performance of pavement lane markings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The developed models are expected to assist in establishing maintenance plans, formulating budgets, and determining repair work, as well as developing relevant regulations and standards in Seoul.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180450/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Osseointegration properties of niobia-modified yttria-stabilized zirconia implant surface: an <em>in vivo</em> study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sandblasted (Y,Nb)-TZP implants indicated superior osseointegration in comparison to SLA titanium and smooth-surface 3D-printed 3Y-TZP implants. The enhanced osseointegration observed in this study supports the clinical potential of (Y,Nb)-TZP as a next-generation zirconia implant material.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the accuracy of removable partial denture frameworks fabricated using conventional and digital impressions: a clinical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Clinically acceptable RPD framework accuracy was achieved in both groups. However, accuracy was significantly better in the IOS group, especially at the terminal abutments of distal-extension RPDs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180327/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparing impression techniques in the prosthodontic treatment for edentulous patients: a 3D finite element analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Selective pressure trays modified tissue loading locally at the relief site; however, these did not seem to provide a substantial biomechanical advantage, particularly on bone. Their clinical relevance remains limited and needs further supporting evidence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International Statistical Classification of Diseases and data gaps in traditional medicine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of Modified High-Performance Ion Chromatography Analytical Method for Inositol Phosphates in Soybeans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Phosphorus in the form of phytic acid or myo-inositol hexakisphosphate is not absorbable by animals, leading to decreased bioavailability of essential minerals such as iron, zinc, and calcium. This study aimed to develop and validate a simple and efficient method for measuring inositol phosphates in soybeans. The four types of inositol phosphates analyzed were D-myo-inositol-1,5,6-triphosphate, D-myo-inositol-1,4,5,6-tetraphosphate, D-myo-inositol-1,3,4,5,6-pentaphosphate, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180089/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of <em>Levilactobacillus brevis</em> KU15159 on Intestinal Function and Bowel Activity in Loperamide-Induced Constipation in Sprague-Dawley Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Constipation is one of the most common gastrointestinal disorders, with an increasing prevalence. Lactic acid bacteria are known to improve the colon microenvironment; however, the ameliorative effect of Levilactobacillus brevis KU15159 on constipation has not been examined. This study aimed to investigate the effects of L. brevis KU15159 administration on improving intestinal function and defecation activity in an animal model of loperamide-induced constipation. Six-week-old Sprague-Dawley rats...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recognizing emotions in music through a computerized method: a novel way of evaluating social maturity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This study used music emotion recognition to evaluate emotion perception and aimed to explore the relationship between social maturity and musical emotion recognition in both autism spectrum disorder (ASD) and controls groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Costs and cost-effectiveness of robotic-assisted surgery in South Korea: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This is the first comprehensive systematic review and meta-analysis specifically assessing the economic implications of RAS in Korea. Our findings indicate that RAS is more costly than other surgical modalities at the time of surgery. However, the current review identified a lack of evidence on post-discharge costs, and no comprehensive cost-effectiveness or cost-utility analyses have been conducted in Korea. Future studies are encouraging to explore the long-term costs across...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preliminary Study on Host Use and Phylogenetic Analysis of <em>Corethrella nippon</em> in Taiwan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated frog-biting dipteran species using newly designed frog-calling traps in Taiwan. The trap effectively collected specimens from both families, Culicidae and Corethrellidae, demonstrating its utility. Host preference analysis revealed that Odorrana swinhoana (Boulenger, 1903) and Kurixalus eiffingeri (Boettger, 1895) were most frequently associated with collected specimens of Corethrellidae. Additionally, the corethrellids were predominantly attracted to a sound frequency...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179342/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valorization of Kraft Lignin via Isocyanate Modification for Use in Polylactic Acid Biocomposites with Improved Mechanical and Functional Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study focused on improving the dispersibility and phase compatibility of kraft lignin (KL) with polymeric matrices by introducing hexyl alkane groups onto its surface through urethane bonds, yielding hexyl isocyanate-modified KL (KL-HIC) with an 82% degree of substitution (DS). The chemically modified lignin was characterized by Fourier transform infrared spectroscopy (FT-IR) and nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR). This modification enhanced thermoplasticity, decreased the glass transition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A GC-MS-Based Urinary Metabolomic Profiling to Identify Potential Biomarkers of Metabolic Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic syndrome (MetS) is a multifactorial condition characterized by central obesity, dyslipidemia, hypertension, and insulin resistance, increasing the risk of cardiovascular disease and type 2 diabetes. Despite its clinical significance, current diagnostic methods rely on invasive blood-based assessments. This study investigates the potential of urinary metabolomics as a noninvasive alternative for MetS diagnosis. Using gas chromatography-mass spectrometry (GC-MS), we analyzed urinary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41179179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Additive renoprotective effects of oral calcitriol on patients with IgA nephropathy receiving RAS blockers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The addition of 0.25 μg/day calcitriol to RASBs safely lowered residual proteinuria and slowed the eGFR decline in patients with IgAN, suggesting a potential therapeutic role for calcitriol in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Integration of Frequency-Dependent Impedance and Machine Learning in Semiconductor Metal Oxide-Based Breath Sensors for High-Performance Gas Discrimination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Frequency-dependent impedance spectroscopy in combination with machine learning offers a powerful strategy for discriminating among gas species using mutually interacting semiconductor metal oxide (SMO) gas sensors. In this study, 0.3 at% platinum-loaded SnO(2) sensing materials were employed to breath-based disease detection, with a focus on machine learning-assisted discrimination of mixtures of acetone (0.5-2.5 ppm) and ethanol (0.5-2.5 ppm) under both dry and humid environments (80% relative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Brain Variability in Recent-Onset and Chronic Schizophrenia: Evidence from Person-Based Similarity Index Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients with schizophrenia show marked structural brain heterogeneity compared with healthy controls, which is detectable even in the early stages of the illness. Although there were few differences in PBSI scores between the recent-onset and chronic schizophrenia groups and limited correlations between PBSI scores and clinical measures, the PBSI may still provide valuable insights into individual differences contributing to clinical heterogeneity in schizophrenia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolution of Newcastle Disease Virus Subgenotype VII.1.1 in Iran, 2017-2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Newcastle disease (ND), caused by Newcastle disease virus (NDV), has posed a continuous threat to Iran's poultry industry since its first detection in the early 1950s, with subgenotype VII.1.1 currently recognized as the dominant circulating strain. To gain deeper insights into the evolutionary dynamics of NDV in Iran, we performed genome sequencing and phylogenetic analysis on 60 viruses isolated from domestic poultry and wild birds between 2017 and 2024. Maximum likelihood and Bayesian...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superior affinity of ubiquicidin peptide united with <em>ortho</em>-borylated acetophenone to an amine-containing model bacterial membrane]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) have been considered as potential agents to combat bacterial resistance to conventional antibiotics. It has been shown that modifying the cationic peptides with 2-acetylphenylboronic acid (2-APBA) improves the binding efficacy with these resistant bacterial membranes via the formation of a covalent iminoboronate bond with lipids, such as 1,2-dioleoyl-sn-glycero-3-[phospho-rac-(3-lysyl(1-glycerol))] (Lys PG). In the present study, the cationic peptide UBI (29-41) is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of consultation-based hospice palliative care team on self-determination respect rates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVES: Despite the increasing implementation of consultation-based hospice palliative care teams in tertiary hospitals of Korea, there is limited research on their impact on self-determination respect rates. Understanding this impact is crucial for improving end-of-life care practices and respecting patient autonomy. The aim of this study is to assess the trends in self-determination respect rates regarding advance care planning before and after the introduction of a consultation-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rare Clinical Presentation of Diffuse Large B-Cell Lymphoma as Otitis Media and Mastoiditis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lymphomas originating in the ear are extremely rare. As with other malignancies of the temporal bone, diagnosis of lymphoma in the middle ear and temporal bone is often delayed, negatively impacting treatment and prognosis. The delay in diagnosis is primarily due to its clinical presentation overlapping with benign infectious conditions of the middle ear. Here, we present a rare case of a 46-year-old woman with prolonged otorrhea, hearing disturbances, intermittent vertigo, and headache. She...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178480/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility of Minimal Inverted-J Incision for Bone-Anchored Hearing Aid Attract Implantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our novel incision technique for BAHA Attract implantation addresses the limitations associated with both the classical and minimal linear incision approaches.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178479/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polarity-Controlled Volatile HfO<sub>2</sub> Memristors with Bimodal Conductance for Neuromorphic Synapses and Reservoir Computing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this work, an HfO(2)-based memristor exhibiting bimodal switching, wherein the device's conductance is modulated not only by the input stimulus but also by the polarity of the read voltage, is introduced. Uniquely, this device demonstrates reliable short-term memory (STM)-like behavior and supports 16 well-separated conductance states through 4-bit pulsed inputs. Remarkably, under the same input conditions, reversing the polarity of the read voltage results in 16 more different conductance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Complementary Multi-Resonance Thermally Activated Delayed Fluorescence Design for Blue OLEDs Beyond the Concentration Limit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advances in boron-based organic compounds exhibiting multi-resonance (MR)-type thermally activated delayed fluorescence (TADF) have been primarily driven by their potential as narrowband blue emitters for wide-gamut display applications. Nevertheless, the intrinsically planar architecture of MR-type TADF molecules often leads to pronounced concentration quenching at elevated doping levels, posing a significant impediment to realizing highly efficient organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Purity Single Photon Extraction from Diamond Nitrogen-Vacancy Centers in Low-Numerical-Aperture Optical Systems via Defect-Selective Metalens Printing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid-state quantum emitters, such as nitrogen-vacancy (NV) centers in diamond, offer a promising route toward scalable quantum technologies. However, their random spatial distribution and inherently broad dipole emission severely hinder high-purity single-photon extraction-particularly in low-numerical-aperture (NA) optical systems, which are essential for compact and scalable quantum photonic systems. Here, a defect-selective metalens integration approach is presented that allows precise and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent Progress of Vanadium Oxide and its Hybrid Composites-Based Electrochromic Supercapacitors: An Advanced Future Energy Storage Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supercapacitors with integrated electrochromic functionality, capable of changing color in response to stored energy levels, represent a promising and emerging technology. These multifunctional devices offer simultaneous energy storage and real-time visual feedback through dynamic color modulation, making them particularly appealing for modern digital applications. When integrated into smart windows, they can contribute to energy savings by reducing the need for artificial heating and cooling....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178229/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in Smoking Status in Depressed Patients and the Risk of Dementia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Changes in smoking behavior after depression diagnosis influence dementia risk, underscoring the need for cessation strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Forensic detection of medical image manipulation using PACS and DICOM artifacts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the digitization of medical information, illegal activities such as medical crimes and insurance fraud through tampering have increased. Medical images are particularly vulnerable due to their nature as soft copies and their transmission over networks. National research institutions such as NIST provide guidelines that define security control elements for managing medical images, primarily out of concern for system vulnerabilities. However, there is still a lack of established or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phosphate adsorption by poultry manure biochar impregnated with different sources of magnesium]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rise in fertilizer prices and decline in fertilizer availability have prompted concerns about the sustainability and equity of fertilizer use. Utilizing P‑rich feedstocks for biochar production and further enriching them with P recovered from wastewater has the potential to transform conventional industrial P fertilizers. We explored different sources and levels of Mg as impregnation materials for poultry manure biochar production to optimize the retention of dissolved inorganic phosphate....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178117/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of suicide in cancer patients: nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In cancer patients, suicide risk remained elevated for several years after diagnosis, but decreased over time and became similar to that of matched controls after 5 years. However, the temporal pattern varied by cancer type, and suicide risk remained high for patients with haematological cancers. Suicide risk screening is necessary from the time of cancer diagnosis, even in long-term survivors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying overtraining biomarkers through proteomic analysis of extracellular vesicles derived from the central nervous system of male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Overtraining, which results in central nervous system (CNS)-fatigue-related symptoms, leads to a long-term decline in performance. This study investigated CNS-derived EV protein content under overtraining conditions to identify potential biomarkers. Eight-week-old C57BL/6J mice were randomly divided into three groups: sedentary (SED, n = 7), exercise control (EX, n = 8), and overtraining (OT, n = 9) groups. The OT group underwent an 8-week downhill treadmill-based overtraining induction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Skin barrier as a target for the prediction, prevention, and treatment of atopic dermatitis and food allergy in infancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atopic dermatitis (AD) and food allergy (FA) frequently manifest during infancy and share skin barrier dysfunction as a critical early pathogenic event. Recent research has elucidated structural, lipidomic, microbial, and immunologic abnormalities that compromise the skin barrier and contribute to disease onset. Filaggrin gene mutations, altered ceramide profiles, and type 2 cytokine-driven inflammation are among the key factors disrupting epidermal integrity. While AD and FA exhibit overlapping...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41178020/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nanoscale Au-Si eutectic mixtures formed by dewetting of a Au-Ni film on Si<sub>3</sub>N<sub>4</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Formation of a eutectic AuSi compound was observed during the solid state dewetting and agglomeration in a Ni-Au bilayer thin film grown on a Si(3)N(4) substrate using coherent X-ray diffractive imaging, X-ray diffraction, and scanning electron microscopy. During rapid thermal annealing at 850 °C in vacuum, AuNi films first separate into islands that are composed of a mixture of Au-rich and Ni-rich phases. As the dewetting proceeds, Si and nitrogen dissociate due to the catalytic action of Ni,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transforming cell-surface signatures into customizable protein functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineered non-expansive matrix for blood vessel organoid development and ischaemic stroke repair]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The periodontal pathogen Fusobacterium nucleatum is associated with disease severity in multiple sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Increasing evidence suggests that periodontitis may contribute to central nervous system disorders through chronic inflammation, but its role in multiple sclerosis (MS) remains unclear. This exploratory, cross-sectional study investigated the associations between the relative abundance of periodontal pathogens in the oral cavity and the clinical characteristics of MS. We enrolled 98 patients with MS, neuromyelitis optica spectrum disorder, or myelin oligodendrocyte glycoprotein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184431/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased autoantibodies against incretin indicate poor prognosis in patients with diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective cohort study aimed to elucidate the clinical significance of measuring autoantibodies against incretins in diabetes. We enrolled 274 patients with diabetes (mean age ± standard deviation [SD]: 63.1 ± 12.1 years) and 109 healthy controls (mean age: 58.0 ± 5.8 years). Titers of autoantibodies against incretins (glucose-dependent insulinotropic peptide and glucagon-like peptide-1) were measured using an amplified luminescent proximity homogeneous assay-linked immunosorbent assay....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184416/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of multipoint flexible optical probe for intra-abdominal visceral perfusion monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The maintenance of postoperative blood flow is essential to ensure the optimal condition of transplanted organs. Further, early detection of circulatory disturbances is necessary to prevent graft failure, but is complicated by the closed space after surgery. Continuous and prompt inspection of organ blood flow can help to ensure post-operative blood flow monitoring. A recent study described the development of a wearable flexible sensor probe able to measure short-term changes in pulse waves and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184339/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sulphites: Hidden Allergens in Epoxy Resin Products?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184181/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Hidden Sensitising Impurities and Additives in Cosmetic Raw Materials: A Call for Greater Transparency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184179/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safeguarding drug safety in neonates: addressing the impact of in-hospital medication administration errors through prevention and standardization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41184067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the anti-fibrotic potential of a JAK inhibitor in a bleomycin-induced pulmonary fibrosis model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our data suggest that baricitinib may improve pulmonary fibrosis by directly inhibiting fibroblast activation via JAK2 blockade. J. Med. Invest. 72 : 298-307, August, 2025.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183930/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of carriers and pre-dissolved polymers in drug-rich nanodroplet formation during dissolution of amorphous drug formulations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The formation of drug-rich nanodroplets via liquid-liquid phase separation (LLPS) during the dissolution of amorphous drug formulations has recently gained attention as a strategy to enhance the absorption of poorly water-soluble drugs. This study investigates how formulation carriers and pre-dissolved polymers influence drug dissolution behavior and the generation of drug-rich nanodroplets. The felodipine (FEL) dissolution behavior from amorphous FEL, FEL-loaded mesoporous silica (MPS), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183675/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient recombinant protein secretion in Mycobacterium smegmatis: A valuable platform for protein production involved in biomedical development targeting mycobacterial diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mycobacterium smegmatis is often used as a host for preparing various recombinant mycobacterial proteins that are used for structural and functional studies. The advantages of M. smegmatis as a host are that it is fast-growing, non-pathogenic, easy to manipulate, and has similar post-translational modifications to other mycobacteria. It is critical to express recombinant proteins with similar conformations and/or functions to native proteins from major pathogenic mycobacterial strains, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wine-Red to Tea-Brown Urine in Rhabdomyolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of discrepancy in SNEDDS performance for a "brick dust" mebendazole between in and vitro and in-vivo estimation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oral absorption of mebendazole (MBZ), a brick dust, was successfully improved 10 times by dosing 2 % HPMCP-50 SNEDDS of MBZ co-amorphized with (+)-10-camphorsulufonic acid (CSA) (MBZ-CSA), compared with crystal powders in our previous study. However, an in-vitro non-sink dissolution study with pH3.9 acetate buffer or FaSSIF (conventional method) revealed that 2 % HPMCP-50 SNEDDS of MBZ-CSA improved the dissolution of MBZ over 440 times compared to the crystal. In the current study, we assessed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183581/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and Safety of Single Antiplatelet Therapy With Prasugrel in Carotid Artery Stenting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BackgroundDual antiplatelet therapy (DAPT) is used peri-operatively as standard care for patients who undergo carotid artery stenting (CAS). Nonetheless, this regimen is associated with several problems, including ischemic complications due to antiplatelet resistance, as well as hemorrhagic complications. This study investigated the feasibility of single antiplatelet therapy (SAPT) with prasugrel for CAS.MethodsRecords of consecutive patients who underwent elective CAS between January 2015 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183448/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Photocatalytic hydrogen peroxide production toward quantum yields exceeding 100]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen peroxide (H(2)O(2)) is not only an important substance widely used in large quantities in chemistry and the chemical industry, but also a promising clean fuel and oxidant for fuel cells. In recent years, photocatalytic H(2)O(2) synthesis from O(2) and/or water has been actively researched with the aim of green on-site production. The intrinsic reaction efficiency can be evaluated by the external quantum yield or apparent quantum yield defined by the ratio of the number of H(2)O(2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183371/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond AUROC: Critical evaluation of FSTL-1 as a liver fibrosis biomarker]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183308/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identifying Terminologies Used Prior to the Onset of Interstitial Lung Disease in Patients With Lung Cancer: Descriptive Analysis of Electronic Medical Record Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Terms related to respiratory symptoms, pain or analgesics, and appetite were identified as associated factors for ILD onset in patients with stage IV lung cancer using RWD from acute care institutions for malignant tumors. These findings may support the early detection of ILD and underscore the potential of RWD to generate real-world evidence that informs drug discovery and pharmaceutical development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Estimating psychophysiological loads by repeated temperature steps on humans using a state-space model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humans are exposed to daily temperature differences indoors and outdoors worldwide; however, the associated risks to health and fatigue remain unclear. This study aimed to clarify the psychophysiological loads by repeated short-term temperature differences on Japanese individuals. Herein, 28 healthy individuals were repeatedly moved between two temperature environments, and their psychological/physiological responses to temperature differences in the environment were recorded [T26-26 (control),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183098/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DPDispatcher: Scalable HPC Task Scheduling for AI-Driven Science]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is reshaping computational science, but AI-driven workflows routinely span heterogeneous tasks executed across diverse high-performance computing (HPC) systems. We introduce DPDispatcher, an open-source Python framework for scalable, fault-tolerant task scheduling in such environments with an emphasis on lightweight submission, automatic retries, and robust resumption. DPDispatcher separates connection and file-staging concerns from scheduler control, supports...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41183016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A neural network approach to sarcopenia prediction based on bioelectrical impedance in community-dwelling older adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to apply a neural network to raw bioelectrical impedance analysis data and to test whether sarcopenia could be predicted with high accuracy. The study population comprised 727 community-dwelling older adults aged 65-85 years who participated in the Kasama Study from 2015 to 2018. Sarcopenia was determined using the standard values set by the Asian Working Group for Sarcopenia 2019. Skeletal muscle mass index, grip strength, and five-times sit-to-stand test (Dataset 1) or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cohort profile and representativeness of participants in the Danish monozygotic twin study on migraine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Danish Monozygotic Twin Study on Migraine is a population-based twin study established in 2023-2024. The cohort was created to lay the foundation for innovative studies of the role of environmental, genetic, and epigenetic factors and their complex interactions in the pathogenesis of migraine. The aim of this paper is to describe data collection, content, characteristics of participants and to assess the representativeness of the cohort by comparing participants to non-responders. Danish...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of total arch replacement with frozen elephant trunk for type B aortic dissection involving left subclavian artery-adjacent entry: a strategy for anatomically challenging cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Total arch replacement with a frozen elephant trunk is safe for anatomically challenging type B aortic dissection with an entry near the left subclavian artery and represents a viable treatment option in this setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CD40 transcriptomic expression patterns across malignancies: implications for clinical trials of CD40 agonists]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: High CD40 expression correlated with liver and bile duct, pancreatic, and ovarian cancers, as well as with CD28 and GITR transcripts. Immune marker co-expression in individual patients merits further exploration for the development of CD40-based and other immunotherapy interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The intensive care medicine research agenda for the management of ICU acquired weakness: a multinational, interprofessional perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intensive care unit acquired weakness (ICUAW) is common in critically ill patients, contributing to substantial morbidity. Major trials and novel mechanistic findings published over the past years have advanced knowledge for the prevention and treatment of ICUAW. To streamline future research priorities, a multinational, interdisciplinary group of ICU clinicians, researchers, and people with lived experience convened to develop this evidence-based research agenda. Using a stepwise process...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond the flush: rethinking reactions to ethanol-based disinfectants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interspecific secondary plasmodesmata at parasitic interface]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obligate parasitic plants often establish symplastic connections with their hosts. This symplastic continuity is mediated by plasma membrane-lined channels referred to as interspecific secondary plasmodesmata, which develop at the interface between the parasite and its host. However, the molecular mechanisms underlying the formation of these interspecific secondary plasmodesmata remain unclear. In this mini review, we summarize current knowledge of plasmodesmata biogenesis at diverse cellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182262/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differentiation of iPS Cells into Periodontal Ligament Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periodontal ligament (PDL) is a thin connective tissue that connects the tooth to the bony socket and plays a crucial role in the regeneration and maintenance of homeostasis of periodontal tissues by supplying stem/progenitor cells. Induced pluripotent stem cells (iPSCs) are highly anticipated in regenerative medicine because of their differentiation potential into a wide variety of cell types. In this study, we investigated the effects of humoral factors on iPSC differentiation by culturing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Host-microbiota matching and epigenetic modulation drive Daphnia magna responses to cyanobacterial stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial communities are crucial in host adaptation to stressors, particularly in dynamic ecosystems. In aquatic environments, Daphnia magna is ideal for studying host-microbiome interactions due to its ecological importance and sensitivity. Adaptation to toxins, such as those produced by cyanobacteria, may involve both host and microbial gene repertoires. Yet, the influence of microbiota composition and function on host performance remains poorly understood. Because epigenetic mechanisms such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182235/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sterically Stabilized (Zr,Ti)-(Al,Sn,Pb,Bi)-C MAX Phase Solid Solutions with Zn Additions and Enhanced Chemical Complexity on the A-Site]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The MAX phases constitute a family of nanolaminated ternary carbides and nitrides renowned for their compositional versatility, as reflected in the easy formation of solid solutions with variable chemical complexity. Synthesizing MAX phase solid solutions with intentionally tailored chemical complexity can produce materials that are able to meet the property requirements of the targeted application(s). This work presents an effective strategy specifically developed to design and fabricate highly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Representational dynamics of the main dimensions of object space: Face/body selectivity aligns temporally with animal taxonomy but not with animacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Object representations are organized according to multiple dimensions, with an important role for the distinction between animate and inanimate objects and for selectivity for faces versus bodies. For other dimensions, questions remain how they stand relative to these two primary dimensions. One such dimension is a graded selectivity for the taxonomic level that an animal belongs to. Earlier research suggested that animacy can be understood as a graded selectivity for animal taxonomy, although a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41182013/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Case of Adipophilin-Positive Pancreatic Intraductal Papillary Mucinous Neoplasm (IPMN) With Eosinophilia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adipophilin expression and eosinophilia associated with intraductal papillary mucinous neoplasm (IPMN) are extremely rare in the literature, and the relationship between adipophilin expression and IPMN remains unclear. This study reports the case of a 67-year-old male patient with adipophilin-positive IPMN and eosinophilia, which diminished following R0 surgical resection. The patient underwent pancreaticoduodenectomy for a pancreatic head (Ph) tumor detected by abdominal echo screening....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel water-from-air technology: creeping clathrate desalination of deliquescent salt solutions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Water scarcity is an escalating global challenge driven by population growth and resource depletion. Conventional fresh water production methods typically require access to liquid water sources, limiting their applicability in remote or arid regions. Water-from-air technologies offer a potential solution but are often hindered by high energy demands and/or climatological conditions. This study introduces clathrate-based desalination of deliquescent salt solutions as a novel approach for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wrapping a single crystal spin-crossover complex with a single crystal non-spin-crossover complex to modulate the spin-transition temperature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The formation of a heterojunction interface between different materials could lead to emergent functions that are not the simple sum of the properties of each component. Here we report the modulation of physical properties due to the lattice mismatch between two molecular crystals. Using metal complexes as a motif, we created a crystalline object that can be referred to as a core-shell crystal, in which a single crystal of one complex (Fe^(II) complex) is wrapped with a single crystal of a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181226/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Colletotrichum tofieldiae</em> enhances phosphorus uptake and biomass production and alters the microbial interactions in the rhizosphere of komatsuna (<em>Brassica rapa</em> var. <em>perviridis</em>) grown in phosphorus-deficient farm soils]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microbial bioinoculants should play important roles to achieve sustainable phosphorus (P) management in agriculture. Colletotrichum tofieldiae (Ct), a fungal endophyte, is a promising material that supports phosphorus acquisition in Arabidopsis under low phosphorus (P) conditions and promotes maize and tomato growth in a greenhouse. However, its effects on leafy vegetables such as komatsuna, particularly those with a range of P availability in the soil, remain largely unclear. This study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preface to the special issue "Diverse Symbiotic Relationships between Plants and Microbes in the Phyllosphere and Rhizosphere"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phyllosphere C1-microorganisms: Their interaction with plants and contribution to the global carbon cycle]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plants emit a variety of volatile organic compounds (VOCs), including C1-compounds such as methane and methanol, which are major components of plant-derived VOCs. A group of microorganisms called methylotrophs or C1-microorganisms utilize these C1-compounds as a single source of carbon and energy and contribute to driving the global carbon cycle between two major greenhouse gases, CO(2) and methane. C1-microorganisms inhabit the surface of the above-ground part of plants (phyllosphere), and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell Raman spectroscopic analysis of bacteroids in soybean nodules to observe the relationship between biomolecular constituents and symbiotic nitrogen fixation activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogen fixation in soybean occurs as a result of symbiosis between the plant and rhizobia in the nodules. This process allows both the plant and the symbiont to acquire vital nutrition. To fully understand the symbiosis, many researchers have attempted to attain a deeper interpretation of the biomolecular behavior or enhance the nitrogen fixation activity of bacteroids. However, most studies have focused on forward and reverse genetics approaches to evaluate the contribution of a particular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181076/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Various types of mycorrhizal fungi sequences detected in single intracellular vesicles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A diverse range of microbes have been observed to coexist in plant roots in the field, among which arbuscular mycorrhizal fungi (AMFs) are universal and have recently been shown to be of two types: one belonging to the subphylum Glomeromycotina (G-AMF) and the other to the subphylum Mucoromycotina (M-AMF). These two types of mycorrhizal fungi are known to co-occur in roots. This is because, in addition to the morphological evidence, diverse ribosomal RNA (rRNA) gene sequences, including those of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181073/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elimination mechanism of vanillin from non-phenolic β-O-4-type terminals formed in guaiacyl lignin: a combined kinetic and theoretical study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The alkaline aerobic oxidation of lignin to vanillin (4-hydroxy-3-methoxybenzaldehyde) has been employed as an industrial method for producing bio-based low-molecular-weight aromatic compounds. To deepen the molecular-level understanding of this reaction, we have been investigating the vanillin formation mechanism from native softwood lignin. One of the major reaction pathways involves oxidative degradation of β-O-4-type internal units, followed by alkaline-induced elimination of vanillin from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41181016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimum colonoscopy observation time for colonic diverticular bleeding: A new benchmark based on the 5% plateau time]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although it varied according to the CT findings, the overall 5% plateau time was 40 minutes. This offers a practical benchmark for the minimum observation time without SRH detection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41180987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20251104023827&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>