<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 19:38:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dokdothiocin, an Anti-Neuroinflammatory Thiopeptide from <em>Streptomyces</em> sp. 20A130]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dokdothiocin, a ribosomally synthesized and post-translationally modified peptide (RiPP) belonging to the thiopeptide family, was isolated from Streptomyces sp. 20A130. Its structure was elucidated by extensive NMR analyses, high-resolution mass spectrometry, and chemical derivatization, revealing a 29-membered macrocyclic scaffold bearing oxazole, thiazole, and a central pyridine ring. Dokdothiocin differs from previously reported thiopeptides in macrocycle size, heterocycle arrangement, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757706/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ion-Regulating SPEEK-BNNS Hybrid Interfaces Enabling Low-Barrier Zn-Ion Transport and Dendrite-Free Zinc Anodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The practical application of aqueous Zn-ion batteries (AZIBs) is severely limited by unstable Zn-metal anodes caused by dendritic growth and parasitic interfacial reactions. Herein, we report an organic-inorganic hybrid protective layer composed of sulfonated poly(ether ether ketone) (SPEEK) and boron nitride nanosheets (BNNS), fabricated via a scalable and controllable spray-coating process. The hybrid architecture synergistically integrates the mechanical robustness of BNNS with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757580/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unilateral biportal endoscopic partial cervical laminectomy and facetectomy: An ex vivo study and case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Unilateral biportal endoscopic laminectomy provided adequate visualization in cadaveric specimens and was associated with a successful outcome in one clinical case.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Clinical Outcomes of Acute Myocardial Infarction Based on Institutional Experience With IVUS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The association of IVUS-guided percutaneous coronary intervention with lower adverse event rates was more apparent and statistically demonstrable in centers with higher IVUS use. These findings suggest that institutional experience may amplify the observable impact of IVUS guidance, underscoring the potential value of standardized IVUS implementation in acute myocardial infarction management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based prediction of herbal medicine response in functional dyspepsia: protocol for a randomized, assessor-blinded, multicenter trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Integrating a machine learning-based prediction system into treatment strategies for FD may enhance clinical practice and support the broader adoption of artificial intelligence-driven approaches in personalized medicine.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring <em>LEPR</em>-Linked Metabolic Diversity through Gut Microbiome-Metabolome Network Analysis in Non-Obese Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Genetic variation in the leptin receptor (LEPR) gene has been implicated in metabolic regulation, while the gut microbiome and circulating metabolites are increasingly recognized as mediators of host metabolic phenotype. However, the systems-level interactions among LEPR genotypes, gut microbial composition, and serum metabolomic profiles remain poorly understood, particularly in healthy individuals. We conducted a cross-sectional study involving 37 healthy Korean adults. Three LEPR single...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755783/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploratory Proteomic Profiling Reveals Potential Mediators of 5-FU Response under p53 Deficiency in Colon Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mutations in p53 have been implicated in poor prognosis and reduced sensitivity to 5-fluorouracil (5-FU) treatment in colon cancer. While p53-dependent mechanisms have been widely studies, less is known about how p53 deficiency reshapes cellular signaling and contributes to 5-FU resistance. In this study, we aimed to profile proteomic alterations associated with p53 loss by comparing colon cancer cells with and without p53 expression. Differentially expressed proteins (DEPs) related to cell...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755778/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Body Image And Self-Efficacy As Mediators Between Prepregnancy Body Mass Index And Health Behaviors In Pregnant Women: A Secondary Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined how prepregnancy body mass index (BMI) relates to healthy eating and physical activity during pregnancy through body image and self-efficacy. Data from 369 Korean women in their third trimester were analyzed using validated instruments. Serial mediation analyses indicated that BMI was indirectly related to healthy eating through body image and self-efficacy, with no direct effect. In contrast, BMI showed both a direct association and a sequential indirect effect on physical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a competitive immunoassay platform for quantifying the oligonucleotide products of nucleotide excision repair in UV-irradiated cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nucleotide excision repair (NER) system removes UV photoproducts from the genome in the form of small, excised, damage-containing DNA oligonucleotides (sedDNAs). However, the methods that are traditionally used to detect these repair products in human cells have several limitations, including the presence of other contaminating large DNAs and labeling efficiency. We therefore developed a novel microplate-based competitive immunoassay platform to precisely measure sedDNAs containing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Croup in Infancy and Subsequent Asthma Development: Is There a Link?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Recurrent croup, but not a single episode, was associated with an increased risk of subsequent asthma, suggesting that recurrent croup may be an early clinical marker of asthma susceptibility, particularly in children with coexisting atopic conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circularly Polarized X-Band Fan-Beam Antenna and Its Application to Offset Reflector Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this letter, a circularly polarized (CP) 4 × 4 array antenna generating a fan-beam radiation pattern is presented, along with its application as the primary pattern of an offset reflector antenna. A sequentially rotated feed network is incorporated into the proposed antenna, enabling a wide axial ratio (AR) bandwidth of 1.9 GHz centered at 8.2 GHz. The proposed array antenna generates about 27.5° and 14.5° of half-power beamwidth (HPBW) in ϕ=0° and ϕ=90° planes, respectively. The fabricated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755240/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Food Agency and Intentions to Improve Cooking Skills Among Korean Young Adults: Demographic Differences and Motivators]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study aimed to examine levels of food agency and intentions to improve cooking skills among Korean young adults in their 20s, and to identify demographic differences and underlying motivators. Subjects/Methods: An online survey was administered from February 18 to 25, 2021, targeting Korean adults aged 20-29 years (n = 1102; 579 men, 523 women). Food agency was assessed using the Cooking and Food Provisioning Action Scale (CAFPAS), comprising three subscales:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754173/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Triglycerides and Hypertension in a Korean Population: An Individual-Level Mendelian Randomization Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Although elevated triglyceride (TG) levels are consistently associated with hypertension in observational studies, whether TGs have a causal effect on hypertension remains uncertain, and evidence in East Asian populations is limited. Methods: We analyzed 2159 Korean adults (20-86 years) whose individual-level genetic and phenotypic data were obtained from a cross-sectional health check cohort. Candidate TG-associated genetic variants were identified using genome-wide association...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754150/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stage-Dependent Metabolic Responses to Oral Nutritional Supplementation in Cancer Cachexia: A Single-Arm Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study showed the feasibility of integrating ONS with multi-omics profiling. Our findings suggest that metabolic alterations might precede clinically detectable changes, potentially providing a rationale for early intervention. Specifically, certain fatty acids were identified as candidate biomarkers that warrant further validation in larger cohorts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping the Landscape of Medical AI Research in Korea Using Topic Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: This study analyzed ten years of domestic research on medical artificial intelligence (AI) from 2015 to 2024 using topic modeling and keyword network analysis. Chronological comparison showed that the research emphasis evolved through three stages-Introduction (2015-2018), Expansion (2019-2022), and Post-ChatGPT (2023-2024)-reflecting the growing incorporation of AI into clinical and service domains. Methods: We collected a curated set of 686 papers from the Korea Citation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Resident Doctors' Strike on Psychological Outcomes Among Paramedics in Teaching-Hospital Emergency Departments: A Nationwide Multicenter Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: In March 2024, a resident doctor's strike in South Korea created staffing gaps in teaching-hospital emergency departments. The purpose of this study was to evaluate pre- and post-strike changes in job stress, self-efficacy, job satisfaction, and job performance confidence among paramedics who work in hospitals and to compare patterns of change by career stage. Methods: Paramedics who work in hospitals designated as regional and local emergency medical centers completed a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Androgen Deprivation Therapy on Lower Urinary Tract Symptoms in Patients with Prostate Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41752758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: The increasing number of patients with prostate cancer receiving long-term androgen deprivation therapy (ADT) underscores the importance of maintaining quality of life during treatment. Lower urinary tract symptoms (LUTS), influenced by prostate size, represent significant determinants of quality of life in this population. This study aimed to investigate the impact of ADT on LUTS in patients with prostate cancer, particularly focusing on how ADT, which reduces...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41752758/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Limited Impact of Short-Term Osteoporosis Medication on Vertebral Height Loss in the Acute Phase of Osteoporotic Vertebral Compression Fractures: A 3-Month Longitudinal Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41752698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background and Objectives: The optimal pharmacological strategy to mitigate progressive vertebral collapse during the acute phase of osteoporotic vertebral compression fractures (OVCFs) remains a subject of debate. This initial 3-month window is the most critical period for evaluating the structural stability of the fracture, as the majority of progressive height loss occurs before solid bone union is achieved, directly influencing the decision to continue conservative management or transition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41752698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Vitro and Clinical Evaluation of the Anti-Wrinkle Efficacy of Medipep-6PN, a Novel Peptide Identified by Phage Display]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Face wrinkles caused by skin aging can be classified into dynamic wrinkles, which are caused by repetitive contraction of facial expression muscles, and static wrinkles, which are related to extracellular matrix damage and collagen breakdown caused by ultraviolet and oxidative stress. These two mechanisms are closely related, and prolonged, repetitive muscle contractions act as mechanical stress that promotes extracellular matrix degradation within the dermis, accelerating wrinkle formation. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751890/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hybrid Forecast-Enabled Adaptive Crowbar Coordination for LVRT Enhancement in DFIG Wind Turbines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a hybrid forecast-enabled adaptive crowbar coordination strategy to enhance low-voltage ride-through (LVRT) performance of doubly fed induction generator (DFIG) wind turbines. A unified electro-mechanical model in the αβ/dq frames with dual closed-loop control for rotor- and grid-side converters is built in MATLAB/Simulink (R2018b), and LVRT constraints on current safety and DC-link energy are explicitly formulated, yielding an engineering crowbar-resistance range of 0.4-0.8...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>N</em>-(<em>p</em>-Coumaroyl) Serotonin Ameliorates LPS-Induced Inflammation in BV2 Microglia via MAPK/NF-κB Inactivation and HO-1/NQO1 Upregulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Uncontrolled inflammation contributes to the development of neurodegenerative diseases (NDs) like Alzheimer's disease (AD). N-(p-Coumaroyl) serotonin (CS) has demonstrated a significant capacity to modulate hyper-inflammation. We explored whether CS could mitigate inflammatory responses in endotoxin-challenged microglial cells and sought to elucidate the specific molecular mechanisms governing these effects. ELISA, nitric oxide (NO) assays, Western blotting and immunocytochemistry were performed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>γ</em>-Amino Carboxylic Acid Modification Enhances the Efficacy of Peptide Nucleic Acids Targeting miR-221-3p in Lung Cancer Cell Lines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peptide nucleic acids (PNAs) are versatile molecules with promising diagnostic and therapeutic applications, including gene expression regulation and miRNA targeting. However, their moderate biological efficacy limits their therapeutic application. This can be addressed by leveraging a key advantage of PNAs over other nucleic acids-the ease of modification, which enhances their functional properties. Notably, γ-modified PNAs have improved binding affinity and cellular uptake properties,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oral and Intranasal Administration of Polydeoxyribonucleotide Isolated from <em>Porphyra</em> sp. Ameliorates Acute Lung Injury via Suppressing Proinflammatory Cytokine Production in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute lung injury (ALI) is a severe inflammatory condition with high mortality rates, necessitating the development of effective therapeutic agents. Polydeoxyribonucleotide (PDRN), a DNA-derived compound known for its tissue repair and anti-inflammatory properties, has gained attention as a potential therapeutic agent. However, the efficacy of PDRN derived from marine sources, particularly Porphyra sp. (laver), remains unexplored in respiratory inflammation. In this study, we investigated the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751449/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Water Extract of Mixed Mushroom Mycelia Mitigates Cognitive Deficit and Oxidative Stress After Global Cerebral Ischemia-Reperfusion Injury]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that GMK confers dose-dependent behavioral and histopathological protection against GCIRI, potentially by modulating redox- and apoptosis-related signaling (Bax/Bcl-2, GPX/CAT, and ERK/iNOS pathways), with more consistent effects at a higher dose.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Ammonia Concentration Prediction with a Transfer-Learning-Based Model: Application in a Pig Farm]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Globally, the swine industry is a major component of agricultural production, and the increasing scale and intensification of pig farming have heightened concerns about NH(3) emissions. As farms expand and adopt smart farming technologies, there is a need for reliable prediction of NH(3) concentrations without relying solely on costly physical sensors. In this study, we developed an artificial intelligence-based prediction model for NH(3) concentration in commercial pig houses and examined the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41751069/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision Biomarker Identification in Gynecological Cancers Using Coexpression Networks and Attention-Based LSTM in Healthcare 4.0]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Cervical cancer (CC) and ovarian cancer (OC) are among the most prevalent and lethal gynecological malignancies in women, necessitating the identification of reliable biomarkers for early diagnosis and prognosis. Methods: This study integrates bioinformatics and Healthcare 4.0 to identify key biomarkers associated with these cancers. Differentially expressed genes (DEGs) were identified from two microarray datasets. mRMR followed by SVM-RFE was applied to the identified DEGs to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750695/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Mode Decomposition-Based Clustered Pattern Projection for Reliable Alzheimer's Disease Detection from EEG]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Detecting Alzheimer's disease (AD) from normal aging using eyes-open (EO) EEG is challenging due to stimulus-driven nonstationarity and fragmented oscillatory responses. This study aims to determine whether prototype-based representations derived from Dynamic Mode Decomposition (DMD) can improve AD detection from EO photostimulation EEG. Methods: We propose a DMD-based framework termed DMD-based Clustered Pattern Projection (DMD-CPP). Segment-wise DMD representations were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750680/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stigmasterol Is Associated with Alterations in nNOS-PSD95/CAPON Signaling and Synaptic Plasticity in a PTSD Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The efficacy of stigmasterol (STG) has not been previously evaluated in post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) models. Mice exposed to single prolonged stress with foot shock (SPS + FS) received oral STG (25 or 50 mg/kg) for 14 days. Serum corticosterone and serotonin levels were measured, anxiety and cognition were assessed, synaptic plasticity-related proteins and genes were quantified, and neuronal nitric oxide synthase (nNOS), nitric oxide (NO) accumulation, nNOS-postsynaptic density protein...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750618/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extraction Processing Technologies and Their Effects on Antioxidant Activity in <em>Cinnamomum camphora</em> (L.) J. Presl Leaves]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the bioactive potential of Cinnamomum camphora (L.) J. Presl (C. camphora) leaf extracts obtained using hydrothermal extraction (HE) and ultrasound-assisted extraction (UAE) with 30%, 50%, and 70% ethanol (v/v). Extracts were analyzed for their phytochemical composition and biological activities. UAE extracts, particularly with 70% ethanol, exhibited the highest total polyphenol (363.0 ± 1.40 mg GAE/g) and flavonoid (174.5 ± 0.42 mg QE/g) contents. This extract also...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[p38α MAPK-Mediated Redox Regulation of Transglutaminase 2 Drives Microvascular Leakage in Diabetic Retinas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microvascular leakage is an early hallmark of diabetic retinopathy (DR), but the redox-dependent mechanisms underlying this dysfunction remain unclear. Here, we investigated whether p38α mitogen-activated protein kinase (MAPK) activates transglutaminase 2 (TGase2) through reactive oxygen species (ROS) generation, thereby promoting hyperglycemia-induced vascular permeability in diabetic retinas. In human retinal endothelial cells (HRECs), vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF), which is...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biosacetalin (1,1-Diethoxyethane) Improves Healthy Lifespan in <em>C. elegans</em> and Rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recent evidence has highlighted the pivotal roles of reactive oxygen species (ROS) and the SIRT1, AMPK, and mTOR signaling pathways in aging and longevity, making them attractive targets for studies of lifespan-extending interventions. We previously demonstrated that 1,1-diethoxyethane (1,1-DEE) could interact with mitochondrial complex I (NADH-ubiquinone oxidoreductase), leading to transient mitochondrial ROS (mtROS) production and activation of the AMPK pathway. This study further examined the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41750541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immune and Tumor Microenvironment Mechanisms of <em>Hedyotis diffusa</em> Willd: A Scoping Review and Network Pharmacology Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41749926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The tumor microenvironment (TME) is a dynamic ecosystem that critically shapes tumor progression, immune escape, and therapeutic responses. Hedyotis diffusa Willd (HDW) has long been used in East Asian medicine for conditions associated with inflammation and malignancy, yet its immunological and microenvironmental mechanisms have not been systematically synthesized. Methods: A scoping review of preclinical studies (2016-2025) was conducted following the Arksey-O'Malley framework and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41749926/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population Pharmacokinetic-Pharmacodynamic Analysis of Zolpidem in Healthy Volunteers: Covariate Contributions to Variability in CNS Responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41749515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Population pharmacokinetic-pharmacodynamic (PK-PD) modeling was used to explore covariate effects on zolpidem PKs and PDs in 30 healthy Korean volunteers (15 males, 15 females) who received a single 10 mg dose. The dataset included 325 PK observations and 388 observations each for the digit symbol substitution test (DSST), choice reaction time (CRT), and visual analog scale (VAS). A one-compartment PK model with transit compartment absorption and first-order elimination was developed, followed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41749515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamics of interleukin-23/interleukin-17 axis and type 1 regulatory T cells across disease stages in axial spondyloarthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings indicate that IL-23-associated immune activity may be relatively more prominent in early axSpA and that differences in Tr1 cell-related regulation across disease stages could contribute to this pattern.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erythropoiesis-Stimulating Agents and Development of Cancer Among Patients Receiving Dialysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this case-control study of patients undergoing dialysis, high-dose ESA use was associated with greater odds of new cancer development. These results suggest that caution should be exercised to avoid aiming for excessively high hemoglobin levels during ESA therapy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative efficacy of four different prefilled CO<sub>2</sub> absorbent brands in clinical practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In vivo performance of prefilled CO₂ absorbents may differ from previously reported in vitro results and can vary according to particle composition and device-specific conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PBPK modeling of the antidepressant doxepin incorporating CYP2D6 genotype for precision pharmacotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Doxepin, a tricyclic antidepressant, exhibits substantial interindividual variability in pharmacokinetics, mainly attributable to genetic polymorphisms of cytochrome P450 (CYP) enzymes, particularly CYP2D6. Such variability may lead to clinically relevant differences in drug exposure, therapeutic response, and adverse effects when doxepin is used for antidepressant therapy. The present study aimed to develop and validate physiologically based pharmacokinetic (PBPK) models of doxepin and its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease and adverse pregnancy outcomes: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When viruses recede and alcohol advances: demographic momentum and policy gaps in alcohol-associated liver cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758302/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Impact of Metastatic Sites in Patients with Biliary Tract Cancer Treated with Cisplatin, Gemcitabine, and Durvalumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study did not show statistically significant differences in outcomes associated with location and number of metastatic sites in a large population of patients with BTC treated with CGD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WATCH-SS: Developing a Trustworthy and Explainable Modular Framework for Detecting Cognitive Impairment from Spontaneous Speech]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early detection of cognitive impairment (CI) is critical for timely intervention in Alzheimer's disease and AD-related dementias. To address this, we propose the Warning Assessment and Alerting Tool for Cognitive Health from Spontaneous Speech (WATCH-SS), a modular and explainable three-stage framework for detecting CI from a patient's speech sample. The framework uses detectors for five linguistic and acoustic indicators of CI, aggregates their outputs into a set of clinically interpretable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758152/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ReXVQA: A Large-scale Visual Question Answering Benchmark for Generalist Chest X-ray Understanding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present ReXVQA, the largest and most comprehensive benchmark for visual question answering (VQA) in chest radiology, comprising 694,841 questions paired with 160,000 chest X-rays studies across training, validation, and test sets. Unlike prior efforts that rely heavily on template based queries, ReXVQA introduces a diverse and clinically authentic task suite reflecting five core radiological reasoning skills: presence assessment, location analysis, negation detection, differential diagnosis,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Speaker Role Identification in Clinical Conversations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Patient-clinician communication research is crucial for understanding interaction dynamics and for predicting outcomes that are associated with clinical discourse. Traditionally, interaction analysis is conducted manually because of challenges such as Speaker Role Identification (SRI), which must reliably differentiate between doctors, medical assistants, patients, and other caregivers in the same room. Although automatic speech recognition with diarization can efficiently create a transcript...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758139/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3DReasonKnee: Advancing Grounded Reasoning in Medical Vision Language Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Current Vision-Language Models (VLMs) struggle to ground anatomical regions in 3D medical images and reason about them in a step-by-step manner-a key requirement of realworld diagnostic assessment. This ability is essential for aligning model outputs with the diagnostic workflows clinicians use in practice, enabling trustworthy clinician-AI collaboration. Existing 3D datasets provide localization labels, but none support this "grounded reasoning" ability. To address this gap, we introduce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Disease in Asia: Decreasing Rates and Increasing Absolute Burden]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of fatty acid elongation enhances hydroxy fatty acid biosynthesis and accumulation in Arabidopsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seed oils of castor (Ricinus communis) and lesquerella (Physaria fendleri) mainly contain hydroxy fatty acids (HFAs) useful in industrial applications. As castor seeds contain toxin ricin and lesquerella is not yet a commercial crop, extensive efforts have been directed to develop safe commercial sources of HFAs in Arabidopsis (Arabidopsis thaliana). We over-expressed a lesquerella elongase, PfKCS18, in a previous transgenic Arabidopsis pCam5 line which expresses five castor genes. pCam5+PfKCS18...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757983/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laser-Processed 2D Germanane on Graphene for Organohydrogel-Based Zinc-Ion Hybrid Capacitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Group 14 monoelemental two-dimensional (2D) materials beyond graphene, such as silicene and germanene, have gained significant attention in the scientific community. Covalent functionalization of germanene with hydrogen and methyl leads to germanane (hydrogen/methyl-terminated germanene; HGe/MGe). While the optical and electronic properties of HGe and MGe were explored previously, there is no report on their zinc ion storage electrochemistry. Though the layered HGe/MGe sheets have tunable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757735/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of Common Blood Metabolic Derangements Using Magnetic Resonance Signatures of the Pancreas and Liver]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Automated magnetic resonance signatures of pancreatic and hepatic tissue composition were significantly associated with clinically relevant disturbances in lipid metabolism and indices of glucose homeostasis. These findings support the feasibility of opportunistic, automated detection of abnormal blood metabolic parameters using high-resolution cross-sectional imaging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phase-Tuning of Ru Nanostructures in Ru/ZrO<sub>2</sub> Catalysts for Controlling Radical and Nonradical Pathways of Peroxymonosulfate-Based Oxidation and Defluorination of a Fluorinated Anticancer Drug]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study demonstrates that the catalytic performance of Ru catalysts is strongly influenced by the crystal facets and structures of Ru nanoparticles, with hexagonal close-packed (hcp)-Ru exhibiting superior activity (turnover frequency = 18.1 s^(-1)) compared to face-centered cubic (fcc)-Ru (5.27-10.6 s^(-1)). Notably, the crystalline phase of ZrO(2) (i.e., tetragonal (t-ZrO(2)), monoclinic (m-ZrO(2)), and mixed phase (mixed-ZrO(2))) preferentially directs the formation of distinct Ru...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757641/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deterministic Néel Vector Switching of Altermagnets Via Magnetic Octupole Torque]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Altermagnets have recently emerged as promising materials for next-generation spintronic devices. For their device applications, realizing a single-domain configuration is essential but remains challenging. We theoretically consider injecting magnetic multipoles into altermagnets, which can be achieved by applying an in-plane current to an altermagnet/normal metal bilayer. We demonstrate for d $d$ -wave altermagnets that the torque generated by the magnetic octupole injection can achieve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757577/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Systematic Review of Complication Management During Uniportal and Biportal Endoscopic Spine Surgery: Dural Tear and Bleeding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Study DesignSystematic Review and Narrative Review.ObjectiveTo evaluate the incidence, risk factors, and management strategies for iatrogenic dural tears and to provide a narrative review of intraoperative bleeding management during uniportal and biportal endoscopic spine surgery (ESS).MethodsA systematic literature search was conducted according to PRISMA guidelines using PubMed/MEDLINE, Embase, Cochrane Library, Scopus, and Web of Science for studies published between January 1990 and August...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Model-Inversion-Resistant Physical Unclonable Neural Network Using Vertical NAND Flash Memory]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The growing use of neural networks in privacy-sensitive applications necessitates architectures that inherently protect both data and model integrity. We present a model-inversion-resistant physical unclonable neural network (PUNN) implemented on commercial vertical NAND (V-NAND) flash memory. A physical unclonable layer generated through weak gate-induced drain-leakage erase exploits intrinsic device-level variations to create chip-unique conductance patterns that are concealable and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757537/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Physical Implementation of Optical Material-Based Neural Networks Processing Enabled by Long-Persistent Luminescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rapid advancements in artificial intelligence have magnified the inherent bottlenecks and energy inefficiencies of conventional von Neumann architecture. To address these limitations, processing information in a highly parallel, memory-integrated manner mimicking the human brain, neuromorphic devices have emerged as a cornerstone of next-generation computing. Among these, optical-neuromorphic devices are particularly promising. By using light, they offer transformative advantages, such as high...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TLR Agonist/Copper-Based Metformin Carbon Dot-Loaded Homologous Membrane Nanocarriers with Enhanced Immunogenic Cell Death for Synchronous Amelioration of Tumor Microenvironment Hypoxia, Immunosuppression, and Metastasis Inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The immunosuppressive tumor microenvironment (TME) and hypoxia are core drivers of tumor metastasis and recurrence. In this study, we constructed a biomimetic delivery system (CMCMCDR) coated with CT26 tumor cell membranes, loaded with copper metformin carbon dots (CuMCDs), doxorubicin (DOX), and Toll-like receptor 7 (TLR7) agonist R837. This system aims to reverse immunosuppression and hypoxia through multimodal synergy, thereby enhancing antitumor efficacy. CMCMCDR exhibits pH-responsive drug...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757516/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to "Interpretation and reflections on the association between obstructive sleep apnea and venous thromboembolism risk"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Hepatitis B Virus Infection on the Efficacy and Safety of Pembrolizumab Plus Chemotherapy for Advanced Biliary Tract Cancer in the KEYNOTE-966 Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Efficacy and safety outcomes were consistent between HBV-positive and HBV-negative participants receiving first-line pembrolizumab compared with placebo plus gemcitabine and cisplatin.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757470/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermomechanics of Picoliter Liquids Encapsulated in Metal Microarchitectures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Probing the mechanical behavior of liquids at the nanoscale-especially under hydrostatic stress with various strain rates and extreme temperature conditions-holds significant potential for advancing microfluidic, biomedical, and energy systems. However, it remains experimentally challenging due to the inherent difficulties in encapsulation of liquid at micro/nanoscale and in accurately applying and measuring stress within confined microscale environments. In this work, we present a novel...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dose-Escalation Regimens for Incretin Mimetics in Type 2 Diabetes Are Associated With Tolerance for Nausea and Vomiting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS/INTERPRETATION: Taken together, optimised dose-escalation regimens may lead to greater tolerance for nausea and vomiting, which allows to use of higher doses, which are associated with greater therapeutic effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757397/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endogenous β-hydroxybutyrate and the risk of cognitive decline: a nested case-control study in the UK Biobank cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: β-hydroxybutyrate (BHB) has been linked to improved cognitive function via enhanced cerebral metabolism and anti-inflammatory effects. However, evidence on the relationship between endogenous plasma BHB levels and cognitive decline remains limited. This study investigated whether higher plasma BHB levels are associated with reduced cognitive decline in middle-aged and older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual TYK2/JAK1 Inhibition by Brepocitinib Reprograms Synoviocyte Pathobiology: Mechanistic Insights Into Targeted Therapy for Rheumatoid Arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Brepocitinib exerts multi-faceted effects on RA synoviocytes by simultaneously inhibiting inflammatory signaling, suppressing cytokine expression, restoring apoptotic sensitivity, and reducing migratory potential. These findings provide mechanistic support for brepocitinib as a targeted therapeutic agent in RA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of monkeypox skin lesions using edge enhancement algorithms integrated with hybrid deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed framework significantly advances medical image detection for monkeypox lesions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756609/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validating the Korean versions of the flourish index and the secure flourish index: a comprehensive psychometric approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings imply that culturally sensitive adaptations may enhance the interpretability and applicability of the instruments in cross-national research, thereby contributing to a more nuanced understanding of flourishing across diverse cultural contexts.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756494/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Relationships among perceived stress, anxiety, and well-being in Chinese hospital staff: the mediating role of self-efficacy and the moderating role of empathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings underscore the importance of interventions targeting self-efficacy and empathy to improve well-being among hospital staff. This study contributes to the growing body of literature on occupational mental health in high-stress healthcare settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the psychological mechanisms underlying new Olympic sports consumption: the expectation disconfirmation theory framework applied to Millennials' and Generation Z's experiences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results support the applicability of the EDT to Olympic sports content consumption while offering strategic implications for promoting sustained engagement among younger generations in newly introduced Olympic sports.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy of Exosome-Based Therapies for Skin Rejuvenation: A Systematic Review of Human Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Exosomes are secreted tiny organelles that are single-membrane enclosed and can perform a broad spectrum of functions upon release, such as the reorganization of extracellular matrix and communication with other cells through the release of signals and chemicals, which play an important role in development, immunity, tissue homeostasis, cancer, and neurodegenerative diseases, among other aspects of human health and disease. This systematic review aimed to evaluate the clinical efficacy and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiotherapy for recurrent venous malformation involving the thigh and pelvic organs while preserving organ function: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This case demonstrates the potential of RT as an effective treatment for extensive, recurrent pelvic VMs. RT achieves durable disease control while preserving ovarian function, highlighting its role as a viable alternative in select cases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41756161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MEK1/2 Inhibitor (U0126) and PI3K Inhibitor (LY294002) Suppress Herpes Simplex Virus Type 1 Replication by Targeting MAPK/ERK1/2 and PI3K/AKT Signaling Pathways: Implications for Oral Health and Translational Control of Orolabial HSV-1 Infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Targeting host signaling bottlenecks with U0126 and LY294002 offers a dual-pronged antiviral strategy against HSV-1 by dismantling the ERK/AKT axis critical for replication and inflammatory amplification. These findings position MEK1/2 and PI3K as promising therapeutic nodes for managing cutaneous HSV-1 infections. This host-directed dual-pathway inhibition may therefore help reduce recurrent orolabial HSV-1 lesions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioinformatic Analysis to Identify Biomarker Candidates of Complex Karyotype Soft Tissue Sarcomas with <em>CDK4</em>-Amplification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soft tissue sarcomas (STSs), a diverse group of mesenchymal malignancies, are characterized primarily by copy-number alterations rather than a high tumor mutation burden. In this study, we sought to identify expression-based biomarkers in complex karyotype STS (CKS) with CDK4-amplification to support improved therapeutic strategies. Using transcriptome data from National Cancer Center (NCC)-CKS samples, we selected genes whose expression levels were more than two-fold higher or less than half in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755777/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clemastine Restores Myelination Protein Expression in S16 Schwann Cells by Enhancing AMPK Activation and Reducing H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub>-Induced Oxidative Stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peripheral nerve injury and oxidative stress can severely impair Schwann cell function by disrupting the expression of key myelin proteins, promoting intracellular lipid accumulation, and damaging mitochondrial integrity. These pathological changes are central to various neurodegenerative disorders and chemotherapy-induced peripheral neuropathy, yet effective therapeutic approaches remain limited. Clemastine, an FDA-approved antihistamine with known remyelination-enhancing effects in the central...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755774/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hypoxia Preserves Chromatin Integrity and Delays Cellular Senescence through Epigenetic Regulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hypoxia is a physiologically relevant microenvironment in both normal and diseased tissues and has emerged as a potent modulator of cellular senescence and organismal longevity. This review synthesizes evidence that hypoxia delays senescence across diverse experimental systems and species, and highlights mechanisms by which hypoxia rewires chromatin states during senescence-associated transitions. We focus on oxygen- and α-ketoglutarate-dependent epigenetic regulators, particularly histone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755769/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hemostasis-Sparing Antiplatelet Therapy: Current Concepts and Emerging Targets in Arterial Thrombosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Arterial thrombosis remains a leading cause of cardiovascular morbidity and mortality despite widespread use of dual antiplatelet therapy (DAPT) with aspirin and P2Y12 inhibitors. Although these agents reduce ischemic events, their efficacy is counterbalanced by dose-dependent bleeding and their inability to distinguish pathological platelet activation from physiological hemostasis. Recent advances in platelet biology have shifted therapeutic development toward hemostasis-sparing antiplatelet...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Excimer UV-Induced Selective Etching of Single-Layer Graphene for Tailored Graphene Architectures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The commercial adoption of graphene for next-generation electronics requires fabrication techniques that are clean, precise, and scalable. Conventional O(2) plasma etching with polymer masks causes severe contamination and damage. We introduce a polymer-free method for the selective etching of single-layer graphene (SLG) using a 172 nm Xe(2) excimer UV lamp under ambient conditions. This process utilizes high-energy 172 nm photons to directly dissociate atmospheric oxygen and water, enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lithography-Patterned Nafion Interlayers Enable High-Injection Contacts in p-MoTe<sub>2</sub> FETs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A lithography-compatible approach for site-selective contact engineering is developed by using electron-beam lithography to pattern ultrathin Nafion interlayers at the metal contacts of p-type MoTe(2) field-effect transistors. The patterned Nafion films are prepared by electron-beam irradiation followed by development, forming conformal nanometer-thick layers localized exclusively at the source and drain regions. Due to its high work function, Nafion facilitates localized charge transfer that...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pregnant Women's Experience and Perceptions of Seatbelt Education: Assessing the Impact of Maternity Seatbelt Safety Interventions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Education on seat belt use during pregnancy significantly improved both knowledge and correct usage among pregnant women. Routine, formal educational programs are recommended to promote maternal and fetal safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755583/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing emergency department physician workload: A NASA-TLX analysis by experience and care type]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Perceived workload in the ED varies significantly by task type, experience level, and patient acuity. These findings provide actionable data that may support evidence-based staffing decisions, workload redistribution, and training strategies to optimize physician performance and mitigate cognitive overload in resource-limited emergency departments.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755582/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Japanese Encephalitis: Understanding Its Impact, Prevention, and the Role of Vaccination]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Japanese encephalitis (JE) is a mosquito-borne viral disease and remains an important cause of viral encephalitis in Asia and parts of the Western Pacific. Earlier WHO-supported global burden estimates published around 2014 suggested approximately 68,000 clinical cases and up to 20,400 deaths annually; however, the World Health Organization emphasises that the true burden of JE is difficult to quantify due to substantial underreporting and heterogeneous surveillance systems. Although vaccination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-enabled early risk stratification of β-Iactam-induced electrolyte imbalances]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Electrolyte imbalances were common during β-lactam/β-lactamase inhibitor therapy. An interpretable model using routine clinical variables may support risk-informed monitoring; external validation is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755534/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implant rehabilitation of extensive maxillary bone loss secondary to chronic odontogenic sinusitis using a press-fit autogenous ramal block graft: a multidisciplinary staged approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This report details the implant rehabilitation of a patient with extensive maxillary bone loss secondary to chronic odontogenic sinusitis. Prolonged inflammation rendered the right posterior maxilla unsuitable for spontaneous regeneration, necessitating a staged multidisciplinary intervention. Treatment commenced with sinus management via incision and drainage and a targeted pharmacological regimen. Once clinical resolution was achieved, reconstruction was performed using an autogenous bone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individualized multidisciplinary management of severe odontogenic deep neck infections with and without descending necrotizing mediastinitis: a report of two cases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Severe odontogenic deep neck infections (DNIs) can rapidly extend along cervical fascial planes and progress to descending necrotizing mediastinitis (DNM) with high mortality, requiring early diagnosis and multidisciplinary management, especially in elderly patients with comorbidities. We report two elderly patients with rapidly progressive odontogenic infections: one with DNM fulfilling Estrera's criteria (Endo type IIA) and another with extensive DNI without mediastinal spread. Clinical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peri-implantitis as a potential risk factor for peri-implant oral malignancy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Peri-implant oral malignancy (PIOM) refers to malignant tumors arising around dental implants and is an increasingly reported complication of implant therapy. PIOM may follow distinct pathophysiological mechanisms, including chronic peri-implant inflammation and implant-related factors that contribute to carcinogenesis. This current review aims to explore the potential role of peri-implantitis (PI) as a risk factor for PIOM, discussing the proposed pathogenic mechanisms, histological findings,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Korean medication-related osteonecrosis of the jaw position paper-a milestone toward practical, evidence-based guidance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755377/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Workplace Incivility and Nurses' Health: The Mediating Role of Positive and Negative Affect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nurses are particularly vulnerable to workplace incivility, a form of deviant behavior that can evolve into severe workplace mistreatment. Although the psychological and organizational consequences of incivility have been documented, its impact on health, particularly through emotional pathways, remains unclear. Therefore, this study investigated the association between workplace incivility and nurses' self-rated health, focusing on the mediating roles of positive and negative affect-broad...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Context-Aware Semantic Localization with Adaptive Sensor Fusion Under Adverse Conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To achieve Level 4 and above autonomous driving, vehicle localization must remain accurate and reliable under diverse real-world conditions, including complex traffic scenarios, environmental changes, and partial sensor failures. Conventional localization approaches primarily rely on geometric consistency among multi-sensor observations, which can produce physically or contextually implausible pose estimates when sensor reliability degrades or observations become ambiguous. This paper proposes a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bias-Optimized Hydrogen Sensing in a Mo-Electrode Pd/SnO<sub>2</sub> Thin-Film Sensor with Integrated Microheater]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen is a key energy carrier for fuel cell vehicles and hydrogen energy systems. However, its colorless and odorless nature, combined with a wide flammability range, poses significant safety risks in the event of leakage. Accordingly, compact and reliable hydrogen sensors capable of low-ppm detection at moderate operating temperatures are essential for early-stage safety monitoring. In this study, a bias-optimized hydrogen gas sensor based on a Pd-functionalized SnO(2) thin film with Mo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Comparative Study of OCR Architectures for Korean License Plate Recognition: CNN-RNN-Based Models and MobileNetV3-Transformer-Based Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a systematic comparative study of optical character recognition (OCR) architectures for Korean license plate recognition under identical detection conditions. Although recent automatic license plate recognition (ALPR) systems increasingly adopt Transformer-based decoders, it remains unclear whether performance differences arise primarily from sequence modeling strategies or from backbone feature representations. To address this issue, we employ a unified YOLOv12-based license...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cross-Protocol Domain Gap in Internet of Things Intrusion and Anomaly Detection: An Empirical Internet Protocol-to-Bluetooth Low Energy Study of Domain-Adversarial Training]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Intrusion and anomaly detectors trained on Internet Protocol (IP) traffic are increasingly deployed in heterogeneous IoT environments where Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) links coexist with IP networks. We quantify the cross-protocol domain gap in an IP → BLE transfer setting under unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA), where target labels are unavailable for training and model selection. Using 14 lightweight window-level statistics and leakage-aware splits, we benchmark classical baselines and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QbD-Based Formulation Development of Amiodarone Hydrochloride Tablet]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: We conducted this study to develop a generic amiodarone tablet pharmaceutically equivalent to the reference drug. This development is crucial for securing a stable supply chain for this orphan drug, which currently faces domestic market instability. Amiodarone, a national essential medicine, often experiences unstable supply due to its limited profitability. Methods: To secure this stable supply chain, we employed a factorial design, utilizing a Quality by Design (QbD)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41755005/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the Impact of CYP2D6 Phenotype on Fluvoxamine Pharmacokinetics in Geriatric Patients Using Physiologically Based Pharmacokinetic Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Fluvoxamine is commonly prescribed for depressive disorders in elderly patients, a population that frequently exhibits variable drug responses and increased susceptibility to adverse effects due to age-related physiological changes. CYP2D6 polymorphisms may further affect fluvoxamine pharmacokinetics in elderly patients, complicating dose optimization for this group. Previous pharmacogenetic studies examining the impact of CYP2D6 phenotype on fluvoxamine treatment outcomes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhalation-Based Nanoparticle Drug Delivery Targeting the Diseased Lower Airways in Idiopathic Pulmonary Fibrosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Initiated in the lower airways, idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis (IPF) is a fatal disease that disrupts the lung's functional architecture, for which therapeutics are of limited efficacy; consequently, the disease is progressive and incurable. New therapeutic approaches providing delivery of mechanism-modifying drugs directly to the diseased regions may maximize therapeutic effects while minimizing systemic exposure. In this context, inhalable nanomedicine is an emerging approach for targeted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754911/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pharmacogenomics of Antineoplastic Therapy in Children: Genetic Determinants of Toxicity and Efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Over the past decades, remarkable progress in multimodal therapy has significantly improved survival outcomes for children with cancer. Yet, considerable variability in treatment response and toxicity persists, often driven by underlying genetic differences that affect the pharmacokinetics and pharmacodynamics of anticancer drugs. Pharmacogenomics, the study of genetic determinants of drug response, offers a powerful approach to personalize pediatric cancer therapy by optimizing efficacy while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754908/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Cytoplasmic Transcription and Trimeric RBD Design Synergize to Enhance DNA Vaccine Potency Against SARS-CoV-2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The emergence of immune-evasive SARS-CoV-2 variants highlights the need for adaptable vaccine strategies. Trimeric receptor-binding domain (tRBD) antigens offer structural and immunological advantages over monomeric RBDs, but DNA vaccine efficacy has been limited by inefficient antigen expression, particularly in non-dividing antigen-presenting cells. Although cytoplasmic transcription-based DNA platforms have been developed to overcome nuclear entry barriers, their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microbe-Derived Extracellular Vesicles as Carriers for Doxorubicin Delivery to Colorectal Cancer Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Microbe-derived extracellular vesicles (MEVs) provide a biocompatible, naturally derived platform for drug delivery. Methods: We encapsulated doxorubicin in Lactobacillus plantarum-derived EVs and evaluated their ability at delivering doxorubicin to colorectal cancer cells in vitro. Endocytosis inhibitors were used to investigate the mechanisms by which the MEVs entered the cells. Results: The MEVs maintained structural stability under physiological conditions. Cellular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Traditional Chinese Medicine Retention Enema for Endometriosis: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Herbal retention enema is widely used in Traditional Chinese Medicine for the management of endometriosis; however, its clinical efficacy and safety have not been systematically evaluated. Methods: Ten electronic databases were searched up to May 2025 to identify randomized controlled trials evaluating herbal retention enema as a standalone treatment for endometriosis. Primary outcomes included total effective rate and pain-related measures. Risk of bias was assessed using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing CYP3A4 Inhibition Prediction Using a Hybrid GNN-ML Model with Data Augmentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Cytochrome P450 3A4 (CYP3A4) metabolizes approximately 30-50% of clinically used drugs; thus, accurate prediction of CYP3A4 inhibition is essential for early assessment of drug-drug interaction (DDI) risk and toxicity. This study evaluated an integrated artificial intelligence framework for predicting CYP3A4 inhibition (%) using a large, curated chemical dataset. Methods: A dataset of 23,713 compounds was compiled from the Korea Chemical Bank and multiple commercial and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754799/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Highly Thermally Conductive PDMS/h-BN Composites Enabled by Aspect-Ratio-Driven Alignment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Shear-induced alignment of hexagonal boron nitride (h-BN) platelets offers a scalable route to high-performance, electrically insulating thermal management materials, yet the role of filler geometry under practical shear processing remains unclear. Here, we examine how platelet aspect ratio governs alignment and heat transport in PDMS/h-BN composites processed by sequential roll-gap controlled two-roll milling. Using a geometric moment-arm perspective, we relate the platelet effective radius to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754728/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can Microplastics (MPs) Replace Conventional Mineral Aggregates? A Brief Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microplastics (MPs) are an increasingly pervasive pollutant, prompting interest in using them as a waste valorization feedstock in cementitious composites-most commonly as partial replacements for mineral aggregates. This review critically assesses the technical feasibility and implications of this approach based on current experimental and analytical evidence. Across the literature, MPs differ fundamentally from natural aggregates in stiffness, density, and surface chemistry, which weakens...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Doping Mechanisms and Rational Molecular Design Strategies for High Doping Efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review provides a comprehensive overview of molecular doping in organic semiconductors (OSCs), with particular emphasis on the mechanistic understanding of doping processes, rational material design strategies, and processing approaches for achieving high doping efficiency and stability. We discuss fundamental doping mechanisms, including integer charge transfer and orbital hybridization models, and highlight how molecular structure, polymer design, and dopant-host interactions influence...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754689/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Allomorphic Transformation of Cellulose for Enhancing Enzymatic Accessibility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent decades, lignocellulosic biomass has attracted increasing attention as a sustainable alternative to fossil-fuel-based resources. However, the compact and highly crystalline structure of cellulose remains a major limitation to its effective utilization. In this study, the allomorphic transformation of cellulose was induced through chemical treatments using sodium hydroxide (NaOH) and ethylenediamine (EDA), enabling the conversion of native cellulose I into cellulose II and cellulose...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754631/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conductive Polymers in Lithium-Ion Battery Cathodes: Enhancing Performance and Stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conducting polymers are extensively researched due to their remarkable characteristics, including adaptable and tunable electrical conductivity, straightforward manufacturing process, enhanced mechanical strength, lightweight composition, affordability, and convenience in handling. Furthermore, they demonstrate outstanding chemical stability and elevated thermal conductivity. Conducting polymers can be easily modified with other substances to create composites with improved performance. They are...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754619/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Herpesvirus 6-Associated Miller-Fisher Syndrome in a 5-Year-Old Child: A Case-Based Narrative Review of Pediatric Cases with Infectious Triggers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case raises the hypothesis that HHV-6 may represent a potential post-infectious association in pediatric MFS. The review findings indicate that pediatric MFS generally follows infection, responds well to immunotherapy, and has an excellent prognosis. Viral testing may be considered in selected, hypothesis-generating contexts in atypical or seronegative pediatric MFS presentations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Dietary Patterns and Frailty in Korean Older Adults: Evening-Skewed and Morning-Evening Eating Patterns Associated with Frailty Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Older adults with evening-skewed or morning-evening TDPs had greater frailty risk than those with balanced eating patterns. Optimizing meal timing-by reducing late-day energy loading and ensuring adequate overall intake and dietary quality-may represent a feasible chrono-nutrition strategy for frailty prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Combination of Amaranth Protein Hydrolysate and Korean Mint Extract Ameliorates Cisplatin-Induced Nephrotoxicity and Cachexia in CT26 Tumor-Bearing BALB/c Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings demonstrate that AKE confers comprehensive protection against cisplatin-induced cachexia and nephrotoxicity by coordinately preserving muscle and adipose tissue and attenuating renal injury, suggesting its potential as a functional nutritional strategy to alleviate chemotherapy-associated tissue wasting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754182/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Association Between DTC Obesity-Related Gene Polymorphisms and Obesity Risk Factors in Koreans: Focus on <em>BDNF</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings support the relevance of BDNF rs6265 in obesity phenotypes among Korean adults and provide Korean-specific evidence for genotype-based nutrition strategies. Given the cross-sectional study, the interpretation of personalized nutrition approaches for genetic risk carriers should be made with caution.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Individually Recognized Functional Ingredients of Korean Health Functional Foods: Functional Classification, Regulatory Context, and Clinical Implication]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The global health functional food (HFF) market is expanding rapidly, driven by increasing consumer interest in preventive healthcare and evidence-based nutrition. The Republic of Korea has established a systematic regulatory framework for HFFs, through the Individually Recognized Functional Ingredient (IRFI) system introduced in 2004. Designed to accommodate innovative physiologically active ingredients beyond standardized categories, the IRFI system is increasingly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vitamin D-Mediated Immunoregulation in Degenerative Diseases: Insights into Cardiovascular, Neurodegenerative and Musculoskeletal Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Degenerative diseases are characterized by the gradual loss of cellular integrity, tissue function, and regenerative capacity. Cardiovascular diseases, neurodegenerative disorders, and musculoskeletal deterioration are considered major categories of degenerative diseases, and vitamin D deficiency has been linked with an increased risk of these conditions. Vitamin D has the potential to modulate neurogenerative process by influencing the progression of neuronal survival, neurogenesis, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754146/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Heat-Killed <em>Lactobacillus acidophilus</em> IDCC 3302 on Skin Aging Parameters: A Randomized, Double-Blind, Placebo-Controlled Trial in Healthy Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The 12-week supplementation with ID-ACT 3302 was safe and well tolerated. However, no placebo-adjusted benefit was observed for the prespecified primary wrinkle endpoints. An exploratory between-group difference was observed for the Cutometer overall elasticity index (R2), but because secondary endpoints were not multiplicity-adjusted and the effect size was small, this finding should be interpreted as hypothesis-generating and requires confirmation in adequately powered trials.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coenzyme Q10 Supplementation Modulates Hepatic Lipidomic Alterations and Attenuates Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatohepatitis in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: CoQ supplementation was associated with attenuation of MCD diet-induced MASH and modulation of hepatic phospholipid homeostasis, supporting its potential as a nutritional intervention targeting membrane lipid dysregulation in MASH.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acceptability and Implementation Considerations for 40 Hz Auditory Stimulation Using Nature-Based Soundscapes for Cognitive Health Applications: A Qualitative Exploratory Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In a single-session evaluation among adults aged ≥ 40 years, embedding a 40 Hz sine wave within nature-based soundscapes was generally acceptable, with acceptability sensitive to perceptual integration and usage context. This qualitative study does not assess clinical or cognitive efficacy. These findings inform implementation considerations for cognitive health-oriented delivery, including space-oriented playback options, simplified automation, conservative acoustic safeguards, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41754025/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Disease Activity and Psychosocial Factors Associated with Heath-Related Quality of Life in Patients with Crohn's Disease: A Cross-Sectional Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Crohn's disease has a pattern of recurrent remissions and flare-ups which makes patients experience psychological complications; however, few studies have been conducted to identify intra-personal factors associated with health-related quality of life in individuals with Crohn's disease. This study aimed to explore how disease activity, coping, and post-traumatic growth were associated with health-related quality of life in patients with Crohn's disease. Methods: A cross-sectional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753945/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Low Back Pain in Korea: Survey Weighted Analysis with Age Sex and Lumbar Radiographic Grade Matching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Low back pain (LBP) is a major public health problem that contributes substantially to disability and impaired quality of life. Methods: Using nationally representative data from the fifth Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (KNHANES V), this study evaluated the epidemiology of LBP among Korean adults aged 50-79 years and explored factors associated with LBP in relation to lumbar radiographic findings. Weighted analyses corresponding to an estimated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753936/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parametric Optimization of Microcontact Stamping for Rapid Thermo-Color Change in Pigment-Coated Thin Film]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microcontact stamping is a promising microfabrication technique for producing functional patterned thin films on flexible substrates; however, systematic optimization of its process parameters for thermochromic applications remains limited. In this study, we present a comprehensive parametric optimization of the microcontact stamping process to fabricate thermochromic pigment-coated thin films with rapid and reversible color responses. The effects of liquid resin type, SU-8 mold thickness,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753892/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An End-to-End Design and Simulation Methodology for Evaluating Package-Induced Signal Integrity Degradation in PCIe Channels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an end-to-end simulation methodology for evaluating package-induced signal integrity (SI) degradation in a peripheral component interconnect express (PCIe) 5.0 channel. By integrating package, printed circuit board (PCB), and add-in card (AIC) structures into a unified simulation flow, the proposed approach enables accurate assessment of system-level eye diagram degradation. Various package-level degradation factors, such as impedance mismatch, meander routing, and via stubs,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coarse-to-Fine Contrast Maximization for Energy-Efficient Motion Estimation in Edge-Deployed Event-Based SLAM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Event-based vision sensors offer microsecond temporal resolution and low power consumption, making them attractive for edge robotics and simultaneous localization and mapping (SLAM). Contrast maximization (CMAX) is a widely used direct geometric framework for rotational ego-motion estimation that aligns events by warping them and maximizing the spatial contrast of the resulting image of warped events (IWE). However, conventional CMAX is computationally inefficient because it repeatedly processes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Genetic Characteristics of <em>Enterobacter cloacae</em> and <em>Klebsiella aerogenes</em> in Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the clinical and genomic characteristics of Enterobacter cloacae complex (ECC) and Klebsiella aerogenes bloodstream infections (BSIs) in pediatric patients. A total of 115 BSI episodes (ECC: 86, K. aerogenes: 29) from 110 children hospitalized between 2011 and 2024 were retrospectively analyzed. Whole-genome sequencing was performed on available isolates to determine species, sequence types, and antimicrobial resistance (AMR) genes. Clinical characteristics, antibiotic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Docking and Structure-Activity Relationship Study of Polyphenols with Antibacterial and Antibiotic-Modulating Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The antibacterial activity of 18 phenolic compounds, including flavonoids and phenolic acids, against organisms of Escherichia coli, Klebsiella pneumoniae, and Proteus vulgaris that are resistant to several drugs was assessed in this study using the agar diffusion method. The strain's strong resistance was confirmed by antibiotic susceptibility testing, which used fourteen drugs and only found inhibition zones for five of them. Out of the polyphenols, four compounds were effective against P....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753568/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of Creep Reduction Factors of High-Density Polyethylene Geogrids Using Conventional and Stepped Isothermal Methods]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The long-term creep performance of geosynthetics is crucial for the safe design of reinforced-soil structures. Previous studies have not sufficiently clarified the long-term creep behavior of high-density polyethylene (HDPE) geogrids or the influence of different failure criteria. Therefore, further research is needed to validate creep reduction factors' (RF(CR)) estimation and the applicability of the stepped isothermal method (SIM). In this study, the creep behavior of HDPE geogrids was...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep-Infiltrating Endometriosis Causing Acute Mechanical Intestinal Obstruction Without Intestinal Invasion: A Case Report with Diagnostic and Surgical Insights]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This rare case demonstrates small bowel obstruction caused by DIE adhesions without intestinal invasion. Preoperative imaging facilitated a minimally invasive approach, while combined surgical and hormonal therapy was associated with reduced recurrence risk. These findings expand the recognized spectrum of endometriosis-related intestinal complications and support tailored management strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sustained Intraocular Pressure Control After iStent Infinite<sup>®</sup> Implantation for Steroid-Induced Glaucoma: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Steroid-induced glaucoma (SIG) or ocular hypertension is a well-known complication after corticosteroid exposure to the eye, particularly intravitreal dexamethasone implantation. The main mechanism of elevated intraocular pressure (IOP) is trabecular meshwork dysfunction, leading to increased aqueous outflow resistance. Although most SIG cases respond to medical treatment, some patients develop persistent IOP elevation, requiring surgical intervention. Minimally invasive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753344/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coexistence of Relapsing Polychondritis and Crohn's Disease: Clinical Insights from a Rare Case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Relapsing polychondritis (RP) is a rare immune-mediated inflammatory disorder characterized by recurrent inflammation of cartilaginous structures. Although RP frequently coexists with other autoimmune disorders, its association with inflammatory bowel disease (IBD), particularly Crohn's disease, has been rarely described. We report the case of a 53-year-old man who presented with bilateral auricular inflammation sparing the earlobes and was diagnosed with RP based on clinical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753295/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unrestricted Kinematic Alignment Is a Feasible Strategy for Lateral Compartment Osteoarthritis: Short-Term Outcomes of a Contralateral Knee-Referenced Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Although unrestricted kinematic alignment (uKA) has gained increasing acceptance in total knee arthroplasty (TKA), its application in knees with lateral compartment osteoarthritis (OA) remains a subject of debate due to concerns over postoperative gap imbalance and alignment outliers. The purpose of this study was to evaluate the surgical, radiographic, and clinical outcomes of contralateral non-OA knee-referenced, caliper-verified uKA in lateral compartment OA. Methods:...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753293/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hemodynamic Challenges of Lower Extremity Lymphovenous Anastomosis: A Critical Reappraisal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lymphovenous anastomosis (LVA) has become an established microsurgical treatment for lymphedema, yet the hemodynamic basis for its efficacy in the lower extremity has not been rigorously examined. Most assessments of anastomotic function are performed in the supine position, where lymphatic pressure exceeds venous pressure, creating a favorable gradient for drainage. However, adults spend 16-18 h daily in upright postures, during which ankle-level venous pressure rises to 80-100 mmHg while...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753281/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Does Patellar Resurfacing Improve Outcomes in Valgus Osteoarthritis with Compromised Patellofemoral Joint Status? A Retrospective Consecutive Comparative Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The benefit of patellar resurfacing (PR) in total knee arthroplasty (TKA) remains controversial. No previous study has examined the impact of PR in valgus osteoarthritis (OA) with compromised patellofemoral joint (PFJ) status. Methods: We retrospectively reviewed 2250 primary TKAs performed between 2011 and 2025. Among 152 valgus OA cases, 87 had compromised PFJ status, defined as Outerbridge grade 3-4 chondral damage or patellar tilt >10° on Merchant-view radiographs. Two...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753274/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Upper Extremity Motor Evoked Potentials and Hand Function in Elderly Stroke Survivors: A Correlational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The impact of stroke on upper extremity function in the older adult population underscores the need for accurate recovery prediction. Motor evoked potential (MEP) has been explored as a predictor of upper extremity function recovery in patients with stroke. However, research specifically targeting the geriatric population remains limited. Therefore, this study focused specifically on patients aged 65 years and older to investigate correlations between MEP parameters and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiac Contractility Modulation (CCM) Therapy in Contemporary Heart Failure Care: Mechanisms, Evidence, Patient Selection, and Emerging Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cardiac contractility modulation (CCM) is a bioelectronic therapy that delivers precisely timed electrical signals during ventricular refractoriness to modulate myocardial contractility without triggering depolarization. Unlike pacing-based therapies, CCM does not initiate a new depolarization but instead modulates intracellular signaling pathways to enhance myocardial contractility without increasing myocardial oxygen consumption. CCM therefore represents a myocardial conditioning strategy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of Long-Term Clinical Outcomes Between Immediate-Release and Slow-Release Carvedilol: A National Real-World Database Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Carvedilol, a non-selective β- and α1-blocker, is available in immediate-release (IR) and slow-release (SR) formulations. While carvedilol IR requires twice-daily dosing, SR was developed to improve adherence by allowing once-daily administration. This study aimed to compare long-term clinical outcomes between SR and IR carvedilol. Methods: A total of 38,563 patients taking either SR (n = 6223) or IR carvedilol (n = 32,340) were retrospectively analyzed using national claims data....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753105/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of an Intraoperative Visual Assessment System Based on Bone Mechanical Properties for Selection of Cementless Total Knee Arthroplasty in an Asian Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Successful cementless total knee arthroplasty (TKA) requires adequate bone quality. However, reliable tools for intraoperative assessment remain limited. This study aimed to introduce a novel visual grading system for evaluating femoral bone during surgery and to assess its correlation with actual bone mechanical properties and suitability for cementless fixation. Methods: We prospectively recruited 193 patients receiving posterior-stabilized TKA. Intraoperatively, femoral...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753093/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erector Spinae Plane Block Versus Thoracic Paravertebral Block for Postoperative Analgesia in Thoracic Surgery: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Randomized and Observational Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Both erector spinae plane block (ESPB) and thoracic paravertebral block (TPVB) are widely used for thoracic surgery analgesia, but comparative evidence remains inconsistent. This meta-analysis compared their analgesic efficacy and safety with time-stratified analyses and trial sequential analysis (TSA). Methods: We searched MEDLINE, Embase, Web of Science, and CENTRAL (inception to January 2026) for randomized controlled trials (RCTs) and observational studies comparing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Investigation of the Effects of Entelon150<sup>®</sup>, Losartan, and Rosuvastatin Following Subdermal Valve Prosthesis in a Rat Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Entelon150^(®) (Vitis vinifera seed extract), losartan, and rosuvastatin have been shown to be effective in reducing calcification and inflammation of bovine pericardium implants. However, no study has compared the effects of the drugs on bioprosthetic heart valve (BHV). This study aimed to compare the anti-calcification and anti-inflammatory effects of each drug in a rat model. Methods: Twenty-eight female Sprague-Dawley rats (two weeks old) were implanted with BHV...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41753024/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bmal1 regulates thermogenic function by modulation of lipolytic and OXPHOS gene expression in male mice brown adipocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41749434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The circadian clock plays a critical role in coordinating energy metabolism across tissues, including brown adipose tissue (BAT), a major site of nonshivering thermogenesis. This study aimed to elucidate the cell-autonomous role of the peripheral circadian clock in brown adipocyte thermogenesis using an in vitro model independent of extrinsic cues. Primary brown adipocytes were differentiated from the stromal vascular fraction of interscapular BAT isolated from C57BL/6J mice. An in vitro model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41749434/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-resolution ultrasound imaging of scrotal metastasis from colorectal cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Large atypical cells with foamy cytoplasm in bone marrow in primary splenic angiosarcoma: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial occurrence of glaucomatous visual field damage in the combined 24-2 and 10-2 test locations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758374/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequency and patterns of craniomaxillofacial surgery during and after COVID-19: analysis of the Japanese national database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758370/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robot-assisted anterior resection for rectal cancer in a patient with Leriche syndrome: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758297/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD): a new disease category within the steatotic liver disease (SLD) framework]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758279/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Establishment of local diagnostic reference levels for planning CT in adult and pediatric radiotherapy patients in 18 Japanese university hospitals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occurrence and health risk assessment of AFM1 in commercial yogurt in Thailand]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Milk and dairy products, including yogurt, provide essential nutrients and are widely consumed as valuable protein sources. However, considering then increasing prevalence of Aflatoxin B1 (AFB1) in the diet of dairy cows, concerns arise regarding the possible contamination of milk and dairy products with AFM1, the major metabolite of AFB1 excreted in the milk of lactating animals. AFM1, although less potent when compared to AFB1, has been associated with an increase in the prevalence of human...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758242/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preferential sacral fracture sites in fragility fractures of the pelvis type IVb and comparison of internal fixation methods: CT-based morphological mapping and finite element analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758241/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Intention-Execution Disconnect in Medical AI: The ReXecution Framework for Evaluating Real-World Clinical Performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We present the ReXecution framework for conducting clinician-centered assessments of medical AI assistants, providing detailed insights into their reliability in realistic clinical settings. Using this framework, we assessed AI assistants for chest X-ray (CXR) interpretation, exploring the gap between current model capabilities and real-world radiological needs. Unlike prior benchmarks that rely on automatically generated questions with limited clinical relevance, our dataset consists of 100...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogel microwell with pneumatic soft actuator for compression formation of three-dimensional cellular tissue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Three-dimensional cellular tissue reproduces the structure and function similar to the tissues in the body. So far, as a means for the formation and maturation of three-dimensional cellular tissues, various mechanical stimuli have been applied to cells. Compression by mechanical actuators is a popular method for applying mechanical stimulation to cells. However, the use of linear or rotary actuators limits the direction of compressive stimulation to one axis and requires the cell to be adhered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758116/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Carotid plaque macrophage burden and inflammatory lipid-associated macrophage markers predict secondary major adverse cardiovascular events after endarterectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Together, these findings provide critical insights into the functional differences and origin of macrophage subpopulations in human atherosclerosis and show their clinical significance and risk prediction value in relation to future cardiovascular events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41758068/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automatic acromegaly detection using deep learning on hand images: a multicenter observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights the utility of dorsal hand and fist sign as diagnostic clues for acromegaly, which the AI model captured more accurately than endocrinologists. Using this privacy-conscious feature, this model can be deployed in public settings like health checkups. Further validation using larger datasets, including healthy individuals and diverse diseases, is necessary.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757900/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[External validation and comparison of nomograms for prediction of long-term disease recurrence and survival for bladder cancer patients who undergo radical cystectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All evaluated nomograms showed comparable accuracy in predicting 5-year DFS or CSS, supporting their use in clinical practice. Nonetheless, their limitations should be considered when applying them to individual patient-specific decision-making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From evidence to practice: considerations in the treatment of CRS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND SIGNIFICANCE: Good clinical practice in CRS requires more than adherence to guidelines. Patient-centred care, integration of comorbidities, reinforcement of adherence to basic therapies, and the judicious use of advanced interventions are essential. The future of CRS management lies in reconciling algorithmic guidance with professional judgement to deliver care that is effective, equitable, and sustainable.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757729/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heteroatom doping in carbon macrocycles for advanced synthesis and applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Macrocycles have garnered significant research interest due to their tunable structures, unique physicochemical properties, and broad range of applications in areas such as aggregation-induced emission (AIE), molecular recognition, bioimaging, and photocatalysis. While conventional carbon-rich macrocycles depend mainly on ring-size adjustments for property modulation, the incorporation of heteroatoms (N, O, and S) allows precise control over electronic structure, band gap, and functionality....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757690/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Post-exercise ketone supplementation improves endurance performance and mitochondrial adaptations during an 8-week endurance training intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-exercise ketone supplementation (PEKS) previously improved endurance performance and muscular adaptations during overload training. However, whether and how PEKS improves endurance performance during a periodised endurance training period remains unclear. Twenty-eight trained males completed 8 weeks of supervised cycling, receiving either 25 g of the ketone monoester (R)-hydroxybutyl (R)-hydroxybutyrate (KE, n = 14) or isocaloric placebo (CON, n = 14) post-exercise and before sleep....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757674/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Divergent Synthesis of 1-Aminonaphthalene Derivatives via the Diels-Alder Reaction of 3-Aminoarynes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A divergent synthesis of 1-aminonaphthalenes by the Diels-Alder reaction of 3-aminoarynes followed by diversification is disclosed. The cycloaddition of 3-aminoarynes with 2-substituted furans exhibits unusual proximal selectivity. Owing to the significant versatility of the resulting tricyclic ethers, a wide variety of highly functionalized 1-aminonaphthalenes can be prepared, thereby enabling rapid development of fluorescent dyes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling Halogenated and Nitrogenous DBPs in Chloramination-Ozonation Process: DFT-Driven Formation Pathways from Tyrosine and Toxicity Assessment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The prechloramination followed by ozonation (NH(2)Cl-O(3)) process effectively mitigates bromate (BrO(3)^(-)) formation in bromide-containing waters but inadvertently enhances the production of halogenated and nitrogenous disinfection byproducts (DBPs). Cytotoxicity assays revealed that the presence of precursors such as L-tyrosine (Tyr), L-tryptophan (Trp) and tannic acid during the NH(2)Cl-O(3) process contributed to this increase in nitrogenous and halogenated DBPs and resulted in elevated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Determinants of Site-Specific Core Fucosylation in Human Transferrin: Insights from Crystallography and Molecular Dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Core fucosylation of N-glycans, catalyzed by fucosyltransferase 8 (FUT8), plays a crucial role in various biological processes; however, the structural factors that determine which glycans are site-specifically modified by FUT8 remain poorly understood. Human transferrin carries two N-glycans at Asn432 and Asn630, of which only that at Asn630 is core-fucosylated in serum and cerebrospinal fluids. Here we compared the structural features of the two glycosylation sites on human transferrin as a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circulating microRNAs as biomarkers in pediatric epilepsy: A longitudinal cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</link>
            <description><![CDATA[OBJECTIVE: Epilepsy is the most common chronic neurological disorder in children, and approximately one third of patients develop drug-resistant seizures. Reliable biomarkers are needed to improve diagnosis, prognostic assessment, and treatment monitoring. This study evaluated four circulating microRNAs-miR-15a-5p, miR-106b-5p, miR-146a-5p, and miR-152-3p-as potential diagnostic and prognostic biomarkers in pediatric epilepsy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41757388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260227143827&amp;v=2.19.0.post6+133c1fe</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>