<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:38:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effects of Eye Rubbing on Corneal Topography and Biomechanics in Children With Allergic Conjunctivitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Children with allergic conjunctivitis exhibit increased anterior corneal surface height and front difference deviation. These abnormalities are associated with the frequency of eye rubbing, which influences the TBI via changes in Fe and Df.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090994/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RBC Transfusion Practices in Critically Ill Patients With Sepsis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: RBC transfusions are common in critically ill patients with sepsis, highlighting a gap between clinical practice and guideline recommendations. Although not associated with overall mortality, a qualitative interaction was observed at a hemoglobin threshold of 10 g/dL. Transfusion decisions may be guided by physiologic markers up to 9-10 g/dL, but should be avoided when hemoglobin levels exceed 10 g/dL due to the potential for harm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090988/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystalline Phase-Dependent Emissivity of MoSi<sub>2</sub> Nanomembranes for Extreme Ultraviolet Pellicle Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Extreme ultraviolet (EUV) pellicles must withstand intense thermal stress during exposure due to their limited heat dissipation, which results from their ultrathin geometry and the vacuum environment within EUV scanners. To address this challenge, we investigated the crystalline phase-dependent emissivity of nanometer-thick molybdenum disilicide (MoSi(2)) membranes. Membranes exhibiting amorphous, hexagonal, and tetragonal phases were independently prepared via controlled annealing, and their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutriomics and artificial intelligence nutrition obesity cohort (NAINOC): a design paper for a prospective cohort for nutrition and obesity research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41089592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The strength of this cohort will be as follows. First, the cohort will enable the integration of nutritional intake data with other multiomics data for a comprehensive analysis. Second, inclusion of both obese individuals with various metabolic traits and non-obese individuals as controls is advantageous for studying a wide range of obesity phenotypes in comparison with non-obese conditions. Third, diverse modalities to assess metabolic and complication status will facilitate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41089592/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transparent UVA photodetectors based on oxide semiconductors for real-time wearable skin protection monitoring]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41091884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ultraviolet A (UVA) radiation penetrates deeply into the skin and can potentially damage skin health. Therefore, continuous monitoring of UVA exposure is essential to prevent long-term effects on skin health. For this purpose, UV light sensors should provide selective UVA detection while maintaining high optical transparency in the visible range, enabling integration into wearable and transparent electronic devices. In this study, we fabricated a photodetector optimized for UVA detection based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41091884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Inhibition of NR2F2 suppresses invasion ability and modulates EMT marker in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41091303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nuclear receptor subfamily 2 group F member 2 (NR2F2) has emerged as a potential therapeutic target in cancer due to its involvement in tumor progression, metastasis, angiogenesis, and epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT). However, its precise role in head and neck squamous cell carcinoma (HNSCC) and other cancer types remains to be elucidated. To investigate the role of NR2F2 in HNSCC, we examined its expression in relation to lymph node metastasis (LNM) in patient samples. Further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41091303/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Bifidobacterium longum</em> P77 and <em>Lactiplantibacillus plantarum</em> P72 and Their Mix-Live or Heat-Treated-Mitigate Sleeplessness and Depression in Mice: Involvement of Serotonergic and GABAergic Systems]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sleeplessness (insomnia) is a significant symptom associated with stress-induced depression/anxiety. In the present study, we selected Bifidobacterium longum P77, which increased serotonin production in corticosterone-stimulated SH-SY5Y cells, from the fecal bacteria collection of healthy volunteers and examined the effects of B. longum on depression, anxiety, and sleeplessness induced by immobilization stress or by transplantation of cultured fecal microbiota (cFM) from patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090775/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulating the strigolactone pathway to optimize tomato shoot branching for vertical farming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optimizing plant architecture for specific cultivation methods is essential for enhancing fruit productivity. Unlike indeterminate growth plants, the total productivity of determinate growth plants relies on cumulative fruit production and synchronized fruit ripening from both main and axillary shoots. Here, we focused on SlD14 and SlMAX1, two key genes involved in the regulation of strigolactone (SL) signaling and biosynthesis, with the goal of maximizing yield and synchronizing fruit ripening...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090549/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of Group Cognitive Behavioral Therapy and the Role of Cognitive Ability in Adult Attention-Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41089022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Group-based CBT is an effective adjunct intervention for managing adult ADHD symptoms. Notably, the intervention led to significant improvements in functional impairment, highlighting its potential to enhance daily functioning in adults with ADHD. Tailoring interventions based on cognitive profiles and emphasizing treatment adherence may enhance therapeutic outcomes. Future studies should employ larger sample sizes, randomized controlled designs, and longitudinal follow-up...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41089022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[National Trends in Influenza Vaccination Rates in South Korea Before and During the COVID-19 Pandemic, 2011-2022]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The influenza vaccination rate in South Korea was significantly affected by the COVID-19 pandemic, showing a notable decrease among vulnerable demographic groups. This suggests the need for targeted public health strategies to address vaccine hesitancy and improve vaccination rates, particularly among high-risk populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088811/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Myeloid-Specific STAT3 Deletion Aggravates Liver Fibrosis in Mice Fed a Methionine- and Choline-Deficient Diet via Upregulation of Hepatocyte-Derived Lipocalin-2]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The signal transducer and activator of transcription 3 (STAT3) in myeloid cells suppresses proinflammatory cytokine production and reduces collagen deposition. However, its role in methionine- and choline-deficient (MCD) diet-fed mice remains unclear. This study investigates the effects of myeloid-specific STAT3 deficiency on hepatic inflammation and fibrosis in MCD diet-fed mice. Myeloid-specific STAT3 knockout (mSTAT3KO) mice were fed the MCD diet for four weeks to induce metabolic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41090751/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Protocol of a Nationwide Observational Cohort Study for Long-Term Impacts on Lung Health and Life After Tuberculosis in Korea (LIFE-TB)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study will be the first nationwide observational cohort for PTLD in Korea. It will provide essential real-world data to inform national and global post-TB management strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088970/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence in total knee arthroplasty: clinical applications and implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AI has the potential to significantly reshape TKA by enabling more precise, data-driven, and patient-centered care. However, its promise is contingent on overcoming critical limitations. Broader implementation requires robust multicenter validation to ensure model reliability, the development of explainable algorithms to build clinical trust, and a commitment to responsible innovation. With continued progress, AI can serve as a powerful complementary tool to augment surgical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superoxide-derived singlet oxygen generation via electron transfer-mediated activation of persulfate by heterogeneous biochar catalysts for naproxen degradation: Effects of graphitization degree on electron exchange capacity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41086966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, heterogeneous biochar catalysts derived from spent coffee grounds (HCBCs) and walnut shells (HWBCs) were synthesized at three pyrolysis temperatures (500 °C (HCBC500, HWBC500), 650 °C (HCBC650, HWBC650), and 800 °C (HCBC800, HWBC800)) to elucidate effects of changes in the aromatization degree determining electron exchange capacity (EEC) of heterogeneous biochar catalysts on the degradation of naproxen (NPX) via electron transfer-mediated activation of peroxydisulfate (PDS). The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41086966/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Family roles and limitations as mediators in medical communication for cancer patients: A qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41086197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This qualitative study explored the role and limitations of families as mediators of medical communication among cancer patients in South Korea. Semi-structured interviews were conducted with 46 participants including patients, family members, doctors, and nurses. This study examined how families alleviate communication burdens and navigate power dynamics between patients and physicians. The findings revealed that families gather, interpret, and translate medical information, often acting as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41086197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Composition-Controlled Cathode Protective Layer via Powder-Atomic Layer Deposition for All-Solid-State Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Controlling the ionic and electronic conductivities of the protective layers on cathode active materials (CAMs) is critical for interface stabilization with sulfide-based solid electrolytes in all-solid-state batteries (ASSBs). In this study, lithium zirconium oxide layers with varying compositions are grown on LiNi(0.8)Co(0.1)Mn(0.1)O(2) using an O(3)-based atomic layer deposition process. The ionic conductivity reaches 2.20 × 10^(-7) S cm^(-1) at 25 °C, and the electronic conductivity ranges...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxidation Dynamics and Surface Chemistry of Iridium and Iridium Oxide Films Grown by Atomic Layer Deposition Using O<sub>2</sub> and O<sub>3</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Atomic layer deposition of Ir and IrO(2) is demonstrated using O(2) and O(3) with various exposure conditions as reactants. The nucleation density of Ir increases with the oxidation potential of the reactants, leading to the formation of continuous and conductive films at lower thicknesses. A higher oxidation potential improves the continuity and crystallinity of the Ir films, resulting in a decrease in their resistivity. O(2)-based processes result in Ir metal films regardless of O(2) exposure...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Korean Clinical Practice Guideline of Korean Society for Research on Nicotine and Tobacco (KSRNT) and National Evidence-based Healthcare Collaborating Agency (NECA) on Treatment of Tobacco Use 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tobacco use is a leading cause of preventable death, disease, and disability worldwide. Thus, smoking cessation is a critical public health intervention globally. This clinical practice guideline was developed to provide recommendations on pharmacological and non-pharmacological treatments for smoking cessation, tailored strategies for smoking cessation in special populations, and interventions for users of electronic cigarettes and multiple tobacco products. Thirty key questions and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Stroke in COVID-19 Survivors With Asthma: A Nationwide, Population-Based Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study highlights a significant association between severe COVID-19 and stroke occurrence in adults with asthma, emphasizing the need for ongoing stroke monitoring to improve long-term asthma outcomes during the COVID-19 endemic period.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suppressing Second-Order Jahn-Teller Distortion in VO<sub>2</sub>(B): A Dissolution-Resistant Electrode for Durable Aqueous Energy Storage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of robust, high-performance electrode materials constitutes a critical research frontier in aqueous energy storage systems. Vanadium oxides (VO(x))-based compounds, particularly VO(2)(B), stand out as promising candidates owing to their multivalent redox chemistry and structural diversity. However, their practical implementation frequently encounters obstacles such as dissolution. The corresponding dissolution issue originates from the second-order Jahn-Teller (SOJT) distortion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atrial Cardiopathy Worsens Neurological Severity, Raises Recurrence Rates, and Leads to Poor Vascular Outcomes in Patients With Embolic Stroke of Undetermined Source]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Especially with multiple factors, AC was associated with adverse clinical outcome in patients with ESUS. These findings underscore the importance of AC stratification in the management of ESUS patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real World Efficacy of 1st-Line Nivolumab Plus Ipilimumab and its Practical Predictive Biomarkers in Advanced Renal Cell Carcinoma: First Analysis from RENOIR Study (KCSG GU22-13)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: First-line NI showed comparable and competent efficacy in Korean patients with aRCC. We suggest completing full exposure to ipilimumab and durable response as practical predictors of enriched benefits of NI in our real-world.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084176/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resting state EEG reveals no reliable biomarkers of tinnitus laterality]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study assessed whether resting-state quantitative EEG (qEEG) can differentiate tinnitus laterality under rigorous multiple-comparison control and nested, cross-validated machine learning (ML). We analyzed 210 pre-specified qEEG features-spectral power (n = 95), functional connectivity (n = 80), and hemispheric asymmetry indices (n = 35)-in 110 patients with chronic tinnitus (bilateral = 58, left = 27, right = 16, non-lateralized = 9). Group differences were tested with Kruskal-Wallis tests...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nonsurgical lower eyelid rejuvenation using a novel 1064-nm Nd:YAG laser with a 650- microsecond pulse duration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The lower eyelid region is prone to age-related concerns, including wrinkles and dark circles, resulting from structural changes, such as collagen depletion, fat prolapse, and reduced elasticity. Traditional treatments, such as surgery, fillers, and conventional lasers have limitations including risks, downtime, and variable efficacy. This study evaluated the safety and efficacy of a novel 1064-nm neodymium-doped yttrium aluminum garnet (Nd: YAG) laser with a 650 µs pulse duration for...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085744/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Dual-Responsive Starch Nanoplatform for Triggered Iodine Release against <em>Helicobacter pylori</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Helicobacter pylori is a major cause of chronic gastritis, peptic ulcers, and gastric cancer, yet its eradication is increasingly challenged by antibiotic resistance and poor drug retention in the gastric mucosa. In this study, we developed and characterized iodine-incorporated chitosan-coated starch nanoparticle (I-CS-SNP) as a dual-responsive antibacterial platform. The nanoparticles exhibited uniform size, high iodine loading, and strong mucoadhesive properties with mucopenetrative...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085521/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Annual Dry Weight Changes on Mortality and Cardiovascular Outcomes in Patients Undergoing Haemodialysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Moderate weight gain and loss were differentially associated with lower survival among patients undergoing haemodialysis, with the former in patients with obesity and the latter in normal-weight patients. Particularly, dry weight gain increased the risk of cardiovascular events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085121/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OsABCG37 mediates root development and the stress response by modulating feruloylputrecine levels]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41083912/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydroxycinnamate amides (HCAAs) represent a major class of phenylpropanoid metabolites prevalent throughout the plant kingdom, garnering significant interest due to their roles in various biological processes. In this study, we identified a rice (Oryza sativa) ATP-binding cassette (ABC) transporter, OsABCG37, that influences the level of feruloylputrescine, a HCAA compound. Using the CRISPR/Cas9 system to mutate OsABCG37, we observed impaired development of lateral roots and root hairs....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41083912/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nursing students' perception of integrating flipped learning in a nursing theory course: a qualitative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41088084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solcumin™: a functional hybrid particle with potent anti-inflammatory and antioxidant activities and enhanced storage stability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: To the best of our knowledge, this is the first study to report the development of biomineralization-based Solcumin™ and evaluate its in vitro bioactivity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors influencing serum uric acid levels and their impact on cardiovascular risk in patients with pediatric chronic kidney disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In pediatric CKD, higher serum uric acid levels were associated with male sex, older age, and lower eGFR, suggesting that these factors should be considered in clinical management. Additionally, the U-shaped relationship between serum uric acid levels and cardiovascular risk of hypertension and left ventricular hypertrophy underscores the importance of maintaining serum uric acid within an optimal range.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087594/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning estimation and optimization for evaluation of pharmaceutical solubility in supercritical carbon dioxide for improvement of drug efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study focuses on predicting the solubility of paracetamol and density of solvent using temperature (T) and pressure (P) as inputs. The process for production of the drug is supercritical technique in which the focus was on theoretical investigations of drug solubility and solvent density as well. Machine learning models with a two-input, two-output structure were developed and validated using experimental data on paracetamol solubility as well as density. Ensemble models with decision trees...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087587/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A fusion transfer learning framework for intelligent pest recognition in sustainable agriculture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With the fast growth in the population of the world, there is a constantly increasing requirement for sustainable food supplies. Agriculture is the backbone of the global food supply, with vegetables and fruits being essential for a balanced intake. Still, in recent years, the global distribution of malignant plant pests and illnesses has given rise to significant losses in the quality and yield of crops. Thus, automated detection of plant diseases is vital in monitoring huge areas of crops and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087550/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augmented Reality-Based Exercise for Older Adults: A Randomized Controlled Trial on Physical Function and Mobility]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: AR-based exercise improves physical fitness, especially lower limb and respiratory muscle function, in older adults. These findings support its potential to promote functional health and mobility in aging populations. Significance/Implications: With growing demand for engaging rehabilitation strategies, AR-based exercise programs could support healthy aging and independent living in clinical and community settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41087006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Anti-atopic Perilla Seed Oil and Ethanol Extract on TNF-α/IFN-γ-Stimulated inflammatory Responses in Human HaCaT Keratinocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chronic inflammatory atopic dermatitis (AD) is a skin disorder characterized by cutaneous inflammation and a dysfunctional skin barrier. Although perilla seed oil (PO) is known to exhibit various biological activities, including anti-cancer, anti-inflammatory, and anti-oxidant effects, its inhibitory effects together with the ethanol extract of PO (PE) on atopic and inflammatory responses in the dermal skin has not yet been investigated. In the present study, PE significantly reduced mRNA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41085638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of ambient exposure to benzene, toluene, ethylbenzene, and xylene with daily mortality: a multicountry time-series study in 757 global locations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: The presence of benzene, toluene, ethylbenzene, and xylene isomers (BTEX) in the environment is of increasing concern due to their toxicity and ubiquity. Although the adverse health effects of BTEX exposure have been documented, robust epidemiological evidence from large-scale, multicountry studies using advanced exposure assessment methodologies remains scarce. We aimed to assess the association of short-term ambient exposure to individual BTEX components and their mixture with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084608/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[11α-hydroxyprogesterone dampens lung metastasis via EMT modulation in PyMT-induced breast cancer murine model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that 11α-OHP may suppress breast cancer metastasis by modulating EMT, highlighting its potential as a therapeutic target for preventing metastatic progression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41084087/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of mechanisms and efficiencies for Mn decrease at unit processes in passive treatment facilities for mine drainage]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In passive treatment facilities, a limestone reaction and oxidation alone are generally ineffective in treating Mn, but decreases in Mn concentration are observed. Predicting Mn decrease efficiency and assessing the mechanisms underlying Mn treatment in passive treatment facilities are important steps in calculating the area required for conventional Mn treatment or in deciding whether the addition of limestone beds, slag leach beds, slag reactors, or the Pyrolusite process is required. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081950/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expressway conflict risk mechanism considering the interactions between vehicle-group and road-segment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study demonstrates that vehicle-groups and road-segments interact in the propagation of expressway conflict risk. Integrating these two dimensions enables more accurate conflict risk prediction and analysis. This research provides a novel perspective by integrating vehicle-group and road-segment interactions for more accurate conflict risk prediction and analysis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Premorbid functioning trajectories and the one-year course of cognitive performance in first-episode psychosis: a cluster analysis in PSYSCAN]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41079561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study confirms a positive association between PMF and cognitive performance in the early years following psychosis onset. It aligns with findings that individuals later diagnosed with schizophrenia already show developmental deficits/lags from childhood to early adolescence compared to normally developing children. As PMF can be considered a proxy for cognitive reserve, our results suggest that higher reserve acts as a buffer against cognitive decline and supports better...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41079561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Significant Reduction of Systematic PAH and NPAH Discharges from Hazardous Waste Treatment by the Advanced Scrubbing and Circular GASMILD Combustion]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study systematically investigates the application of sludge and fly ash circular combustion (SFACC) under gasification-moderate or intense low-oxygen dilution (GASMILD) incineration in a hazardous waste thermal-treatment system (HAWTTS) to achieve significant reductions in hazardous air pollutants. The aim of this research is to evaluate whether integrating residue reinjection into a closed-loop GASMILD system can enhance the net removal efficiency of polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons (PAHs)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078800/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence-Driven Drafting of Chest X-Ray Reports: 2025 Position Statement From the Korean Society of Thoracic Radiology Based on an Expert Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The KSTR supports the use of an AI-based automated CXR report-drafting tool only in health-screening settings with radiologist validation and opposes its standalone use in routine practice, recommending performance optimization and society-endorsed education and guidelines before its adoption.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design of Scalable and Flexible Supercapacitors Based on Mulberry Paper: Optimizing Electrochemical Performance and Reliability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Paper-based supercapacitors are emerging as promising alternatives for next-generation wearable energy storage applications, attributed to their renewable feedstocks, scalability, flexibility, and lightweight properties. However, the inherent limited electrochemical conductivity and poor stability of paper remain significant challenges for making high-performance applications. In this study, we designed a scalable and flexible supercapacitor utilizing carbonized mulberry paper (cMP) to overcome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effect of Tegoprazan on Serum Gastrin Levels and the Development of Hypergastrinemia in the Maintenance Treatment for Gastroesophageal Reflux Disease: Comparison to Lansoprazole]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Tegoprazan has a smaller impact on increasing serum gastrin levels and the development of hypergastrinemia than lansoprazole, suggesting that tegoprazan may reduce safety concerns related to hypergastrinemia, particularly at half doses.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Enhanced Dietary Education Program on Gastrointestinal Symptoms in Patients With Functional Gastrointestinal Disorders: A Multicenter Prospective Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although, EDE has the potential to help improving the symptoms in patients with FGIDs, further research is needed to prove the usefulness of this program.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077747/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robotic arm control by augmented reality-assisted object detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41083557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Various robotic arm control systems have been proposed to support the daily lives of patients with severe motor impairments; however, existing robotic arm control devices typically require physical input devices, such as joysticks, which are often difficult for patients with motor impairments to use. To overcome these limitations, this paper proposes a new method for controlling a robotic arm using augmented reality and object detection. The system automatically configures the path from the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41083557/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term effectiveness of live zoster vaccine against herpes zoster and related complications: a nationwide emulated target trial in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Live attenuated zoster vaccination was associated with substantially reduced risks of herpes zoster and its complications in South Korea. Despite waning, protection persisted for 8 years, supporting the continued role of live attenuated zoster vaccine, particularly where recombinant vaccines are limited.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082816/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AP2M1 Amplification Orchestrates Notch-Mediated Chemoresistance in Hematopoietic Stem Cells of Acute Myeloid Leukemia Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acute myeloid leukemia (AML) is a complex hematological malignancy characterized by chemotherapy resistance, leading to poor patient outcomes. This study investigates the role of adaptor protein complex 2 subunit mu 1 (AP2M1) in hematopoiesis and drug response. Utilizing multimodal analyses on bone marrow samples from AML patients and healthy controls, zebrafish models, and human AML cell lines, it is identified that dysregulation of AP2M1 impairs hematopoietic stem and progenitor cell (HSPC)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082341/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SIRT1-FOXO1 Signaling in Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sirt1 (sirtuin 1) is a member of the sirtuin family of NAD^(+)-dependent histone deacetylases, which mediates the deacetylation of both histone and nonhistone protein substrates, including enzymes and transcription factors. Through this process, Sirt1 regulates gene transcription and activates various cellular functions. FOXO1 (forkhead box protein O1), a key substrate of sirt1, is a transcription factor that controls the expression of genes involved in a wide range of cellular processes. In the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082310/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acceptor engineering in triphenylamine-based push-pull dyes for enhanced photosensitization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Donor-acceptor dyes were designed by conjugating a common triphenylamine donor with acceptors of varying strengths to enhance Type I photosensitization efficiency. Among these, TTCF, featuring the strongest tricyanofuran acceptor, generated 2.4 times more superoxide radicals than the reference photosensitizer rose bengal, through aggregation-induced intersystem crossing leading to efficient electron transfer mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41082193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feed-forward inhibitory circuit from the anterior cingulate cortex regulates periaqueductal gray's panic-like responses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Threatening events elicit panic responses characterized by rapid movement, sympathetic arousal, and negative emotions-critical, instantaneous reactions that can determine survival in moments of acute danger. This study elucidates the neural circuit architecture underlying these responses, focusing on projections from the anterior cingulate cortex (ACC) to the dorsolateral periaqueductal gray (dlPAG) in male mice. We demonstrate that a subpopulation of GABAergic neurons (^(ACC→)dlPAG neurons) in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resection arthroplasty for deep shoulder infection in a native shoulder with an intact rotator cuff: a salvage option when reverse shoulder arthroplasty is not feasible]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41081919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kinase suppressor of Ras 1 (KSR1) promotes liver carcinogenesis via activation of the RAS/RAF/MEK/ERK signaling pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overexpression of KSR1 activates the RAS/RAF/MEK/ERK signaling pathway and drives hepatic tumorigenesis in the absence of mutations in RAS or RAF.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078702/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DeepUS-ReconSeg: A multi-angle paired B-mode Ultrasound dataset for medical imaging reconstruction and segmentation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41079693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article presents a curated dataset of 4,200 B-mode ultrasound images of human forearms, intended for use in deep learning-based image reconstruction and segmentation tasks. Data have been collected using the Verasonics Vantage 64LE system equipped with an L11-5v linear array transducer, known for its high spatial resolution. Each scanning session captures 100 frames per orientation across both arms of 14 healthy subjects, covering multiple anatomical views. The dataset provides grayscale...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41079693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydroxyapatite particles substituted with Pd ions for remarkable antibacterial performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing threat of bacterial infections to human health has positioned the development of antibacterial materials as a critical global research priority. Recently, hydroxyapatite (HAP), which is chemically similar to the main components of bone and teeth, has attracted considerable attention as a promising antibacterial material due to its ability to inhibit bacterial adhesion and proliferation through electrostatic repulsion. However, hydroxyapatite exhibits lower antibacterial activity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41078389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Observation of Λ Hyperon Local Polarization in p-Pb Collisions at sqrt[s_{NN}]=8.16 TeV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41076707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The polarization of the Λ and Λ[over ¯] hyperons along the beam direction has been measured in proton-lead (p-Pb) collisions at a center-of-mass energy per nucleon pair of 8.16 TeV. The data were obtained with the CMS detector at the LHC and correspond to an integrated luminosity of 186.0±6.5 nb^{-1}. A significant azimuthal dependence of the hyperon polarization, characterized by the second-order Fourier sine coefficient P_{z,s2}, is observed. The P_{z,s2} values decrease as a function of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41076707/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-proliferative effects of novel T-type calcium channel blocker KCP10043F in human pancreatic cancer cells through Ca<sup>2+</sup>/CaMKII pathway via ER stress induction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic cancer is among the most lethal cancer types with a 5-year survival rate of approximately 5 %. Although a T-type calcium channel blocker, 4-(4-fluorobenzylcarbamoylmethyl)-3-(4-cyclohexylphenyl)-2-[3-(N,N-dimethylureido)-N'-methylpropylamino]-3,4-dihydroquinazoline (KCP10043F, OZ-001), previously exhibited the anti-tumor effects in lung cancer, its anti-proliferative effects and the specific molecular mechanisms in pancreatic cancer remain unclear. This study was conducted to evaluate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41077271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Free testosterone and cognitive function: Sex-specific links in adults in the nationwide Korean frailty and aging cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41076785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This population-based cross-sectional study of older Korean adults found that lower serum FT levels were independently associated with cognitive impairments across multiple domains in women but not men. These findings highlight FT's potential role in cognitive impairment, particularly among women.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41076785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Trends and determinants of red blood cell transfusion in liver cancer surgeries in Korea (2012-2020)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study detailed RBC transfusion trends in liver cancer surgeries in Korea from 2012 to 2020, identifying a significant decline in transfusion rates and key factors like surgical method and timing. The importance of this research is its potential to guide optimal patient blood management strategies, emphasizing considerations necessary for improving transfusion practices and patient outcomes in liver cancer surgeries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075347/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shift from Streptococcus pneumoniae to Klebsiella pneumoniae: A 15-year nationwide study of bacterial meningitis in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41076061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Over 15 years in Korea, the declining incidence of S. pneumoniae meningitis coincided with widespread pneumococcal vaccination, while K. pneumoniae has become the leading cause. Given its association with poor outcomes, K. pneumoniae meningitis requires increased awareness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41076061/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Superheated steam for regeneration of biomass-derived activated carbon: comparative evaluation of performance, life cycle impacts and net CO<sub>2</sub> offset potential]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coconut-shell derived activated carbon (AC); GCN has been used extensively in water treatment as an efficient adsorbent material. However, ACs progressively saturate with contaminants over time and require periodic regeneration to regain adsorption efficiency. This study presents an advanced superheated steam (SPH) (at 600 °C) method to regenerate saturated AC. This steam drives adsorbed contaminants to break down and detach from the carbon pores. With a regeneration efficiency of 95 %, SPH...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Schizandrin ameliorates post-traumatic stress disorder-like behaviors via 5-HT<sub>1A</sub> receptor in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors are the primary treatment for post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), they do not address all aspects of PTSD, highlighting the need for new therapies. Schizandrin, a lignan compound found in Schisandra chinensis, alleviates cognitive dysfunction, depression-like behaviors, and anxiety, suggesting that it may ameliorate PTSD symptoms. However, to date, no studies have explored the effects of schizandrin on PTSD symptoms. In the present study, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controlling 3-hydroxyhexanoate mole fraction in poly (3-hydroxybutyrate-co-3-hydroxyhexanoate) by altering enoyl-CoA hydratase (phaJ) ribosome-binding site in Cupriavidus necator H16]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyhydroxyalkanoate (PHA) is a bioplastic attracting interest as an alternative to petroleum-based plastics. Particularly, poly (3-hydroxybutyrate-co-3-hydroxyhexanoate) (P(3HB-co-3HHx)), which shows notable polymeric properties, is usually produced using the engineered Cupriavidus necator. Currently, production of P(3HB-co-3HHx) is primarily possible by engineering phaC, however, relatively rare study of controlling the expression of enoyl-CoA hydratase (phaJ(Pa)), which is directly involved...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074969/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genistein Reduced Eosinophilic Inflammation and Remodeling by Downregulating PAI-1 and TSLP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074673/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of heart transplantation using ECMO-supported donation in brain dead donors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Prior to donation, ECMO can be effectively used in brain-dead donors, to improve the rate of heart transplants. The postoperative outcomes of recipients, who received hearts procured from ECMO-supported donors, were satisfactory. Among ECMO-supported DBD donors, the median age tended to be lower in the transplanted donor group.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41075114/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suprahyoid Muscle Strengthening Using a Novel Exercise Device in Older Adults With Oral Hypofunction: A Randomised Placebo-Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that the novel neck-collar exercise device is effective in enhancing suprahyoid muscle activation and thickness, and in reducing the risk of airway penetration and aspiration in older adults with oral hypofunction.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Progressive Hippocampal Neuroarchitecture Changes in the 5×FAD Alzheimer's Disease Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest a potential relationship between AD-related protein pathology, neuroinflammation, and structural plasticity impairments in the hippocampus. Collectively, these changes may contribute to disrupted synaptic transmission and behavioral deficits associated with AD pathology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41074418/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A web-based mouse-tracking task for early perceptual language processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The study of language processing requires data from a wide range of languages but also data that are free from demand characteristics and meta-linguistic strategies. While eye-tracking has been successfully used to address the later issue, pragmatically, eye-tracking is often difficult to achieve with less well-studied languages. Therefore, the current paper presents a web-based mouse-tracking task that generates data that seem to reflect early perceptual processes similar to eye-tracking but...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073846/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tunnel enabled programmable switches obfuscate network topology to defend against link flooding reconnaissance in software defined networking]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Recently, Software-Defined Networking (SDN) has emerged as an increasingly popular network paradigm due to its virtualization capabilities and flexibility. However, its robustness in link connectivity is threatened by Link Flooding Attacks (LFAs). To launch LFAs, adversaries use probing tools to infer network topologies and identify target links with bottlenecks. Thus, protecting SDN topologies against disclosure is crucial to ensure system security and preserve infrastructure functionality. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated AI based identification of autism spectrum disorder from home videos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Autism spectrum disorder (ASD) is a prevalent childhood-onset neurodevelopmental condition. Early diagnosis remains challenging by the time, cost, and expertise required for traditional assessments, creating barriers to timely identification. We developed an AI-based screening system leveraging home-recorded videos to improve early ASD detection. Three task-based video protocols under 1 min each-name-response, imitation, and ball-playing-were developed, and home videos following these protocols...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A highly miniaturized circularly polarized self-duplexing implantable antenna with enhanced performance for wireless capsule endoscopy applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Multiband implantable antennas are crucial components of biomedical implantable devices (BIDs), enabling the establishment of wireless communication links with external base stations. These types of antennas perform various functions such as data transmission, wireless power transfer, and control signaling. However, this scenario requires an external multiplexer in the BIDs to separate various frequency bands, imposing size constraints on the BIDs. This work proposes a self-duplexing circularly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073415/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pre-lithiation empowers the future of lithium-ion batteries: strategies, applications, and outlook]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073199/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending the Lens: Long-Term Impact of COVID-19 on COPD Management and Outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073042/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimal Strategy for Thromboprophylaxis in Fontan Circulation: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis with a Focus on Ethnic Differences]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fontan circulation alters cardiovascular hemodynamics to maintain circulation using a single ventricle, which may consequently increase the risk of thromboembolism. This highlights the need for effective thromboprophylaxis strategies. This study assessed optimal thromboprophylaxis regimens for patients with Fontan circulation through a comprehensive meta-analysis of literature focused on personalized, ethnicity-based approaches. PubMed, Embase, and Cochrane Library databases were searched to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ApneaWhisper: Transformer-Based Audio Segmentation for Fine-Grained Non-Invasive Sleep Apnea Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The model's fine-grained temporal resolution enables precise apnea event localization, duration estimation, and subtype classification. While ApneaWhisper performs robustly for OSA, challenges remain in distinguishing central (CSA) and mixed (MSA) sleep apnea, due to subtle or ambiguous acoustic patterns. The frame-level segmentation also facilitates accurate apnea-hypopnea index (AHI) estimation, which could reduce dependence on full PSG studies in certain clinical and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069504/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Normal and nonnormal polynomial regression mixture modeling for differential congruence effects: A simulation and tutorial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polynomial regression with response surface analysis (PRRSA) has been widely adopted in congruence research when the relation of congruence to an outcome is examined. However, PRRSA assumes that the congruence effects are homogeneous across all individuals. Polynomial regression mixture analysis (PRMix) allows for heterogeneity in the effect of congruence on an outcome across individuals and identifies latent classes of differential congruence effects. In this study, through Monte Carlo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073630/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unraveling the roles of network and tunnels in the conductivity of carbon nanofiber composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, an advanced conductivity model for polymer-carbon nanofiber (CNF) samples is introduced, stated as PCNFs. This model considers the length (l), radius (R) and amount of CNFs, interphase depth, percolation onset (PT), waviness, network portion, and tunneling length (d), by reasonable and meaningful equations. The proposed model is verified through the measured conductivity of samples and by studying the features' influences on the PCNF conductivity. The model calculations display...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discovery of molecular signature of long-term psychiatric sequelae in COVID-19 through proteome profiling of dried blood spots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuropsychiatric sequelae represent a significant aspect of post-acute sequelae of SARS-CoV-2 (PASC, or long COVID), posing considerable public health challenges. This study identified molecular signatures associated with PASC in individuals with psychiatric morbidities via dried blood spot proteomic analysis. We evaluated 51 COVID-19 survivors ≥ 60 days post-infection, categorizing them into three groups: those with new-onset psychiatric disorders (n = 16, psychiatric PASC), those with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073392/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of 10 principles of radiation protection in oral and maxillofacial radiology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The finalized principles constitute a structured, evidence-based guideline aligned with international standards while addressing specific challenges unique to oral and maxillofacial radiology. They offer practical strategies to enhance patient safety and standardize radiographic decision-making. Further research should investigate their clinical implementation and recommend periodic updates to reflect evolving technologies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Performance of GPT-4 for planning acupuncture treatment: comparison with human clinician performance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GPT-4 made reasonable acupoint suggestions, with notable overlap observed with the prescriptions of doctors. This shows its promise for supporting medical decisions, education, and personalized medicine for patients undergoing acupuncture treatment. Future studies and validation are necessary to ensure the reliability and efficacy of applying GPT-4 in real-world settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070078/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative Pharmacoinformatic and Experimental Validation of Indonesian Red Algae as Novel Functional Food for Anti-Gastric Cancer Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gastric cancer remains a major global health burden with limited therapeutic options due to resistance and toxicity of current treatments. Marine red algae-Gracilaria edulis, Eucheuma denticulatum, and Kappaphycus striatus-are underexplored sources of bioactive compounds that may offer multi-targeted, low-toxicity agents for gastric cancer therapy. This study integrated phytochemical profiling, structure-activity relationship (SAR) analysis, network pharmacology, molecular docking, molecular...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069123/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cationic Point Defect Fluoride to Improve Reaction Kinetics in (All) Solid-State Li Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nickel-rich cathode materials (NCM) have emerged as promising candidates for lithium-ion batteries (LIBs) and all-solid-state batteries (ASSBs) due to their high reversible capacity (>200 mAh g^(-1)). However, surface side reactions with liquid and solid electrolytes during cycling increase interfacial resistance and accelerate capacity fading, thereby hindering the practical implementation of NCM cathodes. To achieve high-energy LIBs and ASSBs, it is essential to control the interfacial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069062/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utilization of sequential model-based optimizer integrated machine learning models in correlation of famotidine solubility in supercritical carbon dioxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigated solubility variations of a medication in supercritical carbon dioxide with an insight into preparation of nanomedicines with improved aqueous solubility. As the case study, the solubility of famotidine (FAM) medicine in sc-CO(2) (supercritical carbon dioxide) was computed as a function of temperature and pressure, with a particular focus on modeling and predicting solubility and sc-CO(2) density. Three regression models with machine learning behavior including Quadratic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073646/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography angiography findings in patients with sudden sensorineural hearing loss]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sudden sensorineural hearing loss (SSNHL) is a common otological condition; however, its pathophysiology and prognostic factors remain unclear. We aimed to investigate the relationship between retinal microvascular changes and the severity and prognosis of SSNHL using optical coherence tomography angiography (OCTA), exploring the role of ocular microcirculation. A prospective cohort study was conducted on 88 patients with SSNHL between December 2019 and December 2022. All patients underwent OCTA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073417/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and Safety of Rosuvastatin/Amlodipine FDC in Patients With Hypertension and Dyslipidemia: A Multicenter, Prospective, Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this large real-world study, Ros/Aml demonstrated a favorable safety profile and was effective in reducing MACCE risk, blood pressure, and lipid levels over 12 months. These findings in patients with hypertension and dyslipidemia support its use as a viable strategy for integrated cardiovascular risk management in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41073206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of Phase Angle Cutoff Values Derived From Bioelectrical Impedance Analysis for Sarcopenia Screening in Community-Dwelling Older Korean Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: The established PhA cutoff values can be integrated into routine health assessments, enabling early detection and targeted interventions that could improve the quality of life of this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41072487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Management of the pterygoid plate in orthognathic surgery: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: All three methods of pterygoid plate management-fracture, removal, and grinding-are all effective methods that provide skeletal stability and demonstrate no significant differences in complications including bleeding. Optimal technique selection should be guided by detailed anatomical knowledge, patient-specific factors, and intraoperative findings to maximize surgical safety and effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41071524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of nutritional awareness, body mass index, mental health, and fitness components among undergraduate university students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The study generally aimed to examine nutritional awareness, body mass index, mental health, dietary awareness, and components of physical fitness among university students by investigating the health behaviors, physical activity, diet, sleep, internet use, and mental health of 153 undergraduate university students.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41070009/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of inhaling <em>Cunninghamia lanceolata</em> essential oil on the physiological and psychological relaxation of university students]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[University students face multiple stressors, which can impair their physical and mental health without timely intervention. Despite the close link between nature and wellbeing, as well as the growing interest in using natural substances for health management, the effectiveness of Cunninghamia lanceolata essential oil (C. lanceolata EO) in alleviating emotional disorders among university students remains underexplored. This study investigated the physiological and psychological effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41069676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between physical activity domains and cardiovascular diseases among US adults: evidence from NHANES 2007-2020]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined the associations between different domains of physical activity, leisure-time (LTPA), occupational (OPA), and transportation-related (TPA), and cardiovascular disease (CVD) risk among U.S. adults. Data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES) 2007-2008 through March 2020 were used. Physical activity was self-reported using the Global Physical Activity Questionnaire. Weekly minutes of LTPA, OPA, and TPA were calculated and categorized as: <150,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tizoxanide associated with anti-virulent activity controls fire blight disease caused by Erwinia amylovora in Malus asiatica]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Erwinia amylovora is a causative pathogen of fire blight disease, affecting apple, pear, and other rosaceous plants. This study aimed to discover new anti-virulence agents to control this plant bacterial disease by preventing its pathogenesis. To this end, 2485 small molecules were screened for targeting the type III secretion system (T3SS) which is a critical virulence factor in E. amylovora. Our screening identified tizoxanide as a potent inhibitor, significantly reducing the promoter activity...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068275/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SAPP: Structure Aware PTM Prediction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Post-translational modifications (PTMs) play critical roles in regulating cellular processes such as signal transduction, cell growth, and differentiation. Accurate identification of PTM sites is fundamental to understanding cellular mechanisms and developing therapeutic interventions. However, traditional computational models have predominantly relied on sequence data alone, neglecting important structural contexts such as intrinsically disordered regions and solvent accessibility. To address...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066820/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phytochemical inhibition of quorum sensing and biofilm formation by <em>Paederia foetida</em> Linn. against multidrug-resistant <em>Acinetobacter baumannii</em>: An integrated <em>in vitro</em> and <em>in silico</em> investigation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: P. foetida extract exhibits potent antibacterial, anti-QS, and antibiofilm activity against MDR A. baumannii, supported by its phytochemical diversity, favorable pharmacokinetics, and strong protein-ligand interactions. These findings suggest its promise as a plant-derived therapeutic aligned with the One Health framework to combat antimicrobial resistance in both human and veterinary medicine.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Independent associations between obesity, glucose metabolism, and breast cancer risk through unrelated pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although BMI and WC are robustly linked to BC risk, FBG plays a negligible mediating role. These findings suggest that obesity and glucose metabolism independently influence breast cancer risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Higher-order factorization machine for accurate surrogate modeling in material design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient and robust optimization is important in material science for identifying optimal structural parameters and enhancing material performance. Surrogate-based active learning algorithms have recently gained great attention for their ability to efficiently navigate large, high-dimensional design spaces. Among surrogate models, 2^(nd)-order factorization machine (FM) models are widely employed as the surrogate model in active learning algorithms due to their balance between simplicity and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41068231/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Controversies, Consensuses, and Guidelines on the Etiology, Diagnosis and Management of Intraocular Foreign Bodies (IOFBs) by the Academy of Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO) and the Asia-Pacific Vitreo-retina Society (APVRS)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41067482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The strong majority of consensus statements serves as a useful guidance, enabling clinicians to approach IOFB removal in a systemic manner with more confidence and improve patient outcomes. The varying levels of agreement in some statements underscore remaining uncertainties in IOFB clinical management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41067482/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Harnessing lignin in membrane engineering: from green polymer to high-performance applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41067354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lignin, a widely used natural polymer, has garnered significant interest as a sustainable and cost-effective resource for the production of separation membranes. This review emphasizes current progress in the application of lignin as a primary polymer and additive in diverse membrane separation technologies, including exchange, pressure-driven, antifouling, gas separation, adsorption, battery separator, and pervaporation membranes. The distinctive physicochemical characteristics of lignin-its...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41067354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence of and factors associated with potassium supplementation in older adults from general practices in Germany]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this preliminary research, less than 5 % of older adults received potassium supplementation in primary care. More data are warranted to corroborate this figure in other settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066889/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of radiation dose for opening and closing the steam generator primary manways during the overhaul period]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In primary system maintenances performed during the overhaul period of nuclear power plant, radiation exposure mainly results from neutron-activated corrosion products. During the overhaul period, opening and closing the steam generator primary manways is one of the representative maintenances. This maintenance activity involves performing tasks in close proximity to the activated corrosion products, resulting in somewhat high exposure levels for workers. In this study, worker radiation doses...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessment of K-40 and Cs-137 radioactivity concentrations and annual effective dose due to ingestion of staple foods in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Korea Institute of Nuclear Safety (KINS) has designated Rice and Napa cabbage, which account for a large proportion of the Korean diet, as staple foods for continuous radioactivity monitoring. Assessing internal exposure from food ingestion is essential for public health and radiation safety. This study evaluated the radioactivity concentrations of these foods and quantified annual effective doses from their ingestion. Samples of Rice and Napa cabbage collected from 15 regions nationwide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrochemical Dehydrogenation of Piperazine on Pd-Based Multimetallic Alloy Catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrogen, an essential clean energy carrier, poses challenges in terms of efficient and scalable storage. Liquid organic hydrogen carriers (LOHCs) have gained attention as viable chemical media for hydrogen storage and release, providing advantages such as high energy density and compatibility with zero-emission fuel cells. Nevertheless, a critical bottleneck is the development of cost-effective and stable electrocatalysts for LOHC dehydrogenation, particularly using noble metal catalysts such...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Jujuboside B Induces Ferroptosis and Overcomes Radioresistance Through the PPARγ-ATF3-Gpx4 Signaling Pathway in Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Jujuboside B (JJB) is a saponin extracted from the Ziziphus jujuba var. spinose and has been reported to have anticancer effects. However, the detailed mechanism of its anti-cancer effect in non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) remains unclear. New combination therapies may be able to overcome TRAIL resistance. In this study, we found that JJB regulates the activity of PPARγ and investigated whether the combination of JJB and TRAIL had synergistic anti-cancer effects against NSCLC cells....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolvin E1 improves the maturation of porcine oocytes by suppressing oxidative stress via Nrf2 pathway activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41067363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Resolvin E1 (RvE1) is a specialized pro-resolving mediator from the bioactive lipid family that has been detected in follicular fluid and serum and is secreted by cumulus cells during culture. However, its role in mammalian oocyte maturation remains poorly understood. We investigated the antioxidant function of RvE1 and its underlying mechanisms during meiotic progression. RvE1 significantly enhanced cumulus cell expansion and increased the rate of metaphase II oocytes compared to controls....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41067363/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The soil nematode exposome: Unraveling the impacts of particulate plastics from agroecosystems to one health]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The escalating accumulation of particulate plastics in terrestrial ecosystems demands innovative, biologically informed approaches to evaluate their ecological and human health impacts. Soil nematodes are gaining recognition as sensitive and ecologically relevant bioindicators for assessing the effects of plastic pollution in soils. Their widespread distribution, trophic adaptability, and close association with soil particles make them ideal sentinels for detecting subtle yet significant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41066946/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of cyclosporine in colitis: An updated meta-analysis of randomized control trials (1998 to 2024)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: There is no statistically significant difference between cyclosporine compared to the control group in improving clinical outcomes for patients with ulcerative colitis. Future studies with larger sample sizes can explore its role with combination therapy in targeted patient sub-groups.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tongue-Strengthening Exercise in Older Adults With Sarcopenic Dysphagia: A Randomised Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: TSE with an intensity of 80% 1RM was more effective than 50% 1RM in increasing tongue strength and thickness in older adults with sarcopenic dysphagia, but showed a relatively high dropout rate. Thus, it is recommended to select and apply an appropriate exercise intensity.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41065294/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Study of the electronic, magnetic, and thermoelectric aspects of spinel chalcogenides SrCe<sub>2</sub>Z<sub>4</sub> (Z = Te, Se, S) for spintronic and energy applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spinel chalcogenides are promising candidates for the advancement of spintronic and thermoelectric devices. Therefore, this article presents the structural, electronic, and magnetic characteristics of SrCe(2)Z(4) (Z = S, Se, Te) spinels employing WIEN2k in the context of density functional theory. The expansion of the unit cell is witnessed with the incorporation of larger anions and lattice parameters, including 12.01 Å for SrCe(2)S(4), 12.52 Å for SrCe(2)Se(4), and 13.42 Å for SrCe(2)Te(4)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41064135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unveiling the clinical and genetic impact of neuropsychiatric involvement in systemic lupus erythematosus]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Neuropsychiatric involvement in SLE increases clinical manifestations and extends organ damage beyond the nervous system, with NPSLE-related genetic variants highlighting their potential functional roles in various brain regions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning based prediction of waste activated sludge generation for optimization of WWTP operational efficiency]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study predicted the amount of waste activated sludge withdrawn for external disposal based on process operation and water quality data using machine learning models. By combining hyperparameter optimization with a sliding-window-based moving average method, the performances of Random Forest, XGBoost, and LightGBM models were compared and analyzed. Additionally, we present an integrated prediction-optimization pipeline that couples the model-predicted waste activated sludge with NSGA-II to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061876/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Myeloid Cell-Targeted Immunostimulant Cocktail (MyTai) Enhances Cancer Immunotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The efficacy of tumor vaccines depends in large part on additional immunostimulation of antigen-presenting cells (APC) in tumor microenvironments. Various Toll-like receptors (TLR), and in particular TLR3 stimulation by dsRNA, generate a cellular immune response well suited for vaccines. A major drawback of currently used Poly I:C-based TLR3 agonists is their size heterogeneity, variable stability, as well as the toxicity of lipid nanoparticle (LNP) delivery vehicles. To improve existing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel framework for forward osmosis in zero- and low-flow conditions: Applicability and fundamental differences from reverse osmosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Forward osmosis (FO) systems operating under low or zero cross-flow velocities present modeling challenges due to the limitations of conventional external concentration polarization (ECP) formulations, which often predict near-zero flux under stagnant conditions, contradicting experimental observations. To address this, we propose a revised ECP model incorporating an asymptotic Sherwood number that enables continuous mass transfer prediction as the Reynolds number approaches zero. The model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061659/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hyperosmolar Dehydration in Sepsis: Implications for Initial Fluid Management]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Hyperosmolar dehydration at the diagnosis of sepsis was associated with increased 30-day mortality. A liberal fluid management benefits patients with hyperosmolar dehydration by improving lactate levels without increasing sequential organ failure assessment score. These findings highlight the importance of individualized fluid management based on the dehydration status in sepsis management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Illumination-induced deep trap state activation at the nanocluster/TiO<sub>2</sub> interface: the origin of intrinsic photocapacitance in sensitized solar cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41059107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Noble metal nanoclusters (NCs) in photoelectrochemical systems reveal novel functionalities. This study unveils that metal nanocluster-sensitized solar cells (MCSSCs) can intrinsically function as photocapacitors, storing charge in the dark. Illumination of Au(22)(SG)(18) NC-sensitized TiO(2) activates deep surface trap states, forming an interfacial capacitance responsible for a persistent dark built-in potential. Open-circuit voltage decay experiments demonstrate a stable dark voltage...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41059107/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pseudoballs as a distinct endotype of sinonasal bioballs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41058579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The pseudoballs were dual-negative in GMS and Gram staining and showed distinct clinical and radiological characteristics as a different endotype.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41058579/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interchangeability of patellar height measurement using the Insall-Salvati ratio at 0° and 30° of knee flexion during weightbearing in total knee arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ISR measured at 0° or 30° of knee flexion during weightbearing can be interchanged reasonably before and after TKA. Although knee flexion of 30° is the standard, lateral radiograph of 0° flexion can be a reasonable alternative for evaluating patellar height using the ISR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063216/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal trends and patterns in suicidal ideation among adolescents in 23 countries from 2003 to 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although suicidal ideation is a significant issue among adolescents, previous studies have largely relied on cross-sectional data collected at a single time point or have been limited to individual countries, providing limited insight into temporal trends across diverse populations. Therefore, we aimed to examine temporal trends in suicidal ideation among adolescents across 23 countries. We analyzed data from the Global School-Based Student Health Survey (2003-2021), which included adolescents...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062596/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitochondrial redox imbalance and CoQ<sub>10</sub> deficiency in Rett syndrome: Insights from patient-derived fibroblasts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rett syndrome (RTT), a neurodevelopmental disorder primarily affecting females, is characterized by mutations in the MECP2 gene, leading to systemic oxidative stress and mitochondrial dysfunction. This study investigates the role of Coenzyme Q(10) (CoQ(10)), particularly its reduced form ubiquinol, in modulating oxidative stress and mitochondrial function in primary dermal fibroblasts derived from RTT patients with distinct MeCP2 mutations. Baseline assessments revealed significant CoQ(10)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valorization of banana peels to highly effective catalysts for micropollutant degradation: Effects of hydrothermal carbonization conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In this study, hydrochars were prepared under various hydrothermal carbonization (HTC) conditions and pyrolyzed to fabricate hydropyrochars under the hypothesis that hydrochars are good precursors of pyrochars and that their reactivity and characteristics are controlled by the HTC conditions. For hydrochars and hydropyrochars, graphitization degree, defects, and graphitic/pyridinic/pyrrolic N increased, whereas the stacking degree and number of acidic O-containing groups decreased as the HTC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062039/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of the Healthy Aging Index with all-cause mortality: Results from the Korean Frailty and Aging Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Lower levels of healthy aging were associated with higher mortality, particularly among older adults with lower educational attainment. These findings highlight the need for targeted strategies to promote healthy aging, especially among those with lower levels of education.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062004/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Translation and validation of the artificial intelligence anxiety scale in German]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41060923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AIAS-G is a psychometrically sound instrument designed to determine AI anxiety levels among German speakers. Further translation and validation studies are necessary to enable comparisons across various countries.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41060923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Effects of lyophilized Korean rice wine (Makgeolli) on intestinal function and bowel activity in loperamide-induced constipation in rats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41060155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Correction for 'Effects of lyophilized Korean rice wine (Makgeolli) on intestinal function and bowel activity in loperamide-induced constipation in rats' by Soyoung Jung et al., Food Funct., 2025, 16, 7617-7628, https://doi.org/10.1039/D5FO01577D.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41060155/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of eco-friendly management of golf clubs on golfers' behavioral intention to return: green image, perceived quality as mediator and green marketing as moderator]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41058895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Amid growing concerns about environmental sustainability, the sports and leisure industry has seen increased interest in green management practices. However, few empirical studies have explored how such practices influence consumer behavior in golf clubs. This study addresses that gap by examining how eco-friendly management affects golfers' behavioral intention to revisit. Specifically, the study investigates the mediating roles of green image and perceived quality, and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41058895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and experiences of sexual harassment among Saudi female nursing students: a cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: More than half of nursing students reported experiencing sexual harassment during clinical training, highlighting a serious concern. Academic institutions and health policymakers must ensure a safe clinical environment through awareness sessions, clear reporting procedures, and education on legal protections under Saudi law.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063066/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Obstetric outcomes following artificial and natural cycle frozen embryo transfer in patients with and without endometriosis: a national cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AC-FET was associated with an increased risk of adverse obstetric outcomes, including threatened abortion, HDP, and placenta previa in endometriosis patients. The additive effect observed for threatened abortion underscores the need for careful monitoring during early pregnancy in this population and supports considering NC-FET for those at high risk of miscarriage.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41063059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Planet-wide performance of a skin disease AI algorithm validated in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To address the diversity of skin conditions and the low prevalence of skin cancers, we curated a large hospital dataset (National Information Society Agency, Seoul, Korea [NIA] dataset; 70 diseases, 152,443 images) and collected real-world webapp data ( https://modelderm.com ; 1,691,032 requests). We propose a conservative evaluation method by assessing sensitivity in hospitals and specificity in real-world use, assuming all malignancy predictions were false positives. Based on three...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41062650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endovascular Management of Common Femoral Artery Occlusion Caused by Suture-mediated Vascular Closure Devices: A Single-Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[ObjectiveVascular closure devices (VCDs) are frequently employed to achieve hemostasis at the femoral puncture site, offering an alternative to traditional manual compression. However, a rare yet significant complication is common femoral artery (CFA) occlusion caused by suture-mediated VCDs. The optimal management of this complication remains unclear, with open surgical repair traditionally regarded as the standard of care. This paper aims to share our clinical experience in managing CFA...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41061705/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Survival Benefits of Early Treatment With Blinatumomab in Adult Patients With Relapsed/Refractory B-Cell Acute Lymphoblastic Leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41058382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Early use of blinatumomab showed survival benefits in both Ph-negative and Ph-positive ALL subgroups in the salvage setting. Proceeding to allo-SCT after blinatumomab could improve long-term outcomes in patients with Ph-negative ALL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41058382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the necessity of prophylactic lateral neck dissection in medullary thyroid carcinoma based on preoperative calcitonin levels: a multicenter retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Prophylactic LND did not significantly impact long-term oncologic outcomes in MTC patients without clinically evident lateral LN metastasis, even among those with elevated preoperative calcitonin levels above 200 pg/mL. Although prophylactic LND was associated with higher biochemical cure rates, this did not translate into reduced recurrence rates or improved survival. Routine prophylactic LND may not be necessary, and the decision to perform it should be carefully individualized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Sodium Rare Earth Silicate Solid Electrolyte with Grain Boundary Electronic Insulation for Ultra-Durable Solid-State Sodium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sodium rare earth silicate is regarded as a novel and promising solid electrolyte (SE) for solid-state sodium metal batteries (SSSMBs) because the merits of high ionic conductivity, low sintering temperature, and excellent chemical stability. However, impurity phases and voids induced by sintering always cause weak ion conduction and large electron conduction at grain boundaries, resulting in the growth of Na dendrites. Herein, a facile grain boundary modification strategy is conducted by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dimensions of childhood trauma and identity disturbance in male adolescents: Examining affected experiences and mediating cognitive functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The results highlight the complexity of identity formation pathways, with distinct patterns of association across trauma types and cognitive functions. By differentiating these domains within an underrepresented cultural context, this study enhances conceptual clarity and advances understanding of mechanisms linking trauma and identity disturbance, offering insights for future research and potential clinical applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41056623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cephalometric differences between patients with REM- and NREM-Predominant OSA: implications for selecting surgical candidates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Anatomical factors, including nasal and maxillary width, hyoid bone position, and tongue length, are linked to OSA type. These findings may suggest that targeted treatments strategies, including MAD, MMA, genioglossus advancement, or transverse maxillary expansion, may be effective based on individual anatomical characteristics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polycaprolactone Impregnated 3D Printed Nanohydroxyapatite for Sinus Augmentation: A Randomized Controlled Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Dimensional stability of the augmented bone was comparable between the groups. However, group 3DPHA-PCL demonstrated inferior new bone formation and implant survival compared to group BB. Long-term follow-up is warranted to monitor the behavior of 3DPHA-PCL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055506/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editing of rice PSEUDO-ETIOLATION IN LIGHT microProtein genes promotes chloroplast development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rice (Oryza sativa) PSEUDO-ETIOLATION IN LIGHT (OsPEL) microProtein family members function as dominant-negative regulators of chloroplast development and are conserved among land plants. Knockout of all three OsPEL genes enhanced plant greening traits and was accompanied by leaf anatomical modifications associated with chloroplast-enriched bundle sheath cells in rice. These phenotypic changes correlated with increased CO2 assimilation efficiency and yield. OsPEL1 specifically interacts with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Global safety profile of PD-1/PD-L1 inhibitors in hepatic autoimmune disorders: A global disproportionality analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of programmed cell death protein-1 (PD-1) and programmed death-ligand 1 (PD-L1) inhibitors in cancer therapy has raised concerns regarding immune-related adverse events. However, global pharmacovigilance studies on autoimmune diseases remain scarce. This study aimed to evaluate the signal detection between PD-1/PD-L1 inhibitors and hepatic autoimmune disorders. A global pharmacovigilance study was conducted using data from individual case safety reports. The analysis centered...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054153/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep learning framework for mapping nitrate pollution in coastal aquifers under land use pressure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Diffuse nitrate (NO₃^(-)) contamination is a critical environmental concern threatening the quality of coastal groundwater resources, particularly in regions undergoing agricultural intensification and rapid land use changes. This study presents an explainable deep learning framework for predicting nitrate concentrations and identifying areas at risk of elevated contamination. The framework integrates key hydrochemical parameters electrical conductivity (EC), chloride (Cl^(-)), organic matter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Air-assisted Liquid-Liquid Microextraction in the Primary Amine-based Supramolecular Solvent for Determination of Tricyclic Antidepressants Prior to High-Performance Liquid Chromatography-Ultraviolet Detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study developed an air-assisted liquid-liquid microextraction method using a primary amine-based supramolecular solvent (SUPRAS) and a monoterpenoid as a coacervation agent to determine two tricyclic antidepressants (amitriptyline and nortriptyline) from human plasma and urine samples prior to high-performance liquid chromatography analysis. The extraction of two antidepressant drugs was performed using a micellar solution of the primary amine (1-octylamine) as an amphiphile. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41057284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The efficacy of bedside percutaneous cholecystostomy in critically ill patients: comparison with cholecystostomy performed in angiography suite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Bedside percutaneous cholecystostomy is a viable alternative for critically ill patients who are unable to be moved. This method provides effective biliary decompression even in patients with high disease severity who require multi-organ support.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41055787/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ubiquitous-Based Testing in Dental Education: Insights From the Unified Theory of Acceptance and Use of Technology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study identifies performance expectancy, social influence, facilitating conditions, and habit as key factors influencing dental students' intention to adopt UBT. These insights can guide effective implementation strategies, though further research is needed to validate findings across diverse contexts and examine actual usage and outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41054248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nutritional knowledge and dietary practices among young Arab adults: disparities and predictors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Nutritional knowledge varied across different Arab countries, and dietary patterns showed significant differences among the countries included in the study.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of vascular aging on stroke prognosis: the novel severity and arterial stiffness (SASt) score]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ePWV and the new SASt score show promising potential as tools for identifying patients at higher risk for poor outcomes at 3 months post-stroke. While these findings are encouraging, further prospective studies are needed to validate their utility before they can be adopted in clinical practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053532/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bottom-Up Synthesis of 2D AlN Nanosheets with Superior Hydrolytic Resistance and Thermal Conductivity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41051185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advanced electronics require efficient thermal management materials, yet aluminum nitride (AlN) faces critical limitations despite its outstanding thermal conductivity (320 W m^(-1) K^(-1)). Conventional spherical AlN suffers from moisture-induced degradation producing hazardous ammonia gas and requires excessive loading fractions for thermal network formation. Herein, an innovative synthesis strategy producing 2D AlN nanosheets is developed through graphene oxide-templated chemical deposition...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41051185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the impact of cultural intelligence on multicultural literacy in university students: a serial mediation model of cultural exposure and cross-cultural communication skills]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41050798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Cultural intelligence plays a central role in shaping students' ability to navigate diverse cultural environments, yet the mechanisms through which it influences multicultural literacy remain underexplored. This study investigates a serial mediation model to examine how cultural intelligence indirectly enhances multicultural literacy through two psychological pathways: cultural exposure and cross-cultural communication skills.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41050798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of Korean CARcinogen EXposure: IARC Group 2A Carcinogens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41048861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The K-CAREX database was developed to estimate exposure prevalence and intensity by industry and occupation for 18 IARC Group 2A agents. These findings provide valuable data for cancer prevention and epidemiological studies. Future work may expand K-CAREX to include IARC Group 2B agents and other carcinogenic agents.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41048861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Situ Formation of 3D Cross-Linked Binders in Silicon-Graphite Composite Anodes for All-Solid-State Lithium Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41048106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-solid-state lithium batteries (ASSLBs) with sulfide-based solid electrolytes offer improved safety compared to conventional lithium-ion batteries. Silicon-based anode materials enable an increase in the energy density of ASSLBs. However, the substantial volume change during cycling induces interfacial degradation, leading to significant capacity loss. In this study, the composite silicon-graphite (Si-C) anodes were fabricated via an in situ cross-linking reaction between polybutadiene (PBD)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41048106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Skin Delivery of Liposomes via Flexibility Optimization with Fatty Alcohol Incorporation for Skin Barrier Reinforcement and Brightening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41047878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to enhance the skin delivery of active compounds by evaluating how the incorporation of fatty alcohols into nanoliposomes influences their structural flexibility and propensity to deliver ceramide and niacinamide across the skin barrier. The findings demonstrate that fatty alcohols not only stabilize ceramide, which is prone to crystallization, but also modulate the flexibility of the liposomal membrane by altering the phospholipid bilayer arrangement, thereby influencing the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41047878/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computed Tomographic and Ultrasonographic Features of Feline Gastrointestinal Eosinophilic Sclerosing Fibroplasia in Cats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41047662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to characterize the computed tomographic (CT) and ultrasonographic features of feline gastrointestinal eosinophilic sclerosing fibroplasia (FGESF) and its concurrent abnormalities. A retrospective multicenter study was conducted on 16 cats with histopathologically confirmed FGESF. CT and ultrasonographic characteristics were retrospectively evaluated to assess the lesion location, shape, size, and layering patterns. The contrast enhancement patterns, including the attenuation...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41047662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=16ywSWzIPvPjkjZL5IOJ6EoFrfLJCBZcYAq0zId87nG-u18olu&amp;fc=20250824200857&amp;ff=20251016033754&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New insights to effective carbon nanofiber features due to defective interphase for prediction of tunneling conductivity in composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Many nanocomposites include a defective interphase influencing the charge transfer through network. However, the impact of defective interphase on the conductivity of composites including carbon nanofiber (CNF), mentioned as PCNFs, has often been overlooked. In this study, the defective interphase is characterized by the parameter L(c), representing the minimum CNF length necessary for effective conduction transfer from the CNF to the matrix. The effective concentration and length of CNFs in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41053145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual role of microglia in neuroinflammation and neurodegenerative diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41052547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Microglia are the principal innate immune cells of the central nervous system, playing cardinal roles in regulating immunity and mediating neuroinflammation - a chronic inflammatory response occurring in the brain and spinal cord. Microglia exhibit a dual role in this process: they can suppress neuroinflammation through anti-inflammatory polarization or inhibition of proinflammatory intracellular signaling, or conversely, they can exacerbate neuroinflammation via activation of proinflammatory...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41052547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deteriorated oral health and function as risk factors for physical disability and mortality in community-dwelling older adults: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41051730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This systematic review revealed that oral health and function, particularly, masticatory ability and the number of teeth, significantly contributed to physical disability and mortality in older adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41051730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Elemental composition, physicochemical properties, and calcium bioavailability of calcined gill powders from Asian seabass and catfish]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41050865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Calcined gill powders (CGPs) from Asian seabass and catfish were prepared by calcination at 900 °C for 6 h. Seabass (SB-CGP) and catfish (CF-CGP) were characterized for their chemical composition, morphology, functional groups, and crystallinity. Cytotoxicity was assessed using BJ cells, and calcium bioavailability was compared with CaCO(3) using a Caco-2 cell model. Both CGPs had high ash content (99.21-99.58 %). SB-CGP showed a larger particle size and higher crystallinity than CF-CGP. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41050865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An octupolar donor-acceptor dye exploiting aggregation-induced intersystem crossing for efficient ROS generation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41047834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photodynamic therapy (PDT) requires photosensitizers (PSs) that efficiently generate reactive oxygen species (ROS) or otherwise induce cell damage, even under the hypoxic conditions typical of solid tumor environments. Here, we report a heavy-atom-free octupolar donor-acceptor dye, 3CN, designed with a triphenylamine core and three cyanovinyl-benzothiazole acceptors. This dye harnesses aggregation-induced intersystem crossing (AI-ISC) to promote efficient triplet state population. In aqueous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41047834/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251016033745&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>