<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:03:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent insights into the biological functions of hesperidin]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660145/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comprehensive genomic profiling of synchronous invasive adenocarcinoma and squamous cell carcinoma within the same lobe: a case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This case demonstrates that synchronous lung cancers may result from the combined effects of carcinogen-induced field cancerization and DNA repair deficiencies. The identification of PMS2 and ERCC2 alterations provides mechanistic evidence of genetic vulnerability, highlighting the importance of counseling, surveillance, and potential DNA repair-targeted strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659267/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical implications of plasma EGFR T790M and ctDNA shedding across metastatic sites in plasma- or tissue-confirmed EGFR-mutant non-small cell lung cancer treated with lazertinib: a prospective multicenter cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Baseline plasma T790M, interpreted alongside metastatic distribution, provided prognostic information in EGFR-mutant NSCLC treated with lazertinib. Liver and adrenal metastases occurred exclusively in plasma T790M-positive patients and were associated with markedly worse outcomes, consistent with a ctDNA-shedding phenotype. Bone metastasis was an adverse prognostic factor independent of plasma T790M, underscoring the combined prognostic impact of molecular and metastatic features.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiological Characteristics of Pertussis in the Chungcheong Region in the Republic of Korea in 2024: Focusing on Sex and Outbreak Patterns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Analysis of individual and epidemic cases of pertussis from this surveillance report can contribute to pertussis prevention through education and outreach targeting school-age populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining the influence of deterrent and enhancement factors on QR-code mobile payment continuance intention: insights from PLS-SEM and IPMA analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: The rise of contactless payment has made quick response (QR) code-mobile payment (QR-MP) platform increasingly popular among mobile financial service (MFS) users, especially in emerging economies. It has been demonstrated that the ongoing use of QR payments can significantly drive the growth of emerging economies. However, despite its importance, the continued use of this technology has not been satisfactory. Thus, this study seeks to explore the modified Unified Theory of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659019/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Potential Therapeutic Synergy of High-Dose Vitamin C and Nicotinamide as Adjunctive Therapy in an Elderly Patient With Extensive-Stage Small-Cell Lung Cancer: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the case of a 78-year-old male with extensive-stage small-cell lung cancer (ES-SCLC) involving the brain, bone, and adrenal gland at diagnosis, who exhibited a near-complete thoracic radiologic response following platinum-etoposide-atezolizumab therapy with consolidative thoracic and whole-brain radiotherapy. In addition to standard chemoimmunotherapy, the patient self-administered high-dose oral vitamin C (3g/day) and nicotinamide (3g/day) continuously throughout treatment, raising...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658660/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Aldehyde-Functionalized Cellulose Nanofiber Hydrogels for pH-Sensitive Drug Delivery via Dynamic Imine Bonding]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We designed a hydrogel system that not only responds to disease-relevant pH conditions but also allows precise control over the network density and drug release via acid-catalyzed imine bond formation. By comparing drugs with and without amine functionalities (DOX vs α-MS) and evaluating the effect of an acid catalyst on cross-linking and drug diffusion, we provide mechanistic insights into the rational design of cellulose-based smart hydrogels. Drug release experiments revealed pH-dependent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658154/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In Situ Accelerated Carbon Mineralization for Synergistic Immobilization and Recovery of Hexavalent Chromium Oxyanions from Coal Ash Leachates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coal ash, a substantial global solid waste stream, offers considerable potential for diverse industrial applications. However, its widespread utility is significantly constrained by the high leachability of hazardous elements, most notably hexavalent chromium (Cr-(VI)). This study introduces a novel carbonation-based process designed for the effective immobilization and recovery of Cr-(VI) present in coal ash leachate. The chemical interactions among Ca^(2+), Cr-(VI), and CO(3) ^(2-) were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658113/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and associated factors of major VCI in first-ever ischemic stroke patients with mild VCI: a five-year prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Long-term outcomes of ischemic stroke patients having mild vascular cognitive impairment (VCI) are not well-known. The aim of this study was to investigate the five-year outcomes of ischemic stroke patients with mild VCI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predicting Brain Amyloid PET Positivity Using the Amyloid Beta Composite (ABC) Index in Patients With Cognitive Impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The ABC index, utilizing commonly accessible clinical data, serves as a simple and practical screening tool for predicting cerebral amyloid deposition. It may aid in patient selection for amyloid PET, anti-amyloid therapies, and clinical trials, thereby reducing unnecessary imaging.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657473/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive value of 6-minute walk test for weight loss after bariatric and metabolic surgery in individuals with class III obesity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Preoperative 6MWT performance provides promising prognostic information for early nonresponse to weight loss following MBS. The 6MWT/BMI ratio showed the strongest and most consistent predictive performance within our cohort, supporting its potential role as a valuable supplementary risk stratification tool. Absolute 6MWT distance may serve as a high-sensitivity screening tool. When used in conjunction with other clinical assessments, this two-step approach may help identify...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657084/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fe-Mediated Destabilization of Oxygen Intermediates Boosts Oxygen Evolution in Multimetallic Layered Double Hydroxides]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rational design of efficient and robust electrocatalysts for the oxygen evolution reaction (OER) is essential for advancing electrochemical water splitting systems. In this work, we report an Fe-incorporated NiCo layered double hydroxide (NiCoFe-LDH) nanosheet array grown directly on three-dimensional (3D) nickel foam via a facile hydrothermal route. Among the various compositions investigated, optimized NiCoFe-LDH exhibits significantly enhanced OER activity, delivering a low overpotential of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657045/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HIF1α Activates Glycolysis to Suppress Mycobacterium tuberculosis Growth in Mouse Bone Marrow-Derived Macrophages]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tuberculosis, caused by Mycobacterium tuberculosis (Mtb), remains a significant global health challenge due to the pathogen's ability to evade host immune responses and persist within macrophages. We investigated the metabolic changes in mouse bone marrow-derived macrophages (BMDMs) upon Mtb infection and identified significant alterations in gene expression related to key metabolic pathways through RNA sequencing analyses. Among them, glycolysis-related genes, including hypoxia-inducible factor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Arbitrary Total Angular Momentum Vectorial Holography Using Bi-Layer Metasurfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advanced holographic techniques are increasingly demanded for high-capacity and secure information processing. In this context, orbital angular momentum (OAM) stands out as a powerful resource for optical multiplexing, offering access to an unbounded set of orthogonal modes. To harness this potential, metasurfaces, with their considerable ability to control light, have emerged as key platforms for OAM-multiplexed holography. Nevertheless, conventional OAM holography suffers from limited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The comparative effects of S-amlodipine versus racemic amlodipine on long-term cardiovascular outcomes in subjects with hypertension: a nationwide population-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although S-amlodipine is known to have similar effects in lowering blood pressure and fewer side effects compared to amlodipine (= mixture of S- and R-amlodipine), there are no available data on its impact on long-term cardiovascular prognosis. This retrospective cohort study analyzed claims data from Korean subjects with hypertension treated with either S-amlodipine or amlodipine from 2010 to 2020. Subjects with prior history of cardiovascular disease or stroke were excluded. The composite...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661542/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bridging Languages, Broadening Access: Examining an Observation-Based Autism Assessment with a Latinx Sample]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These results add to the literature, positioning the BOSA as a promising, affordable, and adaptable tool for improving timely access to high-quality autism assessments in culturally and linguistically diverse, underserved communities. Additional research is needed to assess its usefulness in different circumstances while aiming to increase ease and efficiency of coding. The BOSA's suitability for use by non-specialists in intervention and school-based settings could help reduce...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel citrivirus and prunevirus genomes further demonstrate the recurrent, independent acquisition of nucleic acid-binding proteins in the family Betaflexiviridae]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings expand the known genomic and taxonomic diversity of the genera Citrivirus and Prunevirus, and support the hypothesis that NABP genes have been independently and repeatedly acquired within the family Betaflexiviridae.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fractionated radiotherapy adjuvant to surgery of WHO-2 meningioma with and without gross total resection: a multicenter, retrospective cohort study of 1,452 patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical outcomes after medial open-wedge high tibial osteotomy are not affected by joint space in extension and flexion on standing radiographs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing duration of renin-angiotensin system inhibition after ST-elevation myocardial infarction with drug-eluting stent-percutaneous coronary intervention: Real-World Landmark Evidence from the Korea Acute Myocardial Infarction Registry-National Institutes of Health Registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In STEMI treated with DES-PCI, RASi at discharge offers a survival benefit concentrated within the first year. After 12 months, associations were neutral among event-free survivors, supporting early initiation and maintenance of RAS inhibition with individualized reassessment beyond 1 year.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of Adiposity and Lipid Biomarkers in Postmenopausal Breast Cancer Risk: A Causal Mediation Analysis Based on a Nationwide Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study confirmed that obesity, particularly central adiposity, is a strong independent risk factor for postmenopausal breast cancer, with minimal mediation by lipid biomarkers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661190/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Laparoscopic Iliopubic Tract Repair for Acquired Pediatric Inguinal Hernia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Laparoscopic IPTR is a safe and effective surgical approach for acquired PIHs. It provides reliable posterior wall reinforcement and may reduce the risk of recurrence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661108/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>N</em>-Terminal Octylated Peptoid Hydrogels as 3D-Printable Cell Scaffolds and Proteolytically Robust Cargo Depots]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Supramolecular hydrogels that mimic the extracellular matrix (ECM) represent promising materials for tissue engineering and drug delivery. However, conventional hydrogels formed via the self-assembly of natural or synthetic building blocks often face a trade-off between biological functionality and biochemical stability, limiting their utility in long-term or protease-rich environments. Peptoids, a class of peptide-inspired, sequence-defined polymers, offer a compelling alternative due to their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660999/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, IBS, KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mutation of STAY-GREEN 1 in tomato increases volatile organic compounds during fruit ripening]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clavicular augmentation with hyaluronic acid six-point technique: A novel non-surgical approach to skeletal definition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The HA clavicular augmentation six-point technique is a safe, versatile, and reversible option for achieving predictable skeletal definition. This structured, minimally invasive treatment provides consistent, aesthetically pleasing outcomes, underscoring the potential for injectable solutions in skeletal contouring.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660666/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structure-guided design of a bivalent SARS-CoV-2 mRNA vaccine with NTD stabilizing mutations enhances broad immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2 evolution, particularly the emergence of Omicron variants, has challenged vaccine efficacy, necessitating antigens with broad and variant-specific protection. To design mRNA vaccine antigens with broad-spectrum immunity and enhanced stability, we developed two spike antigens using in silico optimization: Css_dsg S, the ancestral strain-Delta variant consensus with stabilizing mutations, and Omi_dsg S, an Omicron-adapted design. Computational analysis identified two critical N-terminal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660617/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Appreciation to Our Reviewers in the Past Year 2025]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660531/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Position Paper on Lipoprotein(a) From the Lipoprotein(a) Task Force of the Korean Society of Lipid and Atherosclerosis: Current Evidence, Clinical Applications, and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipoprotein(a) [Lp(a)] is a genetically determined risk factor for atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) and calcific aortic valve stenosis (CAVS), with plasma levels largely unaffected by lifestyle modification or conventional lipid-lowering therapy. Although international guidelines increasingly recognize Lp(a) as a risk-enhancing factor, in many Asian populations thresholds for high Lp(a) and treatment strategies remain undefined. This Korean position paper, developed by the Lp(a)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660526/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of Changes in Metabolic Syndrome Status and Risk Factor Count With Incident Cardiovascular Events Among Cancer Survivors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Changes in metabolic syndrome status and metabolic syndrome risk factor count after cancer diagnosis were significantly associated with CVD risk among cancer survivors.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Update to <em>Journal of Thoracic Disease</em> (<em>JTD</em>) Cough Section in 2026]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarcopenia: an overlooked predictor of the progression risk in pulmonary nontuberculous mycobacterial infections?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sarcopenia was not a significant predictor of radiologic progression in pNTM infection. Instead, treatment history and prior TB were more closely related to progression, suggesting that these clinical factors may be more relevant indicators for radiologic surveillance and management decisions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early detection and genetic characterization of clade 2.3.4.4b H5N1 and H5N9 highly pathogenic avian influenza viruses at the onset of fall migration in wild birds during october 2025 in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Highly pathogenic avian influenza (HPAI) viruses of clade 2.3.4.4b continue to diversify through reassortment with co-circulating low-pathogenic avian influenza (LPAI) viruses and are repeatedly introduced into South Korea via migratory flyways. During national wild bird surveillance in October 2025, two HPAI viruses of different subtypes, H5N1 and H5N9, were detected in Common teals in the southwestern Korea. Whole-genome sequencing confirmed both isolates as clade 2.3.4.4b viruses belonging to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660429/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reporting quality and risk of bias in randomized controlled trials of rotavirus vaccines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adherence to the CONSORT 2025 guidelines is essential for future rotavirus vaccine trials, enhancing the quality of individual studies while reinforcing the broader evidence base that informs immunization strategies and public health policies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660219/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging risk of tick-borne diseases in South Korea: Lyme disease, anaplasmosis, and babesiosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tick-borne diseases are an emerging public health concern in South Korea, driven by climate change, ecological shifts, and increasing contact between humans, wildlife, and companion animals. This review aimed to provide an updated synthesis of 3 tick-borne infections of concern-Lyme disease, human granulocytic anaplasmosis, and babesiosis. Relevant literature, national surveillance data, and international guidelines were reviewed to describe pathogen characteristics, tick ecology, epidemiology,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of herbal medicine decoction for facial palsy: Coarsened exact matching analysis of the national health insurance database]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: There was no significant difference in the risk of safety outcomes between HMD users and non-users with BP. Further research is warranted to understand the safety of specific herbal formulas or individual herbs using broader safety measures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assessing the effectiveness of the one paleopathology workshop]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND IMPLICATIONS: The workshop structure and outcomes assessment presented here evaluate an initial effort in effecting conceptual change in the social sciences. Participants were enthusiastic about One Paleopathology, and over the following year new collaborations and research agendas aligned with the concept emerged. Importantly, participants reported integrating transdisciplinarity into their long-term research, indicating that the workshop had a sustained impact.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659236/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beyond Incidence and Mortality: Socioeconomic Mediation of Gastric Cancer Disparities in the United States, 1990-2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Gastric cancer (GC) remains a major global health burden, yet US trends often obscure disparities hidden within national averages. Although incidence and mortality have declined overall, profound geographic, racial, and socioeconomic differences persist. Few studies have systematically examined how demographic composition and social determinants jointly shape GC burden across states. Methods: We analyzed Global Burden of Disease 2021 estimates for GC incidence, mortality, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Recent advances in human papillomavirus vaccines and therapeutic strategies: Combating cervical and non-cervical cancers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human papillomaviruses (HPV) are a major cause of several cancers, particularly cervical cancer, and remain a serious public health challenge, particularly in low-resource countries. In addition to cervical cancer, HPV is linked to vulvar, vaginal, penile, anal, and oropharyngeal cancers, especially in men. The integration of HPV into the human genome plays a key role in cancer development. This review highlights the progress in HPV vaccination and new treatment approaches for non-cervical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659208/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A behavioral activation mobile application for depression among Korean young adults: a pilot study of multi-modal app usage patterns and clinical outcomes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The B-ACT shows promise as a scalable and culturally responsive intervention for depression among young Korean adults. Participants demonstrated significant improvements in depressive and anxiety symptoms, the level of behavioral activation, and quality of life from baseline to post-treatment. Involvement in activities that elicit positive emotions emerged as a key therapeutic mechanism. Randomized controlled trials are needed to evaluate long-term outcomes and broader...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659172/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assistant-independent robotic lung transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658917/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gel Shrinkage in Discontinuous Electrophoresis: How to Stabilize the Electrolyte Boundary in Epitachophoresis - Part 2 - Nongel Solid Support]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the first part of this study, we have examined the shrinkage of hydrophilic gels during epitachophoresis, an isotachophoresis-like discontinuous electrophoretic technique, applied to concentrate DNA samples. In the present work, we evaluated selected solid porous media (sponges, nanofibers, foamed polymers, membranes, and structured inserts) as alternative anticonvective media. All materials were assessed based on zone shape, ease of creating the boundary between the leading and trailing...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Galloylated Phenolics from Indian Gooseberry (<em>Phyllanthus emblica</em> L.) and Their Protein Tyrosine Phosphatase 1B (PTP1B) Inhibition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Indian gooseberry (Phyllanthus emblica L.) fruits are traditionally consumed for their nutritional value and diverse medicinal properties. In this study, the ethanol extract of the fruits exhibited potential effects on the inhibition of protein tyrosine phosphatase 1B (PTP1B). Two novel galloylated phenolics (1 and 2) and nine known compounds (3-11) were isolated and structurally identified. The absolute configurations of new compounds were determined using spectroscopic analyses, Mosher's ester...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658106/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid Evaluation of Amine-Functionalized Solvents for Biomass Deconstruction Using High-Throughput Screening and One-Pot Enzymatic Saccharification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient and sustainable pretreatment of lignocellulosic biomass is critical for biofuel and biochemical production, yet its optimization is often hindered by slow, labor-intensive experimental methods. Here, we report the first demonstration of a custom-built, miniaturized, high-throughput screening platform integrated with one-pot enzymatic saccharification, enabling parallel evaluation of solvent type, feedstock, and temperature with minimal material use and high reproducibility. As a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658097/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overcoming Volatility in Ion Gel via Ag Doping for Nonvolatile Memristive Switching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ion-gel-based memory devices can effectively change their resistance states even at low voltages, owing to the rapid mobility of ions and the formation of an electric double layer. However, their volatile characteristics limit their use in nonvolatile memory and neuromorphic applications. In this paper, we report an ion-gel-based memristive device capable of both digital data storage and analog data processing through the incorporation of silver nanoparticles (AgNPs). The memristive device...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658072/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Causal links between serotonin dynamics and cued fear learning: evidence from experimental studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Serotonin is thought to regulate emotional learning and memory, but there remains much to be explored regarding its causal role in cued fear conditioning and extinction (CFC-E). Recent in vivo recording of dorsal raphe nucleus serotonin neuronal activity during CFC-E paradigm showed that the time course of serotonin level includes both rapid responses to conditioned and unconditioned stimuli and a slowly accumulating component that spans inter-trial intervals and reverses during extinction. By...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[History of the International Union of Societies for Biomaterials Science and Engineering]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The International Union of Societies for Biomaterials Science and Engineering (IUSBSE) is a global organization in the field of biomaterials that brings together national and international biomaterials societies. It is dedicated to the advancement of not only biomaterials but also surgical implants, prosthetics, artificial organs, tissue engineering, drug delivery, and regenerative medicine. IUSBSE and the World Biomaterials Congress were established in 1996. This article highlights the efforts...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657888/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Park morphology and urban structure for active living: a suburban case from Seongnam City]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: This study investigates how park morphology and built environments are associated with residents' physical activity in a suburban context, focusing on Seongnam City, South Korea. It further examines how these relationships differ between master-planned new towns and incrementally developed old towns, which reflect contrasting planning legacies and spatial structures.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657696/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation of the Korean Moss Attention Rating Scale in Traumatic Brain Injury: Reliability and Validity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The K-MARS is a psychometrically reliable and valid tool for assessing attention-related behaviors in Korean inpatients with msTBI. By capturing behaviorally observable attention deficits, the K-MARS helps identify individual attentional problems and guides the development of tailored cognitive rehabilitation plans.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A 20-Year Bibliometric Analysis of the <em>Korean Journal of Neurotrauma</em> Including its Transition From Domestic to International Journal]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The Korean Journal of Neurotrauma (KJNT) has been the official journal of the Korean Neurotraumatology Society for over 2 decades, and has evolved from a domestic publication to an internationally indexed journal. We aimed to comprehensively evaluate this journal's long-term development and academic trajectory using bibliometric analysis. A bibliometric analysis was conducted on all articles published in the KJNT between 2005 and 2025. Publication trends, article types, authorship, institutional...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lumbar Artery Pseudoaneurysm Presenting as Psoas Muscle Hematoma Following Vertebral Compression Fracture in an Elderly Patient: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lumbar artery pseudoaneurysm is a rare vascular complication of vertebral compression fractures that can lead to life-threatening retroperitoneal hemorrhage. We report the case of an 84-year-old man with a history of cerebral infarction who was on clopidogrel and presented with acute back pain after a fall. Initial imaging revealed L1 and L2 compression fractures and left psoas hematoma without active bleeding. The patient was managed conservatively. However, follow-up computed tomography...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657644/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface Modification of Cranioplasty Implants to Reduce Postoperative Cerebrospinal Fluid Collection: A Preliminary Clinical Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Grid-patterned surface modification of patient-specific PEEK flaps appeared feasible and safe, potentially helping prevent CSF collection after cranioplasty. These preliminary results are hypothesis-generating and warrant confirmation in larger controlled studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preparing for the Next 20 Years]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657640/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tobacco use trends in South Korea, 2013-2023: Persistent disparities and emerging challenges in a repeated cross-sectional study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Korea's progress in reducing CC smoking has not extended to vulnerable populations, and rising EC and poly-tobacco use, particularly among young adults, present new challenges. These findings underscore the need for tailored cessation interventions for vulnerable populations and for ongoing efforts to tackle the emerging use of novel tobacco products.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657541/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Concordance Between Subtest-Based and Domain Score-Based Determinations of Cognitive Impairment on the SNSB-II]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Concordance between the 2 classification methods was moderately high for Attention, Language, and Visuospatial Function but substantially lower for Memory and Frontal/Executive Function, especially in individuals with mild cognitive impairment. These findings highlight the need to consider both subtest-level performance and domain scores when determining impairment in memory or frontal/executive function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657478/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Association Between Physical Fitness Components and Cognitive Function in Older Korean Adults: The SUPERBRAIN Exploratory Sub-study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Coordination, as measured by T-wall response time, emerged as the only physical fitness component consistently associated with cognitive performance in older adults. Coordination-related fitness may be an important correlate of cognitive function in older adults and a promising target for future exercise interventions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657476/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Clinical Utility of the Cognitive Impairment Screening Test (CIST)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The CIST demonstrated strong validity and discriminatory ability for detecting cognitive impairment. It also showed acceptable discrimination for amyloid positivity in non-demented participants, supporting its utility as a screening tool in both clinical and community settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Protocol of Korean JOint RegistrY for ALZheimer's Treatment and Diagnostics (JOY-ALZ)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: JOY-ALZ is expected to promote understanding of the long-term clinical outcomes, safety, and cost-effectiveness of recently introduced diagnostics and treatments for AD, thereby supporting the progress of precision medicine in AD care and diagnosis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657474/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erratum: Nationwide Survey on the Awareness of Mild Cognitive Impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article on p. 198 in vol. 24, PMID: 40746342.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657472/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Gaze to Movement: Observational Learning in Dance]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Observational learning plays a crucial role in the acquisition of complex motor skills such as dance, where learners observe expert demonstrations and transform perceptual information into coordinated motor execution. This process depends on how visual attention is allocated during observation, yet the role of gaze behavior in perception-action coupling during structured dance learning remains poorly understood. Purpose: This study examined how differences in expertise are reflected...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Moderating effect of avoidance on the relationship between depression and suicidal ideation across different types of trauma exposure]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings underscore the relevance of targeting avoidance symptoms to mitigate suicidal ideation, particularly in individuals with late-onset, single-incident or non-interpersonal trauma exposure. Exposure-based therapeutic interventions may offer particular benefit for reducing suicidal ideation among trauma-exposed individuals with depressive symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657233/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hair growth enhancement via mitochondrial activation by Mito-activator complex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The approach of this study to promote hair growth through mitochondrial activation was successful. In addition, when applied to the human body beyond the in vitro level, a significant increase in hair growth was obtained without any side effects. In conclusion, this study suggested a promising candidate for hair loss treatment.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prevalence and Patterns of Cranial Nerve Involvement in CIDP, Autoimmune Nodopathy, MMN, and Anti-MAG Neuropathy: A Multicenter Korea/UK Study of 582 Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cranial nerve involvement serves as a diagnostic clue in chronic autoimmune neuropathies, particularly in identifying AN and CIDP. Cranial+ CIDP appears to represent a distinct subset with partial overlap to GBS, suggesting unique underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657082/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chiropto-Neuromorphic Devices Based on a Photocatalytic Dye/Polymer Semiconductor Bulk Heterojunction for Circularly Polarized Light Detection and Memorization]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neuromorphic computing, which emulates the energy-efficient processing of the human brain, has emerged as a key technology for next-generation artificial intelligence. Integrating sensitivity to circularly polarized light (CPL) provides an additional degree of freedom for optical data encoding, yet practical implementation remains limited by material instability and complex, non-scalable fabrication. This work introduces a chiropto-neuromorphic device that addresses these challenges through a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656991/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Label-Free 3D Holotomography and AI Quantification of Macrophage Inflammation Induced by Urban Particulate Matter]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Overall, our findings advance the mechanistic understanding of PM-cell interactions and introduce a novel methodological paradigm for studying the toxicological effects of environmental pollutants.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Rapid Genomic DNA Extraction Method for Direct Quantitative Polymerase Chain Reaction-Based On-Site Detection of Soil-Borne Fungal Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soil-borne phytopathogenic fungi cause root rot, wilt, and damping-off in crops, leading to major yield losses worldwide. Because symptoms appear only after underground infection progresses, early detection is crucial. Here, a rapid 20-min genomic DNA extraction method was developed for eight pathogens-Alternaria tenuissima, Botryosphaeria dothidea, Fusarium oxysporum, Glomerella cingulata, Phytophthora cactorum, Rosellinia necatrix, Sclerotium rolfsii, and Sclerotinia sclerotiorum. The protocol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Vibe Coding Workflow for AI-Assisted Analysis and Visualization of Genbank Records of Pepper Infecting Viruses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding and predicting epidemiological trends of plant viruses is essential for sustaining crop productivity and control strategies. The National Center for Biotechnology Information (NCBI) GenBank provides nucleotide sequences with metadata such as date, location, and host, offering valuable resources for research. However, GenBank lacks automated tools for visualizing temporal and spatial patterns. To address this limitation, we applied a vibe coding approach, a generative AI assisted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656722/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A CRISPR-Cas13a-Based Amplification- and Extraction-Free Fire Blight Diagnostic System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Fire blight, caused by Erwinia amylovora, is an economically devastating disease affecting apple and pear orchards, and reliable detection is critical for effective management. However, field detection is challenging due to inhibitory compounds and the time-consuming nature of nucleic acid extraction, which limits the speed and accessibility of current diagnostic methods. Here, we present a CRISPR-Cas13a-based diagnostic platform designed for rapid, amplification-free, and extraction- free...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656721/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Detection of Soil-Borne Pathogens Using Fine-Tuned Deep Learning Models: A Case Study on the Soybean Cyst Nematode (Heterodera glycines Ichinohe)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soybean (Glycine max [L.] Merr.) is a globally important crop; however, its productivity is severely constrained by the soybean cyst nematode (Heterodera glycines Ichinohe). This nematode often remains undetected during early infection and persists in the soil as dormant cysts, causing long-term yield losses. Although conventional detection methods, such as microscopic inspection and polymerase chain reaction assays, provide accuracy, they are labor-intensive and unsuitable for large-scale...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Strategies and Regulatory Networks in the Early Infection Stages of Plant Pathogenic Fusarium Species]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant pathogenic fungi have evolved molecular arsenals that enable them to successfully invade their host plants and ultimately achieve colonization. These mechanisms involve multifaceted and complex processes that require spatiotemporal regulation of various genes. The cosmopolitan genus Fusarium has been recognized worldwide as an important group of plant pathogens that exhibit diverse virulence mechanisms. This review seeks a broad overview of (a) how the virulence factors and their...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monopolar electrocautery in providing hemostasis of the percutaneous tract during tubeless miniature percutaneous nephrolithotomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that monopolar electrocautery might effectively reduce the risk of postoperative bleeding and alleviate the burden on patients who may require additional blood transfusions in patients undergoing tubeless mini-PCNL.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Firefighters as a Key Alliance Group to Advocate for Tobacco Control Policies in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Tobacco control is a public health priority. However, Korea has recently experienced a reversal in its long-term decline in smoking prevalence. To address this trend, it is essential to broaden advocacy networks by engaging new stakeholders. We propose that firefighters represent a strategic yet under-represented partner in tobacco control because their professional interests closely align with tobacco-related policy goals. First, cigarette butts have consistently been the leading cause of fire...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of COVID-19 on the Profitability of General Hospitals in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings highlight the uneven financial effects of COVID-19 on Korean hospitals, emphasizing the importance of targeted government financial support. Policy measures should prioritize structural financial reforms to ensure hospital sustainability beyond short-term crisis management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656663/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in Adolescents' Compliance Rate in Response to Policy Changes: COVID-19 Toothbrushing Restrictions in Schools for Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study highlights that adolescents' health behaviors are highly sensitive to environmental and policy changes. Variations in compliance and recovery rates underscore the need for adolescent-centered policies that account for both compliance and recovery, especially during crises such as pandemics.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656662/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Measuring Trends in Disability-adjusted Life Years and Life Expectancy in Korea: 2008 to 2021]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Unlike previous studies, this research presents DALYs and DALE concurrently, offering a more comprehensive perspective on summary measures of population health. The post-2020 rise in DALYs underscores the growing need for effective chronic disease management. Additionally, widening income-based disparities in DALE highlight the urgency of addressing health inequities. Continued monitoring and updates of DALYs and DALE are necessary to understand and respond to these evolving trends.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656661/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Hyperacute Blood Pressure Lowering and Outcomes in Patients With Endovascular Thrombectomy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Active BP lowering in the ED before EVT was associated with worse functional outcomes and increased infarct growth without a corresponding reduction in the occurrence of symptomatic intracerebral hemorrhage. These findings highlight the need for caution in initiating antihypertensive therapy before reperfusion and support further investigations to define optimal pre-EVT BP management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Application of Pharmacogenomics in Stroke Management: Current Evidence and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pharmacogenomic variations may significantly influence responses to commonly prescribed stroke medications. Despite accumulating evidence, genetic testing has not yet been widely integrated into stroke care. This review summarizes current evidence and provides practical guidance for clinical implementation. Pharmacogenomic studies and clinical guidelines related to antiplatelet agents, anticoagulants, and statins were reviewed, with particular emphasis on East Asian populations. Substantial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanism-Oriented Treatment of Early Neurologic Deterioration in Acute Ischemic Stroke]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early neurologic deterioration (END) is common and occurs within a few hours to days after an ischemic stroke. Traditionally, END has been treated as a collective entity, including the occurrence of new deficits (recurrence) and the aggravation of pre-existing neurologic deficits (progression). END arises from distinct mechanisms that require different therapeutic approaches. We reviewed clinical and experimental studies addressing the epidemiology, mechanisms, and treatment of END, focusing on...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Monomethylmercury Isotopes Reveal a Hidden Biomagnification Pathway in Marine Ecosystems and Their Environmental Implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monomethylmercury (MMHg) is a potent neurotoxin to which humans are exposed via fish consumption. However, the relative importance of planktonic and benthic biomagnification pathways to fish MMHg concentrations in marine food webs is challenging to quantify. Here, we apply compound-specific isotope analysis (CSIA) of Hg to identify fish MMHg biomagnification pathways across nearshore bay (NB), marine continental shelf (MCS), and pelagic ocean (PO) regions. We observe significant differences in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661058/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Conformation-Modulated Lignin for Durable and High-Output Cellulosic Triboelectric Materials Toward Self-Powered Sensing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cellulose-based triboelectric sensors offer a sustainable pathway toward self-powered electronics, yet their practical reliability is severely constrained by long-term tribo-induced fiber fibrillation and the resulting interfacial degradation. Herein, we report a conformation-engineered alkali lignin (EAL) that enables simultaneous enhancement of mechanical durability and electrical output in cellulose-based triboelectric materials. Succinic-anhydride grafting introduces flexible aliphatic side...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657284/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knocking Out Two Polyphenol Oxidase Genes Significantly Improves Recombinant Protein Purification in Nicotiana benthamiana]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient purification remains a key technical challenge affecting the recovery efficiency of recombinant proteins in plant-based systems. Complex metabolites, particularly polyphenols, often cause recombinant protein aggregation during purification. In this study, we identified two key polyphenol oxidase genes, PPOa and PPOb from Nicotiana benthamiana, as responsible for these effects. Using CRISPR-Cas9, we generated two ppoa;ppob double knockout lines that significantly improved the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-Dependent Area-, Lamina- and Cell-Type-Specific Distribution of the Cannabinoid Type 1 Receptor in the Mouse Visual Cortex]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The efficient processing of visual information relies on a mature visual cortex, characterized by hierarchically organized areas and a broad diversity of inhibitory and excitatory neurons. A tightly regulated excitation-inhibition (E/I) balance is essential for the optimal processing of visual inputs. A known regulator of the cortical E/I balance is the endocannabinoid (ECB) system, which relies on the cannabinoid type-1 receptor (CB1R) to perform its functions. To better understand the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661643/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood pressure variability and frailty: mechanisms, evidence, and clinical implications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Blood pressure variability (BPV), fluctuations in blood pressure across beat-to-beat, 24-h, day-to-day, and visit-to-visit timescales, has emerged as a risk marker that is independent of mean blood pressure. Frailty, a multidimensional syndrome of diminished physiological reserve, shares core biology with BPV, including vascular aging, impaired baroreflex function, autonomic dysregulation, and chronic low-grade inflammation. This narrative review synthesizes mechanistic, epidemiologic, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kidney function and all-cause mortality in the oldest-old population: a three-cohort longitudinal study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[With increasing global life expectancy, the prognostic significance of kidney function in centenarians and supercentenarians should be clarified. The conventional estimated glomerular filtration rate (eGFR) threshold of < 60 mL/min/1.73 m² may not accurately reflect chronic kidney disease (CKD) in this population, highlighting the need for age-adapted definitions. This study investigated the association of kidney function with all-cause mortality across three age groups. Data from the Tokyo...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of the short-term and mid-term outcomes between robot-assisted and laparoscopic surgery for splenic flexure colon cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661328/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Postoperative outcomes of pancreatoduodenectomy for pancreatic head malignancy in patients over 85 years of age: A safety evaluation using propensity score matching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PD can be safely performed in patients aged ≥ 85 years without increasing postoperative complications and recurrences in the cases with appropriate patient selection.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661325/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The prognostic significance and clinical application of Mac-2 binding protein glycosylation Isomer, Lectin-Reactive α-Fetoprotein Fraction, and protein induced by vitamin K Absence-II in resectable hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of Coexisting Low Tongue Pressure and Sarcopenia with Pharyngeal Residue in Older Adults with Presbyphagia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In age-related swallowing decline, low tongue pressure (LTP) represents a localized functional decline, and sarcopenia represents a systemic functional decline. However, their combined relationship with swallowing function is not fully understood. We examined whether the coexistence of LTP and sarcopenia is associated with pharyngeal residue, an indicator of swallowing efficiency, among older patients with dysphagia. A cross-sectional study was conducted in 102 outpatients aged 65 years or older...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661306/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-Term Tofersen in SOD1 Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Final data from VALOR and the OLE demonstrated the benefit of tofersen in SOD1-ALS and provide clear rationale for its use in this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661214/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Milk and honey: how skin changes reveal the deeper dangers of nutritional deficiencies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although scurvy is more common in low- and middle-income countries, it still occurs in high-income settings. It should be considered in at-risk patients presenting with suggestive symptoms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661213/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Behavioral and Psychological Symptoms of Dementia Clusters on Activities of Daily Living in a Subacute Rehabilitation Setting]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Cognitive function and hyperactivity-related BPSD significantly influenced the functional outcomes in patients with dementia undergoing subacute rehabilitation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Friction Mechanism on Steel Surface in <em>n</em>-Hexadecane Containing Stearic Acid Based on Cross-Sectional Observation Using Frequency-Modulation Atomic Force Microscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the relationship between interfacial molecular structures and their frictional properties is one of the key issues in analyzing boundary lubrication mechanisms. In this study, the interfacial structure and frictional behavior of stearic acid (SA) solution were investigated using frequency-modulation atomic force microscopy (FM-AFM) and lateral force microscopy (LFM). FM-AFM visualized two distinct repulsive regions on steel and self-assembled monolayer substrates corresponding to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creation and Detection of Optical Spin in a Coupled Emitter-Plasmon System]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the system of a linearly polarized dipole emitter coupled to the plasmonic modes of a gold nanorod (GNR). We show numerically that asymmetrical placement of the emitter relative to the GNR axes gives rise to a net optical spin for the field inside the rod, despite the apparent achirality of the system. We experimentally demonstrate this effect using electron beam excitation to create an effective point dipole emitter and coupling luminescence evanescently to a nanofiber probe...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661148/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Lead(II)-Based Coordination Polymer Exhibiting Photocatalytic and Electrochemical CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction Activities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mixed-anion compounds incorporating multiple anionic species within a single crystal lattice can exhibit novel structural and functional properties and so have recently attracted much attention. These materials offer unique coordination environments that can lead to emergent behaviors relevant to various applications. Coordination polymers (CPs) comprising metal centers bridged by molecular anionic linkers represent a subclass of mixed-anion compounds and are of interest. In particular, CPs...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661067/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Probing thermal stability in CsPbI<sub>3</sub> quantum dots with coupled Pb-site doping and halide passivation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[All-inorganic CsPbI(3) quantum dots (QDs) exhibit exceptional optoelectronic properties but suffer from poor thermal and structural stability, hindering their device integration. Here, we systematically investigate the temperature-dependent stability of pristine and Pb-site-substituted QDs combined with halide surface passivation, namely CsPb(0.95)Co(0.05)I(3) and CsPb(0.95)Ag(0.05)I(3), within the 20-80 °C range. Comprehensive X-ray diffraction (XRD), transmission electron microscopy (TEM),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystallization and X-ray structure of a highly aggregation-prone monobody engineered for high-affinity small-molecule recognition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Monobodies, engineered protein scaffolds derived from the fibronectin type III domain, are powerful alternatives to conventional antibodies. While the native scaffold is robust, engineering the variable loops can often compromise solubility and promote aggregation. Here, we report the crystallization and structure determination at 2.57 Å resolution of a monobody (Mb-P') engineered to bind the synthetic small molecule HPPU [1-(4-hydroxyphenyl)-3-phenylurea] with nanomolar affinity. Although Mb-P'...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of diabetes care discontinuation on healthcare costs in older patients with type 2 diabetes: a retrospective study using medical claims data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Interruption of diabetes care in older adults is associated with increased healthcare costs. Early intervention may help reduce care interruptions and healthcare costs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660678/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emerging diagnostic and therapeutic opportunities in food allergy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Food allergy is characterized by acute onset of symptoms affecting multiple organ systems following the ingestion of otherwise innocuous food antigens. The prevalence of this potentially life-threatening disease is globally increasing and poses a significant burden on society and healthcare systems. In this review, we summarize the pathophysiology of food allergy focusing on pre-clinical evidence of how oral tolerance is broken and the role of systemic and mucosal immunoglobulin E (IgE) in food...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvent-based or nab-paclitaxel plus ramucirumab for pretreated gastric cancer with peritoneal dissemination and prespecified biomarker analysis (P-SELECT/WJOG10617G): a randomised phase 2 trial in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Gastric cancer (GC) with peritoneal dissemination remains a challenge with poor prognosis and limited treatment options. We aimed to compare solvent-based paclitaxel (sb-PTX) + ramucirumab (RAM) vs. nanoparticle-albumin-bound paclitaxel (nab-PTX) + RAM as second-line therapy for unresectable or recurrent GC with peritoneal dissemination.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modified posterior full-endoscopic cervical discectomy for highly migrated cervical disc herniations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Partial cephalad and caudal pediculotomy represents a safe and effective technical modification of the pFECD approach for significantly migrated CDHs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41660353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emotional Acculturation: Emotions as a Pathway to Social Integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This article reviews recent research that examines how emotional processes change in response to exposure to new cultures and how successful changes in emotional processes play crucial roles in immigration outcomes. Social-psychology research has shown that emotional fit (i.e., having the "right" emotions in a given social context) is a pathway to social integration. Combining these findings with research on the crucial role of culture in shaping emotional experiences, this article aims to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Detection of Volatile Organic Compounds through Cationization Using ICP-MS/MS]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We have developed a new analytical technique for the detection of volatile organic compounds (VOCs) using inductively coupled plasma tandem mass spectrometry (ICP-MS/MS). Eight VOCs of various polarities (acetic acid, 2-butanone, pyridine, 2-methylfuran, ethylene, benzene, toluene, and limonene) were introduced into the collision/reaction cell (CRC) of the ICP-MS/MS, bypassing the ICP ion source. This approach enabled a softer ionization than the typical ICP, allowing the detection of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High Recovery Stop-and-Go Extraction Tips Using Polytetrafluoroethylene Disks Embedded with Poly(styrene-divinylbenzene) Particles for Proteomics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The stop-and-go extraction tip (StageTip) is widely used for peptide purification in bottom-up proteomics, yet the original 3M Empore disk is no longer available, prompting the need to evaluate current alternatives. Two types of commercially available poly(styrene-divinylbenzene) (SDB)-containing polytetrafluoroethylene (PTFE) disks were used to fabricate StageTips. Desalting was performed on 500 and 20 ng of HeLa tryptic peptides, and the nanoscale liquid chromatography-tandem mass spectrometry...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659730/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of the effects of plasma-generated active species on cells cultured in a microperfusion system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Promoting cell growth is required in life science and medical applications. Thus far, microdevice researchers have been developing microperfusion systems for simulating in vivo conditions that are suited for cell growth. For advancing cell growth technology further, we applied plasma technology. Plasma is the fourth state of matter after solid, liquid, and gas. When plasma is generated under atmospheric conditions, it reacts with ambient air, producing reactive oxygen and nitrogen species...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41659348/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional characterization of the bovine sour taste receptor Otopetrin 1 (OTOP1) in response to dietary and ruminal acids]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cattle frequently consume acidic feeds such as silage and are continuously exposed to acidic substances originating from ruminal fermentation during rumination. These acids are presumed to be detected via sour taste receptors expressed in taste buds; however, the functional properties of bovine sour taste receptors remain poorly understood. In this study, we focused on the bovine sour taste receptor candidate Otopetrin 1 (OTOP1) and characterized its functional responses to physiologically...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Facts and Issues of Submitting Applications (Public Knowledge-Based Applications) for Unapproved and Off-label Drugs With High Medical Needs in Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that the availability of existing domestic therapies and the approval or standard use status of a drug in the 6 Western countries influence the judgment of the applicability of public knowledge-based applications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658419/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes and management strategies of pregnancies after heart and lung transplantation across Europe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We show reassuring pregnancy outcomes for post-HTx, LTx, and HLTx patients in an exclusive European cohort, despite high pregnancy complication rates. Graft function and overall maternal survival appear unaffected. We highlight differences in pregnancy management between centers and suggest development of a uniform approach.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658238/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Co-Optimization of in Vitro Biofunctionality and Electrochemical Passivity in Self-Doped TiO<sub>2</sub> Surfaces]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Titanium is a well-established biomaterial, with its passive oxide film playing a key role in regulating interfacial chemistry and biofunctionality. However, the relationship between the biofunctionality of the passive TiO(2) film and its semiconducting properties remains underexplored. To address this gap, self-doped TiO(2) was fabricated on titanium via hydrothermal oxidation in hydrogen peroxide. This additive-free approach enabled the intrinsic effects of semiconducting behavior to be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658110/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Design of Gold Extraction Solvents Using Machine Learning Models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dibutyl carbitol (DBC) has been conventionally used for solvent extraction of Au-(III), which exists as tetrachloroauric acid (HAuCl(4)), leached by chlorination. However, the water solubility of DBC (3 g/dm³) leads to organic contamination of the aqueous phase. To identify solvents with both high gold extractability and low water solubility, a model Y = f(X) was constructed to predict extractability and water solubility Y from molecular descriptors X of chemical structures using experimental...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658059/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Splenic Metastasis in Ewing Sarcoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ewing sarcoma (ES) is a high-grade osseous malignancy that typically occurs between 10 and 20 years of age. Prognosis is poor with a 30% five-year survival in the case of metastatic disease. This case describes a 20-year-old female patient with known lumbar vertebral ES developing a splenic metastasis years after primary treatment. To the best of our knowledge, metastatic spread to the spleen in ES has not been reported before. Teaching point: In patients with a history of Ewing sarcoma, new...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41658052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A mechanochemical route to triazatrinaphthylenes: building blocks for π-extended, nitrogen-enriched two-dimensional metal-organic frameworks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nitrogen-containing polyaromatic heterocycles are the key molecular materials in semiconducting and optoelectronic devices, yet their synthesis typically depends on high-boiling, toxic organic solvents and multi-step catalytic processes. Herein, we report a metal-free solid-state synthetic strategy followed by thermal treatment for the efficient synthesis of the functionalized C (3h)-symmetric triazatrinaphthylene (TNP) derivatives. Through rigorous optimisation of catalyst concentration,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crystal structure of tris-[4-(3,4-di-meth-oxy-thio-phen-2-yl)phen-yl]amine]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the title compound tris-[4-(3,4-di-meth-oxy-thio-phen-2-yl)phen-yl]amine (DMOT-TPA), C(36)H(33)NO(6)S(3), the central nitro-gen atom shows no pyramidalization, with the three para-phenyl-ene rings arranged in a propeller-like geometry. Each thio-phene ring is twisted by about 25-29° relative to the adjacent phenyl-ene ring, giving a distorted π-conjugated framework. In the crystal, mol-ecules are linked through multiple C-H⋯π inter-actions into two-dimensional sheets, which extend into a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657502/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A reference-grade genome assembly data of sika deer in Hokkaido, Japan, <em>Cervus nippon yesoensis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sika deer (Cervus nippon) is naturally distributed across East Asia and includes 14 subspecies, showing phenotypic and genetic diversity. In this study, we constructed a de novo genome assembly of wild sika deer using one of the largest subspecies, C. n. yesoensis. We used HiFi, high quality long-read based on Pacific Bioscience to assemble our novel genome assembly CerNipYes1.0. The genome size of CerNipYes1.0 is estimated to be 3.1Gb, which is 0.6Gb larger than the other genome assembly of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41657413/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fused Rubrene Derivatives with Embedded Seven-Membered Rings: Curvature-Dependent Photophysical and Semiconductor Properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The synthesis and characterization of a fused rubrene derivative with two embedded seven-membered rings are described. Owing to the incorporation of heptagons, fused rubrene was obtained as two isolable conformers in the C(2h)-symmetric saddle and D(2)-symmetric twisted structures. The isomers were both highly curved, as judged from the mean plane deviation of 1.10 Å (saddle) and 1.15 Å (twist). Kinetic studies using NMR spectroscopy and DFT calculations revealed that the saddle isomer was 11.0...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656745/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Wildfires Oppositely Modify Radiocesium Mobility in Forest Litter and Soils: Evidence from Radiologically Contaminated Areas in Fukushima]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wildfires in radiologically contaminated areas have raised concerns about radionuclide redistribution and increased radiation exposure. Most radionuclides, such as radiocesium (^(137)Cs), remain in the charred residues and burned soil even after wildfires. This study investigated the impact of wildfires on ^(137)Cs speciation in forest litter and soils following the Fukushima nuclear accident. Extraction tests of ^(137)Cs from unburned litter and soil artificially combusted at 250, 375, and 500...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41656648/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interactions between Huangjiu Polysaccharides and Polyphenols: Mechanisms and Influence on Volatile Organic Compounds Release]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Huangjiu is a traditional Chinese fermented beverage whose aroma perception is affected by the release of volatile organic compounds (VOCs) from its matrix. This study is the first to evaluate the combined effects of Huangjiu polysaccharide (HJPS) with four representative polyphenols (epicatechin, ferulic acid, vanillic acid, and syringic acid) upon esters release, which was accomplished via two complementary aroma models: 58 VOCs were identified using headspace solid-phase microextraction gas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661669/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Phonetic clustering characteristics in verbal fluency: A potential marker for differentiating subjective cognitive decline from mild cognitive impairment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Retrieving sequences of words based on their phonetic proximity while performing not only PVF but also SVF tasks pointed to more preserved cognitive functioning and appeared vulnerable to early cognitive changes. Linguistic analysis of VF performance can capture subtle cognitive reorganization missed by scoring of the total number of correct words only and may enhance early dementia-risk profiling.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk Factors for the Development of Food Allergy in Infants and Children: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this meta-analysis, the most credible risk factors associated with development of childhood food allergy are a combination of major and minor risk factors, including early allergic conditions (atopic march/diathesis), delayed allergen introduction, genetics, antibiotic exposure, demographic factors, and birth-related variables.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661638/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Changes in Inpatient and Skilled Nursing Facility Care After the Medicare 3-Day Rule Reinstatement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study, reinstating Medicare's 3-day hospitalization requirement was associated with longer inpatient stays without decreases in SNF utilization or improvements in short-term health outcomes. These findings suggest that the policy imposes additional costs on hospitals while failing to lower Medicare spending on hospitalized patients. More generally, results raise questions regarding the value and continued relevance of a broadly applicable 3-day inpatient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661627/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Emergency Department Visits and Hospitalizations for Unintentional Exposures to Oral Prescription Medications Among Young Children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661610/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reattracting Nurses to Hospital Employment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661599/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Organizational Factors to Reattract Nurses to Hospital Employment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661597/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Episode Charges and Subsequent Visits After Telemedicine vs In-Person Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this comparative effectiveness research using target trial emulation of outpatient telemedicine and in-person visits, telemedicine visits overall were associated with lower charges and fewer subsequent visits within the 30-day episode than were in-person visits. For mental and behavioral conditions, charges were comparable. These findings suggest that telemedicine may serve as a lower-charge alternative to in-person care without increasing the need for subsequent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Determining Duration of Oral Anticoagulation Treatment for New-Onset AF After Coronary Artery Bypass Grafting -Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661586/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Externalizing problems and reward-punishment sensitivity: Testing within-person reciprocal associations in an elementary school sample-A replication of Ramer et al. (2024)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Temperament is closely linked to externalizing problems during adolescence, but the possible interrelationships between them remain unresolved. Reinforcement sensitivity theory proposes that sensitivity to reward modulated by the behavioral activation system (BAS), and sensitivity to punishment modulated by the behavioral inhibition system (BIS), influence how certain kinds of reinforcements shape adolescents' behaviors. A study by Ramer et al. (2024) observed that higher levels of reward...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can measuring coercive conflict in family dyads be easier? The psychometrics of coercion measures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coercion theory has profoundly impacted our understanding of aggressive behavior in relationships; coercive processes are linked with numerous negative psychological and physical health outcomes. Coercion theory's influence on the aggression and violence literature is remarkable given that standard measurement requires painstaking, moment-by-moment coding of direct observation of dyadic interactions-an expensive, time-consuming endeavor. Thus, we sought to develop less costly and less cumbersome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661575/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mass Spectrometry-Based Multi-Protein Panel Assay for Detecting Immune Checkpoint Proteins in Immune Cells of Oral Cancer Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer immunotherapy represents a transformative approach to cancer treatment, paving the way for personalized and precision medicine strategies. Despite the significant advances in immunotherapy, the treatment response rate remains a major clinical challenge. The stratification of patients into responders and nonresponders is paramount for immunotherapy treatment response, which reduces the likelihood of treatment challenges, expenses, and potentially severe adverse effects in cases where...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Providers' and administrators' perspectives of massed posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD) treatment in Veterans Affairs (VA) PTSD outpatient clinics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Posttraumatic stress disorder (PTSD) treatments delivered in a massed format (i.e., therapy sessions at least 3 days per week) can significantly reduce dropout rates and result in similar PTSD symptom reduction as standard delivery (i.e., once or twice a week). The VA Health Care System is the largest integrated delivery system in the United States and is uniquely positioned to provide mass treatment to veterans with PTSD. Understanding providers' and administrators' perceived barriers and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661566/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community living center-mental health integration in the Veterans Health Administration: Evaluation of practice patterns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Starting in 2008, the Veterans Health Administration required mental health (MH) provider integration in nursing homes, called Community Living Centers (CLCs), to promote access to quality MH services. This project aimed to understand MH practice patterns and service integration in the CLC and to identify facilitators and barriers to integrated MH services. CLC physician and nurse leaders, and MH providers, were invited to participate in national surveys in the fall of 2022. Survey questions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661565/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Automated Screening and Education for Women With Urinary Incontinence in Primary Care]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: Findings of this study suggest that implementation of a large-scale, automated UI screening and education program is feasible and could be used to increase awareness and promote treatment of this condition among patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Absolute moral perceptions of the self and others: People are bad, a person is good, I am great]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[For decades, psychologists have appreciated that the average person sees themselves as better than average, particularly in moral domains. Although self-other comparisons permit establishing normative violations, they leave unanswered whether people see themselves and others positively or negatively in an absolute sense. The present research introduces a novel measure of moral thresholds to identify the behavioral tipping point that subjectively differentiates morality from immorality....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661556/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Progress in the discovery and development of anticancer agents from marine cyanobacteria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Correction for 'Progress in the discovery and development of anticancer agents from marine cyanobacteria' by Hendrik Luesch et al., Nat. Prod. Rep., 2025, 42, 208-256, https://doi.org/10.1039/D4NP00019F.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661553/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Vaccine safety for individuals receiving immune checkpoint inhibitor therapy: A narrative review of current literature and recommendations for future research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Some individuals with cancer may receive immunomodulatory treatment such as immune checkpoint inhibitors (ICIs). ICIs are now part of standard of care for many cancers and have improved survival for cancer patients. However, they are also associated with immune-related adverse events (irAEs), which can affect any organ or system, and can range from mild to severe. It has been hypothesized that vaccination of these individuals could increase the risk of irAEs or other vaccine-associated adverse...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can geriatric expertise be codified? Why geriatric judgment extends beyond algorithms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661536/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integral Metabolic Indicators in the Development of Obesity in Arctic Residents Differing by Ethnicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Overweight and obesity are prevalent among the population of the Russian Arctic, irrespective of ethnicity. However, a notable exception is observed among indigenous men, who exhibit a lower prevalence of obesity (13.6%). In both ethnic groups, obesity was associated with cardiometabolic risk factors, particularly among female subjects. However, the metabolic consequences of obesity in the indigenous population were comparatively less pronounced than in the Caucasian population....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661528/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Feasibility, Acceptability, and Utility of the Keepin' It REAL Program for Preventing Adolescent Substance Use in Nigeria]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adolescent substance use remains a pressing public health concern, particularly in low- and middle-income countries (LMICs) where prevention infrastructures are limited. This mixed-methods study evaluated the feasibility, acceptability, utility, and preliminary efficacy of a linguistically adapted version of the keepin' it REAL (KiR) substance use prevention curriculum for junior secondary school students in Lagos, Nigeria. Participants included 532 students (age 11-13) from eight public schools...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661523/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a Patient-Level Multi-objective Optimisation Model for Screening Strategies for Childhood Type 1 Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This article and corresponding model code can be used as a reference for implementing a multi-objective optimisation pipeline in patient-level simulation models.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661522/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A gel-forming antioxidant eye drop for photoreceptor protection in retinitis pigmentosa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Retinitis pigmentosa (RP) is a chronic genetic condition that leads to progressive loss of photoreceptor cells and vision. While gene therapy is available for a small subset of patients with specific mutations, developing a therapeutic that broadly targets the cellular stresses that lead to cell death could address a major unmet need. One such option would be utilizing antioxidant therapies to neutralize reaction oxygen species (ROS) in the retina that underlie RP progression. Here, we describe...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661511/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CBCT assisted diagnosis system for temporomandibular joint disc displacement based on deep learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The proposed model demonstrates preliminary screening capability for TMJ disc displacement using CBCT images. While its current performance precludes standalone diagnostic use, the model may serve as a practical triage tool in orthodontic settings, assisting in the early identification of patients who should be referred for confirmatory MRI and offering references for related research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661510/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One-Step Formation of 2D/3D Perovskite Heterojunction via Ligand Intercalation and Facet Engineering for Efficient Perovskite Solar Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional/three-dimensional (2D/3D) perovskite heterojunctions at the contact interfaces have been proven to enhance the stability and power conversion efficiency (PCE) of perovskite solar cells (PSCs). The 2D/3D bilayer is typically formed via a solution post-treatment onto the 3D perovskite, where the 2D layer's dimensionality depends on the ligand size and its reactivity. Despite their stability, long-chain ligands typically form 2D perovskites with low dimensionality (n = 1, 2) which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661507/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women's pain and psychogenic diagnoses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Healthcare providers often rely on the following sort of concerning reasoning when encountering patients with difficult-to-explain symptoms: in the absence of evidence for a physical cause, the symptoms are presumed to be psychological in origin. In this paper, we take up this concern in the context of chronic pain, with particular attention to how such reasoning disproportionately affects women and how it interacts with the many levels of gender bias in medicine. We first examine the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Safety of Early Diet After Endoscopic Full-Thickness Resection of Gastric Tumor: A Propensity Match Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Compared with the long fasting protocol, early feeding after EFTR for gastric tumors did not increase the incidence of discomfort or postoperative complications. In addition, short fasting protocol has a tendency to shorten hospital stays, which represents potential clinical benefits.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661495/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Premorbid Weight Status Predicts Weight Gain During Treatment of Adolescents with Anorexia Nervosa and Atypical Anorexia Nervosa]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Weight gain is instrumental in recovery from anorexia nervosa (AN)/atypical AN, yet the effect of premorbid weight status on treatment-related weight gain is unclear. In 71 medically hospitalized adolescents with AN/atypical AN, relative weight gain, measured via change in BMI z-scores, was assessed over 12-months of outpatient treatment following hospitalization and compared for premorbid weight status. Patients with premorbid overweight/obesity had a longer illness duration (p = .03) and more...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661486/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ASO Visual Abstract: Long-Term Patient-Reported Outcomes After Multiport Robot-Assisted Surgery Versus Video-Assisted Surgery for Lung Cancer: An Observational Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661481/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A New Species of Oxyascaris (Nematoda, Cosmocercidae) from Hylid Scinax acuminatus from Chaco Seco Ecoregion, Argentina]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The genus Oxyascaris consists of seven species of nematodes that parasitize the digestive tract of amphibians and reptiles in the Neotropical region. This paper describes a new species of the genus based on specimens collected from a hylid anuran in the Dry Chaco ecoregion. A total of 14 specimens of Scinax acuminatus were collected between 2017 and 2021 in Matacos department, Formosa province, Argentina. The morphology of the nematodes was studied in detail using light microscopy and scanning...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early mitral valve repair surgery versus active surveillance in asymptomatic severe primary mitral regurgitation-insights from the Dutch AMR registry]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: After 5.1 years, half of the active surveillance patients required facilitated surgery, with comparable postoperative outcomes to early surgery. Clinical endpoints were comparable between the early and facilitated surgery strategies. There were no differences in baseline additional testing parameters, suggesting no clear targets for upfront stratificatio. Thus, shared decision making weighing the different risks can be used to determine the strategy per patient.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661461/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of Aryl Hydrocarbon Receptor in Airway Remodeling: Mechanistic Insights Across Cellular Functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Airway remodeling, a hallmark of asthma, involves structural and functional changes in the airways including extracellular matrix (ECM) deposition, airway smooth muscle (ASM) cell hypertrophy and hyperplasia, epithelial and fibroblasts remodeling, and mitochondrial dysfunction driven by chronic inflammation. The aryl hydrocarbon receptor (AhR), a ligand-activated transcription factor commonly known for mediating xenobiotic responses, has recently emerged as a key regulator of cellular processes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Healthcare Utilization Disparities Among Older Adults With and Without Cognitive Impairment: Health and Retirement Study Findings]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this study was to determine the healthcare utilization patterns in a national sample of older adults across several factors (ethnicity, gender, race, education) with normal and dementia/impaired cognition. We used datasets from the Health and Retirement Study (HRS, 2018) to evaluate healthcare utilization, including metrics such as hospital and nursing home stays, hospice care, and the number of visits to the doctor. Logistic models were used to predict healthcare utilization...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661455/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mitofusin 2 Alleviates Liver Fibrogenesis by Suppressing β-Catenin Nuclear Translocation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: MFN2 inhibits HSC activation and liver fibrosis by suppressing β-catenin nuclear translocation, making it a promising therapeutic target for NAFLD-related fibrosis and associated complications, such as hepatocellular carcinoma.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Effect of Lipopolysaccharide on Anxiety Levels in Rats Exposed to Chronic Unpredictable Mild Stress of Varying Duration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Anxiety-like behavior in rats was assessed using a model of chronic unpredictable mild stress of varying duration, with prior administration of LPS. Chronic unpredictable mild stress induced biphasic changes in anxiety levels: an initial reduction during the early phase of stress exposure followed by a significant increase at later stages. Pre-treatment with LPS modulated the trajectory of anxiety development under conditions of chronic unpredictable mild stress: it exacerbated anxiety-like...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661432/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Expression Levels of the Immunomodulatory Cytokine TNFα and Its Receptor TNFRSF1A in Rat Brain Structures during Long-Term Spatial Memory Formation and Forced Swim Stress]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Using real-time PCR, changes in the gene expression of TNFα and its receptor TNFRSF1A, factors involved in the regulation of inflammatory processes and synaptic plasticity, were examined in the hippocampus, frontal cortex, and cerebellum of adult male Wistar rats following either the formation of long-term spatial memory in the Morris water maze or forced swimming stress using a comparable time protocol. An increase in Tnfa gene expression was observed in all three brain regions. In contrast,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41661426/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260209150327&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>