<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:34:25 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Membrane Modulus as the Governing Factor in the Mechanism of Catalyst Layer Transfer for Membrane Electrode Assemblies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hydrocarbon-based proton-conducting membranes are promising alternatives to perfluorinated sulfonic acid (PFSA) membranes for hydrogen-related electrochemical devices. However, inefficient catalyst layer (CL) transfer onto the hydrocarbon membranes through decal transfer remains a critical barrier to membrane electrode assemblies (MEAs) integration. In general, the poor CL transfer efficiency is typically attributed to chemical incompatibility between the hydrocarbon membranes and PFSA-based...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562623/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Data-Density, High-Decoding-Speed, and High-Decoding-Accuracy DNA Data Ink for Digital Preservation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[DNA-based storage offers exceptional information density, durability, and energy efficiency compared to conventional digital media, yet practical implementation faces challenges including high synthesis costs, sequencing errors, and slow access speeds. Here, we present an integrated DNA storage system with optimized encoding and processing strategies to address practical implementation issues. Our approach achieves 9.78 bits/nt net information density with a flexible index allocation system...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562500/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ultrasmall Ni Nanoclusters on Perovskites: Highly Stable and Coke-Resistant Catalysts for Methane Reforming with CO<sub>2</sub>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Catalytic dry reforming of methane (DRM) offers a sustainable route for converting greenhouse gases (CH(4) and CO(2)) into syngas, yet suffers from rapid catalyst deactivation due to coke formation. Here, we report a rational approach to control Ni nanostructure and interface properties by tuning the reduction temperature of Ni-substituted La(2)Ti(2)O(7) perovskite catalysts. Catalysts reduced at 800 °C formed ultrasmall, fully exposed Ni nanoclusters with a Ni-Ni coordination number of ∼3....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562456/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, KAIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lithium-Ion Conduction Through Frozen Phase of Organic Electrolytes for Lithium Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Organic ice electrolytes in their frozen states are presented as molecular-solid Li^(+) conductors for lithium metal batteries (LMBs), challenging the notion that frozen electrolytes lack ionic conductivity. Ethylene carbonate, a cyclic carbonate, was predicted to form Li^(+)-conductive channels in its frozen crystal structure. A room-temperature ice-phase electrolyte, EC(0.2T) (0.2 m LiTFSI in ethylene carbonate), exhibited a high ionic conductivity (∼0.64 mS cm^(-) ¹) and a high Li^(+)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Light-Responsive Block Copolymer Particles with Persistent Shape Memory and Programmable Reconfiguration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Light-responsive polymeric particles provide a versatile platform that can undergo precisely programmed shape and color transformations, offering opportunities for advanced multi-level memory systems. We report a block copolymer (BCP) particle system that functions as a structural memory element by reversibly switching among distinct morphologies and retaining each state with long-term stability. The incorporation of hydrazone-based photoswitches into polystyrene-block-poly(2-vinylpyridine)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Declining insulin sensitivity is a key pathological contributor to dysglycemia: a longitudinal validation study in the Korean genome and epidemiology study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Declining IS, independent of BCF, is associated with progression to T2D in lean Koreans. Preserving IS through lifestyle interventions is crucial for diabetes prevention, particularly in those with low BCF. Insulin resistance, β-cell function, disposition index, oral glucose tolerance test, body mass index.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561051/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, KIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cryo-EM Structures Reveal the Molecular Basis of Asymmetric Allosteric Activation by MMOB in the Hydroxylase of Soluble Methane Monooxygenase]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Soluble methane monooxygenase (sMMO) catalyzes the hydroxylation of methane at non-heme di-iron active sites under ambient conditions. The regulatory component (MMOB) is essential for catalytic activity, inducing conformational changes in the active site and facilitating substrate ingress in hydroxylase (MMOH). Advances in cryogenic electron microscopy (cryo-EM) have enabled structural studies of sMMO under near-native conditions. 3D variability analysis reveals that an asymmetric MMOH-MMOB...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrical Manipulation of Magnon Diffusion Length in Pt/YIG Three-Terminal Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Magnons transport spin angular momentum without involving charge current, offering the potential for energy-efficient spintronic devices. While the generation, manipulation, and detection of magnons, key elements for magnonic devices, have been demonstrated in various systems, electrical control of the magnon diffusion length (λ(m)) has not been reported. In this work, we demonstrate electrical control of λ(m) in three-terminal Pt/YIG devices, where injector-to-detector distance and modulator...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-Crystalline Borate Covalent Organic Frameworks for Solid-State Lithium Metal Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[To advance lithium metal batteries, novel solid-state electrolytes are crucial. Covalent Organic Frameworks (COFs) are promising due to their crystalline, porous structure, light composition, strong bonds, high surface area, and stability. COFs can be engineered for enhanced ion conduction, with their porosity and ion-functional groups enabling fast ion movement and uniform lithium deposition. We synthesized a single-crystalline 3D borate COF (B-COF), achieving an ionic conductivity of 8.1 mS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560291/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Proteomics and CRISPR/Cas9 Editing Reveal UPR-Mediated Control of Immunoglobulin Homeostasis in Hybridomas]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite their tremendous economic value, monoclonal antibodies are often compromised by the loss of immunoglobulin (Ig) chains, which disrupts antibody homeostasis and quality control. Through subclone screening and characterization, we identified that the loss of Ig production impaired the recognition ability of hapten-specific hybridomas. Proteomic analysis further highlighted the critical role of the unfolded protein response (UPR) pathway in regulating aberrant Ig chain production. Using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560288/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Universal energy equalization under Haar-random unitary operations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the work done on finite quantum systems initially in an energy-diagonal ensemble when subjected to Haar-random unitary operations. On average, the system's energy shifts toward the infinite-temperature value, effectively equalizing the energy distribution. This suggests that states with energy above the infinite-temperature value serve as a resource for work extraction. This trend becomes typical in large systems as fluctuations vanish. Numerical simulations for a spin model...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560212/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ni Single-Atom Modulation of Ti-O Covalency Boosts Ammonia Oxidation Electrocatalysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Non-noble transition metal oxides, particularly TiO(2)-based systems, can be an alternative to noble metal-based catalysts for the electrochemical ammonia oxidation reaction (AOR) due to their abundance, low cost, and corrosion resistance, but it remains hindered by lower performance and undesired selectivity toward oxygenated nitrogen species instead of N(2), largely stemming from insufficient active sites and higher energy barrier for coupling intermediates. To overcome the issues, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559956/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MIG-6 Regulates HDAC1-Mediated Angiogenesis and Tumorigenesis in PTEN-Deficient Endometrioid Endometrial Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endometrioid endometrial cancer (EEC) is the most prevalent gynecological malignancy, yet no targeted therapies are currently approved by the FDA specifically. To identify therapeutic targets for EEC, we performed transcriptomic and proteomic analyses in genetically engineered preclinical cancer models, including uterine-specific Pten-deficient (Ptend/d) mice and Ptend/d mice with additional overexpression of tumor suppressor Mig-6 (Ptend/dMig-6over) mice that develop EEC. Transcriptomic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563767/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selective Retina Therapy With Fundus Image-Based Titration in Central Serous Chorioretinopathy: Prospective Outcomes and Predictive Factors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SRT with fundus image-based titration yielded favorable functional and anatomical outcomes in CSC. Female sex was associated with persistent SRF, although this finding should be interpreted cautiously.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563733/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: Deep learning prediction of steep and flat corneal curvature using fundus photography in post‑COVID telemedicine era]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The OsMADS18-OsbZIP60 module plays a critical role in influencing grain chalkiness in rice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Grain chalkiness is a detrimental trait that significantly reduces the quality and economic value of rice, yet its regulatory mechanisms remain poorly understood. To identify genetic loci regulating grain chalkiness, we performed high-throughput activation tagging-based T-DNA insertion mutagenesis in the model rice variety (Oryza sativa L.) Kitaake. We found that a loss-of-function mutation in OsMADS18 resulted in enhanced grain chalkiness, reduced plant height, and delayed flowering time....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563665/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pan-Asian subgroup analysis of EV-302/KEYNOTE-A39: a phase 3 study to evaluate enfortumab vedotin and pembrolizumab in patients with untreated advanced urothelial carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: EV + P demonstrated a clinically meaningful survival benefit in Asian patients with untreated la/mUC, with no new safety signals observed, consistent with the global EV-302 study. Results support guideline recommendations for EV + P as preferred first-line therapy in la/mUC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563650/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the letter regarding "One-year bone mineral density gains with anti-osteoporotic medications and clinical factors associated with non-BMD gainers"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and economic impact of deep learning-enhanced opportunistic osteoporosis screening using chest radiographs with and without the osteoporosis self-assessment tool for Asians (OSTA)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: DL-enhanced chest radiographs offer a cost-effective approach for opportunistic osteoporosis screening in Singaporean women aged ≥ 50 years. Combining with OSTA slightly improves efficiency, but DL screening alone is already cost-effective and provides a scalable preventive strategy in real-world healthcare.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bone Mineral Density and the Risk of Fracture According to eGFR in Postmenopausal Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogels in Periodontal and Craniofacial Regeneration: Current Applications and Next-Generation Biomaterials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periodontal and craniofacial tissue defects are complex regenerative targets as the reconstitution of tissue heterogeneity, interconnection and function is essential for favorable clinical outcomes. Periodontal tissues are additionally challenged by the bacterial and immunological factors associated with oral regeneration. Hydrogels are extracellular matrix-like hydrated polymer networks that represent a diverse class of regenerative materials. Current applications of hydrogels for periodontal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563343/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Novel Interferometric Device for Measurement of Tear Film Lipid Layer Thickness in Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We successfully photographed the interference pattern caused by the tear film LL in mice and quantitatively measured the LLT using an LED panel, mirror, dissection microscope, and camera.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563047/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cardiovascular Disease Burden in Rural Central Asia: A Systematic Review of Epidemiological Trends and Mortality Patterns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: Cardiovascular diseases (CVDs) remain a leading cause of mortality worldwide, with a particularly high burden in Central Asian countries. Despite ongoing urbanization, rural populations constitute a significant demographic in this region, yet epidemiological data stratified by urban and rural residence are limited and fragmented. This systematic review aimed to synthesize current evidence on the incidence, prevalence, mortality, and risk factor profiles of CVDs among urban...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562687/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rapid Isolation and Characterization of High-Affinity Single-Domain Antibodies for Broad-Spectrum Detection of SARS-CoV-2 Variants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of SARS-CoV-2 presents substantial challenges to maintaining diagnostic accuracy. Single-domain antibodies (variable domains of camelid heavy-chain antibodies, VHHs), commonly referred to as nanobodies, are attractive tools for diagnostic applications due to their high specificity, stability, affinity and expression yield. In this study, three high-affinity VHHs that recognize the receptor-binding domain (RBD) of the SARS-CoV-2 BA.2 variant were isolated from a large naïve...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Copper- and Silver-Catalyzed Reactions of Active Methylene Isocyanides: Facile Access to Highly Substituted Five- and Six-Membered Heterocycles]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Copper- and silver-catalyzed reactions of active methylene isocyanides provide powerful and versatile strategies for the construction of heterocyclic architectures relevant to pharmaceutical and materials science. Owing to their unique ambiphilic reactivity, active methylene isocyanides serve as key building blocks for the synthesis of fused, bicyclic, polycyclic, and spirocyclic heterocycles under mild catalytic conditions. This review summarizes recent advances in the copper- and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Setting the Standard in Robotic Whipple Surgery: International Multicenter Benchmark Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study establishes the first international benchmarks for robotic Whipple, demonstrating oncologic outcomes and morbidity comparable to open surgery with the benefits of minimally invasive surgery.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562520/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of Ultrasound-Derived Fat Fraction and MRI PDFF Measurements: A Prospective Study in Pediatric Patients With Suspected MASLD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: As pediatric metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) increases in prevalence, ultrasound-based methods have emerged as accessible alternatives to MRI for hepatic fat quantification in children. Objective: To evaluate associations of ultrasound-derived fat fraction (UDFF) measurements obtained under free-breathing and breath-hold conditions with proton-density fat fraction (PDFF) measurements in pediatric patients with suspected MASLD. Methods: This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562459/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing Capsule on Dynamic Liver CT: Association With Hepatocellular Carcinoma Diagnosis Using LI-RADS Version 2018]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: The LI-RADS version 2018 (v2018) diagnostic algorithm prioritizes an enhancing capsule differently from other major features. An enhancing capsule's role in hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) diagnosis remains uncertain, particularly for CT. Objective: To compare diagnostic performance for HCC diagnosis on CT between original LI-RADS v2018 criteria for LR-5 and modified LR-5 criteria that treat an enhancing capsule the same as other major features. Methods: This retrospective study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Survival of Dental Implants in Post-Menopausal Women Receiving Denosumab: A Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Implant-based prosthetic rehabilitation is also feasible in post-menopausal women receiving ARD for osteoporosis. Although the implant survival rate was comparable to non-ARD users, caution is advised for patients on high doses of ARD or undergoing long-term therapy due to their pharmacological effects compromising bone metabolism. Additionally, the risk of failure associated with invasive procedures needs to be further evaluated.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562427/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between Serum Levels of Glial Cell Line- Derived Neurotrophic Factor and Cognitive Function in Patients with Methamphetamine Dependence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Unlike the reports on cerebrospinal fluid GDNF concentration, previous reports on the relationship between serum GDNF levels and cognitive function in neurodegenerative and psychiatric diseases have demonstrated mixed results. This study is significant, as it is the first study on the relationship between serum GDNF and cognitive function in patients with methamphetamine dependence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562423/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Evaluation of an Integrated Tri-Modal Transdermal Device for Enhanced Serum Absorption]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562333/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linking cellular metabolism to chromatin modifications in plants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Beyond their traditional roles as biological building blocks and energy sources, metabolites also influence gene expression, exerting direct effects on the epigenetic landscape. For example, core metabolites such as acetyl coenzyme A (acetyl-CoA) and S-adenosylmethionine (SAM) serve as substrates or cofactors for chromatin-modifying enzymes, thereby modulating transcription through the chemical modification of histones and DNA. In addition, metabolites regulate the transcription of the genes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562316/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Graphene oxide-based fluorescent biosensor for high-throughput screening to discover SARS-CoV-2 RdRp inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic caused by SARS-CoV-2 underscored the global need for rapid, efficient drug discovery platforms to combat emerging viral threats. Conventional antiviral screening methods are often time-consuming and low-throughput, making them insufficient for timely therapeutic development during acute outbreaks. RNA-dependent RNA polymerase (RdRp), a key enzyme in viral replication, represents a validated antiviral target for RNA viruses, including SARS-CoV-2. However, few assays directly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562220/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Neisseria bacilliformis</em> is a periodontal pathogen exacerbating periodontitis by inducing nitric oxide production]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Periodontitis, a chronic inflammatory disease, often causes alveolar bone loss. Neisseria bacilliformis is a Gram-negative bacterium that has been identified in periodontal patients, but its role in periodontitis remains unclear. In the present study, we examined whether N. bacilliformis exacerbates periodontitis in a mouse ligature-induced periodontitis (LIP) model and investigated its underlying molecular mechanism. Topical treatment with N. bacilliformis on maxillary second molar exacerbated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562056/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Robust neutralization of emerging JN.1 subvariants by the updated JN.1 vaccine: rationale for catch-up booster recommendations in high-risk individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The updated JN.1 monovalent vaccine (MoV) for the 2024-2025 season elicits strong cross-neutralizing activity against subsequently circulating SARS-CoV-2 variants in 2025, including the recently emerging NB.1.8.1, with titer increases comparable to those against the vaccine strain JN.1. The immune response induced by the JN.1 MoV was markedly stronger than that induced by XBB.1.5 MoV in the previous season, both against the vaccine strain and post-vaccine variant (all P < 0.001). These results...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562050/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A systematic review of the effects of shared decision-making in the South Korean healthcare system]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This review highlights the potential of SDM to enhance patient-centered care in South Korea. However, inconsistencies in intervention components and evaluation methodologies limit the generalizability of the findings. Given the unique features of the Korean healthcare system-such as very short consultation times, limited reimbursement for counseling, and provider-patient information asymmetry-future research should focus on developing SDM models tailored to these constraints and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MDL-CA: a multimodal deep learning approach with a cross attention mechanism for accurate brain cancer diagnosis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Brain cancer diagnosis poses a significant clinical challenge due to the complex interplay between molecular mechanisms and anatomical abnormalities. Traditional diagnostic techniques, including invasive biopsies, isolated genomic assays, and standalone Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI), often exhibit limitations such as procedural risks, inadequate sensitivity, and incomplete assessment of tumor heterogeneity. These shortcomings contribute to delayed diagnosis, inaccurate tumor...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sodium-Glucose Cotransporter 2 Inhibitors in Diabetic Solid Organ Transplant Recipients: A Systematic Review and Meta-Analysis of Comparative Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SGLT2 inhibitors were associated with improved glycemic control, weight reduction, and favorable trends in cardiovascular outcomes among solid organ transplant recipients. Most safety outcomes, including urinary tract infection and graft rejection, were comparable between groups or more favorable in the SGLT2 inhibitor group, particularly among kidney transplant recipients. These findings support the use of SGLT2 inhibitors in this population. However, further large-scale studies...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The impact of empathy with nature on tourists' responsible behavioral intentions in natural heritage tourism: the moderating roles of escapism and awe]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Natural heritage tourism provides opportunities for visitors to engage with ecological and cultural resources, yet encouraging responsible tourist behavior remains a persistent challenge for sustainable destination management. This study examines how tourists' perceptions of natural and cultural environments shape their intentions to behave responsibly, with a particular focus on the mediating role of empathy with nature and the moderating influences of perceived escapism and awe.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561589/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Age-stratified analysis of descending aorta diameter in traumatic massive hemorrhage: a machine learning approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings reveal age-specific differences in factors influencing the AoD during traumatic hemorrhage. The results highlight the limitations of traditional methods for AoD estimation, especially in senior patients in whom dynamic physiological factors may play a major role. These insights can improve the accuracy of AoD assessment and management in hemorrhage patients across different age groups. The findings may contribute to developing an artificial intelligence-derived score...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561395/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exosomes in trichology: A literature review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Exosome therapy is a promising, minimally invasive approach for AGA, AA, and CIA, supported by robust preclinical biology but preliminary and heterogeneous clinical data. Progress to routine practice will require adequately powered, multicenter randomized trials with standardized outcomes, along with harmonized manufacturing and regulatory frameworks (GMP-compliant production, batch-level quality control) to ensure reproducibility and safety.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561359/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward virtual bladder: real-time bladder volume monitoring with flexible AuCNT strain sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Digital twin technology holds considerable potential for personalized diagnostics and treatment of bladder dysfunction, particularly neurogenic conditions such as underactive bladder (UAB). In this study, to address the need for precise monitoring, we introduce a flexible, stretchable strain sensor composed of gold-coated carbon nanotubes (AuCNTs) embedded in Ecoflex. We specifically designed a three-channel configuration to capture anisotropic expansion and evaluated the sensor's performance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness of three vestibular rehabilitation exercises for treating acute unilateral peripheral vestibular dysfunction: a multicenter randomized study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: All three vestibular physical therapy approaches effectively improved symptoms and functional balance in patients with aUPVD. While between-group differences were not statistically significant, the customized rehabilitation group showed the most consistent pattern of improvement. These findings suggest potential clinical advantages of individualized therapy, warranting confirmation in larger studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Systematic discovery of disease-modifying targets by prediction from knowledge graph-based AI model and experimental validation: Parkinson's disease case]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The development of disease-modifying therapies (DMTs) for Parkinson's disease (PD) remains a critical unmet need. Despite extensive research efforts, no therapy capable of slowing or halting PD progression has been approved. Here, we apply a knowledge graph-based artificial intelligence (AI) framework, combined with subgraph-level enrichment-based re-prioritization, to identify novel PD-modifying targets without requiring disease-specific training or additional experimental datasets. Using...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561322/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Significance of an Incidentally Detected Lateral Lingual Foramen on Cone-Beam Computed Tomography (CBCT): A Case Report and Review of Pertinent Literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The lateral lingual foramen (LLF) is an often-overlooked anatomical variant of the mandible with important clinical implications during implant placement and oral surgical procedures. Unlike the consistently present midline lingual foramen, LLF exhibits marked variability in its prevalence, morphology, and neurovascular content, contributing to potential complications when unrecognized. This case report describes an incidental LLF identified during routine cone-beam computed tomography (CBCT)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561272/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Single radiation exposure induces gut microbiota dysbiosis and decreases short-chain fatty acid metabolism and intestinal barrier integrity in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[[This corrects the article DOI: 10.3389/fcimb.2025.1654976.].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561083/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antidepressant prescriptions by provider in patients with kidney failure and depression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our findings suggest a potential benefit of specialty psychiatric care for improving clinical outcomes in patients with ESKD and depression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560948/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kimchi friend or foe: preserving cultural foods developed pre-refrigeration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We propose that reducing sodium content while preserving traditional fermentation methods may enhance the health benefits of kimchi while lowering preventable cancer risk. This commentary highlights the importance of culturally informed dietary strategies for gastric cancer prevention.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reproductive efficacy of a modified-live porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome vaccine against Korean PRRSV-2 challenge in sows]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Evaluation of the reproductive efficacy of a modified-live vaccine (MLV) based on porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome virus-2 (PRRSV-2).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Immunomodulatory role of decellularized extracellular matrix in skin wound healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The extracellular matrix (ECM) plays a pivotal role in skin wound healing by providing structural support and biochemical signals that regulate cellular behavior. Recent studies highlight the immunomodulatory properties of decellularized ECM (dECM), particularly its influence on macrophage polarization and the overall immune response, which are critical for effective tissue repair. During wound healing, macrophages transition from a pro-inflammatory to an anti-inflammatory phenotype, a process...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NIR imaging-guided carbon monoxide nanomedicine: Design strategies, stimuli-responsive release, and multimodal synergistic therapies for precision disease treatment]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Endogenous gaseous molecules, especially carbon monoxide (CO), exhibit unique therapeutic potential in regulating cancer, infections, and inflammation owing to their dose-dependent bioactivity and multi-faceted mechanisms. However, challenges in spatiotemporal control and real-time monitoring of CO delivery hinder clinical translation. The integration of near-infrared II (NIR-II) imaging with CO nanodelivery systems provides a promising avenue for precise visualization and controlled gas...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560795/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced CYP2C19-mediated drug-drug interaction risk with escitalopram in geriatric populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Escitalopram (S-CIT) is commonly prescribed for depression and anxiety in older patients. Previous research has reported that the effect of CYP2C19 polymorphism on S-CIT pharmacokinetics is more pronounced in older adults than in young adults. The current study investigated whether older adults taking S-CIT face a greater risk for CYP2C19-mediated drug-drug interaction (DDI) than young adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560753/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Textile-Derived Micro- and Nanoplastics on Brain Health: An Emerging Environmental Risk]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Textile-derived micro- and nanoplastics (MNPs), primarily shed from synthetic fibers, such as polyester, acrylic, polyethylene, and nylon, constitute a widespread yet underexplored class of environmental pollutants. Despite their pervasive presence in indoor air, household dust, and the human body, these fibrous MNPs have received considerably less attention than polystyrene-based particles, resulting in a critical gap in our understanding of their potential health impacts. This review examines...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advances and challenges in pretreatment strategies for nucleic acid test-based rapid detection of foodborne bacteria: a critical review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Foodborne bacteria are a significant contributor to foodborne diseases worldwide, and effective prevention requires accurate early detection and continuous monitoring. Nucleic acid test (NAT)-based detection methods have been extensively studied and applied due to their high specificity and rapid turnaround time. However, most NAT-based detection systems cannot achieve ideal sensitivity or short assay times without efficient sample pretreatment. Although reviews have individually addressed...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560605/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling and simulation approaches for solid-state battery interfaces: challenges, insights, and future perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Solid-state batteries (SSBs) are crucial for next-generation energy storage because of their higher energy density, better safety, and longer cycling stability compared with traditional liquid-electrolyte batteries. However, their real-world application is limited by issues at the interface, such as dendrite formation, mechanical instability, and low ionic conductivity. Modeling and simulation techniques at the atomic and mesoscale levels have become key tools for understanding, predicting, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560564/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Clinical Experience with the Stealth Autoguide Cranial Robotic Guidance Platform for Stereotactic Brain Biopsy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The Stealth Autoguide system facilitates a more efficient frameless stereotactic biopsy than conventional methods by reducing operative time, enhancing accuracy, and allowing for a smaller, muscle-sparing incision. However, some concerns remain, and further clinical validation is needed to define its optimal indications and safety profile.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560496/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genotype-Driven Prognostication in Dilated Cardiomyopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with DCM exhibited varying prognoses according to genotype. Further research is needed to refine risk stratification and the clinical application of genetic testing in DCM.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560493/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atrial Fibrillation, Brain Structure and Cognitive Function: A Mediation Analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: AF is associated with brain atrophy and cognitive impairment, and brain structure partially mediates the association between AF and cognitive function. Our study findings suggest integrated cardiovascular and cognitive assessments in AF management.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560492/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations Between Accelerometer-Measured 24-Hour Movement Behaviors and Cardiac Conduction Disease in the UK Biobank Cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Higher volumes of MVPA were associated with a lower risk of CCD, whereas increased sedentary behavior was associated with higher risk, highlighting the importance of preventive activity patterns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560489/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The First Korean Clinical Evidence With Tafamidis in ATTR-CM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560488/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antiplatelet Therapy in Patients Receiving Percutaneous Coronary Intervention for Bifurcation Lesions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antiplatelet therapy is crucial for patients after percutaneous coronary intervention (PCI), but there is limited high-quality evidence guiding the best strategy for those with bifurcation lesions. The antiplatelet strategy for bifurcation PCI requires balancing the patient's overall thrombotic and bleeding risks. Bifurcation lesions present a complex, high-thrombotic-risk milieu because the procedure often causes plaque disruption and forms an inevitable gap in the sealing of the stent,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560487/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association Between the Persistency and Severity of Mitral Regurgitation and the Hematologic Z-Values of Inflammatory Biomarkers in Kawasaki Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A comparison of hematological z-values in KD with MR and in KD without MR is useful for predicting more severe inflammation. Neutrophils, z-neutrophils, and ESR were significant and consistently associated with pathogenesis of MR and their levels during the early inflammation can predict the persistency and severity of MR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Early Initiation of Evolocumab on Lipid Profiles Changes in Patients With Acute Coronary Syndrome Undergoing Percutaneous Coronary Intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Early initiation of evolocumab in combination therapy achieved greater LDL-C reduction and target achievement in ACS patients undergoing PCI.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560483/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SrMnGeS<sub>4</sub>: A Two-Dimensional Layered Chalcogenide with Magnetic Triangular Lattice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Two-dimensional (2D) magnetic triangular systems are of great interest due to quantum phenomena, but most are occasionally synthesized. In this study, by using the structure building unit of GeS(4) tetrahedron, a novel 2D chalcogenide SrMnGeS(4) with triangular lattice has been successfully synthesized. The title compound features a layered magnetic triangular lattice of Mn^(2+) ions connected by GeS(4) tetrahedron units, which are further separated by nonmagnetic Sr^(2+) ions. Magnetic...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560443/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Average oocyte quality index as a method for scoring dysmorphic oocytes in women with ovarian endometrioma undergoing in vitro fertilization and its correlation with ovarian reserve]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The AOQI in the ovarian endometrioma group was higher compared to the unexplained infertility group, and this difference appeared to arise primarily from reduced ovarian reserve rather than the direct impact of endometrioma itself. Serum AMH levels showed an inverse correlation with AOQI, emphasizing the central role of ovarian reserve in determining oocyte quality.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations between Ambient Air Pollution Exposure and Menstrual Cycle Irregularity in Premenopausal Women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our results indicate associations between various exposure indices of NO₂ and SO₂ and short-interval menstrual cycle irregularity in a representative sample of Korean premenopausal women. This research represents one of the first investigations on this issue; therefore, further longitudinal studies are warranted to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560388/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Resolving Medication-Related Problems in Older Adults through a Multidisciplinary Approach in Korea's Hospital-Based Polypharmacy Program]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Hospital-based multidisciplinary teams effectively identify and rectify MRPs in older Korean adults with polypharmacy. Targeting interventions towards high-risk subgroups (very elderly, high medication count, specific drugs) could optimize PMP efficiency. Long-term clinical and economic outcome studies are needed.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impairment of Cerebral Interstitial Fluid Dynamics after Whole-Brain Radiotherapy and Its Association with Leukoencephalopathy Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: WBRT is associated with impaired cerebral interstitial fluid dynamics, as reflected by a significant reduction in the DTI-ALPS index. A greater decline in the DTI-ALPS index was predictive of LEP development, suggesting its potential utility as a biomarker for early diagnosis of radiation-induced LEP.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and Neuroimaging Findings in Patients with Atypical Visual Field Defects]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Atypical VFDs may indicate lesions along the visual pathway. Neuroimaging is recommended for patients with atypical VFDs, particularly those of older age or presenting with decreased visual acuity, rapid progression or incomplete homonymous hemianopsia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of Multiple Metaphyseal Hole Creation on Long Bone Growth in a Rabbit Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: A single metaphyseal hole promotes overgrowth, whereas an additional hole suppresses growth, likely through vascular disruption. These findings provide insights into bone growth regulation and its underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560384/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Distinguishing Takayasu Arteritis and Giant Cell Arteritis Based on Large-Vessel Involvement Patterns]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Distinct patterns of LV involvement, particularly aortic arch involvement, either alone or combined with right subclavian artery involvement, could accurately differentiate TAK and GCA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endoscopic Diagnosis of Eosinophilic Esophagitis Using a Multi-Task U-Net: A Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our method showed robust performance compared to expert endoscopists and could assist endoscopists of all experience levels in the early detection of EoE-a rare but clinically important condition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steatosis-Associated Fibrosis Estimator Score in Asian Patients with Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: We externally validated the good performance of the SAFE score in Asian patients. The SAFE score has potential as an initial assessment to identify a low-risk population in a primary care setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560381/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Retinal Vascular Occlusive Disease According to Type and Low-Density Lipoprotein-Cholesterol Control after Acute Coronary Syndrome]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: ACS is independently associated with increased RVOD risk, particularly among patients with UA, older age, and poor LDL-C control. Intensive lipid-lowering therapy and ophthalmologic follow-up may reduce vision-threatening vascular events in this high-risk population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560380/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognosis of Infective Endocarditis According to Clinical Characteristics, Economic Status, and Center Experience]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Mortality outcomes of IE were determined by multiple factors, including patients' clinical characteristics, economic status, and center experience. Support for those with low economic status and establishment of well-experienced multidisciplinary teams may help to lower the risk of death in patients with IE.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560379/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fibroneer trials: more than meets the eye]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560330/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Position Paper on Lipoprotein(a) From the Lipoprotein(a) Task Force of the Korean Society of Lipid and Atherosclerosis: Current Evidence, Clinical Applications, and Future Directions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lipoprotein(a) [Lp(a)] is a genetically determined risk factor for atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) and calcific aortic valve stenosis (CAVS), with plasma levels largely unaffected by lifestyle modification or conventional lipid-lowering therapy. Although international guidelines increasingly recognize Lp(a) as a risk-enhancing factor, in many Asian populations thresholds for high Lp(a) and treatment strategies remain undefined. This Korean position paper, developed by the Lp(a)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560299/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeling multistability and hysteresis in urban congestion spreading]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Growing evidence suggests that the macroscopic functional states of urban road networks exhibit multistability and hysteresis, but microscopic mechanisms underlying these phenomena remain elusive. Here, we demonstrate that in real-world road networks, the recovery process of congested roads is not spontaneous, as assumed in existing models, but is hindered by connected congested roads, and such hindered recovery can lead to the emergence of multistability and hysteresis in urban congestion...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560193/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exercise amounts, barriers, and preferences among patients with cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study analyzed exercise amounts, preferences, and barriers among individuals without cancer (Group 1), individuals diagnosed with colorectal, breast, endometrial, or prostate cancer within the past 5 years (Group 2), and those diagnosed >5 years ago (Group 3) in China. We included individuals aged 18 to 75 from a Chinese university hospital in 2021. Groups 1, 2, and 3 comprised 162, 154, and 157 individuals, respectively. Data were collected using questionnaires and analyzed using analysis...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560085/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Annular reconstruction in infective endocarditis: Comparative analysis of surgical outcomes and infection recurrence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Infective endocarditis (IE) presents significant clinical challenges, particularly when the infection extends to the cardiac valve annulus, resulting in severe complications, such as abscesses and fistula formation. Annular reconstruction (AR) has emerged as a crucial surgical technique aimed at eradicating infections and restoring the cardiac anatomy. This study aimed to demonstrate the efficacy of AR by comparing the postoperative outcomes and recurrence rates between the 2 groups. This...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560060/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic impact of baseline left ventricular ejection fraction in patients with coronary chronic total occlusion after successful percutaneous coronary intervention or medical therapy: A prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Left ventricular ejection fraction (LVEF) is a key determinant of prognosis in patients with coronary artery disease. However, the impact of LVEF categories on long-term outcomes in patients with coronary chronic total occlusion (CTO) remains underexplored. This study aimed to evaluate the 3-year clinical outcomes in CTO patients according to LVEF category. We retrospectively analyzed 1255 patients with coronary CTO, categorized into 3 groups based on LVEF: reduced (rEF, ≤40%), mildly reduced...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560022/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>GIST, Hanyang University, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of patient blood management protocol to reduce transfusion rates in limb salvage operations for osteosarcoma: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oncologic orthopedic surgery stands as one of the primary causes necessitating blood transfusions. In an endeavor to mitigate transfusion requirements, the implementation of patient blood management (PBM) holds significant value. We undertook a retrospective study to juxtapose pre and post-PBM implementation scenarios in the context of treating osteosarcoma through limb salvage surgery in patients' extremities. This study encompasses 25 patients who underwent surgery between 2008 and 2016 at our...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559989/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Is omentectomy mandatory in patients with epithelial ovarian cancer having a macroscopically normal-appearing omentum?: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aims to determine the necessity of mandatory omentectomy during staging surgery in patients with epithelial ovarian cancer (EOC) with a normal-appearing omentum. This study analyzed patients with EOC who underwent staging surgery at Korea University Anam Hospital between January 2010 and December 2023, excluding those with incomplete data and those lost to follow-up. The patients were categorized into the omentectomy and non-omentectomy groups. We compared the characteristics,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcutaneous auricular vagus nerve stimulation promotes recovery from otitis media by activating the α7nAChR-mediated anti-inflammatory pathway]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: taVNS was associated with attenuation of LPS-induced acute otitis media and reduced NF-κB activation and downstream cytokine expression in a manner consistent with the involvement of α7nAChR-related signaling. By attenuating excessive inflammatory responses, taVNS was associated with improved auditory function and reduced middle ear injury, suggesting its potential as a non-invasive therapeutic strategy for LPS-induced acute otitis media.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559850/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Suckerin Colloids and Hydrogels With Low Immunogenicity as Resorbable and Hemostatic Tissue Adhesives for Wound Healing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Squid sucker ring teeth proteins (suckerins) have recently been shown to exhibit higher molecular-level adhesion than mussel adhesive proteins-a well-known class of wet-resistant adhesive proteins-and can also assemble into nanoparticles in aqueous conditions. Herein, we present recombinant suckerin-12 colloids and hydrogels as bioadhesives with strong wet adhesion and excellent in vivo biocompatibility. These colloids and hydrogels displayed low cytotoxicity, minimal immunogenicity, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[3D printing of droplet microfluidic devices: principles, wetting control, scale-up, and beyond]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[3D printing is reshaping droplet microfluidics by converting digital designs into sealed, volumetric devices that integrate non-planar droplet generators and junctions, as well as embedded distributors. This Critical Review distills design rules that link geometry, key dimensionless groups (Ca, φ, λ), and wetting control to the robust production of single and multiple emulsions. We compare 3D printing modalities using criteria specific to droplet microfluidics, attainable feature size, optical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562206/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parallel Pathways for Visual and Olfactory Information in the Mushroom Bodies of the Swallowtail Butterfly Brain]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The mushroom bodies (MBs), prominent paired neuropils of the insect brain, are multimodal sensory processing centers. In the MBs of Papilio xuthus, a flower-foraging swallowtail butterfly with sophisticated color vision, the inner zone and the rim of the outer zone of the primary calyx receive prominent visual input. These two visual zones are spatially segregated from the outer zone that receives olfactory input. Sensory information is transmitted to the MB output sites (the lobes) via the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563724/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eosinophilic cholangitis without peripheral eosinophilia presenting as a localized bile duct stricture mimicking perihilar cholangiocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Eosinophilic cholangitis is a rare condition characterized by the infiltration of the bile duct wall by inflammatory cells, predominantly eosinophils, leading to bile duct wall thickening, narrowing, and dilatation. Differentiation between primary sclerosing cholangitis and cholangiocarcinoma remains challenging owing to overlapping clinical and radiological features, and no standardized diagnostic criteria currently exist. We report a case of eosinophilic cholangitis presenting as a localized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563701/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural remission rate and factors associated with radiographic progression in patients with rheumatoid arthritis treated with sarilumab in clinical practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Sarilumab was associated with limited radiographic progression in patients with RA in clinical practice. Associations with MTX use and baseline GC exposure should be interpreted cautiously given the observational design. Key Points • This study reports the structural remission rate and factors associated with radiographic progression in patients with rheumatoid arthritis treated with sarilumab in clinical practice. • The structural remission rate for sarilumab was 78.0%. The change...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563698/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microstructural analysis of a malunited clavicular fracture in a human cadaver]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Clavicle fractures are common, with midshaft fractures accounting for approximately 70-80% of cases. Malunion often occurs following conservative treatment, but the microstructural characteristics of the malunited region remain poorly understood. This case report describes a rare instance of clavicular malunion identified in a 85-year-old male cadaver during a gross anatomy dissection course. Both clavicles were analyzed using radiography, micro-computed tomography (micro-CT), and histology to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Increased anthocyanin accumulation and plant growth by driving PAP1 expression using the 3'downstream region of the sulfate transporter SULTR2;1 gene]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563655/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infiltration of TIM4-positive intratumoral macrophages serves as an adverse prognostic factor in breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These findings suggest that infiltration of TIM4-positive macrophages serves as a strong prognostic indicator in breast cancer and that TIM4 may represent a novel marker for tumor-promoting macrophages.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Year's Greeting 2026 from the Journal of Plant Research]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibody-Drug Conjugates, T-Cell Engager Bispecific Antibodies and Chimeric Antigen Receptor T Cells for Multiple Myeloma: What's the Current Status?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The treatment of multiple myeloma has changed significantly in the last decade. Antibody-drug conjugates, T-cell immunotherapies including bispecific T-cell engaging antibodies and chimeric antigen receptor T-cell therapies, have shown remarkable results in pivotal clinical trials. This has resulted in European Medicines Agency and US Food and Drug Administration approval of agents targeting the B-cell maturation antigen: antibody-drug conjugate belantamab mafodotin (belantamab), bispecific...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563628/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction to: An international survey of allogeneic hematopoietic cell transplantation for X-linked agammaglobulinemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563625/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Insights and Advances in Physical Activity Research on Youth with Type 1 Diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Most youth with type 1 diabetes (T1D) do not meet the guidelines for physical activity engagement, thereby diminishing potential benefits to physical and mental health. This review synthesizes the recent literature on physical activity among youth with T1D and offers recommendations for future research.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563611/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of an educational support tool with a quantitative recording system and feedback function for scaler operation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dental hygienists are professionals responsible for maintaining oral health and assisting in dental treatments. During their training programs, they acquire essential skills and knowledge, including precise intraoral instrument manipulation, such as scaling. Although technical textbooks are available, skills that rely on finger and hand sensations-such as instrument manipulation-are difficult to describe objectively, making instruction heavily dependent on the instructor's expertise. Previous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parental Subjective Disaster Experiences and Behavioral Problems in Children Born After the Great East Japan Earthquake: An Intergenerational Perspective]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study examined associations of parents' subjective perceptions of disaster-related harm from the Great East Japan Earthquake (GEJE) with their mental health and with emotional and behavioral problems in their children born post-disaster. Participants included 218 parents (207 mothers, 11 fathers) and 219 children born post-GEJE, residing in affected areas. Parents served as proxy reporters, completing measures assessing their disaster-related experiences, psychological distress, depressive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pediatric follicular thyroid carcinoma: a clinicopathologic study treated at a single institution during a 30-year period]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563524/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Classical Hodgkin lymphoma associated with immune deficiency and dysregulation exhibits a prognosis similar to sporadic cases but with distinct predictive markers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Immune deficiency and dysregulation (IDD)-associated classical Hodgkin lymphoma (cHL) is one of the common subtypes of IDD-related lymphomas. Patients with IDD-cHL are typically treated with the same chemotherapeutic regimens as those with sporadic cHL. However, the clinical differences between these groups remain poorly elucidated. To assess the impact of immune status on clinical features and treatment outcomes, 44 patients who were newly diagnosed with cHL and treated at our institution,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Five years of experience with skin testing for perioperative anaphylaxis: diagnostic challenges and the need for updated guidelines]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Incidence and clinical significance of inducible perimitral atrial tachycardia in patients with atrial fibrillation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563453/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to the letter regarding "Postoperative risks of type 2 diabetes in elderly hip fracture patients: a propensity score-matched study"]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563445/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Depth-oriented organ-preserving salvage endoscopic strategy with argon plasma coagulation and photodynamic therapy for residual or recurrent esophageal squamous cell carcinoma after chemoradiotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A salvage endoscopic strategy applying APC for ycT1a and PDT for ycT1b-T2, with flexibility based on tumor depth, is feasible, safe, and effective. Tailoring treatment to invasion depth may optimize organ preservation and local control in residual or recurrent ESCC after CRT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Dual Role as Cationic Cu<sup>+</sup> and Cu Alkoxide in Cu-Catalyzed Dearomative Cascade Reactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The reactions of N-alkoxyanilines, which have an electron-donating group at the ortho position, with alcohols in the presence of cationic NHC-Cu and alkoxide cocatalysts afforded dearomative 1,4-cyclohexadiene derivatives in good yields with high product selectivities. The Cu cocatalyst dynamically plays a dual role as a Lewis acidic catalyst to promote the [1,3]-alkoxy rearrangement and a Lewis base catalyst to facilitate the 1,4-addition of the alcohol to the ortho-quinol imine intermediate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563049/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influence of Obstructive Uropathy on Cyst Formation and Nephrogenesis: Insights from a Fetal Lamb Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Obstructive uropathy (OU) during fetal development induces a fetal cystic dysplastic kidney. The mechanisms of cyst formation and the onset of renal dysfunction remain unclear. Determining whether nephrogenic potential persists during fetal life may suggest whether early intervention could preserve renal development. We aimed to evaluate residual nephrogenic activity in fetal cystic dysplastic kidneys using β-catenin and CD10 immunostaining, and to assess whether the site of obstruction...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular architectures and mechanisms involved in protein-mediated molybdate/tungstate acquisition and storage in prokaryotes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Molybdenum and tungsten are essential trace metals whose biological utilization requires strict and selective control of their uptake and intracellular availability. Prokaryotes achieve this through highly specialized systems, involving the oxyanion-specific ATP-binding cassette transporters (ModABC, WtpABC, and TupABC), which discriminate between molybdate and tungstate via distinct periplasmic binding mechanisms. Following molybdenum import, the molybdenum storage proteins store up to ∼130...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Correction: Ikuta et al. Physical Function Trajectory among High-Functioning Long-Term Care Facility Residents: Utilizing Japanese National Data. <em>Geriatrics</em> 2024, <em>9</em>, 123]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There was an error in the original publication [...].]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562794/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directional and Skill-Level Differences in the Speed-Accuracy Trade-Off During Lacrosse Passing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Passing in lacrosse is a fundamental skill essential for both offense and defense, directly influencing game flow. Although the speed-accuracy trade-off is well recognized in motor control, its features in lacrosse passing-particularly regarding directional aspects and skill differences-remain unclear. This study quantified the relationship between pass speed, accuracy, bias, and consistency and examined directional effects and skill-level differences. Methods: Twenty-two female...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562727/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative Analysis of Robotic Assistive Devices on Paretic Knee Motion in Post-Stroke Patients: An IMU-Based Pilot Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Robotic assistive devices are increasingly used in post-stroke gait rehabilitation, yet quantitative evaluations of synchronization between human and robotic joint motion remain limited. This study examined gait kinematics in post-stroke hemiplegic patients using two exoskeleton-type devices-HAL^(®) (Cyberdine Inc., Tsukuba, Japan) and curara^(®) (AssistMotion Inc., Ueda, Japan)-based on synchronized IMU measurements. Methods: Two post-stroke patients performed treadmill walking...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562723/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterologous Production of Torularhodin, the Monocyclic Carotenoid with a Terminal Carboxyl Group, in <em>Escherichia coli</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Torularhodin is the monocyclic C40 carotenoid with the β-ring and a terminal carboxyl group at the acyclic part, with long conjugated double bonds, only synthesized in fungi called red (oleaginous) yeasts, e.g., the genera Rhodotorula and Sporobolomyces. This unique red pigment with strong antioxidant properties is promising for use in food additives, nutritional supplements, and cosmetics. We aimed to produce torularhodin in Escherichia coli through the identification of the biosynthesis genes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rethinking the Origins of Cross-Language Effects: How Heard Verbs Influence Japanese- and English-Speaking Children's Attention to the Details of Actions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Languages differ in how words carve up the world into categories, and these differences in lexical categories often influence how speakers interpret perceived events. Past research has shown that languages with a single and general word for one domain tend to cue attention more broadly than languages with multiple, more specific verbs. This supports the idea that the referential range of lexical categories-how broadly or narrowly a word applies-plays a major role in how heard words guide...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562632/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cotargeting TREM2 and IL2 pathways triggers multipronged anticancer immunity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Triggering receptor expressed on myeloid cells 2 (TREM2) has emerged as a key immunosuppressive target on tumour-associated macrophages (TAMs), where it coordinates protumorigenic and anti-inflammatory functions within the tumour microenvironment (TME). Unfortunately, recent clinical evidence indicates that therapeutic TREM2 blockade has suboptimal efficacy in cancer patients. Now, Von Locquenghien et al. report that MiTE-144, a TREM2 blocking antibody fused to an IL2 variant with TME-restricted...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562407/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[V-ATPase a3 Directs Secretory Lysosome Transport in Enamel Formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Enamel mineralization critically depends on maturation-stage ameloblasts (M-ABs) regulating pH, protein secretion, and cell-matrix adhesion. However, the molecular mechanisms underlying these processes remain poorly understood. This study identifies the vacuolar-type H^(+)-ATPase (V-ATPase) a3 subunit as a key regulator of enamel formation via its role in secretory lysosome trafficking. In a3 knockout (a3KO) mice and cultured ameloblasts, a3 is required for both lysosomal acidification and the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562378/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Cueing Strategies for Gait Impairments in Parkinson's Disease: Protocol of the Multicenter UNITE-PD Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Gait impairments impact independence and quality of life of persons with Parkinson's disease (PD). The application of external and internal cueing strategies can improve gait, but not every person benefits equally from the same strategy. It remains unclear (i) which patient characteristics mediate cueing efficacy, (ii) how cueing efficacy changes over time, (iii) which patient characteristics are associated with long-term compliance, and (iv) what the neural correlates of cueing are. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562323/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Engineering Immortalized Bovine Granulosa Cells Using a Triple-Gene Approach: Mutant CDK4, Cyclin D1, and TERT]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Advancing reproductive technologies in livestock is essential to improve both productivity and genetic potential of cattle. Despite this importance, application of reproductive biotechnologies in cattle breeding remains limited. Bovine granulosa cells (bGCs), which are key components of the ovarian follicle, are critical in female reproduction as they produce steroid hormones and growth factors necessary for oocyte development. However, primary bGCs exhibit restricted proliferative capacity in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synthesis of carbazoles <em>via</em> aryl C-H activation triggered by surfactant-associated palladium nanoparticles under microwave-assisted heating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Herein, we present a novel and environmentally friendly method for synthesizing carbazoles relying on palladium catalysis in water as a green reaction medium. The process utilizes surfactant-associated palladium nanoparticles (PdNPs) with DBU (1,8-diazabicyclo[5.4.0]undec-7-ene) for aryl C-H activation of 2-halo-N-arylanilines under microwave irradiation. There, DBU as a base and ligand enhances the efficiency of the Pd-nanocatalyst. The mild method offers excellent chemoselectivity for the C-I...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562300/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Managing the meniscus part I-Anatomy, biomechanics, and treatment strategies for the atraumatic meniscus tear]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Differentiating atraumatic and traumatic meniscus tears is important for proper diagnosis and management. Many nonoperative modalities exist, yet ultimately operative intervention may be necessary to improve pain and prevent progression to knee osteoarthritis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41562126/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Seasonal Dynamics of Epifaunal Communities on the <em>Sargassum</em> Beds of the Coast of Noto Peninsula, Japan]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Epifaunal communities inhabiting seaweeds are key components of temperate rocky reef ecosystems, playing vital roles in nutrient cycling and biodiversity maintenance. However, limited research has addressed their seasonal dynamics in the semi-enclosed Sea of Japan. This study examined the seasonal changes in epifaunal communities associated with two dominant brown algae, Sargassum macrocarpum and S. patens, in Tsukumo Bay, Noto Peninsula. Over the course of one year, we recorded fluctuations in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561881/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Complete Larval Development of the Pedunculated Barnacle <em>Capitulum mitella</em> (Crustacea: Cirripedia) Using a Standardized Terminology]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We describe the complete larval development of the pedunculated barnacle Capitulum mitella, using both light microscopy and scanning electron microscopy. This includes all six naupliar instars and the final cypris stage. Many previous accounts on the development of barnacle larvae suffer from a shortage in detail and habitually use terminologies that are either inconsistent or hard to compare with those used for other crustaceans. We therefore propose and use a new, completely standardized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561877/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Demonstration of the photo-controllability of the bistable opsin OPN5 using upconversion nanoparticles with multiple emission peaks upon near-infrared photoexcitation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Upconversion nanoparticles (UCNPs) have emerged as promising tools for deep tissue optogenetics because they can convert near-infrared (NIR) light, which has high biopermeability, into ultraviolet (UV) or visible light. In optogenetics, microbially derived photoreceptor proteins such as channelrhodopsin (ChR) have been widely used. G protein-coupled receptor (GPCR)-type opsins have signal amplification capabilities and are emerging as promising candidates for high-sensitivity optogenetic tools....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561484/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modular synthesis of benzothiophene-fused pentalenes reveals substituent-dependent antiaromaticity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antiaromatic π-electron systems provide unique electronic features arising from the cyclic conjugation of 4n π-electrons, yet synthetic access to strongly antiaromatic heteroarene-fused scaffolds remains limited. Here we report a general synthetic route to benzothiophene-fused pentalenes via the first thiophene analogue of Brand's bicyclo[3.3.0]octadiene-2,6-dione intermediate. The pre-installation of the bicyclic five-membered-ring core at an early stage of synthesis enables efficient...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561458/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Real-world effectiveness and safety of lebrikizumab maintenance dosing every 4 weeks starting at week 4 after 2 loading doses in Japanese patients with atopic dermatitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561197/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Influencing factors of physical activity in youths with cystic fibrosis: a socioecological approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings underscore the multifaceted nature of PA behaviour in YwCF and highlight the need for future PA interventions to recognise these multiple levels of influence.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STAT1 drives the immune landscape of murine Toll-like receptor 9-induced liver inflammation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Type I and II IFN-induced STAT1 activation drives TLR9-induced liver inflammation, and support further exploration of JAK1/2 inhibitors, which indirectly inhibit STAT1 activity, in patients with cytokine storm syndromes and other inflammatory liver disorders.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41561071/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characterization of Plant-Based Milk-Derived "Fujiharu Butter": Comparison With Butter and Butter-Like Substitutes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Milk is one of the most widely consumed foods; however, people with lactase nonpersistence or milk protein allergies have difficulty consuming milk, as well as digesting most dairy products. Therefore, plant-based butters made from alternative plant-derived milks have attracted attention. "Fujiharu Butter" is a butter made from plant-based milk. Although it is produced without cow milk, the sensory characteristics of Fujiharu Butter are said to be similar to those of animal-based butter....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560614/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Room-Temperature Magnetic Skyrmions and Intrinsic Anomalous Hall Effect in a Nodal-Line Kagomé Ferromagnet MnRhP]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Topological magnetic semimetals with kagomé lattices have attracted significant attention due to their nontrivial electronic band structures and pronounced electromagnetic responses. The search for kagomé-lattice topological semimetals exhibiting magnetic ordering above room temperature is essential for advancing their potential in device applications. In this work, we report direct observations of topological magnetic textures and anomalous Hall effects driven by topological nodal lines in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Report on the First WEGECA Meeting: Women Endoscopists for Global Exchange and Career Advancement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Treatment adherence and satisfaction of a mobile-based lifestyle intervention in women with prior gestational diabetes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The blended mHealth intervention was feasible and generally well-accepted. Women with both high treatment adherence and high treatment satisfaction showed the most favorable metabolic outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41560335/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Renalase deficiency suppresses hepatic triglyceride accumulation in the progression to MASLD/MASH by GAN diet in male mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) is a growing public health concern characterized by hepatic triglyceride (TG) accumulation, inflammation, and fibrosis. Renalase is known for its role in blood pressure regulation and catecholamine metabolism, but recent evidence suggests broader cytokine-like functions. Moreover, its involvement in MASLD remains unclear. In this study, we examined the effects of renalase deficiency on hepatic lipid metabolism in a Gubra Amylin...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559934/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rop-Mediated Suppression of RpoS Production Increases Resistance to Nitric Oxide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We identified the RNA-binding protein Rop, encoded on the pOSAK1 plasmid of enterohaemorrhagic Escherichia coli (EHEC), as a novel factor that enhances nitric oxide (NO) resistance, although it has previously been reported to regulate plasmid copy number. The Rop-induced increase in NO resistance was significantly reduced in several small noncoding RNA (sRNA) gene-deficient EHEC mutants. Among these sRNAs, DsrA, ArcZ, and RprA were directly involved in the translational regulation of rpoS...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41559857/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260121143420&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shifting the PPARγ conformational ensemble toward a transcriptionally repressive state improves covalent inhibitor efficacy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The nuclear receptor peroxisome proliferator-activated receptor gamma (PPARγ) regulates transcription in response to ligand binding at an orthosteric pocket within the ligand-binding domain (LBD). We previously showed that two covalent ligands, T0070907 and GW9662-extensively used as PPARγ inhibitors to assess off-target activity-weaken but do not completely block ligand binding via an allosteric mechanism associated with pharmacological inverse agonism (Shang and Kojetin, 2024). These covalent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563829/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mesangial Cell-Derived Extracellular Matrix Protein 1 Is Essential for Maintaining Mesangial Matrix Homeostasis and Glomerular Architecture]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: ECM1 was highly expressed in glomerular mesangial cells. Loss of Ecm1 led to altered mesangial matrix composition, matrix expansion, and glomerular abnormalities, while restoration of ECM1 expression reversed these defects, demonstrating an essential role of mesangial cell-derived ECM1 in preserving normal mesangial homeostasis and glomerular structure in mice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563819/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Erasing Identity: Consequences of the Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services's Removal of Race and Ethnicity from Kidney Health Data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Computational Lymphocyte Topology: A Roadmap to Mechanism and Clinical Translation?]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563812/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CLUH Inhibition by Lipocalin-2 Orchestrates Mitochondrial Disruption and Contributes to Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study shows that LCN2 forms a complex with CLUH and inhibits its activity, leading to perinuclear mitochondrial clustering. CLUH loss of function in renal tubular cells is associated with mitochondrial dysfunction and fibrosis, and in humans, CLUH expression inversely correlates with kidney lesions and loss of function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563805/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogen Bonding-Enabled Spider Silk-Mimicking Biodegradable and Self-Sustained Nanofiber Meta-Membranes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The integration of solution electrospinning with biomimetic structures has long been a major challenge in the fabrication of biomimetic membranes. Herein, we unraveled a hydrogen bonding-enabled spider silk-mimicking (HBSS) strategy by multiphase electrospinning. It specifically involved phase-regulating factors to generate a high density of hydrogen bonding within the poly(lactic acid) (PLA) nanofibers of HBSS-PLA. Hydrogen bonding-induced phase separation led to the formation of nanofibrous...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563798/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Acne Incidence and Severity in Transgender Individuals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This study revealed distinct acne incidence patterns in transgender individuals compared with matched cis male and female cohorts. Clinicians should monitor and treat acne in transmasculine individuals prescribed testosterone per clinical guidelines, particularly during the first year. Clinicians should also recognize that acne may develop in transfeminine individuals after estradiol initiation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Direct Difunctionalization of Unsaturated Peptides: A Strategy for Concurrent Incorporation of Trifluoromethyl and Alkynyl Groups]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The simultaneous incorporation of alkyne and trifluoromethyl groups into peptides enables rapid access to multifunctional peptide structures. Herein, we report the first metal-free trifluoromethylalkynylation of unsaturated amino acids and peptides using a cheap trifluoromethylation reagent under mild conditions, offering a practical and versatile route to valuable scaffolds.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563772/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psychiatric Documentation and Management in Primary Care With Artificial Intelligence Scribe Use]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this retrospective cohort study using a matched case-control design examining outpatient primary care notes, incorporation of AI ambient scribes in primary care was associated with greater levels of neuropsychiatric symptom documentation but lesser likelihood of documented management of psychiatric symptoms. Further study will be required to determine whether these changes are associated with differential outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563771/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Valuing Frailty Prevention in Aging in the Post-QALY Era]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563762/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modeled Health and Economic Burden of Frailty and Falls Among Adults With HIV]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this decision analytic modeling study of frailty and falls among people with HIV and viral suppression, the lifetime QALYs lost and costs attributable to frailty and falls were substantial. These findings highlight the potential clinical and economic benefits that could result from interventions to identify, prevent, and treat frailty and falls among people with HIV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563756/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Generative AI Use and Depressive Symptoms Among US Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This survey study found that AI use was significantly associated with greater depressive symptoms, with magnitude of differences varying by age group. Further work is needed to understand whether these associations are causal and explain heterogeneous effects.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prior Concussions and Risk of Disability for Patients After a Motor Vehicle Crash]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: This population-based cohort study suggests a significant increased risk of long-term disability after a motor vehicle crash, particular among patients with a prior concussion. More efforts at concussion prevention and traffic safety counseling may be justified for patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563754/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hope enhances treatment outcome of intensive trauma-focused treatment for PTSD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Hope has been found to positively influence trauma-focused treatment outcomes and is associated with post-traumatic growth (PTG), which contributes to improved treatment efficacy.Objective: This observational study examined the extent to which hope predicts a decline in post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD) symptoms and whether an increase in the level of hope predicts changes in PTSD symptoms. This study also investigated whether PTG mediates the relationship between hope and PTSD...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563752/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prospects of GLP-1 Therapies for Addiction and Mental Health Comorbidities-Quo Vadis?: A Review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: The rationale for studying GLP-1 therapies for ASUDs is supported by preclinical and observational clinical evidence. RCTs are emerging and critically needed at this juncture to determine the safety and efficacy of GLP-1 therapies in people with ASUDs. Pending results from RCTs, GLP-1 therapies have the potential to be repurposed for ASUDs. However, there are several relevant questions in need of further investigation, including the specifics of treatment with GLP-1...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Discordance in Treatment Response Assessment Between Clinicians and Patients With Skin Chronic Graft-vs-Host Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS AND RELEVANCE: In this cohort study, discordance in treatment response assessments between clinicians and patients was common in cutaneous cGVHD, yet clinician-reported and patient-reported treatment responses were both associated with survival. In patients with sclerosis who were more likely to experience discordance, patient-reported response was a critical treatment end point, and approaches should be developed to bridge discordance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563741/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[VFQ-25 With and Without Rasch Scoring Assessed Using Simulated Data in Trials Comparing Laser With Anti-VEGF for Diabetic Retinopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Treatment group differences in Rasch calibrated VFQ-25 domains (visual function, socioemotional, combined) had the highest correlation with differences in VA, although the original multidimensional non-Rasch composite and near activities were similar.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563732/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Toward Optimal Treatment Outcomes in New-Onset Polyarticular-Course Juvenile Idiopathic Arthritis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Polyarticular-course juvenile idiopathic arthritis (polyJIA) is a chronic inflammatory arthritis involving > 4 distinct joints over the course of the disease. PolyJIA tends to be more difficult to treat than other forms of nonsystemic JIA, but advances in immunosuppressive therapies over the past 25 years have dramatically reduced patient morbidity. Despite significant advances in treatment options and outcomes, there is little evidence to guide how and when these treatments should be...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563700/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for disease progression in primary Sjögren's syndrome patients with low disease activity: a multicenter registry-based cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Nearly one-third of pSS patients with low disease activity experience disease worsening. Renal involvement, anti-Sm antibodies, and dry eye symptoms independently predict progression. Risk stratification based on these factors can identify patients requiring closer monitoring and potentially more intensive therapeutic intervention. Key Points • This multicenter registry study of 745 primary Sjögren's syndrome patients with low disease activity found that 28.7% experienced disease...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41563697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260121143419&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>