<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:22:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BPH1 negatively regulates ABA signaling via AtSAP9 degradation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have shown that BPH1 represses the abscisic acid (ABA)-mediated cellular responses. To further understand the mechanism of action of BPH1 in ABA signaling, the putative binding partners of BPH1 were investigated. Arabidopsis stress associated protein 9 (AtSAP9), which acts as a positive regulator of ABA signaling, has been identified as a BPH1-binding protein. Both BPH1 and AtSAP9 proteins were localized in the nucleus and cytosol, and a direct interaction between BPH1 and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114849/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel SYK Variant Causes Enhanced SYK Autophosphorylation and PI3K Activation in an Antibody-Deficient Patient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: We identified a novel gain-of-function variant in SYK to underlie hypogammaglobulinemia and atypical autoinflammatory disease. Flowcytometric screening for phospho-S6 in lymphocytes of IEI patients can guide genetic diagnosis of B-cell signaling abnormalities.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114848/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antenatal Care Utilization in Somalia, 2020 Somalia Demographic Health Survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study reveals that only 7 out of 100 pregnancies in Somalia receive the WHO-recommended minimum of four ANC visits, placing Somalia among the lowest-performing countries globally for antenatal care utilization. These findings underscore the urgent need for targeted interventions and equity-focused policies to close the maternal health service gaps, particularly in nomadic and rural populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114755/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[User-informed recommendations for enhancing smart home services among people with disabilities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Smart home technology offers significant potential to improve independence, convenience, and daily functioning for individuals with disabilities. Despite its promise, there is limited research examining how people with different types of disabilities experience and adopt smart home systems in their everyday lives. This study aimed to explore user perspectives and suggest strategies for enhancing smart home services by conducting a cross-sectional qualitative study with 25 participants, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114709/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding Electrochemical CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction Selectivity of Cu Binary Alloys from Electronic Structure Descriptors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We investigate the electrochemical reduction of carbon dioxide (CO(2)RR) using Cu-M (M = Ni, Pd, Ag, Au, Zn, Cr) binary alloys. Through experimental and theoretical analysis, we explore the structural and electronic properties of these alloys and their impact on CO(2)RR product selectivity. Our findings reveal that the d-band center of Cu-M alloys serves as a crucial descriptor, influencing product distribution. As the d-band center increases, more CO is produced, while the formation of C(2)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114686/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluating the feasibility and usefulness of electric knee-ankle-foot orthosis in stroke rehabilitation: Association with pretest Berg balance scale scores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stroke often leads to hemiplegia, significantly impairing walking ability. Traditional rehabilitation methods commonly use mechanical knee-ankle-foot orthoses (KAFOs) to stabilize gait, but these can restrict knee flexion and reduce walking efficiency. This study aimed to evaluate the feasibility and effectiveness of an Electric KAFO (E-KAFO) for stroke survivors with hemiplegia, using the Berg Balance Scale to determine its impact on walking function. Fourteen individuals with hemiplegia (mean...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114559/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Organ-Specific Dedifferentiation and Epigenetic Remodeling in In Vivo Reprogramming]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The advent of in vivo reprogramming through transient expression of the Yamanaka factors (OCT4, SOX2, KLF4, and c-MYC) holds strong promise for regenerative medicine, despite ongoing concerns about safety and clinical applicability. This review synthesizes recent advances in in vivo reprogramming, focusing on its potential to restore regenerative competence and promote rejuvenation across diverse tissues, including the retina, skeletal muscle, heart, liver, brain, and intestine. We highlight...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114535/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adult K18-hACE2 mice are suitable for studying intranasal SARS-CoV-2 infection but not direct-contact transmission]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The rapid global spread of severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus-2 (SARS-CoV-2) since 2019 emphasizes the need to understand its transmission routes, which mainly comprise airborne and contact transmission. Contact transmission, where the virus spreads through direct or indirect contact, is key to the disease epidemiology. Therefore, investigating contact transmission in animal models is crucial for understanding SARS-CoV-2 behavior and developing effective preventive measures. Although...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Optimizing thermoelectric efficiency in Sn-doped Sb2Te3 alloys through Se alloying by modulating carrier and phonon transport]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sb2Te3-based alloys have attracted considerable attention owing to their favorable thermoelectric transport properties in the mid-temperature range. Herein, the thermoelectric transport properties of pristine Sb2Te3 and Sn0.03Sb1.97Te3-ySey (y = 0, 0.05, 0.10, 0.15, 0.20, and 0.25) alloys were systematically investigated by combining Sn doping with Se alloying. The 1.5 at. % Sn doping in Sb2Te3 as Sn0.03Sb1.97Te3 increased the density-of-states effective mass (md*) and reduced lattice thermal...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114475/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel HLA-B*51:429 and HLA-DRB1*11:352 Alleles, and Extension of HLA-DQB1*06:161]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The novel alleles HLA-B*51:429 and HLA-DRB*111:352 and the extended allele HLA-DQB1*06:161 were identified during routine HLA typing.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114462/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative effectiveness of digital versus face-to-face cognitive behavioral therapy for alcohol use disorder: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Alcohol use disorder (AUD) is a chronic condition that impairs health and function. Cognitive behavioral therapy (CBT) is an evidence-based treatment traditionally delivered face-to-face. Recently, digital CBT delivered online has gained prominence because of access barriers and user preferences. Although many digital CBT studies have emerged, few systematic reviews have directly compared digital and face-to-face CBT in adults with AUD. This systematic review and meta-analysis aimed to evaluate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative study on bone mineral density in premenopausal patients with estrogen receptor-positive breast cancer in ASTRRA Study: a 5-year follow-up study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings highlighted the deleterious impact on BMD following OFS addition, compared with tamoxifen only treatment. Early OFS exerted an even more detrimental influence on bone health in premenopausal patients with estrogen receptor-positive breast cancer and recovered ovarian function.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114338/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparative immunohistochemical expression of TROP2 in brain metastatic and primary tumors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[TROP2 overexpression was reported to predict poor prognosis and increased metastatic potential. This study evaluates TROP2 expression in brain metastases from diverse solid tumors and its consistency with primary tumors, addressing the limited research on TROP2 heterogeneity and its implications for CNS-targeted therapies. TROP2 immunohistochemical staining was performed on 61 brain metastatic tumors and 14 corresponding primary tumors. Based on TROP2 expression, cases were categorized into...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Molecular Evaluation of Expression Changes in Genes Associated With Colistin Resistance and Virulence Development in <em>Salmonella enterica</em> From Two Iran Hospitals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Salmonella entericais one of the most frequent causes of gastroenteritis in humans. The emergence of antimicrobial-resistant strains of the bacterium, especially those which are resistant toward colistin (CST), the latest antibiotic introduced to cure this bacterial disease, has become a severe health problem. Beside pmrA and pmrB genes, CST resistance is determined by mobilized colistin resistance (mcr) genes. Accordingly, in the present study, the expression pattern of these genes and fliC...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dysregulated vitamin D signaling in Hashimoto's thyroiditis: an integrated transcriptomic study in a Korean cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study presents RNA-seq data acquired from the Korean HT cohort in this study, and highlighted dysregulated vitamin D signaling in thyroid tissues from the HT cohort. Further investigations are needed to elucidate the causal role of vitamin D signaling in the pathogenesis of HT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113708/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between metabolic activity of visceral adipose tissue and retinal vein occlusion: a preliminary <sup>18</sup>F-FDG PET/CT study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The metabolic activity of VAT, as assessed by ^(18)F-FDG PET/CT, was found to be associated with the presence of RVO and correlated with the degree of systemic inflammation. Therefore, VAT SUVmax may serve as a potential surrogate marker for obesity-related VAT inflammation linked to RVO.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113704/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[XEN Surgery as a "Rescue" for Previous Glaucoma Drainage Device Surgery with Corneal Endothelial Cell Loss: A Case Report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Replacing a GDD tube with a XEN stent is a promising alternative to prevent further corneal endothelial cell loss while maintaining IOP control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113684/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mapping sponsorship portfolios in esports: implied strategic continuity and diversification in the league of legends pro league]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings suggest that clubs should prioritize a core set of enduring sponsors while expanding into diverse categories to reduce revenue volatility, strengthen bargaining power, and enhance resilience to market shocks. The study provides a replicable framework for evaluating sponsorship continuity and diversification, supporting evidence-based decision-making in esports managerial practice.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113469/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Practical Approach to Rectal Cancer Staging with Abbreviated Liver MRI]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Occurrence and exposure assessment of erythritol from distributed foods in Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Given the increasing concerns regarding the safety of sugar alcohols such as erythritol, this study quantified erythritol concentrations in commonly consumed processed foods in Korea and assessed dietary exposure by age and gender. A total of 110 products were analyzed using a validated high-performance liquid chromatography method with ultraviolet detection. The method showed linearity (R ^(2) = 0.9999), a limit of detection of 0.01 mg/kg, and recovery rates of 81.38-108.08%. Erythritol...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113277/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How we learn to like: the role of perceptual learning in development of liking, quality perception, and appreciation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This review explores how perceptual learning contributes to the development of liking for novel and unfamiliar foods. Food acceptance evolves dynamically with repeated exposure. Repeated exposure significantly enhances the acceptance of novel and unfamiliar foods through perceptual changes, as evidenced by empirical studies and theoretical frameworks. Repeated exposure facilitates perceptual learning by enhancing the ability to detect specific sensory attributes and to filter out irrelevant...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113273/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dietary sphingolipids and milk fat globule membrane: emerging roles in cardiometabolic health and muscle function]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sphingolipids (SPLs) are bioactive lipids that play a critical role in metabolic health. Milk fat globule membrane (MFGM) is a rich source of SPLs, and emerging evidence suggests that dietary SPLs and MFGM contribute to cardiometabolic health. Dietary SPLs, including MFGM, have been shown to reduce intestinal lipid absorption, improve hepatic lipid metabolism, and modulate cholesterol transport. The ceramide (Cer)/sphingosine-1-phosphate (S1P) ratio, rather than total plasma Cer levels, appears...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neuroprotection of fermented small black soybean (<em>Rhynchosia nulubilis</em>) on hippocampal neurons through antioxidant effect]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rhynchosia nulubilis (RN), a small black soybean, is traditionally used in Korean oriental medicine. In this study, RN was fermented using a novel lactic acid bacterium, Pediococcus pentosaceus AOA2016 (AOA2016), which enhanced its antioxidant properties. Fermentation significantly increased total phenolic acid and procyanidin levels. Among phenolic acids, protocatechuic acid (PCA) increased the most (11.83 mg/100 g), while gentisic acid (GA) was newly produced (1.23 mg/100 g). Fermented RN...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113270/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Quality attributes of canned whelk (<em>Buccinum striatissimum</em>) sterilized under various temperature and time conditions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The aim of this study was to characterize the effects of sterilization conditions on the quality attributes of canned whelk. Thermal sterilization was performed to achieve the same target sterility (F(0) value of 32 min) under seven temperature and time conditions ranging from 116 °C for 105 min to 128 °C for 11 min. After sterilization, quality attributes including cooking loss, pH, color, and texture were assessed. The processing conditions significantly impacted the physicochemical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Validation and determination of steviol glycosides in processed food products]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Steviol glycosides have gained attention as low-calorie sweeteners. The acceptable daily intake (ADI) for steviol glycosides is 4 mg/kg bw/day, requiring continuous exposure assessments. To generate occurrence data for exposure evaluations, this study validated a high-sensitivity HPLC- variable wavelength detector (VWD) analytical method for quantifying five steviol glycosides and applied the method to processed food products distributed in South Korea. The limit of detection (LOD) was in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113266/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The antihyperglycemic potential of <em>Saccharina japonica</em>: a comparative study of water and ethanol extracts through chemical profiling and in vitro and in vivo studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Type 2 diabetes mellitus (T2DM) is a global health concern due to postprandial hyperglycemia, complications, and mortality. Synthetic drugs, despite efficacy, cause side effects like hypoglycemia, driving demand for alternatives. This study evaluated Saccharina japonica (SJ) extracts' effects on postprandial glucose control. Chemical profiling determined the compound compositions of both water and ethanol extracts. In vitro, water and ethanol extracts inhibited α-glucosidase and glucose uptake,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113264/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Perilla frutescens</em> Britton var. <em>acuta</em> Kudo ameliorates OVA-induced allergic asthma via inhibiting NF-κB and p38 signaling pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Allergic asthma, the most common phenotype of asthma, is a chronic inflammatory airway disease driven by Type 2 immune responses and characterized by eosinophilic infiltration, elevated IgE levels, and activation of inflammatory pathways. This study investigated the anti-inflammatory and immunomodulatory effects of Perilla frutescens var. acuta Kudo extract (PFE), a plant rich in rosmarinic acid (RA), using an ovalbumin (OVA)-induced mouse model of allergic asthma. Given RA's well-documented...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113263/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, Yonsei University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The optimized combination of extracts from Sajabal mugwort and green tea synergistically enhanced antioxidant activity in vitro and in vivo]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In our previous study, the combination of Korean Sajabal mugwort extract (SME) and green tea extract (GTE) at a 9:1 ratio showed synergistic effects on blood flow. In this study, we evaluated the antioxidant activity of the mixture of SME and GTE, and the significance of synergy was confirmed by combination index (CI) value. SME and GTE mixture exhibited synergistic antioxidant activity, compared to individual treatments, and reduced H₂O₂-induced intracellular ROS in a dose-dependent manner. In...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113261/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Improving oral fat sensitivity measurement and evaluating key fat types using a modified signal detection approach and additive-free milk-based emulsions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humans can perceive the taste of certain fat components, especially free fatty acids (FFAs); however, sensitivity varies by fat type and testing methods. This study used a modified descending-block dual-reminder A-Not A (DR A-Not A) signal detection method with repeated measures to assess fat sensitivity within a food emulsion system. Detection thresholds for oleic acid (FFA), canola oil (triacylglycerol, TAG), and their mixture (TAG + FFA) were measured in young Korean females across multiple...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113257/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A novel influenza vector-based vaccine expressing ESAT-6 and TB10.4 confers immunity and protection against <em>Bovine tuberculosis</em> in guinea pigs and calves]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This novel influenza vector-based vaccine expressing ESAT-6 and TB10.4 antigens elicits strong, long-lasting cellular immunity and provides significant protection against M. bovis infection in guinea pigs and calves. The adjuvant-free formulation demonstrated higher immunogenicity, simplified production, and minimal adverse reactions, positioning it as a promising alternative to BCG for bTB control in livestock.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113222/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Landscape of T-cell exhaustion heterogeneity and HBV integration in virus-related HCC revealed by whole-exome, transcriptome, and single-cell sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study revealed the heterogeneity in T-cell exhaustion in the TIME of HCC, along with differences in HBV integrations and molecular subtypes. These findings provide insight into the intricate relationship between high exhaustion, proliferation subtype, increased HBV integrations, and enhanced HBV-induced oncogenic potential in virus-related HCC.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bacteriophage-mediated antibacterial and photodynamic therapies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial resistance threatens global health, with multidrug-resistant pathogens causing millions of deaths annually. Conventional antibiotics face limitations due to bacterial biofilms, resistance mechanisms, and host toxicity. Bacteriophages, due to their high specificity, hold great potential in antimicrobial therapy, targeted drug delivery. In recent years, advances in chemical biology and nanomaterials science have led to the continuous refinement of surface chemical modification...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spontaneous colonic transection following pathologic complete response to pembrolizumab in high microsatellite instability colorectal cancer: A case report and review of literature]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Immune checkpoint inhibitors may cause delayed structural damage to bowel tissue even after apparent complete tumor regression.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113075/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UV curable resin as a rapid and superior sealant for STORM]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Stochastic optical reconstruction microscopy (STORM) relies on controlled photoswitching of fluorophores, enabled by specialized imaging buffers containing thiols and oxygen scavengers. The glucose oxidase and catalase (GLOX) system is still the most widely used, especially for Alexa Fluor 647 dyes. However, GLOX gradually acidifies the buffer due to oxygen infiltration, and this pH drop degrades single-molecule blinking and limits imaging duration to several hours even when sealed with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112786/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Metabarcoding analysis reveals hidden eukaryotic plankton biodiversity in the Ross Sea, Antarctica]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Analyzing eukaryotic plankton communities in the vast and extreme Antarctic environment based on eDNA has proven to be highly efficient, enabling the detection of a greater number of species, including those that were difficult to identify in previous studies. It was observed that in the Ross Sea Marine Protected Area, various species form distinct community structures such as phytoplankton and zooplankton, each inhabiting the area according to different environmental variables and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112759/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Role of Mesenchymal Stem Cells in Drug Resistance in Lung Neoplasms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The tumor microenvironment (TME) is a decisive determinant of therapeutic response and the emergence of drug resistance in lung cancer. Among its stromal constituents, mesenchymal stem cells (MSCs) are pivotal regulators of disease progression because they secrete diverse paracrine mediators. Accumulating evidence indicates that MSC-derived cytokines, growth factors, and extracellular vesicles (EVs) drive epithelial-mesenchymal transition (EMT)-a phenotypic shift that augments cellular motility,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112422/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-nucleotide polymorphisms of donor <em>CYP3A5</em> and recipient <em>ABCB1</em> affect tacrolimus intrapatient variability in living donor liver transplantation: a retrospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: SNPs of donor CYP3A5 and recipient ABCB1 can significantly influence tacrolimus IPV in patients undergoing living donor LT. Identifying these SNPs can help determine high IPV-prone patients, facilitate close monitoring of high IPV-susceptible groups, and improve outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112358/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Patient-reported outcomes of automated breast ultrasound: considerations for screening modality selection, based on a prospective observational survey]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Based on patient-reported outcomes, ABUS could complement handheld ultrasound in breast screening. Selecting modalities by age, BMI, breast size, and density may enhance satisfaction and resource use. Personalized strategies may improve screening experience and efficiency.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112357/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evolving minimally invasive strategies for lumbar hernia repair: a video article comparing conventional laparoscopy, robotic surgery, and articulating laparoscopy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Multiple minimally invasive approaches for lumbar hernia repair are feasible, each with unique benefits, allowing surgeons to choose based on resource availability and expertise.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term clinical outcomes of type 2 endoleak intervention and the crucial role of additional endoleak development after endovascular aneurysm repair: a single-center retrospective observational cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Interventions for T2EL did not improve OS rates, reduce open conversion rates, or increase T2EL closure rates, even in patients with sac growth. This study suggests that current T2EL interventions are not sufficiently effective, emphasizing the need to detect the development of other types of endoleak that may lead to rupture.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112351/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strategic latency with temporal mutualism: a coevolutionary model of the host-varicella-zoster virus relationship]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[After primary infection with varicella, varicella-zoster virus (VZV) establishes a latent state that precedes the clinical manifestation of herpes zoster. Growing evidence, however, indicates that latency is not merely quiescent but represents an active immunological adaptation. We propose the immunosensor hypothesis, in which VZV latency within sensory ganglia contributes to host immune surveillance while simultaneously ensuring viral persistence. Using a game-theoretical framework, we...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112280/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutrophil extracellular traps predict poor survival in cancer: a systematic review and meta-analysis of studies on tissue and circulating biomarkers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Elevated NET levels predict poorer outcomes in patients with cancer independent of specimen source and most analytic modalities (except cell free DNA), supporting NETs as a promising biomarker for risk stratification and precision oncologic decision making.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112271/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Transcultural Adaptation of the Korean Version of the Forgotten Joint Score for Total Hip Arthroplasty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The K-FJS is a reliable and valid method for assessing joint awareness in Korean THA patients. Its application in clinical practice may improve the assessment of patient outcomes following THA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112136/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Predictive Value of Gluteal Muscle Index for Diagnosing Sarcopenia in Community-Dwelling Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The present study highlights the potential of GMI as a clinically meaningful predictor of sarcopenia, outperforming the psoas muscle in diagnostic accuracy. Furthermore, the sex-specific cutoff values identified from the study could aid in early detection and risk stratification, offering a novel approach for sarcopenia assessment in community-dwelling adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112135/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Possible Association between Rotator Cuff Repair and Suicide: A Nationwide Cohort Study Using Propensity Score Matching]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients who underwent RCR demonstrated no association with suicide within the first postoperative year, but a noticeable trend of increased suicide incidence emerged after this period. This finding suggests the potential impact of challenges, such as intense pain, rehabilitation difficulties, persistent functional limitations, and RC retear, on the psychological well-being of patients following RCR. It is imperative that these patients receive close monitoring and appropriate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112134/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Can the Inverted Application of the PHILOS Plate Be an Alternative in Extra-articular Distal Humerus Fractures? A Comparative Analysis with the Extra-articular Distal Humerus Plate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Application of the modified PHILOS plate demonstrated outcomes comparable to those of the EADHP in treating extra-articular diaphyseal distal humerus fractures, with significantly reduced operation time and blood loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel Technique for Depressed Humeral Head Fractures: Arthroscopic Reduction and Subchondral Buttress Fixation Using a Polyaxial Locking Plate]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Humeral head fractures, though relatively rare, pose significant challenges due to the risk of complications such as osteoarthritis and avascular necrosis. Particularly in younger patients, joint-preserving procedures are prioritized over arthroplasty, and their higher activity demands necessitate more precise and reliable reduction and fixation. We have developed a less invasive, more accurate, and more stable surgical technique utilizing arthroscopy and a polyaxial locking plate. Since this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112129/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advancing Precision in Shoulder Arthroplasty: Patient-Specific Instrumentation, Navigation, and Emerging Technologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The evolution of shoulder arthroplasty has seen transformative advancements to improve precision, minimize complications, and optimize functional outcomes. Patient-specific instrumentation and navigation systems are pivotal innovations that improve surgical accuracy and enable tailored approaches for complex anatomy. These tools also impact preoperative planning and decision-making, contributing to more efficient procedures and reduced intraoperative errors. Emerging technologies, including...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112128/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plate Osteosynthesis for Segmental Forearm Fractures: A Comparison of Outcomes in Floating Elbow and Isolated Forearm Fractures]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In our study, good bone union was achieved through open reduction and plate fixation in forearm segmental fractures, regardless of the presence of a floating elbow. However, functional outcomes were significantly worse in floating elbow cases, likely due to the combined effect of soft-tissue injuries and humeral fractures. This suggests that soft-tissue injuries play a key role in determining clinical outcomes. Therefore, meticulous management of soft tissue injuries, combined with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Minimally Invasive Treatment Using Biportal Endoscopic Decompression with Vertebroplasty for Osteoporotic Vertebral Compression Fractures in Older Adult Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: BELD combined with PVP is a safe and effective, minimally invasive option for older adults with OVCFs and neurological symptoms. This technique provides adequate neural decompression and vertebral stabilization while minimizing the risks associated with extensive fusion surgery in this vulnerable population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112125/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Antiresorptive Therapy on Development of Posttraumatic Osteoarthritis after Intra-articular Distal Radius Fracture in Female Patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Initiation of antiresorptive therapy was associated with a lower incidence of radiographic OA after an intra-articular DRF, especially in those without osteoporosis. This study suggests that attempts to decrease bone remodeling might be effective for OA prevention in a joint at risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112124/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between Hypertrophic Change of Greater Tuberosity in Plain Radiography and Rotator Cuff Tears]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: GT spurs observed in plain radiographs of patients with shoulder pain were found to be predictive of supraspinatus tendon tears. Even if there are negative findings in the physical examination, patients with GT spurs should be considered for special imaging to evaluate the possibility of an RCT.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112122/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Repair of Deltoid Ligament Disruption in Bimalleolar Equivalent Fractures: A Cadaveric Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The stability observed in stress tests following ADLR and the results of torque failure testing suggest that ADLR alone is sufficient to restore ankle stability. Initial stability was achieved using ADLR, which can be performed relatively easily even in cases of cDLR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41112120/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association of hemorrhoidal disease with dementia risk: a nationwide cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Research on the association between hemorrhoidal diseases (HDs) and dementia is limited. We explored this relationship in a population-based longitudinal cohort and proposed that individuals with HD may experience a higher incidence of dementia.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orally Administered Edible Snail Extract Powder Enhances Skin Hydration via Hyaluronic Acid Synthesis and Barrier Gene Modulation in SKH-1 Hairless Mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[SKH-1 hairless mice were used as the in vivo model in this study to evaluate the efficacy of oral snail extract powder (SEP) on skin hydration and barrier enhancement. The skin serves as a primary barrier against external stimuli and plays a critical role in maintaining water homeostasis. Optimal skin hydration is essential for preserving barrier integrity and preventing dermatological conditions such as xerosis and atopic dermatitis. Although edible snail has demonstrated moisturizing effects...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111896/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pelubiprofen and Shinbaro: a therapeutic approach for osteoarthritis in a murine medial meniscus destabilization model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Current osteoarthritis treatments can cause serious long-term side effects, and Shinbaro capsules have limited efficacy when used alone. We aimed to determine whether combining pelubiprofen and Shinbaro capsules could offer a more effective and safer treatment strategy for osteoarthritis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111515/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dual-Polarization Second Harmonic Generation Interferometry for Imaging Antiparallel Domains and Stacking Angles of 2D Heterocrystals]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Optical second-harmonic generation (SHG) enables orientational polarimetry for crystallographic analysis and domain imaging of various materials. However, conventional SHG intensity polarimetry, which neglects phase information, fails to resolve antiparallel domains and to describe two-dimensional heterostructures, which represent a new class of van der Waals-bound composite crystals. In this work, we report dual-polarization spectral phase interferometry (DP-SPI) and establish a generalized SHG...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111401/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Liver Week 2025 Highlights: Celebrating the 30th Anniversary of the Korean Association for the Study of the Liver]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111276/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[dpdata: A Scalable Python Toolkit for Atomistic Machine Learning Data Sets]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Seamless management of atomistic data sets is a critical prerequisite for the successful development and deployment of machine learning potentials (MLPs). Here, we present dpdata, an open-source Python library designed to streamline every aspect of MLP data handling. Built upon a flexible, plugin-based architecture, dpdata supports reading, writing, and converting between a broad range of file formats─from popular quantum-chemistry packages and molecular-dynamics engines to specialized MLP...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41114668/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sensory drivers of liking for plant-based meat alternatives: insights from check-all-that-apply with ideal profile integration]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plant-based meats have gained popularity owing to environmental and health considerations; however, their acceptance is often limited by less favorable sensory qualities. This study investigated the sensory drivers of liking for plant-based tteok-galbi by applying penalty analysis and partial least squares regression (PLSR) to check-all-that-apply data. To strengthen the findings, the rate-all-that-apply method was implemented with a separate group of consumers. A total of 200 consumers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41113259/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Electrochemical deposition of mesoporous high-entropy Pt-Pd-Rh-Ru-Cu-Au-Se-Mo films using polymeric micelle templating]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Platinum (Pt)-based high-entropy alloys (HEAs) can optimize catalytic properties through multi-element synergy, yet conventional synthesis requires harsh conditions such as high temperature/pressure or toxic solvents, limiting sustainable applications. Here, we report the synthesis of a mesoporous high-entropy alloy composed of Pt, Pd, Rh, Ru, Cu, Au, Se, and Mo using a micelle soft-templating method by electrochemical deposition. The effects of electrodeposition potentials on entropy changes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Atomic Force Microscopy Analysis of Bridging-Induced Phase Separation Mediated by SMC Proteins]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Structural maintenance of chromosome (SMC) protein is essential for chromosomal architecture and genome stability across all domains of life. SMC proteins, including cohesin, condensin, and the Smc5/6 complex, are known to organize chromosomes through DNA loop extrusion. However, recent atomic force microscopy (AFM) studies showed ATP-independent DNA-bridging-dependent cohesin/DNA condensate formation, suggesting bridging-induced phase separation (BIPS) for genome organization. Here, we present...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111103/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical Benefit of Adjuvant Capecitabine According To Residual Cancer Burden in Patients With Triple-Negative Breast Cancer With Residual Disease Following Neoadjuvant Chemotherapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Adjuvant capecitabine was most beneficial in patients with RCB-III disease, primarily through a reduction in distant metastasis. These findings support its selective use in high-risk TNBC populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111043/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of ultrasound-detected and undetected hepatocellular carcinomas: a post-hoc, subgroup analysis from the MAGNUS-HCC surveillance trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: US is less effective in detecting HCCs in patients with a higher BMI and tumors located in the blind spots or left hemiliver. These limitations should be considered in planning and interpreting surveillance strategies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41111034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Interactions between the Gut Microbiome, Health, and Metabolic Disorders in Preterm Infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Preterm birth, which occurs before the entire gestation is completed, causes serious health challenges for newborns. The gastrointestinal tract often shows delayed development and poor function in nutrient utilization and immune response. Preterm neonates are faced with difficulties in growth, are more vulnerable to infections, and have a higher risk of developing inflammatory diseases. One key factor in these outcomes is the abnormal development of intestinal microbiota. In premature neonates,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110993/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiomics Integration Reveals Microbial Gene Interactions Shaping Host Responses in a DSS-Induced Colitis Mouse Model]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammatory bowel disease (IBD) has been studied with a multi-omics approach to identify key contributors and unravel the biological complexity of its pathogenesis, aiding in the development of early diagnostic markers and therapeutic targets. The dextran sulfate sodium (DSS)-induced colitis mouse model, a widely used system for studying IBD, induces gut barrier disruption and proinflammatory responses, making it an ideal model for investigating host-microbiome interactions. This study...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110987/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MMPP Attenuates the Inflammatory Response by Suppressing ROS and Proinflammatory Cytokine and Chemokine Production in TNF-α/IFN-γ-Stimulated Human Keratinocytes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Keratinocytes play a significant role in regulating skin immune homeostasis, and their dysregulation is central to chronic inflammatory disorders such as atopic dermatitis and psoriasis. Inflammatory mediators such as tumor necrosis factor alpha (TNF-α) and interferon-gamma (IFN-γ) can disrupt this balance, inducing abnormal cytokine and chemokine expression that promotes immune cell infiltration and chronic inflammation in the skin. While (E)-2,4-bis(p-hydroxyphenyl)-2-butenal (BHPB) has shown...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110986/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Similar Microbial Carbon Limitation with Soil Depth despite Decreasing Carbon Availability]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Carbon availability regulates the rate of microbial soil organic matter decay and respiration. However, it remains unclear how much carbon is available to microbes, and if soil organic carbon content influences microbial carbon limitation. Here, the Michaelis-Menten parameters (V(max) and k(m)) were employed to estimate available carbon and the degree of carbon limitation along soil depth profiles (0-60 cm) at two study sites with varying soil organic carbon content. Available carbon as well as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110984/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Lactiplantibacillus plantarum</em> WB3801 and <em>Lactiplantibacillus plantarum</em> WB3808 Showed Antioxidant Effect and Anti-Apoptosis through Activation of the Keap1/Nrf2/HO-1 Pathway in H<sub>2</sub>O<sub>2</sub>-Induced HT-29 Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxidative stress, primarily triggered by elevated levels of reactive oxygen species (ROS) contributes to intestinal epithelial injury and apoptosis, and is closely associated with gastrointestinal disorders. In this study, we evaluated the cytoprotective effects of three Lactiplantibacillus plantarum strains (WB3801, WB3804, and WB3808) isolated from Korean kimchi against H(2)O(2)-induced oxidative stress in HT-29 cells. The strains exhibited markedly strong acid and bile tolerance, as well as...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110982/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reply]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110860/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Overall Survival with Abemaciclib in Early Breast Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Adjuvant abemaciclib-ET resulted in a statistically significant and clinically meaningful improvement in OS compared to ET in patients with HR+, HER2-, node-positive, high-risk EBC. At 7 years, abemaciclib-ET continued to demonstrate a sustained IDFS and DRFS benefit.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110697/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjuvant nivolumab versus placebo for high-risk muscle-invasive urothelial carcinoma: 5-year efficacy and ctDNA results from CheckMate 274]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Five-year results confirm durable DFS benefit and consistent safety profile for adjuvant nivolumab in high-risk MIUC. Post-hoc exploratory ctDNA assessment identified patients at highest risk of recurrence and may inform tailored adjuvant therapy strategies, pending further validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110694/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[\zaAlectinib versus crizotinib in previously untreated ALK-positive advanced non-small cell lung cancer: Final overall survival analysis of the Phase III ALEX study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These final OS data show the sustained long-term systemic and intracranial efficacy of alectinib in the first-line treatment of ALK-positive NSCLC and confirm alectinib as a standard of care in this setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[International consensuses and guidelines on diagnosing and managing Coats' disease by the Academia Retina Internationalis (ARI), Asia-Pacific Vitreo-retina Society (APVRS) and the Asia-Pacific Professors of Ophthalmology (AAPPO)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Coats' disease is a rare, retinal vascular disorder characterized by telangiectasias, aneurysmal dilations, and progressive exudative retinal detachment. Limited understanding of the disease warranted the need to identify controversial issues in through extensive literature search and debate discussion of the international panel of experts. Extensive literature search was done on multiple aspects of the disease-classification patterns, disease, Coats plus and Coats-like response. Other key...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110679/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural-Functional Brain Network Modulation using Transcranial Focused Ultrasound Stimulation: Implications on the Default Mode Network in Humans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Transcranial focused ultrasound (tFUS) has emerged as a promising noninvasive technique for brain stimulation due to its precise focusing and deep penetration capabilities. However, its potential to modulate brain networks beyond the stimulation site and optimal sonication parameters required for such modulation remain unclear. In light of this knowledge gap, this study investigates the effects of tFUS targeted at the medial prefrontal cortex (mPFC), a key component of the default mode network...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110649/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radiological and Clinical Outcomes of Monoaxial Versus Polyaxial Screw Constructs in C1 Jefferson Fracture Osteosynthesis: A Retrospective Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Monoaxial screws provided superior anterior arch reduction, lateral mass realignment, and shorter operative time without compromising motion or clinical outcomes. Both constructs yielded similar improvements in pain and function. Screw selection has significant implications for radiological correction in motion-preserving surgery for unstable C1 fractures; however, larger prospective studies are warranted to determine the long-term outcome.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110595/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Response to comments by Kong et al]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110554/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Population health impacts of national health insurance coverage for neonatal intensive care unit admission in South Korea: evidence from regression discontinuity analyses]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: NICU coverage showed no mortality benefit for the most vulnerable infants and may have led to overuse near full-coverage thresholds. Targeted policies and rigorous evaluation are needed to maximize benefits and avoid harm.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Thermal processing effects on phytochemical profiles, antioxidant activity, and anti-inflammatory potential of extracts from dried rhizomes of Curcuma longa L. evaluated by UHPLC-MS/MS and in vitro assays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study developed and validated UHPLC-MS/MS methods for quantifying seven phytochemicals-five major bioactives (curcuminoids, sesquiterpenoids) and two thermal degradation products (vanillin, dehydrozingerone)-in Curcuma longa L. extracts. Samples were heat-treated (180 °C) in four matrices (dry, water, olive oil, corn oil), and antioxidant and anti-inflammatory activities were evaluated. While curcuminoids degraded significantly under aqueous heating (up to 71.3 % loss), ar-turmerone...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110411/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of brigatinib after alectinib in patients with ALK-positive NSCLC: Integrated analysis of the ALTA-2 and J-ALTA studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This integrated analysis showed that brigatinib has clinically meaningful activity after disease progression on alectinib.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110382/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unlocking carbon lock-in: How data factor marketization propels low-carbon transformation in heavy-polluting enterprises]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In modern economies, data factors have become crucial catalysts for the revolutionary advancement of heavily polluting sectors. The market-driven distribution of these data assets not only generates significant economic benefits but also provides essential assistance for establishing a sustainable development framework. This paper selects the creation of China's data trading platforms as a quasi-natural experiment, analyzing data from A-share listed companies in heavily polluting industries from...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110360/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of maximal handgrip strength and handgrip strength asymmetry with suicidal behaviors: Evidence from a nationally representative sample of Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110311/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epilepsy in children and adolescents with B-cell acute lymphoblastic leukemia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Most seizures in patients with B-ALL were provoked and resolved without the need for long-term antiseizure medication treatment. Acute or subacute MTX neurotoxicity accounted for the majority of provoked seizures. However, these rarely progressed to epilepsy. Long-term neurological surveillance is important in B-ALL survivors, especially those with delayed seizure onset or magnetic resonance imaging evidence of leukoencephalopathy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110283/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Asymmetric Mechano-Electrochemical Energy Harvesting System with Surface Charge-Modified Carbon Nanotube Yarn for Wearable Devices]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Mechano-electrochemical harvesters are being explored for various applications, including wearable and implantable devices. However, their application in practical devices still requires the development of a structurally optimized two-electrode system to avoid mutual voltage cancellation. Herein, the two-electrode system is improved by enhancing individual electrode performance and resolving voltage cancellation through polarity-controlled electrode design via asymmetric surface charge...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110162/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision Measurement of Net-Proton-Number Fluctuations in Au+Au Collisions at RHIC]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report precision measurements on cumulants (C_{n}) and factorial cumulants (κ_{n}) of (net) proton number distributions up to fourth order in Au+Au collisions over center-of-mass energies sqrt[s_{NN}]=7.7-27 GeV from phase II of the Beam Energy Scan program at RHIC. (Anti)protons are selected at midrapidity (|y|<0.5) within a transverse momentum range of 0.4<p_{T}<2.0 GeV/c. Relative to various noncritical-point model calculations and peripheral collision 70%-80% data, the net proton...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110054/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Precision CP Symmetry Test and Polarization Analysis in Σ^{+} Decays]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A stringent test of CP symmetry in hyperon decays is performed using 1.0×10^{10} J/ψ events and 2.7×10^{9} ψ(3686) events collected by the BESIII experiment. The CP asymmetry in the two-body nonleptonic weak decays Σ^{+}→pπ^{0} and Σ[over ¯]^{-}→p[over ¯]π^{0} is determined to be A_{CP}=-0.0118±0.0083(stat)±0.0028(syst), consistent with CP conservation. The average decay parameter ⟨α_{0}⟩=-0.9869±0.0011(stat)±0.0016(syst) represents the most precise measurement in the baryon sector to date. A...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110052/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical impact of gastrectomy in surgically proven stage IV gastric cancers: retrospective analysis from Korean multicenter dataset (PASS-META)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study suggests that gastrectomy offers a significant survival benefit to patients with surgically proven stage IV gastric cancer and limited peritoneal metastasis (P1/P2), distant lymph node (dLN1), or hepatic metastases (H1). Furthermore, specific surgical procedures such as extended lymph node dissection or minimally invasive surgery may be considered for patients undergoing gastrectomy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Identification of candidate genes associated with resistance to Heterodera sojae in soybean]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We identified QTLs and candidate genes associated with resistance to Heterodera sojae and then designed KASP markers from candidate genes on chromosomes 1 and 18 for marker-assisted selection. Heterodera sojae is a recently discovered cyst nematode species that parasitizes soybean roots, reducing soybean growth and yield. However, genes associated with resistance to H. sojae in soybean remain unknown. A genome-wide association study of genes related to resistance to H. sojae was performed with a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Perioperative Pembrolizumab for Locally Advanced Thymic Epithelial Tumors: A Single-Arm, Phase 2 Trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Perioperative pembrolizumab demonstrated promising rates of MPR, R0 resection, and long-term DFS in stage III to IV TETs.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109992/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Updated Overall Survival Analysis From the Phase 2 PHAROS Study of Encorafenib Plus Binimetinib in Patients With BRAF V600E-Mutant Metastatic Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The phase 2 PHAROS study previously showed that encorafenib plus binimetinib has antitumor activity in patients with BRAF V600E-mutant metastatic non-small cell lung cancer (mNSCLC). In PHAROS, 98 patients (59 treatment naïve; 39 previously treated) received encorafenib 450 mg once daily and binimetinib 45 mg twice daily. We report updated results from data cutoff of March 14, 2025. The median duration of treatment with both encorafenib and binimetinib was 16.3 months in treatment-naïve and 5.5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109959/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Propagation of infra-slow and slow brain activities in electroencephalogram related to behavioral information processing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The brain-wide propagation of neural excitability manifested in fast (>1 Hz) electroencephalogram (EEG) oscillations is known to play an important role in behavioral information processing. While fluctuations in EEG infra-slow and slow activity (ISA, 0.01-0.1 Hz; SA, 0.1-1 Hz) are also considered to reflect changes in neural excitability, it remains uncertain whether EEG ISA and SA propagate over the brain and whether such propagation relates to behavioral information processing. To investigate...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110547/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of Ionomer on CO<sub>2</sub> Reduction at Atomically Dispersed Ni─N─C Catalyst]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ionomers play an important role in carbon dioxide (CO(2)) electrolyzers by affecting CO(2) reduction reaction (CO(2)RR) at the cathode. In this study, we systematically examines the impact that different ionomers have on CO(2)RR at atomically dispersed nickel-nitrogen-carbon (Ni─N─C) catalyst. We compare the effects of two acidic cation exchange ionomers, perfluorosulfonic acid (Nafion) and sulfonated poly(aryl ether sulfone), and two alkaline anion exchange ionomers: quaternary...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110141/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Walks in Rotation Spaces Return Home when Doubled and Scaled]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The dynamics of numerous physical systems, such as spins and qubits, can be described as a series of rotation operations, i.e., walks in the manifold of the rotation group. A basic question with practical applications is how likely and under what conditions such walks return to the origin (the identity rotation), which means that the physical system returns to its initial state. In three dimensions, we show that almost every walk in SO(3) or SU(2), even a very complicated one, will...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110096/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-Resolution Characterization of the Bacterial Microbiome in Chili Pepper Powder Using SMRT Sequencing]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chili pepper powder is an essential ingredient of Korean cuisine and kimchi products. As such, ensuring its microbiological safety is crucial from a public health perspective. In this study, the bacterial microbiomes of Korean and Chinese chili pepper powder samples were compared using high-resolution single-molecule real-time sequencing. Nine samples each from Korea and China were analyzed, yielding high-quality sequencing data with N50 values exceeding 1,460 bp and quality scores greater than...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110985/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Linking riverine discharge to shifts in temperate estuarine planktonic food web dynamics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Riverine discharge plays a crucial role in shaping planktonic food web dynamics in coastal systems, though its effects can vary across estuaries. This study investigated the influence of riverine discharge on key biological variables-primary productivity, nitrogen uptake (nitrate and ammonium), biomass, community composition, and mesozooplankton feeding rates-across estuarine gradients in Gwangyang Bay, a low-turbidity temperate estuary in Korea. Principal component analysis identified riverine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41110441/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Domvanalimab and zimberelimab in advanced gastric, gastroesophageal junction or esophageal cancer: a phase 2 trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dual inhibition of T cell immunoreceptor with immunoglobulin and ITIM domain (TIGIT) and programmed cell death protein 1 (PD-1) may enhance antitumor immunity in advanced gastroesophageal cancers. Here we report the EDGE-Gastric study, an ongoing, multicenter, international, phase 2 study with three cohorts, one in the first-line setting (cohort A) and two in the second-line or greater setting (cohorts B and C). Cohort A comprises four arms: two nonrandomized (A1 and A2) and two randomized (A3...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109921/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of proximal segment osteotomy level on mandibular angle changes after intraoral vertical ramus osteotomy: a three-dimensional CBCT study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective study aimed to analyze changes in the mandibular angle, based on the ostectomy level of the proximal segment following intraoral vertical ramus osteotomy (IVRO) for mandibular setback in 40 patients with mandibular prognathism, using three-dimensional reconstruction images obtained from cone-beam computed tomography. The ostectomy level of the proximal segment was categorized into two groups based on the distance from the gonion to the ostectomy site: within 5 mm and over 5...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CCN3/IMP3/HIF1α positive feedback loop enhances malignant progression of triple-negative breast cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cancer cells are often exposed to a hypoxic environment due to indiscriminate proliferation and incomplete vasculature formation. Hypoxia-inducible factor-1 (HIF-1), which is induced by a hypoxic environment, promotes tumor malignancy by regulating cancer cell metabolism, metastasis, angiogenesis, and cancer stem cell formation. Previous studies have demonstrated increased activation of HIF-1-induced signaling pathways in triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC). Therefore, a hypoxic environment or...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109656/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Antibacterial dual-drug delivery fiber system via a multi-layered porous Poly(caprolactone)/poly lactic acid/ZIF-8 composites]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A novel dual-drug delivery platform was developed by integrating porous electrospun poly(ε-caprolactone) (PCL) fibers with a poly(lactic acid) (PLA) coating and in situ-grown zeolitic imidazolate framework-8 (ZIF-8). The porous structure, induced via vapor-induced phase separation, enabled efficient levofloxacin loading, while lysozyme was embedded within the ZIF-8 shell. This multi-layered platform (PFZL) was designed to co-deliver levofloxacin and lysozyme, addressing limitations of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109645/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Growth inhibition in lettuce callus exposed to particulate matter: Cellular injury linked to intracellular accumulation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Particulate matter (PM) pollution poses significant but understudied risks to plant cellular health. This study demonstrates that exposure of lettuce (Lactuca sativa) protoplast-callus systems to standardized diesel exhaust particles at environmentally relevant concentrations results in marked intracellular PM accumulation, severe cytostructural damage, and disruption of chloroplast integrity. PM exposure triggered concentration-dependent oxidative stress, evidenced by increased hydrogen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109622/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk of Hydrocephalus after Head Trauma: A nationwide cohort study in South Korea]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with head trauma are at a significantly higher risk of posttraumatic hydrocephalus, particularly within the first 3 years. These findings highlight the need for early monitoring and intervention. Further research is required to improve our understanding of hydrocephalus risk.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic Value of Fetal Left Ventricular Myocardial Performance Index for Mortality or ECMO in Congenital Diaphragmatic Hernia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Fetal LV MPI at 30-34 weeks independently predicts death/ECMO in CDH. Combining LV MPI with O/E LHR-particularly with liver herniation-enhances prenatal risk stratification.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outcomes of Retreatment for Local Recurrence After Surgery for Metastatic Spine Cancer: A Multicenter Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Only reoperation resulted in significant functional improvement after retreatment for LR. RT was associated with decreased ambulatory function and did not provide significant symptom relief. Retreatment failure was common and associated with increased pain and diminished function. A significant predictor of retreatment failure was a shorter interval-less than 12.5 months-between the initial surgery and LR. These findings highlight the importance of patient selection and the limited...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109513/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tofacitinib in rheumatoid sarcopenia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109314/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A landscape analysis of the vaccine ecosystem in Africa: research and development funding, clinical trials, regulation, and manufacturing readiness]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vaccines are vital for global health, and despite bearing the highest burden of infectious diseases, Africa manufactures less than 1% of its vaccine needs. This Health Policy paper offers an overview of Africa's vaccine ecosystem, examining research and development funding, clinical trials, regulatory maturity, and manufacturing readiness with publicly available data. Funding for research and development (2007-23) was analysed with data from the G-FINDER database, which focuses on diseases...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Volume-Stable Collagen Matrix as a Recombinant Human Bone Morphogenetic Protein-2 Carrier for Maxillary Sinus Augmentation: An Experimental In Vivo Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: rhBMP-2-loaded VCMX enhances bone regeneration in sinus augmentation, suggesting that its volume maintenance may contribute to the improved clinical and radiographic outcomes.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109210/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Biomass derived self-regenerative multifunctional superhydrophobic film for oil-water remediation and drag-reduction behaviour]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wheat (Triticum aestivum) is vital for global food security, providing a basic nutritional source for billions. The wheat straw (WS), a byproduct, is barely valorized and often discarded or burned, causing environmental and health hazards. This study repurposes underutilized WS to develop an economical, non-fluorinated bulk superhydrophobic film using a spray-casting approach. WS fibers were initially cleaned, dried, and ball-milled into particles (WSP). One portion of WSP was directly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109086/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bleeding potential and effectiveness of perioperative ketorolac administration in tonsillectomy: A systemic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study demonstrated that administration of ketorolac for tonsillectomy did not appear to increase the incidence of postoperative bleeding in children or adults; however, further studies are needed to confirm this finding. Additionally, ketorolac could improve postoperative emesis and early pain control.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109074/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20251020152226&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intrinsically Disordered Protein-Inspired Nanovector-Based Coacervates for the Direct Cytosolic Transport of Biomacromolecules]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In eukaryotic cells, membraneless organelles (MLOs) are formed via liquid‒liquid phase separation (LLPS) involving intrinsically disordered proteins (IDPs) and biomacromolecules, enabling biomacromolecule transport without vesicles, transporters, or channels. Although MLO-mimetic coacervates generated from synthetic biomaterials can deliver biomacromolecules into cells, they lack the conformational adaptability of IDPs and a defined internalization mechanism, limiting their stability under...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108606/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[High-throughput Raman platform for microplastics detection on filtration membranes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Plastic materials are ubiquitous across modern industries, leading to widespread microplastic contamination in aquatic systems. The diversity of plastic usage yields microplastics of diverse sizes, shapes, and compositions, posing significant analytical challenges. Current techniques cannot provide high-throughput analysis for the chemical and morphological distribution of numerous microplastics. In this study, we propose an integrated line-scan Raman imaging platform for rapid, high-throughput...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41109029/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of urine arsenic, blood manganese, and serum zinc with pterygium in Korean adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our findings provide epidemiological evidence that excess As and deficient Mn may be associated with pterygium in Korean adults.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108861/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Higher dietary ketogenic ratio is associated with accelerated biological aging among US adults: analysis from NHANES 2005-2018]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ketogenic diet (KD) is widely prescribed for weight management in obese individuals, yet their potential impact on biological aging remains unclear. Using cross-sectional data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES, 2005-2018) to test the hypothesis that KD may accelerate biological aging, biological aging was assessed through 4 indices: biological age acceleration (BioAgeAccel), phenotypic age acceleration (PhenoAgeAccel), homeostatic dysregulation (HD) and serum...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108793/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prognostic factors of mortality in patients with cancer infected with COVID-19: A systematic review and meta-analysis using the GRADE approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study aimed to systematically synthesize the available evidence on prognostic factors affecting mortality in these patients. This review included cohort studies of adult patients with cancer diagnosed with Coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19). We searched MEDLINE and Embase for data from December 2019 to June 2025, and Cochrane Central Libraries and other databases for data to July 2023. Two independent reviewers screened references, extracted data, and assessed bias risk. The Grading of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Segmental Lichen Planus Pigmentosus Successfully Treated With Picosecond Neodymium-Doped: Yttrium-Aluminium-Garnet Laser and Trifarotene in a Korean Patient]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lichen planus pigmentosus (LPP) is a rare variant of lichen planus that presents as hyperpigmented patches, most commonly in individuals with darker skin tones, and is difficult to treat effectively. We report a case of a 22-year-old Korean male with LPP who showed considerable improvement following combination therapy with trifarotene and a picosecond neodymium-doped yttrium-aluminium-garnet (Nd:YAG) laser. Considering the inherently variable clinical course of LPP and the challenges associated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108200/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sex-specific associations of serum 25-hydroxyvitamin D concentrations with incident sarcopenia in older adults: A 2-year follow-up study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Low serum 25(OH)D concentrations are associated with a higher likelihood of incident sarcopenia and its components, particularly among men. Adequate 25(OH)D concentrations may help slow age-related decline in muscle mass and function, with potential sex differences.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41108818/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficient Air-Processed Green-Solvent Based Organic Solar Cells Fabricated via Facile Extremely Low-Temperature Induced Crystallization Approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Glove-Box (GB)-processed organic solar cells (OSCs) using halogenated solvents exhibited ∼20% power conversion efficiencies (PCEs). Air-processed (AP) OSCs, irrespective of halogenated or nonhalogenated solvent, consistently exhibit lower PCEs than GB counterparts. Key challenges in AP-OSCs include nanomorphological control and charge-carrier transport issues. To address these challenges, an extremely low-temperature induced crystallization (ELTC) strategy is devised, precisely modulating the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flexible piezo-responsive photodetector based on hierarchical zinc oxide nanowire branches on a silver nanowire backbone]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Zinc oxide (ZnO) is a highly promising material for ultraviolet (UV) photodetection, owing to its wide bandgap (∼3.34 eV), high exciton binding energy, and cost-effective synthesis. Its piezoelectric properties further enhance its utility in wearable electronics. However, the inherent brittleness of ZnO nanowires (NWs) poses challenges in achieving reliable performance under strain. In this study, a novel flexible piezo-responsive photodetector with enhanced electrical performance is synthesized...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1J__86CjOXspvrvYwWhLha0HUgjE7uW1knCYZ8uwr5FW9x1oDL&amp;fc=20250824200837&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Night-shift neuroradiology under pressure: what trends from a Dutch academic center tell us about future necessities]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41107497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41107497/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Over 20.5% Efficiency of Halogen-Free Solvent-Processed Organic Solar Cells Achieved by Anti-Solvent Strategy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41103198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Halogen-free solvent processing is critical for the industrial-scale production of organic solar cells (OSCs) and environmental sustainability. However, such solvents typically result in suboptimal efficiency due to excessive molecular aggregation and unfavorable phase separation. To address this issue, an innovative anti-solvent (AS) strategy is proposed that accelerates photovoltaic material precipitation by timed introduction of orthogonal solvents to reduce solvent solubility and enhance...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41103198/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morin enhances healthspan and neuroprotection in Caenorhabditis elegans via mitochondrial stress adaptation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41106439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Morin, a dietary flavonoid with antioxidant and metabolic activity, promotes healthy ageing in Caenorhabditis elegans. Morin extended lifespan by ~18% and alleviated age-related decline in neuronal integrity, locomotion, learning and memory, and intestinal fat accumulation. Mitochondrial potential was moderately decreased, suggesting mild uncoupler-like activity. Morin downregulated daf-2 and upregulated daf-16, accompanied by enhanced DAF-16::GFP nuclear localization, indicative of IIS/FOXO...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41106439/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neurotherapeutic effects of Vutiglabridin as a Paraoxonase-2 modulator in preclinical models of Parkinson's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41107874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: These findings indicate that Vutiglabridin may serve as a promising therapeutic approach for reducing reactive oxygen species (ROS) levels by modulating PON2 activity in Parkinson's diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41107874/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning-based early prediction of asthma in preschoolers: The COCOA birth cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study successfully developed robust predictive models for early asthma that demonstrated high performance. The questionnaire-based scoring tool offers particular value because of its clinical applicability. Further validation in diverse populations and investigation of the causative pathways of the identified predictors are necessary to enhance clinical utility.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104825/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvent Evaporation Induced Micelle Assembly for Continuous Mesoporous Amorphous Metal-Organic Framework Films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The thin films of nanoporous materials, including zeolites, metal-organic frameworks (MOFs), and mesoporous materials, are promising for applications in electrodes, separations, catalysis, and sensing. While microporous materials offer high surface areas that expose numerous active sites, their limited diffusion pathways for reactants and products constrain performance. Hierarchically structured mesoporous-microporous materials offer an ideal solution by combining extensive surface areas with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The effect of media golf professionals' image on instructor trust and customer satisfaction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Since media golf professionals are mainly encountered online rather than through face-to-face instruction, it is difficult to assess their competency and expertise as instructors. To this end, the study sought to assess instructors' instructional competence through the construct of instructor image and examine its influence on instructor trust and customer satisfaction. The participants were 290 Korean adult amateur golfers (186 men and 104 women). A questionnaire was used to measure perceptions...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic potential of modified Yukgunja-tang (Liujunzi Decoction, Rikkunshito) as an adjuvant treatment for lung cancer: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Modified YGJT may offer clinical benefits as an adjuvant to standard lung cancer therapy by improving treatment outcomes and reducing toxicity. Large-scale, high-quality trials are needed to confirm these findings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104332/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[D1 Receptor Agonist Ameliorates Synaptic and Behavioral Deficits in a <em>Shank3</em>-Deficient Mouse Model of Autism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41104165/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrating artificial intelligence into Korean medicine: Insights from neural and pulse signal analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41103915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41103915/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peripheral blood transcriptome signatures indicate environmental influences in monozygotic twins discordant for Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Environmental factors have been proposed to contribute to the pathogenesis of Alzheimer's disease (AD). Because monozygotic (MZ) twins share identical genetic backgrounds, they provide a unique model to disentangle genetic and environmental contributions to disease-related molecular changes. Herein, we investigated MZ twins who lived distinctly different lives and became discordant for AD, and analyzed which transcriptome signatures were altered in the affected twin. We further examined whether...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of Particulate Matter on the Exacerbation of Immunoglobulin A Nephropathy: An Animal Experimental Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Particulate matter (PM) exposure is linked to chronic kidney disease; however, its effect on immunoglobulin A (IgA) nephropathy (IgAN) remains unclear. We investigated whether PM exposure exacerbates IgAN in a mouse model. HIGA mice (IgAN model) and BALB/c controls were exposed to PM in a sealed chamber for 13 weeks. Lung Toll-like receptor 9 (TLR9) expression, serum aberrantly glycosylated IgA, A proliferation-inducing ligand (APRIL) levels, mesangial IgA deposition, and kidney pathology were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096658/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1-u-VnOuHrrKiO4WMPvz_i-F2FoAlfu-lcoSZ3mSAjuT4X8gzB&amp;fc=20250824200958&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>KIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Association between RAR and the prevalence and prognosis of suicidal ideation: evidence from a large population-based study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41102676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: RAR was positively associated with both the prevalence of suicidal ideation and mortality among individuals with suicidal ideation. Although this study provides valuable insights into the potential role of RAR in suicidal health, its cross-sectional design limits the ability to infer causality. Future longitudinal studies are warranted to confirm these findings and further elucidate the underlying mechanisms.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41102676/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of Skeletal Muscle Mass and Body Mass Index With Clinical Outcomes in Autosomal Dominant Polycystic Kidney Disease: An Observational Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Among individuals with ADPKD, greater and higher-quality muscle mass were associated with lower risk of mortality and progression of CKD to ESKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101718/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fire-exposed polypropylene as a potential source of nanoplastics in aquatic environments]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Worldwide, mismanaged plastic waste from developing countries is increasing, with a significant proportion of this waste being exposed to fire. As a result, fire-exposed plastics are increasingly entering natural environments. This study aims to enhance the understanding of nanoplastics (NPs) leaching from fire-exposed plastics in water. We selected polypropylene (PP), a widely used polymer that can contaminate the water environment. PP was exposed to fire with a torch at temperatures between...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101167/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhancing the prediction accuracy of pathological downstaging in locally advanced rectal cancer using deep learning models with preoperative MRI and clinicopathological data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41100929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The proposed combined DL models demonstrated strong predictive performance for pT-downstaging after neoadjuvant CRT in LARC, with the MRI characteristics + T2-weighted MR images model also performing well without clinicopathological features.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41100929/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BONE-Net: A novel hybrid deep-learning model for effective osteoporosis detection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41100519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Osteoporosis is a prevalent bone disease characterized by reduced bone density and an elevated risk of fractures, especially in older adults and postmenopausal women. The clinical consequences of osteoporotic fractures extend beyond pain and disability, contributing substantially to morbidity, mortality, and healthcare costs. Early intervention and accurate detection is therefore essential to improve patient outcomes. This paper introduces an advanced deep-learning methodology to enhance the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41100519/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Differential Outcomes of Beta-Blockers According to Heart Rate Following Myocardial Infarction with Reduced Left Ventricular Ejection Fraction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41099960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: In patients with AMI-rEF, beta-blockers were not independently associated with significantly reduced all-cause death after adjustment, though a trend was observed. Notably, beta-blocker use increased the risk of nonfatal myocardial infarction, particularly at higher H-R. These findings suggest that the benefits of beta-blockers in this population may not be uniform and highlight the potential importance of H-R as a clinical marker to guide individualized beta-blocker use in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41099960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effects of mobile application-based dietary recommendations on patients aged 50 and older with type 2 diabetes, obesity, and hypertension in Gwangju, South Korea: a pilot trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41098405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Although a pilot, this mobile app-based dietary intervention yielded marked improvements across several disease indicators, suggesting that its advancement may help prevent and manage chronic diseases.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41098405/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ebselen Suppresses Breast Cancer Tumorigenesis by Inhibiting YTHDF1-Mediated c-Fos Expression]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[YTHDF1, an N6-methyladenosine (m⁶A)-binding protein, plays a key role in breast cancer progression, yet its therapeutic targeting remains underexplored. In this study, we investigated the anticancer effects of the novel YTHDF1 inhibitor ebselen in breast cancer cells. Ebselen treatment reduced cell viability in a dose-dependent manner and induced apoptosis, as demonstrated by Annexin V staining, Sub-G1 accumulation, and DNA fragmentation. Consistently, ebselen increased reactive oxygen species...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096691/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[N-Terminal Metal-Binding Domain of Arabidopsis IBR5 Is Important for Its in Planta Functions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Indole-3-acetic acid (IAA), the predominant natural auxin, is a plant hormone that regulates growth and development in response to various internal and external signals. Arabidopsis thaliana (Arabidopsis) indole-3-butyric acid response 5 (AtIBR5, AT2G04550) encodes a dual-specificity phosphatase in Arabidopsis. The atibr5 mutant exhibits reduced sensitivity to indole-3-butyric acid (IBA), a precursor of IAA, but is also less responsive to another plant hormone, abscisic acid (ABA). We report...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096584/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Percutaneous Atherectomy Versus Balloon Angioplasty/Stenting in the Treatment of Femoropopliteal Arterial Occlusive Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Objectives: Atherectomy use for the treatment of femoropopliteal lesions has significantly increased. This study aimed to assess the clinical benefits of percutaneous atherectomy (PA) over balloon angioplasty and/or stenting (PTA ± stent) for femoropopliteal arterial disease using a nationwide prospective multicenter registry. Methods: Using data from the Damoeum registry of the Korean Society for Vascular Surgery, we identified patients with revascularization due to lower-extremity arterial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41096007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Temporal Evolution of Optic Nerve Sheath Diameter/Eyeball Ratio on CT and MRI for Neurological Prognostication After Cardiac Arrest]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Optic nerve sheath diameter (ONSD) and its ratio to eyeball transverse diameter (ETD; ONSD/ETD) are potential markers for elevated intracranial pressure in comatose survivors of out-of-hospital cardiac arrest (OHCA). However, their prognostic accuracy remains uncertain. We compared their predictive value via compted tomography (CT)and magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) before and after targeted temperature management (TTM) in OHCA survivors. Methods: This retrospective study included...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095971/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early Prognostication After Out-of-Hospital Cardiac Arrest: Modified rCAST Score Incorporating Age and Brainstem Reflexes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background: Out-of-hospital cardiac arrest (OHCA) survivors demonstrate wide variation in neurological outcomes due to hypoxic-ischemic brain injury. Early prognostic stratification in the emergency department is essential to inform clinical decisions. This study aimed to improve the revised Cardiac Arrest Syndrome for Therapeutic hypothermia (rCAST) score by incorporating additional clinical variables and to evaluate its ability to predict poor neurological outcomes. Methods: This multicenter...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095909/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neutrophil-to-Lymphocyte Ratio, Bone Marrow, and Visceral Fat Metabolism as Predictors of Future Cardiovascular Disease in an Asymptomatic Healthy Population]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The neutrophil-to-lymphocyte ratio (NLR), a marker of systemic inflammation, is a known predictor of cardiovascular disease and overall mortality. We examined the relationship between the NLR and the metabolic activity of hematopoietic organs and visceral fat, and their association with the risk of atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD) in an asymptomatic healthy population. Methods: We retrospectively analyzed individuals who underwent F-18-fluorodeoxyglucose...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Efficacy of Olfactory Function Test Using Functional Near-Infrared Spectroscopy with Machine Learning in Healthy Adults: A Prospective Diagnostic-Accuracy (Feasibility/Validation) Study in Healthy Adults with Algorithm Development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background/Objectives: The YSK olfactory function (YOF) test is a culturally adapted psychophysical tool that assesses threshold, discrimination, and identification. This study evaluated whether functional near-infrared spectroscopy (fNIRS) synchronized with routine YOF testing, combined with machine learning, can predict YOF subdomain performance in healthy adults, providing an objective neural correlate to complement behavioral testing. Methods: In this prospective diagnostic-accuracy...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095653/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST, Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exploring the Sound Absorption Potential of Ecoflex™ 00-35 for Soft and Flexible Noise Reduction]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the acoustic performance of Ecoflex™ 00-35, a highly flexible silicone rubber, for use in soft and adaptable vibration and noise control systems. Under normal conditions, Ecoflex™ 00-35 consists of two components-Part A and Part B-which are mixed and cured at room temperature to form an elastomer. In this study, curing parameters such as the A/B mixing ratio, thinning agent addition, and curing pressure were varied to examine their effects on acoustic behavior. The...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41095304/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Autonomous Concrete Crack Monitoring Using a Mobile Robot with a 2-DoF Manipulator and Stereo Vision Sensors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41094944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Crack monitoring in concrete structures is essential to maintaining structural integrity. Therefore, this paper proposes a mobile ground robot equipped with a 2-DoF manipulator and stereo vision sensors for autonomous crack monitoring and mapping. To facilitate crack detection over large areas, a 2-DoF motorized manipulator providing linear and rotational motions, with a stereo vision sensor mounted on the end effector, was deployed. In combination with a manual rotation plate, this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41094944/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12Ak-Eek5aCiXtpXt5nPotfAmzuqq2n4KV7PFY26W42gL0Wk4G&amp;fc=20250824201017&amp;ff=20251020152208&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>GIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of a predictive model for nafamostat mesylate dosing in hemodialysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41102652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The nafamostat dosage prediction model can be used to calculate the dose required for individual patients. However, further studies for model improvement and external validation are required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41102652/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Morphometric similarity network-based graph convolutional networks for schizophrenia classification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41102305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Schizophrenia is a complex neuropsychiatric disorder characterized by significant heterogeneity, posing a challenge for accurate classification using neuroimaging data. Graph convolutional networks (GCNs) have emerged as a promising approach for leveraging the inherent graph structure of brain connectivity to discriminate between patients with schizophrenia and healthy controls. However, existing GCN-based methods often struggle to capture the subtle neuroimaging differences associated with the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41102305/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Anti-pruritic and anti-inflammatory effects of Sopoongsan on atopic or seborrheic dermatitis: A pilot randomized, placebo-controlled clinical trial and translational research using in vitro and in vivo models]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: SPS tended to relieve chronic upper body pruritus without obvious adverse effects in patients diagnosed with atopic or seborrheic dermatitis. This therapeutic effect may be related to STAT1 inhibition.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41101551/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SIRT1 in Aging and Diseases]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41099490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sirtuin 1 (SIRT1) is a NAD^(+)-dependent deacetylase belonging to the sirtuin family, which regulates a broad spectrum of cellular processes through deacetylation of both histones in the nucleus and non-histone proteins in the cytosol. Accumulating evidence indicates that biological aging is associated with a marked decline in the expression and activation of SIRT1/SIRT1, which contributes to the onset and progression of various age-related diseases. Conversely, activation of SIRT1 has been...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41099490/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How Is One's Own and (Ex-)Partner's Professional Prestige Associated With Loneliness and Isolation? Findings Based on Cross-Sectional Data From Middle-Aged and Older Adults Living in Germany in 2022/2023]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41098512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Data suggest that one's own favorable professional prestige was associated with lower loneliness and social isolation levels, whereas the professional prestige of the (ex-)partner was unrelated to such social factors. Future longitudinal studies should analyze whether changing to a job with more professional prestige might be associated with changes in loneliness and social isolation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41098512/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=14wpWf7MA3AKQSRGSBGZnJWuy_XngRdzPRoKvgHBVI3A4IsM3D&amp;fc=20250824201035&amp;ff=20251020152216&amp;v=2.18.0.post9+e462414</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>