<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Korean Academic Publications with ML Classification</title>
        <description>Latest research from top Korean institutions with AI-powered subject classification</description>
        <link>https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/</link>
        <atom:link href="https://rimrim05.github.io/Korean-Academic-RSS/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:47:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <ttl>360</ttl>
        
        
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Microfluidics-guided localized low-temperature modulation of axonal signal propagation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low-temperature stimulation is recognized as a promising approach for neuromodulation, with the potential to suppress or slow neural activity. However, its impact on the spatial and electrophysiological properties of axonal conduction remains poorly understood. Conventional methods have lacked the spatial resolution necessary to isolate axon-specific responses to localized cooling. To overcome these limitations, we developed a microfluidic platform that integrates a microelectrode array (MEA)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631440/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, KAIST, SNU, UNIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of adding a fourth oral antidiabetic drug versus metformin dose escalation in patients with type 2 diabetes inadequately controlled on triple oral combination therapy (EFFORT): A 24-week, randomized, open-label, multicenter trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Oral quadruple therapy achieved greater glycaemic and metabolic improvement without compromising safety, compared with metformin uptitration, supporting its role as an intensification strategy.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630635/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, IBS, KAIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[K-MIMIC: a nationwide Korean multi-institutional Multimodal intensive care dataset]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The K-MIMIC is the first large-scale, multicenter, multimodal ICU dataset in Asia to provide a robust resource for critical care research, including AI-based prediction, monitoring, and longitudinal outcome studies. The dataset demonstrates the feasibility of secure and standardized ICU data integration across diverse institutions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630544/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Two-Wave Study of Avatar Customization and Psychological Benefits in Social Virtual Reality: The Role of Identification]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[As social virtual reality (social VR) platforms increasingly captivate users worldwide, questions arise about how digitally mediated self-representation affects psychological health. This study investigates how avatar characteristics-specifically perceived avatar appearance similarity and perceived attractiveness-shape users' well-being in social VR, with a focus on the mediating role of avatar identification. Drawing on two-wave longitudinal data collected over a three-month period from 486...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effectiveness and safety of bictegravir/emtricitabine/tenofovir alafenamide in people with HIV in Asia: 24-Month findings from the observational BICSTaR study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BICtegravir Single Tablet Regimen is a multiregional, observational cohort study assessing the effectiveness and safety of bictegravir/emtricitabine/tenofovir alafenamide (B/F/TAF) in treatment-naïve (TN) and treatment-experienced (TE) people with HIV. We present 24-month data for the BICtegravir Single Tablet Regimen Asia cohort. Between December 2020 and March 2024, prospective and retrospective data were collected from TN and TE people with HIV receiving B/F/TAF in routine clinical care in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630225/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, Pusan National University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muscle mass in critically ill patients: analysis using ultrasound, traditional bioelectrical impedance analysis, and wearable devices: a prospective observational study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Ultrasound is a reliable method for monitoring muscle atrophy in critically ill patients, demonstrating a consistent decrease in muscle mass. The outcomes of traditional BIA and wearable devices suggest that careful consideration of their interpretations is necessary. Utilizing these tools may be valuable for assessing patient prognosis and facilitating more proactive interventions for patients experiencing muscle loss.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630081/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Multifunctional β-Defensin-3 Mimetic Peptide Modulates Host-Biofilm Interactions and Reduces Bone Loss in Periodontitis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: BDMP exhibited sustained antimicrobial and anti-inflammatory activity and attenuated bone loss in a beagle periodontitis model when used alongside standard SI therapy. These findings support BDMP as a promising adjunctive therapeutic candidate for managing periodontal inflammation and biofilm-associated disease, although further studies are needed to confirm long-term safety and to define its mechanistic contributions to periodontal tissue preservation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631454/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Understanding disease management and the patient journey in chronic myeloid leukemia: results from the CML SUN survey in South Korean patients and physicians]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The results highlight the significant impact of ATP-competitive TKIs on patients' QoL and provide useful insights into CML treatment in South Korea. The differences in patient and physician perspectives emphasize the need for shared treatment decisions that balance efficacy and tolerability to enhance QoL and to minimize unnecessary treatment switching.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631196/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tumor-conditioned inter-patient registration using planning computed tomography for voxel-based analysis to predict radiation pneumonitis in lung cancer patients]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: TRACER improved registration accuracy, with better tumor volume preservation and reduced OAR dose impact. Incorporating VBA-derived dose enhanced RP prediction accuracy compared with using MLD. CRRs identified through VBA were robust to the choice of DIR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631006/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal vitiligo is associated with increased autoimmune and atopic disease in offspring: A nationwide birth cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630866/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Tuning of Doping Efficiency and Charge Transport in n-Type Thermoelectric Polymers via Rational Backbone Design]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the growing interest in organic thermoelectrics, n-type polymers generally exhibit lower performance than their p-type counterparts, limiting the development of efficient thermoelectric generators. Herein, we report two new n-type polymers based on cyanothiophene-flanked diketopyrrolopyrrole (CDPP) copolymerized with either diketopyrrolopyrrole (PCDPP-DPP) or dialkoxybithiazole (PCDPP-BTzOR) to investigate the critical yet scarcely explored role of orbital interaction between counits in...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630671/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Structural Basis of Recognition of Anti-CRISPR Operon by Aca3]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The CRISPR-Cas system equips bacteria with adaptive immunity by storing fragments of invading nucleic acids in CRISPR loci and deploying Cas proteins to recognize and degrade matching sequences. In turn, bacteriophages have evolved small anti-CRISPR (Acr) that neutralize diverse CRISPR-Cas types. Acr genes are often co-encoded with transcriptional regulators called anti-CRISPR-associated (Aca) proteins, which suppress acr expression. Although 13 Aca families have been identified through...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630633/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blood pressure thresholds for the administration of balanced crystalloids and the effect on intra-operative hypotension: A proof-of-concept causal inference analysis featuring idealised dynamic treatment regimens]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Using modern causal inference methods, we demonstrated the clinical utility of idealised DTRs to study the impact of time-dependent haemodynamic management on the incidence of intra-operative hypotension in idealised settings. Future studies are required to investigate more complex DTRs mirroring clinical practice and to assess the robustness of the findings with respect to the different surgical populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630616/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygen-Independent Mineralization of Acetaldehyde by a Cyclodextrin-Anchored WO<sub>3</sub> Photocatalyst under Visible Light]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photocatalytic degradation of volatile organic compounds (VOCs) using visible light has been widely investigated, but its practical implementation remains constrained by several limiting factors. Here, we prepared carboxymethyl-β-cyclodextrin (CMCD)-anchored WO(3) that enabled visible-light-driven mineralization of acetaldehyde even under O(2)-free conditions. Anchoring CMCD on WO(3) facilitated interfacial charge separation, enhancing the photocatalytic performance. Spectroscopic and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630561/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of electroencephalographic changes induced by different hypnotics in elderly patients: a narrative review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aging is associated with widespread structural and functional changes in the brain including reduced neural plasticity, slower information processing, and impaired network integration. These age-related alterations influence the brain's response to anesthetic agents, particularly electroencephalography (EEG) activity. This narrative review summarizes the characteristic EEG features induced by commonly used hypnotic agents such as propofol, inhaled anesthetics, dexmedetomidine, ketamine, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630548/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Comparison of large language models and conventional machine learning in postoperative outcome prediction: a retrospective, multi-national development and validation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The findings support the versatility and efficiency of LLMs for clinical decision support through on-premises compatibility, addressing data privacy. Further validation with diverse datasets is needed to ensure their reliability and applicability across different perioperative settings.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630546/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opioid-based versus opioid-sparing patient-controlled analgesia using ketorolac and nefopam after total knee arthroplasty: a randomized, double-blind, non-inferiority trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Opioid-sparing PCA with ketorolac and nefopam provides non-inferior analgesia to opioid-based PCA, while reducing opioid consumption and drug-related adverse effects after TKA.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630545/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences of Mental Health Nurses in Providing Care to Inpatients With Suicidal Behaviours in Psychiatric Care Settings: A Meta-Synthesis of Qualitative Research Studies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Understanding the context and challenges of psychiatric nursing care is essential for optimising patient outcomes and ensuring effective suicide prevention. While mental health nurses play a pivotal role in caring for inpatients with suicidal behaviours, research on their experiences and perspectives remains fragmented. This study aimed to synthesise qualitative studies on the experiences of mental health nurses in providing care to inpatients with suicidal behaviours. Manual searches were...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630533/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brucine as a Natural Modulator of Cancer Signaling: Cellular Mechanisms, Therapeutic Potential, and Translational Perspectives]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Brucine (BRU), a naturally occurring indole alkaloid primarily derived from Strychnos nux-vomica, has recently gained attention for its notable anticancer potential. Preclinical studies using both in vitro and in vivo models have demonstrated that BRU and its semi-synthetic derivatives exhibit significant inhibitory effects on tumor development across various cancer types, including cervical, breast, liver, skin, colon, and prostate cancers. This review explores the phytochemical properties of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diagnostic Utility of FAR1 Methylation Levels in Hepatocellular Carcinoma Patients Undergoing Liver Transplantation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND Recent research has highlighted DNA methylation as a promising diagnostic biomarker for hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC). Fatty Acyl-CoA Reductase 1 (FAR1) exhibits a high propensity for methylation in HCC. This study aimed to evaluate diagnostic and prognostic potential of FAR1 methylation in liver transplantation (LT) recipients with HCC. MATERIAL AND METHODS This analysis used droplet digital polymerase chain reaction to quantify FAR1 methylation levels in stored pretransplant blood...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630389/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Binational component-wise association between cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic syndrome and life's essential 8 in South Korea and the US: A nationally representative comparative study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although the American Heart Association (AHA) has emphasized the integration of cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic (CKM) syndrome and life's essential 8 (LE8) score, research on their association remains limited. To address this gap, this study analyzed the component-wise association between CKM syndrome and LE8 scores using nationally representative data from South Korea and the US. This binational study included adults aged 30 to 79 years from the Korea National Health and Nutrition Examination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630326/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adjunctive cannabidiol in intractable pediatric epilepsy: A retrospective study on tolerability, efficacy, and safety across genetic and nongenetic etiologies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This retrospective cohort study evaluated the tolerability, efficacy, and safety of adjunctive cannabidiol (CBD) therapy in pediatric-onset intractable epilepsy across diverse genetic and nongenetic etiologies. Twenty-nine patients aged 6 to 24 years, treated at Korea University Hospitals between April 2019 and May 2024, were included. The median follow-up duration was 14.3 months. Confirmed genetic etiologies included SCN1A-related epilepsy (6.9%); GABRB3-, SCN2A-, KCNT1-, KIF1A-, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630268/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term effectiveness on glycemic control of insulin compared to combined oral antidiabetic drugs for initial intensive treatment in newly diagnosed type 2 diabetes: A duplicated target trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Although both intensive insulin therapy (IIT) and combined oral antidiabetic drugs (COAD) can achieve initial intensive glycemic control, evidence comparing their long-term effectiveness following initial remission remains limited. Therefore, this study aims to compare long-term glycemic control and the risk of drug-free remission failure between IIT and COAD in patients who successfully achieved initial intensive glycemic control. This duplicated target trial utilized a cohort of 60,736...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630246/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Kyung Hee University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and side effect of transcatheter arterial embolization using a novel embolic agent for lateral epicondylitis in a diabetic patient: A case report]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[RATIONALE: Lateral epicondylitis (LE) is an overuse syndrome of the extensor carpi radialis brevis tendons of the forearm, leading to pain around the lateral epicondyle of the humerus exacerbated by several activities and a decrease in work productivity. This case study reports the efficacy and side effects of transcatheter arterial embolization (TAE) using Smartgel MIRIP, a novel quick-soluble gelatin sponge particles agent, through a LE patient with diabetes mellitus (DM).]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630245/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hydrogen-Assisted Asymmetric and Nonlinear Memristor Array for Reconfigurable Olfactory Graph Networks]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Memristor-based olfactory systems have attracted significant interest. However, a multifunctional memristor array capable of sensing, memory, and computation has not been realized. This study develops a selector-less crossbar array (CBA) composed of Pt/HfO(2) nanorods/TiN memristors, termed "chemo-memristive" devices, that exhibits asymmetric current-voltage (I-V) characteristics under a hydrogen (H(2)) atmosphere. H(2) exposure creates oxygen vacancies (V(O)) in the nanogap, corresponding to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630143/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KIST, Korea University, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pathological Nitric Oxide-Triggered Microneedle Patch for Spatiotemporally Controlled Therapy of Acute and Chronic Inflammatory Disorders]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Inflammation underlies the progression of both acute and chronic diseases, yet conventional therapies remain limited by systemic side effects, poor compliance, and insufficient responsiveness to dynamic pathological cues. Nitric oxide (NO), a gaseous mediator with high diffusivity and membrane permeability, is aberrantly overproduced in diverse inflammatory conditions and thus represents a promising trigger for responsive drug delivery. Here, we present a NO-responsive microneedle (NOR-MN)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630130/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A comprehensive functional atlas of ALK kinase domain variants reveals resistance landscape to ALK inhibitors]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This study provides a comprehensive functional atlas of ALK tyrosine kinase domain variants under TKI selection, offering a valuable experimental framework for interpreting resistance-associated variants. Although derived from in vitro models and therefore context dependent, this resource complements existing clinical and genomic knowledge and may aid in the functional interpretation of ALK variants observed in ALK-driven cancers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630044/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Efficacy and safety of intravenous administration of high-dose selenium for preventing chemotherapy-induced peripheral neuropathy in platinum-sensitive recurrent ovarian cancer: a phase 3, double-blind, parallel group, randomized controlled pilot study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Intravenous high-dose selenium safely failed to reduce grade 1 or more CIPN, whereas it reduced grade 2 or more motor dysfunction during chemotherapy in patients with PSROC, especially those ≥ 60 years. While the primary endpoint was not met, selenium showed the potential of protective effects against motor neuropathy without safety and survival concerns.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630017/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of housing instability in the association between ambient temperature and preterm birth]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629954/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1bo4uOs-bB_ZLOeoRMDuMyKrqOCTTJrR8i4c8aBDtpAcbJ09ch&amp;fc=20250822163228&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Selection of metal-tellurium (M-Te) alloy as Recyclable Controlled Te Precursors for Wafer-Scale Synthesis of M<sub>x</sub>Te<sub>y</sub> Thin Films]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Wafer-scale synthesis of metal telluride films has been hindered by the high volatility and limited reactivity of tellurium. To overcome this, we introduce a confined tellurization strategy utilizing in situ formed metal-tellurium (M-Te) alloys as controllable Te sources. Systematic investigation on appropriate metal species through cohesive energy calculations and experiments demonstrates that the cohesive energy of the source metal and metal-to-Te atomic ratio in the source bilayer are the key...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631465/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multilevel Regulation in RNA-Protein Hybrid Incoherent Feed-Forward Loop Circuits for Tunable Pulse Dynamics in <em>Escherichia coli</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Regulating gene expression with precision is essential for cellular engineering and biosensing applications, where rapid, programmable, and sensitive control is desired. Current approaches to regulatory circuit design often rely on control at a single regulatory level, primarily the transcriptional level, thereby limiting the capability of fine-tuning the regulatory dynamics in response to complex stimuli. To address this challenge, we developed four novel RNA-protein hybrid type-1 incoherent...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631420/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1ZyzHXV_xuJMd_mA0Sq1F0U-jUGJIU2JUAtLtKea9s3vCCDMAg&amp;fc=20250822201839&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>POSTECH</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal remodelling of the cloacal region determines the position of the anal opening in mouse embryos]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Conventional embryological models propose that the urorectal septum (URS) fuses with the cloacal membrane (CM) to form separate exits for the hindgut and urogenital sinus (UGS). However, previous studies have been re-evaluating this assumption, and the precise morphogenetic mechanisms determining the position of the anal opening remain unclear. To elucidate the spatial and temporal dynamics of cloacal development, we analysed mouse embryos from embryonic day (E)11.5 to E13.5 using serial...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631457/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Chem-Bio Hybrid Synthesis Enables Reengineering of Natural Product-Based Methionine Aminopeptidase 2 Inhibitors for Treating Amebiasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Natural products remain a vital source of therapeutic innovation, but their structural complexity often limits the systematic optimization and clinical translation. This challenge is exemplified by the fungal metabolite fumagillin, a covalent inhibitor of methionine aminopeptidase 2 (MetAP2), which advanced toward clinical development but whose semisynthetic derivatives were discontinued in trials for cancer and obesity because of adverse effects. To overcome these barriers, we reengineered the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631435/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Solvation structures of potassium bis(trifluoromethylsulfonyl)imide-glyme highly concentrated electrolytes and cycling on organic cathodes]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The physicochemical properties of highly concentrated electrolytes consisting of potassium bis(trifluoromethylsulfonyl)imide in oligo(ethyleneglycol) dimethyl ethers (glymes) are reported. The solvation structures were analyzed by Raman spectroscopy, single crystal X-ray diffraction, and theoretical calculations revealing significant ion-pairing at high concentrations especially for the shorter glymes, leading to them being classified as poor solvate ionic liquids with the general formula...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631383/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of unsymmetrical boron complexes bearing (iso)quinolylphenol ligands and their halogenated derivatives; crystal polymorphism for white-light-emitting properties]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Boron complexes bearing (iso)quinolylphenol ligands and their halogenated derivatives were synthesized to investigate their optical properties. The structural effects of the (iso)quinoline rings and halogenated positions on the photoabsorption and fluorescence emission properties of the complexes were observed in both solution and the solid state. In particular, chlorination at the C5 position of the phenol moiety induced crystal polymorphism. This resulted in unique dual emission bands in the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631317/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Directed evolution of phage Romulus in biofilm-embedded <em>Staphylococcus aureus</em>: mutations in baseplate proteins enhanced its antibiofilm activity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The ability of Staphylococcus aureus to form biofilm and the emergence of multidrug-resistant strains make staphylococcal infections often chronic and difficult to treat. To face these challenges, alternative or adjunct strategies to antibiotics are urgently required. In this context, phage therapy gained renewed interest as promising approach to target multidrug-resistant bacteria. To enhance their efficacy as natural phages, they can undergo directed evolution via serial host passages. To...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631269/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EBUS-TBNA for lung cancer in the apical segment of the right upper lobe using a new EBUS scope]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The applicability of ultrasound-guided transbronchial needle aspiration (EBUS-TBNA) for diagnosing central parenchymal tumors has been well established; however, lesions requiring puncturing under extreme angulation, especially the apical segment of the right upper lobe lesions, are often inaccessible with EBUS scopes. We report two cases of centrally located lung cancer in the apical segment of the right upper lobe. Case1. A 77-year-old man presented to the outpatient clinic with right chest...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631186/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Characteristics of human induced pluripotent stem cells cultured on soft substrates]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This study investigated the impact of culture surface rigidity on the proliferation and maintenance of undifferentiated human induced pluripotent stem cells (hiPSCs), which are crucial in regenerative medicine and stem cell-based organ therapy. Given the need for a substantial number of cells per patient, there is a pressing demand for methods that ensure homogeneous and efficient large-scale cultivation of hiPSCs. Mechanotransduction, the process by which cells, including hiPSCs, respond to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631007/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Colloidal state and emulsifying properties of protein isolates from kilned and non-kilned oats]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[There is a strong need for basic insights into the colloidal state of oat proteins as function of environmental conditions, and the relationship with functional properties. Relevant in this regard is the commonly applied industrial oat groat heat treatment ('kilning') which is here hypothesized to affect the colloidal and functional properties of oat protein isolates (OPIs). Here, we prepared OPIs from non-heat-treated (NHT) and industrially heat-treated (IHT, kilned) oats and investigated...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630807/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Utility of APOE testing for reducing ARIA under probabilistic stopping rates to treat with anti-amyloid therapy for ε4-homozygote patients: A simulation study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The direct safety impact of APOE testing for ARIA mitigation is limited, even under universal discontinuation policies. Its primary value lies in supporting shared decision-making and operational planning rather than as a standalone safety lever.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630792/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Prediction of one-year cognitive decline via self-perceived memory in older adults during the COVID-19 pandemic]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND: Subjective memory complaints (SMC) are associated with increased risk of cognitive decline and dementia. SMCs are also influenced by mood and anxiety symptoms, which increased among older adults during the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630790/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional connectivity of youth in family-like residential care in Japan: Impact of reactive attachment disorder and disinhibited social engagement disorder symptoms]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adverse childhood experiences are a risk factor for attachment disorders. While several neuroimaging studies have shown changes in functional networks in children who have experienced institutional care, the results are inconsistent. Furthermore, no research has been conducted on how structured residential care, such as Japan's small-group family-style care, influences attachment-related symptoms and functional connectivity. This study compared attachment-related symptoms (reactive attachment...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630788/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS, Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reliability and validity of Japanese version of Neonatal Pain, Agitation, and Sedation Scale for acute pain in infants]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The N-PASS-J is a dependable and valid instrument for assessing acute pain in infants with illness treated in the NICU.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630571/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Effect of drift-reducing spray configurations on spray deposition and coverage in winter wheat]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Spray configuration had a negligible effect on the relative spray deposition at the different collector positions in winter wheat, except at the spike and at the ground level. The results indicate that spray applications in winter wheat require optimizations tailored to the specific target location within the canopy, rather than a uniform approach. Air support combined with a fine spray quality nozzle appears particularly promising in improving deposition without compromising drift...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630444/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Implementation of AI systems in the clinical laboratory: insights from an expert survey and recommendations for best practice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Although many challenges remain, clinical laboratories demonstrate strong enthusiasm for AI, particularly with the growing prevalence of commercial AI products. The timely expert insights from our survey and C-AILM recommendations for both AI system providers and clinical laboratories on essential information, verification requirements, and monitoring strategies will inform standardized guideline development.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630421/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Epidemiologic and clinicopathologic features of 19,352 jaw cysts: a single-center retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: This large retrospective study provides a detailed epidemiological profile of jaw cysts. The findings revealed distinct patterns according to cyst type, age, sex, and anatomical site, providing a valuable reference for diagnostic refinement and future comparative studies of oral and maxillofacial pathology.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629916/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of proton pump inhibitor use on immune-related adverse events in patients with non-small cell lung cancer: a retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: PPI use was potentially associated with a lower incidence of non-CIP irAEs, whereas no significant effect was observed for CIP. In contrast, PPI use was not an independent prognostic factor, suggesting that irAE occurrence is influenced by multiple factors beyond PPI use. This study highlights the importance of investigating the interplay between PPI exposure, irAE occurrence, and gut microbiome alterations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629832/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=12guA9dSu1tGGvNP7mhhDa45fpbWpGPzILFj69wJJFdG48xkuI&amp;fc=20250822205125&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Korea University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RNA nanostructures based on three-letter coding with non-canonical base pairs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Synthetic RNA nanostructures are typically composed of four nucleotides (A, U, G, and C) following a canonical base pairing rule (A-U/G-C). G·U wobble pairs are commonly employed in many RNA nanostructures, but other non-canonical base pairing remains underexplored. In this work, we design RNA nanostructures with only three nucleotides instead of four. Besides Watson-Crick G-C base pairs, we incorporate A·C non-canonical base pairs into this three-letter coding scheme and allow selective...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631464/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Chinese Family with X-Linked Female-Limited High Myopia Caused by an <em>ARR3</em> Variant]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Our study expands the ARR3 variant spectrum associated with eoHM, highlighting the role of ARR3 c.214C>T (p.R72X), first reported in Chinese populations. The finding of incomplete penetrance underscores the complexity of X-linked female-limited inheritance and provides a reference for genetic counseling of related families.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631463/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Endogenous GIP signaling is indispensable for DPP-4 inhibitor-mediated metabolic control in mice]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Endogenous GIP signaling is essential for both glucose-lowering and anti-obesity actions of DPP-4 inhibitors in mice. GLP-1 elevation alone is insufficient to compensate for GIP receptor deficiency. These findings refined the mechanistic understanding of DPP-4 inhibitors, highlighted the physiological importance of GIP, and suggested context-dependent metabolic actions of incretins.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631452/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KHMDS-Mediated Direct Heteroarylation of C(sp<sup>3</sup>)-H Bonds of 9,10-Dihydroacridines and Analogues for Discovery of Potent Antimicrobial Agents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Acridine scaffolds are key pharmacophores in bioactive molecules and functional materials that exhibit diverse biological activities. Although C9-functionalization methods of 9,10-dihydroacridines have advanced, the development of efficient and transition-metal-free strategies for direct heteroarylation of sp³ C-H bonds to access structurally diverse acridines is highly demanding. Herein, we report a KHMDS-mediated direct coupling of 9,10-dihydroacridines with readily available heteroaryl...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631447/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spatial omics in pulmonary fibrosis: advancing mechanistic insights and therapeutic strategies]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pulmonary fibrosis, a group of chronic interstitial lung diseases charac-terized by persistent inflammation and aberrant deposition of fibrous connective tissue, poses a significant therapeutic challenge, with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis (IPF) being its most representative and severe form. Spatially resolved omics technologies-encompassing spatial metabolomics, transcriptomics, and proteomics-have emerged as transformative tools that preserve the architectural context of tissues while enabling...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631436/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Long-term memory effects of an incremental blood pressure intervention in a mortal cohort]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In the present study, we examine long-term population-level effects on episodic memory of an intervention over 15 years that reduces systolic blood pressure in individuals with hypertension. A limitation with previous research on the potential risk reduction of such interventions is that they do not properly account for the reduction of mortality rates. Hence, one can only speculate whether the effect is due to changes in memory or changes in mortality. Therefore, we extend previous research by...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631433/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Proportion and characteristics of bone marrow dysplasia in advanced HIV infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Cytopenias related to HIV are common and tend to worsen as the disease advances. This emphasizes the importance of investigating the potential for bone marrow dysplasia and conducting cytogenetic diagnostic testing for myelodysplastic syndromes (MDS), as a significant non-AIDS-defining hematological malignancy in individuals with advanced HIV.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631403/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Exposure to Quaternary Ammonium Compounds (QACs) in Assisted Living Facilities: Implications for Older Adults]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Quaternary ammonium compounds (QACs) are commonly used in disinfecting and personal care products for their antimicrobial, surfactant, and preservative properties. This study provides the first comprehensive assessment of QACs in assisted living facilities through the analysis of 19 QACs from three different QAC subgroups in indoor dust and air samples collected from three assisted living facilities in Indiana, United States (US), as well as in wristbands worn by the residents and staff of these...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631402/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Targeted modulation of IGFL2-AS1 reveals its translational potential in cervical adenocarcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Cervical cancer remains a leading cause of mortality among women, particularly in low- and middle-income countries. Despite distinct prognoses and clinical outcomes between its main histological subtypes, squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) and adenocarcinoma (ADC), current treatment regimens remain largely similar, creating an urgent need for targeted therapeutic strategies based on molecular distinctions. To address this gap, the long noncoding RNA IGFL2-AS1 was investigated as a potential...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631399/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lipopolysaccharide and imiquimod stimulation of potential immune biomarkers in whole blood predict alcohol use disorder risk based on AUDIT scores]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: LPS and IMQ stimulations unmasked immune response patterns that separated high- from low-risk individuals, with exaggerated pro-inflammatory responses in the high-risk group. IL-1β, IL-3, IL-18, and CCL11 repeatedly predicted AUDIT scores, with IL-1β and IL-3 LPS-dominant and CCL11 and IL-18 LPS/IMQ stimulus-shared. Stimulation-evoked mediator profiling may complement self-report screening and improve risk stratification in drinkers. Further studies are needed to address the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631396/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Modulation of Ferroptosis by the Irx3-Etfa Pathway Protects Against Cardiac Hypertrophy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Pathological cardiac hypertrophy is a major contributor to heart failure and is often accompanied by ferroptosis and mitochondrial dysfunction. However, the upstream transcriptional mechanisms governing these processes remain poorly defined. We performed integrative bioinformatics analysis using transverse aortic constriction (TAC)-induced hypertrophic heart datasets to identify mitochondria-related differentially expressed genes (MitoDEGs), followed by transcription factor prediction and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631390/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Human Dorsal Root Ganglia Neuronal Cell Line to Study Nociceptive Signaling: A New Pipeline for Pain Therapy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Nociceptive afferent neurons within the dorsal root ganglion (DRG) detect and relay painful peripheral stimuli, and the malfunctioning of this process leads to sustained pain states. Animal model studies have been invaluable for demonstrating the importance of the DRG nociceptor in pain sensation and the development of related analgesic targets. However, a human in vitro model of nociception is essential to confirming the relevance of preclinical findings for therapeutic drug development. We...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631387/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Echinatin Alleviates Experimental Pulmonary Hypertension by PPARγ Pathway Activation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The peroxisome proliferator-activated receptor gamma (PPARγ) signaling pathway plays a pivotal role in regulating the proliferation, apoptosis, inflammation, and metabolism of pulmonary arterial smooth muscle cells (PASMCs), suggesting its central involvement in the pathogenesis of pulmonary hypertension (PH). Although PPARγ agonists have shown promising therapeutic effects in preclinical models, their clinical translation remains challenging. Echinatin (Ecn), a natural flavonoid compound, has...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631386/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Dynamic Binder Exchange Improves Protein Labeling Efficiency in DNA-PAINT up to 15-Fold]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Binder Exchange (DyBE) enhances DNA-PAINT (Point Accumulation for Imaging in Nanoscale Topography) super-resolution microscopy by exploiting transient, reversible binder-target interactions. DyBE uses DNA-conjugated binders such as nanobodies as both targeting and docking moieties, integrating their characteristic higher off-rates with DNA-PAINT blinking to efficiently sample target sites. This dual-kinetic scheme increases labeling efficiency up to 15-fold, enabling sensitive detection...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631385/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Machine learning to predict elevated lipoprotein(a)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Lipoprotein(a), Lp(a), is a genetically determined, lifelong risk factor for atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease (ASCVD). Despite broad guideline support for universal one-time testing, Lp(a) measurement remains rare in clinical practice. This review summarizes recent advances in machine learning-based strategies that can enhance the efficiency, yield, and equity of Lp(a) screening.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631372/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pulmonary rehabilitation in adults with asthma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[PURPOSE OF REVIEW: Nonpharmacological strategies, including pulmonary rehabilitation (PR), are increasingly recognized as essential components of asthma management, particularly for individuals with persistent symptoms, poor asthma symptom control, or complex disease. This review summarize recent evidence on PR and related behavioural, lifestyle, and digital interventions, and explores emerging models to improve access and long-term effectiveness.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631368/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Preoperative Metabolic Predictors of Granulation Subtypes in Somatotroph Tumors: A Multicenter Retrospective Cohort Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The TG-UA index is a promising noninvasive biomarker for identifying the SGST subtype in somatotroph tumors. Although limited by its retrospective design and lack of long-term data, this study provides a foundation for future prospective validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631367/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Localized Periodontitis in Young Individuals: Aggregatibacter JP2 Clone, Immunological Dysfunctions and Other Stories]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Grade C molar-incisor pattern periodontitis (C-MIP) is the latest in a series of names given to a unique phenotype, characterized by an aggressive and rapid loss of tooth-supporting structures, starting early in life and usually affecting first molars and incisors. Although much less prevalent than the more generalized "chronic" forms of this disease in adults, it affects mostly young individuals of lower socioeconomic status and African descent, or from mixed-race populations, and shows a...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631366/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bulk-to-IHP Zn Interphase Engineering With Mannitol Additive Enables (002)-Textured Zn Plating With Suppressed Hydrogen Evolution Reaction for Ah-Level Aqueous Zinc-Iodine Pouch Cells]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Aqueous zinc-iodine batteries are promising contenders for next-generation grid-scale energy storage batteries. However, their deployment is hindered by zinc anode degradation at moderate cycling rates (0.5-2 C), including dendrite growth and parasitic hydrogen evolution reaction (HER), stemming from an unstable Zn/electrolyte interphase. Herein, a sugar alcohol-based multifunctional additive of mannitol (ML), identified via theoretical screening based on molecular characteristics of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631361/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bioinspired Total Synthesis of Curtachalasin B and Biosynthetically Related Cytochalasans]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[We report the first total syntheses of curtachalasin B and a series of biosynthetically related cytochalasans, including ketocytochalasin, xylariasins, brunnesins, zygosporins, arbuschalasins, cytochalasins, and curtachalasin Q, derived from the common precursor zygosporin G. The key intermediate was strategically assembled through an intermolecular Diels-Alder reaction, two Horner-Wadsworth-Emmons (HWE) macrocyclizations, and a late-stage methyl 1,2-addition. The highly functionalized 6/6 ring...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631354/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Synergistic Ternary Heterostructures Cathode With "Electron-Complementation" Bridging Interfaces Enable High-Performance Zinc-Ion Batteries]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Constructing multiphase heterostructures by interweaving characteristically complementary oxides, sulfides, and metals is promising for advancing aqueous battery electrodes, yet versatile synthesis and heterointerface insight pose significant challenges. Traditional methods often suffer from specificity optimization and non-redox-active substrate dependency, compromising performance. Herein, we overcome these limitations with a versatile overpotential-driven synthetic strategy that enables...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631353/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Examining How Academic Subscribers Implement Alcohol eCHECKUP to GO]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Institutions implement Alcohol eCHECKUP TO GO with a variety of student groups and mostly remotely. This study provides intervention and prevention researchers interested in the effectiveness of the program with a better understanding of real-world conditions.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631350/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oxygenated Organic Molecules in Urban Beijing: Contrasting Summer-Winter Composition, Sources, and Roles in Secondary Organic Aerosol Formation]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oxygenated organic molecules (OOMs) are important precursors of secondary organic aerosol (SOA), yet their molecular characteristics and sources in megacities are not fully understood. Here, we characterize the molecular composition, summer-winter differences, and sources of gaseous OOMs in urban Beijing using an iodide chemical ionization mass spectrometer. Our results show that C(4)-C(5) molecules, especially isoprene oxidation products, accounted for 48% of measured OOMs in summer, while CHO...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631324/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Risk factors for revictimization during treatment in patients with co-occurring SUD and PTSD]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction: A host of cross-sectional studies have identified problematic substance use and post-traumatic stress symptoms as risk factors for repeated interpersonal violence (revictimization) in college samples. However, it remains unclear which factors are associated with revictimization for patients who meet diagnostic criteria for both substance use disorder (SUD) and post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD). The identification of factors associated with revictimization is an important step...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631319/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Uncovering light-induced emission enhancement in a dual-emissive photosensitizer for real-time photodynamic theranostics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Photodynamic therapy (PDT) stands out as a promising alternative for cancer treatment due to its low invasiveness and low side effects. Additionally, photosensitizers often exhibit photoluminescent properties, which provide valuable diagnostic guidance for preoperative planning and drug delivery. However, current assessment of therapeutic efficacy largely relies on auxiliary imaging techniques to track tumor volume changes, which fail to provide real-time feedback on treatment outcomes. In this...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631315/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Frequency domain laser ultrasound for inertial confinement fusion target wall thickness measurements]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[In inertial confinement fusion experiments hollow, spherical mm-sized capsules are used as a container for nuclear fuel. To achieve maximum implosion efficiency, a perfect capsule geometry is required. This paper presents a wall thickness measurement method based on zero-group velocity guided elastic wave resonances. They are measured with a non-destructive, contactless frequency domain laser ultrasound microscopy system. Wall thickness measurements along the equator of a high-density carbon...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631265/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A cohort study of exodrift following the recession-plication technique for the treatment of basic type intermittent exotropia in children]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Children with basic type IXT who exhibit varying ocular alignment in the early postoperative period demonstrated a comparable magnitude of 10 PD for long-term exodrift. It is recommended to overcorrect within the range of 0 to 10 PD following RP techniques.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631255/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[An attenuated coxsackievirus B5 mutant carrying VP1-N157K retains oncolytic potency against non-small cell lung cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Oncolytic virus therapy is a rapidly developing cancer treatment method. The development of oncolytic viruses often involves genetic modifications, such as increased expression of foreign proteins for enhancing the antitumor capabilities and knocking out of virulence loci for improving the safety. The wild-type coxsackievirus B5 (CV-B5/F) exhibits potent antitumor activity against non-small cell lung cancer. However, CV-B5 poses pathogenic risks to infants and young children, warranting further...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631248/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[USP34 attenuates cartilage degradation in temporomandibular joint osteoarthritis by ANT1-mediated mitophagy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pain and dysfunction caused by temporomandibular joint osteoarthritis (TMJ OA) can be debilitating. However, effective disease-modifying medicine for TMJ OA remains an unfulfilled need. While progressive cartilage degradation represents the hallmark of TMJ OA, the underlying molecular mechanisms remain incompletely understood. Here, we identify ubiquitin-specific protease 34 (USP34) as a key regulator of mitochondrial quality control in TMJ chondrocytes through its stabilization of adenine...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631201/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Digital phenotyping and ASCVD risk: An exploratory cross-sectional analysis using online behavioral data]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[A retrospective, exploratory cross-sectional analysis exploring whether social media data is associated with cardiovascular disease (CVD) risk beyond traditional clinical models. While social media data may capture behavioral and social markers relevant to CVD, their associations with CVD risk remains uncertain.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631189/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psoriasis flare confused with drug allergy: A collaborative effort is required to treat tuberculosis in the setting of severe psoriasis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Treatment of TB disease in patients with severe psoriasis requires a collaborative effort between the TB treatment team and dermatology. A balanced approach, including treatment of both diseases, is necessary to avoid confusion of psoriasis flare versus drug induced skin reactions from TB medications.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631185/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hospital waterbirth for low-risk birthing people: findings of a randomized controlled trial]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study further contributes to the growing body of evidence that waterbirth reduces intravenous analgesia and anesthesia use and increases maternal satisfaction. The findings of our study provide support for hospitals to offer waterbirth as a pain relief option for low-risk birthing people.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631180/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[European Code Against Cancer 5th edition: 14 ways you can help prevent cancer]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite the growing cancer burden in the European Union, public awareness of effective prevention is low. In response, Europe's Beating Cancer Plan has supported the development of the 5th edition of the European Code Against Cancer (ECAC5). Using a transparent, stepwise decision-making process, around 80 experts reviewed the latest scientific evidence on cancer prevention and used modern communication strategies to update the previous edition. An innovation in ECAC5 is the inclusion of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631169/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pyrimidine-based compounds as promising anticancer agents targeting tumor cell senescence]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The pyrimidine ring is an important structural motif present in numerous bioactive compounds, including those with antibacterial and antitumor activities. In this study, two novel 4,6-disubstituted-2-(4-morpholinyl) pyrimidines (P12 and P14) were evaluated in breast cancer and melanoma cells with different genetic backgrounds. Both compounds demonstrated antitumor activity by reducing cell proliferation in 2D and 3D models. Mechanistic studies showed that these derivatives induce cell-cycle...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631161/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A measles virus encoding a CD19/CD3 bispecific T cell engager shows enhanced preclinical anti-BCP-ALL efficacy without significant toxicity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Children with high-risk B-cell precursor acute lymphoblastic leukemia (BCP-ALL) continue to face relapse and treatment resistance, emphasizing the urgent need for novel therapeutic strategies. In this study, we developed and characterized a recombinant oncolytic measles virus (MV-Blina) engineered to locally secrete a bispecific T cell engager (bsTE) targeting CD19 and CD3 (secBlina) to enhance antitumor immunity while minimizing systemic toxicity. MV-Blina demonstrated superior replication...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631160/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SlERF.D2-mediated antagonism between ethylene and ABA signaling pathways modulates osmotic stress adaptation in tomato]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Ethylene response factors (ERFs) are pivotal regulators in mediating plant stress adaptation; however, the roles of osmotic stress-responsive ERFs in tomato remain poorly characterized. Here, we comprehensively investigate the function of SlERF.D2, a member of the ERF transcription factor family, in modulating osmotic stress adaptation. Expression profiling indicated that SlERF.D2 responded to diverse abiotic stimuli, such as drought and salt, as well as ethylene and abscisic acid (ABA)....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631149/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Integrative chromosome-level genomics and metabolomics uncover regulatory networks linking monoterpenoid biosynthesis and glandular trichome formation in <em>Mosla chinensis</em>]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Xiangru, with Mosla chinensis (Mc, 2n = 18) and its considered cultivar M. chinensis 'Jiangxiangru' (McJ, 2n = 18) as original plants, is an annual herb of the Lamiaceae family, and is widely used as medicinal and edible plant due to its spleen strengthening function. However, absence of genomic resource impedes in-depth research towards Xiangru. In this study, the morphological characteristics and volatile organic compounds (VOC) contents of Mc and McJ were analyzed, showing higher trichome...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631144/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Genome-wide association study in a lettuce core collection from 811 accessions reveals genetic loci for anthocyanin accumulation and cultivar development]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Lettuce (Lactuca sativa) is a globally cultivated leafy vegetable with leafy morphology critically influencing consumer preference and market value. Despite the agronomic importance of leaf traits, the genetic basis underlying their diversity remains poorly characterized. To address this, we resequenced 811 accessions collected from major lettuce production areas as well as the relative wild species, and developed a publicly accessible core collection of 268 accessions that captures 99.4% of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631142/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applications and challenges of utilizing digital pathology and AI-enabled workflows in clinical trials]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[This is a comprehensive review on current utilization and challenges of digital pathology adoption in clinical trials and aims to provide a broad view on its impact on pathology review processes in clinical trials. It provides an overview of current pathology review practices in clinical trials and unique advantages digital pathology adoption can offer. The key areas including existing workflows, use case scenarios in different disease areas in clinical trials, including but not limited to...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631127/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Intracranial hepatitis B virus (HBV) infection following intracerebral hemorrhage in a patient with seronegative occult HBV infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Hepatitis B virus (HBV) infection is primarily associated with liver diseases but can also manifest with various extrahepatic complications. While numerous extrahepatic manifestations have been reported in acute or chronic hepatitis B patients, intracranial HBV infection remains clinically rare. A 43-year-old male had a pre-existing diagnosis of serologically negative occult HBV infection (OBI), which was initially diagnosed by detecting HBV DNA in serum while HBsAg, anti-HBs, anti-HBe, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631112/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["The Doctor Only Knows What He Knows, but I Know What I Know:": Parent Perspectives on Shared Decision Making with Adolescents]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Background. Shared decision making (SDM) involving adolescents with chronic conditions is a triadic process that requires engaging adolescent patients, their parent(s), and their health care provider. We sought to understand the perspectives of parents about these interactions and the parents' role in SDM. Methods. We conducted semi-structured qualitative interviews with parents of adolescents (aged 12-17 y) with chronic conditions. The interviews focused on parents' experiences of medical...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631111/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contraceptive care for patients with bigger bodies in the US: Evaluation of a provider training intervention]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Patients with bigger bodies deserve accurate clinical information and comprehensive access to contraception. To provide person-centered care for patients with bigger bodies, this training increased knowledge of how to deliver contraceptive care for this population.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631102/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Digital Innovation for Enhanced Adherence Counseling (EAC) to Improve Outcomes Among People Living With HIV (PLHIV) in Mumbai, India]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Introduction Early initiation of antiretroviral therapy (ART) and adequate adherence are associated with sustained viral load (VL) suppression and effective treatment in people living with HIV (PLHIV). Enhanced adherence counseling (EAC) has been recommended for PLHIV on therapy with a VL >1000 copies/mL. We developed a digital application, "Samvaad," for counselors at ART centers to document the barriers to poor adherence and to provide thematic EAC for registered PLHIV under the aegis of the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631064/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Iron deficiency in patients undergoing radiotherapy: Prevalence and clinical characteristics]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Patients undergoing radiotherapy show an exceptionally high prevalence for anemia, with iron deficiency being one of the main causes. Our study suggests that oral iron substitution may not be sufficient to treat iron deficiency in patients undergoing radiotherapy, underlining the need to enhance our understanding of iron balance and how to best target deficiencies in these patients.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631034/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Early multimodal behavioral cues in autism: a micro-analytical exploration of actions, gestures and speech during naturalistic parent-child interactions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Early signs of autism often emerge through distinct developmental pathways, particularly in communication, social interaction, and play. While naturalistic parent-child interactions during free play are ideal for observing spontaneous social behaviors, few autism studies have adopted this ecological and developmental approach. To address this gap, we used a fine-grained microanalytic method to examine motor, gestural, and vocal behaviors in young children, integrating machine learning to explore...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631016/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circulating miRNAs combined with AFP improve diagnostic accuracy for HBV-associated hepatocellular carcinoma]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Combining circulating miR-21-5p, miR-34a-5p, and miR-30d-3p with AFP significantly enhances diagnostic accuracy for HBV-related HCC, supporting their utility as complementary non-invasive biomarkers for early screening.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630981/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OVOCs drive radical cycling and ozone formation in background air]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Surface ozone pollution is a critical global environmental challenge driven by the complex, nonlinear photochemical cycling of RO (x) radicals (OH + HO(2) + RO(2)). Oxygenated volatile organic compounds (OVOCs) are central to these cycles as both radical sources and sinks, yet their quantitative impact on regional radical budgets remains poorly understood due to historical limitations in ambient measurements. This knowledge gap hinders the accurate prediction of persistent ozone exceedances....]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630974/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reproductive risk factors and prevalence of cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic syndrome among young women]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: CKM syndrome is highly prevalent among reproductive-aged women in the US. Histories of gestational diabetes and infertility were associated with higher CKM stages. Incorporating reproductive factors into clinical tools could support targeted prevention of CKM progression and future CVD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630962/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Impact of severe infections on the risk of acute cardiovascular and cerebrovascular diseases: A prospective cohort study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The study found that severe infections were associated with the elevated risk of cardiovascular and cerebrovascular events. The findings suggest that more attention should be given to preventing and intervening in cardiovascular events among high-risk infection populations.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630960/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Characterization of a De Novo <em>SCN2A</em> Mixed Variant Linked to Early Infantile Developmental and Epileptic Encephalopathy]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[BACKGROUND AND OBJECTIVES: Pathogenic variants in the SCN2A gene, encoding the α-subunit type 2 of the voltage-gated sodium channel Na(V)1.2, cause a phenotypic spectrum including 4 major disorders as benign familial infantile seizures, developmental and epileptic encephalopathy, intellectual disability, and autism. Gain-of-function variants resulting phenotypes may be treated with sodium channel blockers, while loss-of-function (LoF) conditions are non-respondent. We focused on the effects of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630925/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Diverse intracellular trafficking of insulin analogs by machine learning-based colocalization and diffusion analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Insulin signaling is vital for cellular homeostasis, with dysregulation leading to severe metabolic disorders, particularly diabetes. While insulin analogs are crucial in type 1 diabetes treatment, identifying potential variations in intracellular trafficking and sorting from endogenous insulin is challenging. Current methods rely on static imaging and bulk receptor assays in non-physiological conditions, which disrupts native signaling and masks temporal trafficking dynamics. Here, we directly...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630923/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Circadian <em>ADCY3</em> Ser107Pro variant bridges difficulty awakening in the morning and adiposity]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Modern lifestyles often disturb circadian rhythms, yet the genetic circuits that convert this stress into metabolic dysfunction remain poorly defined. Here, we identify a missense variant in ADCY3 (rs11676272; Ser107Pro) as a pleiotropic regulator of circadian preference and adiposity. Using genome-wide pleiotropy analysis in ∼480,000 UK Biobank participants, we show that the G risk allele (Pro107) increases eveningness, BMI, and fat mass in European (n = 451,324) and African (n = 8,738)...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630919/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Maternal environmental exposure and early-life health risks: The modulating role of nutritional status-A scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Emerging evidence suggests that maternal food intake and nutritional status may modify the relationship between environmental toxicants and early-life health risks, potentially mitigating their adverse effects. However, the interplay between nutritional status, environmental exposures, and health outcomes remains poorly characterized in the literature. Notably, foods can serve as the dual source of toxins (e.g., methylmercury in fish) and protective nutrients (e.g., omega-3 fatty acids), which...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630913/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Non-immersive robot teleoperation does not reliably affect egocentric dishonesty but can influence altruistic dishonesty]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Robot teleoperation enables action through an artificial body while physically elsewhere. We examined whether non-immersive, screen-based teleoperation of the humanoid robot iCub induces embodiment, the sense that the robot's body feels like one's own, and whether embodiment affects dishonest behavior compared to acting with one's real body. Participants performed a task either in person or via teleoperation in a first-person (1 PP) or third-person (3 PP) perspective. Both teleoperation modes...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630907/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Coordinated infraslow cortical oscillations of neuromodulators during NREM sleep]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Neurotransmitters and neuromodulators regulate brain states through diverse mechanisms, yet how their activities are coordinated during sleep remains unresolved. Using in vivo fiber photometry in adult mice expressing genetically encoded fluorescent biosensors, combined with EEG/EMG recordings, we investigated the temporal organization of multiple neuromodulators during sleep in barrel cortex, with norepinephrine (NE) as a reference signal. All five neuromodulators examined, acetylcholine,...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630901/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sodium-Glucose Cotransporter-2 Inhibitors and Cardiorenal Events in Nonalbuminuric Kidney Disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This nationwide cohort study showed that SGLT2is use was associated with a significantly lower risk of progression to macroalbuminuria, and all-cause mortality compared with nonuse in patients with T2D and nonalbuminuric CKD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630897/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Combining bioaffinity-ultrafiltration with <em>in vivo</em> and <em>in vitro</em> analyses to identify and characterize α-glucosidase inhibitors from <em>Rosa roxburghii</em> Tratt. Fruit]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[The fruit of Rosa roxburghii Tratt. (RRT) is frequently eaten in Guizhou Province, China. Thirty compounds from RRT fruit were identified by the bioaffinity-ultrafiltration method. Among them, quercetin, diosmetin, luteolin, and apigenin (IC(50) = 4.80 ± 0.12 μg/mL, 52.62 ± 0.26 μg/mL, 17.51 ± 0.27 μg/mL, 33.24 ± 0.32 μg/mL) exhibited significant α-glucosidase inhibitory activities. Based on multispectral and molecular docking analyses, these active compounds bind to the active site of...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630884/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of scratches and mat hygiene in wrestling-associated skin infections]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630873/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Infection and risk of psoriasis and atopic dermatitis: A systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630871/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deucravacitinib, an oral, selective, allosteric tyrosine kinase 2 (TYK2) inhibitor, in patients with moderate to severe scalp psoriasis: Efficacy and safety results through week 16 in a phase 3b/4, multicenter, randomized, double-blinded, placebo-controlled trial (PSORIATYK SCALP)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Deucravacitinib was efficacious and well tolerated in patients with moderate to severe scalp psoriasis.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630865/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Novel carbon fiber pedicle screw system for the treatment of lumbar degenerative disc disease: Results from a prospective, multicenter, FDA investigational device exemption study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: The CarboClear System is a safe and effective alternative to titanium pedicle screws for lumbar fusion, providing improved imaging compatibility and fatigue resistance.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630858/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development of prediction models for perioperative opioid needs in laparoscopic cholecystectomy patients: A machine-learning approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Prediction of perioperative opioid needs using EMR and machine-learning is feasible and may support individualized pain management, though further refinement of model performance is warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630855/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Investigation and response to rift valley fever outbreak in ruminant livestock from Ngoma District, eastern province of Rwanda, 2024]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Rapid detection, targeted treatment, and mass vaccination, implemented through a multisectoral One Health response, successfully contained the outbreak and prevented human spillover. Sustained surveillance and cross-border coordination remain essential to mitigate future RVF threats.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630841/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical efficacy and safety of endoscopic ultrasound-guided ablation therapies for pancreatic neuroendocrine tumors: a systematic review and meta-analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Both EUS-EI and EUS-RFA are effective, relatively safe, and minimally invasive treatment options for pNETs. However, severe AE can occur, and careful patient selection and treatment indication are essential.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630838/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical diagnosis and biomarkers of acute kidney injury in liver cirrhosis: a systematic review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Serum Cys C and urinary NGAL offer distinct advantages over sCr in the early diagnosis and phenotypic differentiation of AKI. Although prediction models show promise, their routine clinical application requires further standardization and extensive external validation.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630837/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pacing of the first and only female finisher in the world's longest triathlon: The 2024 Triple Deca ultra triathlon]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Tactical considerations most likely influenced pacing, particularly in cycling and running. Future research should further explore pacing strategies in ultra-endurance events.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630831/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Knowledge and practice of adult cardiopulmonary resuscitation among nurses in the Emergency Department of a tertiary hospital in Ghana]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Our study found respondents generally had good knowledge and good practice of CPR. Making AHA guidelines available to ED nurses for managing sudden cardiac arrest was significantly associated with good knowledge of CPR. Therefore, regular CPR training and providing AHA guidelines for managing sudden cardiac arrest are recommended to increase the level of knowledge of adult CPR.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630830/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Functional Brain Activity Associated With Intermittent Rhythmic Delta/Theta Activity: A Transdiagnostic Electroencephalography-Functional Magnetic Resonance Imaging Resting-State Study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: In this study, IRDA/IRTA-related brain activity changes across the groups were identified, with excitatory brain activity especially in fronto-centro-temporal brain areas with similarities to the salience network. Additional disease- or disorder-specific changes were discovered in APS and BPD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630827/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Associations of biomarkers with hypoattenuated leaflet thickening after transcatheter aortic valve replacement]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This exploratory study identified associations between HALT and biomarkers of hypercoagulability and inflammation, which did not persist after correction for multiple testing. These findings should be regarded as hypothesis-generating and warrant confirmation in future studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630814/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Urine-based point-of-care detection of direct oral anticoagulant activity in acute stroke-accuracy at anti-Xa thresholds relevant for intravenous thrombolysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Urine-based DOAC dipstick testing is a rapid, accurate, and reliable method for detecting anticoagulatory activity in AIS patients, providing a valuable tool to guide acute therapeutic decisions. Future studies are warranted to validate its clinical impact and broader applicability, especially in the emergency setting.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630813/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Therapeutic potential, pharmacological role and molecular mechanisms of adelmidrol, an analogue of palmitoylethanolamide]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Adelmidrol is a bioactive semi-synthetic compound with significant therapeutic potential, particularly in resolving inflammation since inflammation plays a key role in the pathogenesis of several diseases. The mechanisms of action of adelmidrol are multifaceted, involving interactions with specific receptors like the PPAR-γ and modulation of signaling pathways associated with inflammation. Adelmidrol demonstrates efficacy in conditions such as inflammatory bowel disease, colon inflammation, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630803/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The role of hemoglobin F in sickle cell disease complications: a descriptive secondary analysis]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Individuals with sickle cell disease (SCD), a prevalent inherited blood disorder, are at increased risk for tissue ischemia and thrombosis secondary to sickle hemoglobin polymerization. Fetal hemoglobin (HbF) protects against the vaso-occlusive nature of sickled erythrocytes. Our study aims to investigate the association between HbF level and various SCD complications. The study used a descriptive and cross-sectional design to analyze existing, secondary medical record data of 496 patients with...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630797/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tse<sup>VF</sup>-Tsi<sup>VF</sup>, a novel bacteriolytic effector-immunity pair of <em>Vibrio fluvialis</em> VflT6SS2, provides a fitness advantage in microbial competition]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Vibrio fluvialis (V. fluvialis) is a halophilic Gram-negative bacterium regarded as an emerging pathogen that can cause severe cholera-like diarrhea and various extraintestinal infections. Type VI secretion systems (T6SSs) are nano-weapons used by bacteria to deliver toxic effectors into host cells or antagonize competitors. VflT6SS2 of V. fluvialis is involved in bacterial pathogenicity and competitive environmental survival. Previously, we have identified some regulatory factors of VflT6SS2...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630785/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The severity of fatigue and its interplay with biological and psychological factors in people with hand osteoarthritis - Results from the Nor-Hand study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Fatigue is likely significant and strongly related to comorbidities, pain, symptoms of anxiety/depression, and sleep problems among hand OA patients. Longitudinal studies using more diverse samples and comprehensive variable selections are warranted.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630780/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The stability of pain phenotypes in people with hand osteoarthritis - results from the NOR-HAND study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Four distinct pain phenotypes were identified among persons with hand OA. Excluding QST from our model did not influence phenotype composition or characteristics. Various longitudinal phenotype stability was observed. Between-class transitions were often characterized by less pain and psychosocial burden, potentially due to regression to the mean or improved disease coping.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630779/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[<em>Blumea balsamifera</em> (L.) DC. and <em>Sargassum aquifolium</em> J. Agardh extracts as anti-atherosclerotic, anti-inflammatory, and hepatoprotective agents in Wistar rats induced by a high-cholesterol diet]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Administration of BBLE+SAE acts as an anti-atherosclerotic and hepatoprotective agent for the liver through reducing pro-inflammatory cytokines, and its use was promising for clinical studies.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630761/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Application of leptospirosis surveillance study at primary health care center in Banyumas and Demak, Central Java, Indonesia]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Leptospirosis surveillance data can be used to identify focal areas of leptospirosis endemicity. The application of the WHO-SEARO (2009) clinical criteria and rapid diagnostic tests supports the identification of suspected and probable cases of leptospirosis at the PHC level.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630749/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Development and characterization of antibodies against <em>Pasteurella multocida</em> through active vaccination in rabbits]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: This study establishes an effective protocol for generating specific anti-P. multocida antibodies in rabbits, providing valuable resources for the development of diagnostic tools and vaccines against P. multocida infections in livestock.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630748/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rabbit hemorrhagic disease: The devastating impact of a highly contagious virus on rabbit populations]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rabbit hemorrhagic disease (RHD) is a highly contagious viral infection in rabbits that can occur in acute, subacute, chronic, or peracute forms and is not fatal. It is caused by RHD virus (RHDV), a member of the genus Lagovirus in the family Caliciviridae, with variants including RHDV1, RHDV1a, and RHDV2. First identified in 1984 in domestic rabbits (Oryctolagus cuniculus) in China, RHD has since been reported in Asia, Europe, Africa, Central America, and North America. Both innate and adaptive...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630742/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Role of tannin, saponin, and cumin in inhibiting deamination during ensiling: A molecular docking and molecular dynamics approach]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: The secondary metabolites punicalagin (from tannins), theasapogenol B (from saponins), and alpha-hederin (from cumin essential oil) showed optimal efficacy as deamination inhibitors in silage. Punicalagin demonstrated optimal and stable results as a deamination inhibitor.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630731/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evaluation of applied foot and mouth disease-providing measures in the Republic of Armenia: A retrospective study]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Sustained preventive strategies, regional surveillance, and updated vaccines have been key to controlling FMD in Armenia. The combination of timely preventive measures, systematic vaccination, and antigen-matched vaccines has effectively reduced outbreak risk and supported long-term disease containment in the country.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630719/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The ameliorative effects of <em>Myrmecodia</em> sp. as an antibiotic growth promoter in broiler chicken with avian pathogenic <em>Escherichia coli</em> infection]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSION: Myrmecodia sp. has the potential to serve as a natural alternative to antibiotic growth promoters in broiler production. However, these results should be interpreted with caution, and further confirmation is required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630715/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Factors Associated With COVID-19 Vaccination and Intention to Vaccinate Children Among a Childbearing Population (in Allegheny County, Pennsylvania)]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: These analyses reveal racial inequities in maternal vaccination against COVID-19. Findings highlight the need to tailor vaccine programming for families to positively impact future behaviors regarding COVID-19 vaccines and boosters for children.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630699/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Single-cell analysis reveals neuroprotective histone deacetylase inhibitor pathways]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Alzheimer's disease (AD) involves β-amyloid (Aβ) accumulation, tau pathology, and neuroinflammation, driving cognitive decline. Despite extensive research, disease-modifying therapies remain elusive. We integrated single-cell RNA sequencing (scRNA-seq), spatial transcriptomics, and in vitro validation to identify repurposable drugs for AD¹.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630642/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The emergence and biological characteristics of linezolid-resistant <em>Clostridioides difficile</em> isolates in the Asia-Pacific Region]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Linezolid-resistant Clostridioides difficile, conferred by the acquisition of cfr-like genes, has been reported in Europe and America. However, the emergence of linezolid resistance in C. difficile in the Asia-Pacific region and its impacts on C. difficile pathogenicity remain unclear. In this study, 881 C. difficile isolates from the Asia-Pacific region were screened for cfr-like genes. Whole genome sequencing was performed on 16 cfr-like gene-positive isolates from four countries. Thirteen...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630629/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Review on the Application of Metalloporphyrin Catalysts as Cytochrome P450 Enzyme Mimics in Biomimetic Modeling]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Drug research, particularly in the early discovery phase, increasingly seeks cost-effective and reliable in vitro models to predict drug metabolism. Metalloporphyrins (MPs), due to their structural and functional resemblance to the heme group of cytochrome P450 enzymes (CYP450s), have emerged as versatile biomimetic catalysts for oxidative reactions. This review focuses specifically on metalloporphyrin-based biomimetic catalysis for oxidative drug metabolism studied in scientific papers...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630621/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Evidence synthesis methodology for questions relating to barriers and enablers in health care: a scoping review]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: A variety of methodological approaches are being followed to undertake reviews focused on barriers and/or enablers in health care. The current state of the literature indicates that most authors answer these questions via the conduct of a systematic review and include diverse types of evidence. Further work is needed to determine whether authors are unclear when deciding on methodology and whether guidance is required.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630620/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Plasma and neuroimaging biomarkers of small vessel disease and Alzheimer's disease in a diverse cohort: MESA]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Little is known about how Alzheimer's disease (AD) plasma biomarkers relate to cerebral small vessel disease (cSVD) neuroimaging biomarkers.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630612/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bayesian modelling of dengue incidence with climatic drivers: comparing fixed-effects, nonlinear and dynamic approaches]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Climatic variability plays a critical role in shaping dengue transmission dynamics, yet empirical findings remain inconsistent across studies. Divergent conclusions regarding the associations of temperature, relative humidity, wind speed, air pressure, precipitation, number of rainy days, and sunshine duration with dengue incidence often stem from unmodelled interactions and methodological limitations. To address these challenges, this study applies a Bayesian modelling framework to examine the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630604/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mechanistic principles of antimicrobial peptides uncovered by charge density-based machine learning]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Antimicrobial peptides (AMPs) are emerging as potent alternatives to conventional antibiotics, yet their diverse nature due to divergent mechanisms of action hinders rational design. Here, we present an electrostatics-stratified computational framework that uncovers key physicochemical principles governing AMP activity. Experimentally validated peptides were grouped by average charge per residue (i.e., the charge/length of the peptide) and analyzed through integrated sequence-, structure-, and...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630602/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Reduced triacylglycerols and lipid droplets are associated with resilience to Alzheimer's disease]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION: Although it has become clear that alterations in lipid metabolism are associated with Alzheimer's disease (AD), it is unclear how they contribute to both cognitive decline and the pathophysiology of AD.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630598/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Enhanced Dual Functionality of Pluronic F127-Blended Poly(ether sulfone) Hollow Fiber Membranes for Improved Separation and Cell Adhesion in Extracorporeal Bioartificial Kidney and Liver Applications]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Rising numbers of organ failures have intensified the demand for high-performance biomaterials to support the development of bioartificial organs and advanced bioreactors. Hollow fiber membranes (HFMs) are particularly well-suited for such applications, including bioartificial kidney, liver, and 3D cell culture systems, due to their unique architecture and functional versatility. In this study, we engineered HFMs by blending amphiphilic Pluronic F127 (PF127) with poly(ether sulfone) (PES),...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630578/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Self-Assembly Approach for Uranium Extraction from Seawater]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Efficient uranium extraction from seawater remains a highly challenging task due to the lack of an available approach to access a precise uranium-identified site in the adsorbent. To this end, we demonstrate herein a novel in situ self-assembly approach by directly using two organic molecules, 2,6-pyridinedicarboxaldehyde and terephthalohydrazide, to execute in situ in-plane self-assembly with [UO(2)(CO(3))(3)]^(4-)composite anions through both covalent Schiff base condensation and coordination...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630574/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Customized birth weight percentiles for identification of SGA short statue]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[CONCLUSIONS: Customized percentiles classify more children as SGA based on their birth weight but do not appear to identify more children with postnatal growth failure than do conventional percentiles.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630573/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Clinical and endoscopic improvement of pediatric pouchitis with ustekinumab]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41630572/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1HyCEy3kccvK7zE0-AQi3b_3KChicv5K_t8YL3UITyEWtrEgUY&amp;fc=20250822210237&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>IBS</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Applications of quantitative <sup>13</sup>C NMR in pharmaceutical analysis: From small molecule drugs to biopolymers]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260203144747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Chemical integrity is indispensable for advancing healthcare by ensuring the availability of high quality, safe, and effective pharmaceutical products. Ingredient quantification is particularly pivotal in this process. Nuclear magnetic resonance (NMR) spectroscopy is a powerful tool for both qualitative and quantitative analysis for complex systems. Compared with 1D quantitative ¹H NMR (¹H qNMR), quantitative ^(13)C NMR (^(13)C qNMR) holds some unique advantages. This technique offers a broader...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41631244/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lIZdG7__acDiOnILwc1UJFv1EU2tzCDqwphAfr3PZolpno9sb&amp;fc=20250824201059&amp;ff=20260203144747&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Pusan National University</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep neural network-based coupling model of inter-organizational knowledge flow and agent collaborative decision-making]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629601/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Orbital exchange-mediated current control of magnetism]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Electrical control of magnetism is critical for advancing both fundamental understanding and technological applications of magnetic systems. Although gate-voltage-induced carrier modulation enables tuning of magnetic properties, current-induced mechanisms offer more dynamic and versatile control. To date, such control has been investigated exclusively through spin exchange interactions between itinerant and localized electrons, leaving the role of orbital exchange interactions entirely...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41629290/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Corrigendum to "E1K, a disease-modifying drug candidate for knee osteoarthritis, alleviates pain and regenerates cartilage simultaneously by inhibiting TGF-β1-mediated SMAD1/5/9 signaling in osteoarthritis models" [Osteoarthr. Cartil. 34 (2) (2026) 240-250]]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41628895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[No abstract]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41628895/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Strain- and species-specific immune responses to human adipose stem cell-derived extracellular vesicles: A comparative pharmacological evaluation in mice and human PBMCs]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41628693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Human adipose stem cell-derived extracellular vesicles (hASC-EVs) have gained attention as potential cell-free therapeutics in regenerative medicine due to their immunomodulatory properties and low immunogenicity. Despite this promise, their immunotoxicity profile remains insufficiently characterized, particularly across species and genetic backgrounds. This study systematically assessed immune responses to repeated high-dose intravenous administration of hASC-EVs in two murine strains-C57BL/6...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41628693/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>Hanyang University, KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Analysis of Exciton-Polaron Quenching in Organic Light-Emitting Diodes Based on Exciton and Polaron Distributions]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41627845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Spontaneous orientation polarization (SOP) in organic molecules is used in organic light-emitting diodes (OLEDs) and induces an internal electric field that facilitates charge injection and transport; however, excessive interfacial charge accumulation can lead to exciton quenching and efficiency loss. In particular, exciton-polaron quenching (EPQ) is significant in devices employing a polar electron-transport layer (ETL), where the SOP-induced field drives a carrier imbalance. Therefore, how the...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41627845/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heterodimensional Interface for Improved Photovoltage and Stability in Narrow Bandgap Sn-Pb Perovskite Solar Cells via Vacancy-Ordered Double Perovskite]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41627187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Sn-Pb perovskite solar cells (PSCs) are considered promising candidates for the bottom subcell in all‑perovskite tandem solar cells, due to their low bandgap and potential to approach the Shockley-Queisser limit. However, their practical application is hindered by the facile oxidation of Sn^(2+) ions and high trap densities. Here, we introduce FA(2)SnI(6) vacancy‑ordered double perovskite (FADP) with excellent stability under environmental conditions, to fabricate highly efficient and stable...]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41627187/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST, SNU</category>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Surface-composition-driven patchy carbon shells unlock high activity and durability in PtCu oxygen reduction catalysts]]></title>
            <link>https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41626963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</link>
            <description><![CDATA[Low-temperature CO treatment induces Pt surface segregation in carbon-incorporated PtCu nanoparticles, creating Pt-rich surface domains that localize carbon growth. Subsequent high-temperature Ar treatment forms a patchy carbon shell, enabling selective near-surface Cu dealloying, boosting oxygen reduction reaction (ORR) activity while suppressing particle degradation and markedly improving durability.]]></description>
            <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41626963/?utm_source=Other&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=pubmed-2&amp;utm_content=1lGTpA7S74whuNVC_kQy0F4ncgCxeB9B9U0hbi6Wldiv2cIgV2&amp;fc=20250822163126&amp;ff=20260203144746&amp;v=2.18.0.post22+67771e2</guid>
            <category>KAIST</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>